<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wah, man finally off the phone after like nearly 10 phone calls to ISPs + PSTN companies. Just got my local home phone changed to B… cos man it’s DAMN cheap… yep, I reckon it is… cos it’s only $29.95 for line rental, (which is cheaper than ANY OPTUS or TELSTRA LINE! – both above $33) and not only is it $29.95… it includes 100 local phone calls!!! – we only make like around 70 or 80 per month so we never have to pay more than $29.95. much cheaper than what we pay which we used to pay (which was $33 for line rental no free calls, and then pay like up to $15 just for local calls, and then we make like an extra $15, for Mobile + STD, for international we make a local call and use a calling card which is even cheaper…)  SO! - $29.95 and that’s all why? – cos I changed ISP to iiNet. Cost only $79.95 per month, but I get $10 off, per month cos I also joined their iiPhone, which means I only pay $69.95 for like 32gb download, which I seriously doubt I’ll ever have to worry about going over, if I don’t plan to download crap loads of stuff. And it’s a 512/128 connection 32gb, for less than $70… then iiPhone, there are no monthly fees or anything, it just for mobile, international and STD calls, (we’ll never use the international calls) but as for the STD and mobile calls, they have the cheapest rates out of all the providers I have ever seen, SO that means we’ll lover that $15 to mobiles to maybe 10… so if I add up everything that’s only $100 per month for all phone and internet! – which is a much better Deal than our current $160 per month deal… so yeah, all is good =) save parents $60 per month. And we’ll get to use the phone more and not pay as much.  Okay… not that you needed to know all that crap! – but man that took me ages… 1 ½ hours to get done… and well 328 words to type what I did =S. I spent like some time yesterday night to check out mobile plans, and then ended up with home phone plans, and I also came across the net plan SO I just got everything changed the next day. No rash decision, all figured out, been thinking about the net thing for ages.  Mobile plans… why was I checking them out? – well, supposedly my family’s gonna have a ABN number… meaning I can sign up for business plans… and the thing is business mobile plans have the CHEAPEST imaginable rates… so yeah, it’ll be good, only down side of things is that they don’t offer Yes time… which I guess right now isn’t such a  BIG deal, cos I’ll just get people to call me, But then again, I don’t use Yes time THAT often so with what I save if I wanted to phone someone even without yes time it would be worth while. BUT my contract only ends like next year… and well I plan to by a new phone in SG or Malaysia end of year… so yeahz. I’ll see what happens… still got heaps of time.   (man what is this guy talking about yeah??? – weirdest blog entry ever right? – hmmm maybe… )  Anyway! How was my day? – Good, cos I feel better =) but still not perfect, I actually was running late for the train on the way home, cos I wanted to go somewhere before home, so I jogged a bit, and got my heart rate maybe up 10 bpm, and well I could feel that even if I wanted to run 100m tomorrow, there was no chance I would make it to the finish line ALIVE! If I tired… cos I think it was like the virus that could attack the heart, and well I could already feel that it wasn’t good. BUT if I didn’t run, I think today, was the best I’ve felt in like 2 weeks.  Spesh first period, man been awhile since I’ve had spesh… I’m so far behind, David Oh, the ultimate genius of Maths… is like Kenny… you’ve done nearly nothing this year… no exercises no home work… if you tired Kenny you would do so much better, (well I guess who would yeah?). in some sense to me that’s a huge encouragement, cos the fact is, right now I’m doing spesh unlike anyone else, but yet, man I’m KICKING like 80% of the people at BHHS!!! Now that is HILLARIOUS! – I feel like one of those people who everyone hates… never do any work… but still can do so well =P hahahz! YES! – man how good does that feel, but yeah I think in the long term, esp when everyone revises at the end of the year, I’m sure to fall behind.  Okay, Maths was my BEST subject by far when I was younger… I ACED maths up to year 9 =S then well, hmmm people got better than me, and I just got used to it. So now I don’t care =S Cos it’s DAVID OH, man how can you beat someone who get perfect mark, even if you tired, you can only equal him, and what the guy don’t even do half the set work… but me =S I do maybe a tenth =S probably less... hmmm I guess what I’m trying to say is that I’m still no over this mental battle to figure out whether I’m dumb, or that I have a brain. (not literally). It’s not good to admit you have one, and well that’s what I’ve refused to do for many years already, making myself believe I’m dumb, so it’s okay to not do well, (my excuse), but then hmmm if I tired, I guess I could do better, and currently, if I tired I don’t know what the possibilities could me. Maybe I could do really well at spesh? Which is kinda important… sighz, I don’t know, maybe I’m scared that if I try and I don’t do that well that I feel that I’m stupid, cos well without trying I’m doing =S alright, but it’s not something to commend… cos it’s pretty dodgy, since it’s no where near an A+… just cos everyone fails… I guess I can’t compare to them… well not can’t I shouldn’t. I should have higher standards… but yeah, doesn’t it feel good to feel that you kicked people’s bums?...  Hmmm, what I seriously wonder about is all the people who are like thinking… what? Kenny kick people’s bums, and he didn’t even do anything… BHHS must be full of the biggest retards… Well that’s where you’re wrong, BHHS got tons of smart people, the school overall does A LOT better than average, and well is one of the schools with the highest percentage of people who get about 90 as an ENTER.  Okay, I’m just gonna shut up now… I just need to study and do spesh for once… but in my head I keep thinking, if I don’t try, I can’t be blamed for getting a crap mark.  Ha… man I write so much crap that, because of this, I’ve decided to open a new blog, and stick all this crap into there… I need to maintain a decently level of quality of saneness in my proper blog.  Well I’ll just end this crappy post which will be my first post in my doggy blog! =) baiz
    
</post>
</Blog>