<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Fridays are funny. At some point, unbeknownst me to me, Friday became a psuedo-holiday as evidenced by the phrase 'Happy Friday'. So how did I spend my happy Friday. An 11 hr shift @ Kaplan, followed by drinks (or rather, drink) with some of the other Kaplanites.  The upside, I got to see my colleagues in a new light, and my manager may not be the crapweasel I thought he was. The downside, looking like a pus cuz I had to leave early.  And i got caught in the rain. Hard. And just think, I get to work Saturday too ______________________________________________   Greatest Songs Ever:  the Prodigy - Smack My Bitch Up; Alana Davis - 32 Flavors    
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My official first real post. Can you feel the electricity in the air.     I don't really have much to say right now. I'm home sweating my ass off. And thanks to oh so timely Parkchester renovations, I won't have AC until next week, which means in the meantime, not only do i get to sweat it out, I have no choice but to take a bath. As opposed to a shower, how dare you think that of me. So here I am, in the greatest city in the world, slowly melting like a big ole' chocolate chip. Its gonna be a long summer  _______________________________________________     Greatest Songs Ever..right now  -  Seven Mary Three - Punch In and  Out; JC Chasez - Some Girls (Dance With Women)  
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So I've established that this works. I'm going to spend some time tweaking the design because, well, I'm a tweaker. Anyone seen my html book around.... 
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Testes..testes..one..two..uh..three?  Now that I have that taken care of, its time to get down to business. I have no business starting a blog, nothing of interest to say, and no real time to dedicate to this. This might be interesting
     

    
</post>
<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I had a most profound experience this morning. After years of cruel hateful comments, I must now admit that Usher happens to be the fucking man. I caught him in Bryant Park this morning before work, and damn. He's like the Michael Jackon of my generation. Ya know..without the pedophilia thing. And the nose thing. Oh well, there's still time.  After work, chilled with Martine and Juan at Mojo on the lower east side. If you're going to go to any type of eatery with a pair of foodies, prepare to bring your A-game. So Juan and I are going to collaborate on a project via email. Might work out for the best. I'm more intellect and dry humor, and Juan's all dripping wet emotion..wait, that sounds bad  Gah..looking forward to another 11 hr shift @ kaplan. As Emily noted, I'm not so much selling my soul by the hour, as I am whoring myself. Which almost makes it worthwhile. Almost ______________________________________________  Greatest Song Ever - Usher - U Got It Bad  
     

    
</post>
<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Just got home from Mike's and tired as hell. Juan and I tossed around movie ideas. I think it helps to talk about it to keep me motivated. I've been stuck in the development stage for quite some time now. I've finally got down to the essence of the story. Twenty-something indifference. I guess it does goood to bounce ideas off of someone. It adds another layer of realness. And additional commitment. As Nietzsche said "</post></Blog>