<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>31,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey ppl..im in victoria now, its so damn hot!!! except for the place im staying...it's really breezy there because it is right next to the sea, and u can see surfers, and parachutists and stuff..its really cool, hehe. yea fung, ill give u guyz my number when i get one, ifi get one, but i dont think it will be that cheap..brian, what did u do to ur mail?? lemmi guess...u changed ur password and 4got it and u also forgot ur secret answer...?? hehe... oh yea, ill definitaly cling on to u guyz, and ill try to keep in touch as much as i can ok, no matter what u say! bout the girls: today, i saw this girl in the mall, and i dont know what it was about her, but i really liker her...but just from her looks...hehe *shallow moi* THERE ARE SOO MANY HOT CHICKS HERE!! but all the hot gurlz are going out with the hot guyz so...thats crap..hehe, anyway, i gtg now so ciao 4 now!!
     

    
</post>
<date>29,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey ppl... just came back from johor... good to hear from you arin.... man we miss u loads... life here is never goin to be da same without u.... hey btw i think it should be damn cheap to sms us from there... if u get a hp line.... so give us ur number when u get one k =)... and yeah dont become daryl... even though i doubt u will.... daryl was a dick even bfore he left and he is still a dumbass.....  and btw brian might not be using his email for a while so dont mail him... just post stuff here.... if u wanna know wat brian did... ask him.... long stupid story  and make new friends dont hold on to us too much.... but dont forget us either.... and send us some pics of da gurls there....  anyway gtg sleep now... ill post summore stuff another time... ciao ppl
     

    
</post>
<date>28,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      haha tell me everything abt ur school when u have the time ..oh btw arin once u learn japanese u can help us traslate when we go to japan on our tour ;) hehe have a good time there and take care dude 
     

    
</post>
<date>24,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      dudes....man, u dont have to worrry bout me turning into daryl... u just have to worry bout me talking like this ' ichh luhhhve maghhell' (french accent if u dont understand)... anyway, i cant wait to travel round the world,and its ok that u didnt get the wah pedal, because my dad sed not to get it anyway.. hehe, k.. im sorry my plane didn't blow up, i really wanted it to though! grrr...i can't wait to come backeither, jac....but i dont believe how much my sister cried and everyone else...anyway...ig6tg bye byeb ye bye, ciao!
     

    
</post>
<date>24,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey dude its good tht u arrived in canada safely ...  no prob for comin to the airport to see ya off ... haha we really wanted you to go :P hehehe jk jk .... hoped u liked our present ..hehe couldn't get you ur wow, wild , woah ( not sure) hehe padle.. we would have gotten it for u dude.. yea we are gonna make life fun for ourselves you better make you life fun too... but we are gonna travel the world!!! can't wait for tht :&gt;.. it be cooll.. hey btw arin u better not change hehe.. don't be like daryl.... just be urself... haha we all miss you dude have fun in canada   PLZ take some pics of " panas ayam ayam " for us :P and good luck with them :&gt;   cya dude 
     

    
</post>
<date>24,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      yoyo arin ma man person dude guy. y didnt 1 of ur plane engine blow up so u could come back to malaysia man? i dun friend u anymore. introduce me to every hot chick in ur skool k? and every friend u haf. and every teacher. hope u enjoy skool on the 2nd. make lots of gurl friends ya? looking forward for u coming back altho u just left yesterday. neways....keep on posting on this site and tell us abt every single thing. cya btw arin, when i wanna post u click on the POST  PUBLISH button. not the POST button
     

    
</post>
<date>24,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Hey everyone... just arrived in  canada, its not cold at all here, and i never said it would be. im soooo sad bout leaving...jac, brian, and fung, im gonna miss u clowns, and thanks for coming to the airport yesterday wif me, i really appreciate that!! the second last day was cool, had fun in bukit kiara on the second last day wif the thunder birds and friends. im gonna miss all the fun we had in kl.... but u guys keep on enjoying before u dont have the chance to anymore k? school starts on the second, i can't wait.......wait, i can wait :'( i don't wanna go to boarding!! but i've seen loaddddds of hot chicks so far...Aactually there were only like 2 really hot ones....hehe. anyway, thats all for now, ill give u guyz all a call as soon as i can ok???? bye bye!  Arin
     

    
</post>
<date>24,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Hello everyone!! havent posted anything up in agggesss!! how has everyone been? pat... i really dont believe i talked to you yesterday although i was planning on callin you for so long...ask brian and fung.... hehe. Ppl.. bukit kiara on tuesday rite??/ u ppl gotta come... my last daY!! and im gonna take loads of photos and frame them up...one of me, jac, brian and fung, one of all the girls, one of me and mel if i can get one, one of family.... one of all of us!! hehe.... its gonna be cool mian! k, then when i meet the girl of my dreams, ill send u all a photo of her, and u r all gonna be sooo jealous, even the girls!...anyway, im going on too much, so talk later, bye bye, arin
     

    
</post>
<date>23,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hiya! whoa..sori i totally 4got bout 4:am....i hope u didnt stay up all nite waitin. im reallll sori!!! how was de football match? haha..ah i got to no a lot more new ppl. so dats kewl :) haha..in my homeroom...theres only 4 gurls n 14/15 guys in de class...lol. but de guys r cool..so no biggie. well..i hope fung will enjoy his stay at k.b. n yah ill miss arin too. he called me up yesterday..i was soooooo surprised!!! though, it was gd 2 hear from him..missed him a lot. i hope we cleared stuff up..cos lately everyone thinks dat im pissed wif em..when im not..n etc. haha....anyways..i miss marc too!!! :( havent heard from him at all. well i juz hope he's fine n all. how bout u yong? u alrite?! its gd 2 hear from u...COME TO OMAN!!! when r u leavin 4 miri again? will u b able 2 get a pc? get jo 2 finally get n account! okie me g2g now...it's like 6:30am here...gettin ready 4 skool :D. byeeeeee!!! mwah..tc of urself n luv ya loads, pat
     

    
</post>
<date>23,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      yo pat its gr8 to hear tht school was THE BOOOMB:P hehehe i m awake hehehe watchin football.. life is GOOD and bad made some new friends online and got tot know ppl better how abt u??.. fung is in kota baru ..and we are all goin to hang out on tuesday vefore arin leaves :'(   hope he has a good time in canada :&gt; anyways cya online laters if ur awake :P 
     

    
</post>
<date>22,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey every1!! omg......1st day of skool was de BBBBOOOOOMMM!!!! :D but i think my ears r gettin deaf.....ppl yellin n screamin when they c each other...hehe. anyways, hows life ppl? yong again..ill get online at 10:00pm ur time. but than again..i can only stay 4 n hour..than i wont b on till.......4 am ur time again (i bet u wont b awake :P) okie..me g2g now..ill mail u a LOOOONG mail later k sweets. ciao! xox, pat
     

    
</post>
<date>22,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      ok im online now
     

    
</post>
<date>21,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      loool......talk bout b'ball!!! it kicks ass..anyways..i get online at 6:00pm my time...which is 10:00pm ur time :) okie?? kewl kewl..anyways..yah i no jac..we always talk bout confusin stuff..but at least it's interestin :P..hehe j/k!!! anyways..wats up ppl?
     

    
</post>
<date>21,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      heyy..any1 on??
     

    
</post>
<date>21,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hahahah...squash???!!! hahah .. ok pat i ll meet u online then we can chat just tell me th time and date  and i ll be there .. and i sent 2 e-mails to u and i already changed my password so don't worry ..and i don't arin fung and jac read ur mails .....trust me.. and chat to u next time i see ya online   ciaow and btw jac atleast get a better sport !! plz  :P  
     

    
</post>
<date>20,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hmmm......squash is a really kool sport. who plays squash? y so little ppl toking. we can tok about squash. there is lots of things to tok about squash.....the rules, the ball, raquets, court. anyways.....ppl, plz try to type stuff if u do af the time. we cant depend on brian and patrina to entertain us toking about confusing stuff.
     

    
</post>
<date>20,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      wat? who's actin weird? who's confused? huh.......ok now im confused...
     

    
</post>
<date>20,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      get onlineeeeeeeeeeeeee!!!!!!!!!
     

    
</post>
<date>20,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      heya..yep ill reply ur mail soon...we're over derek's house now..he sez hiya to everyone. n..oi i wanna appologize if josh was bein a jerk online..he gets protective bout me. dat cud b gd n cud also b bad in sum ways..but i still love de guy..owez will. anyhoos..yah i kinda guess every1 else cud read dis..so i wont b trypin anythin personal..dat cums in ur mails..i can mail u..u juz WONT MAIL ME BACK half de time!!!!!! :( though..i was thinkin, arin n fung n em knows ur password..so how m i spose 2 no dat they dont read ma mails 2 u..n dat u dont go on my account n read my mails while they're around!!! bout de pix..np :) ill post sum up of me n de GURLS soon..cos they think all de pix i have of em r bad..so they dont lemme post em up. especially a pic of sian..de gurl i sed dat looks EXACTLY like Maggie..cept wid a browny-blondy colour hair. i get online..definately at 6:00pm my time..which will b 10:00pm ur time. so dont sleep so early! man i miss u loads! listen..bout dis whole marc situation..im gonna leave it till nxt summer..till than nm will happen. i guess dats it 4 now..ill reply ur mails soon..n bout "choo-choo train" (where de hell did u get dat nick from????) anyways..yah bout her..ill summarize it.."be a MAN" :)!! g2g now..ciao!! luv ya, pat
     

    
</post>
<date>20,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      y are u actin so werid or maybe i m jus confused
     

    
</post>
<date>20,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      yep?
     

    
</post>
<date>20,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey pat thanks for  joinin hehe.. i already replied ur mail so reply mine asap cheerrs mate :P   and u need to tell me more stuff haha anyways don't write any personal stuff here coz other ppl are readin too haha just send as much mail to me as possible .. anyways tell me when u are coming online so we can chat :P ciaow pat btw thanks for the pictures
     

    
</post>
<date>20,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey! well it's 12:50pm/am rite now..n i cant sleep :P im over at josh's house now..so i doubt im gonna sleep anyways...hey de pix i sent u guys of my friends here...de pc kept sendin de same pix n not de ones i added..so sori if it kept on repeatin......anyways...brian reply my mail!!!! take care!!! sweet dreams...nite! xox
     

    
</post>
<date>19,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      heeeeeey.....brian...de pix r cumin soon...so delete ur mails so it can fit
     

    
</post>
<date>18,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey yong..thx 4 addin me in......so um, wat now? :P
     

    
</post>
<date>18,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      yo nothing to do, man is there anyone else in this site or am i like chattin to my self hehe........................ arin's party tomorrow!!!! yes man .. 
     

    
</post>
<date>18,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      SHHEEEEEEEEEESSSSSSS SOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO HIGHHHHHHHHHHHHHH!!!!!!!!!!!!!! ABOVE ME!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! hehehe cool songs dudes feelin like playing it hehehe if anyone knows the tabs or anything send to to e LPAZ and than YOU!!! hehehe so sup sup guys ... COZ SHE"S SO HIGHHH ABOVE ME!!!! ;P
     

    
</post>
<date>17,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      good news... i changed my piano lesson to 10.30 in da mornin... so ill be finished be 11.30... which still isnt dat early... but normally i would still be asleep at dat time...hehe..... my exam... i dunt think i can change it... so im not sure if i can go to malacca...   And wats happenin tommorow... at wat time?... cause wtv it is... i might also have to pick up my pasport... which should take around 30min...at least dats wat my parents say... so i can onli turn up after 12... so it kinda sucks... but then again... im also normally asleep at 12... =P   oh and brian can u get ur mom to buy da stuff... cause i cant get it...  okay ciao for now...
     

    
</post>
<date>17,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hahah cool stuff fung :&gt; * thumbs up* hehehehe  okok if u can change ur times post it up lar .. ok ok and yea i am serious to bring jia weii hehe.. i have 4 free tickets to the water world and safari thing .. yea hahahahah ok i ll kidnap u :P  hahahah ok ok plans again  tuesday... i m goin to the drivin range at around 8 something ..  play golf until like 10 .. something ok ok  we need to call ppl . ok   ill put the ppl we need to call besides us ... ok  jon chay, dawn , fatin , elanie , em , verun , menz , greg , AND JIA WEII !! any body else just post them up... really i think nobody actuallys checks this sit out except us :P hehehe hmmm...  i have a feelin tht the gurls wouldn't wana come hehehe.. but we need to check anyways .. fung can u help me call some of the ppl.... once u called and got the answer just post it up ok??? we need to do this by today..
     

    
</post>
<date>17,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hi ppl... added some stuff again... well im havin trouble plannin for da week... got piano lesson on tues evenin... and piano exam on thursday at 12... so kinda sucks... but ill see wat i can do.. try to change da time and all... hope i can... ill tell u guys if anythin changes in my plan... oh and brian u can kidnap me if u want.... or else i can always just go after 12.30.. exam onli around 15 min... and i would also go with plan C if i can... o well gtg ... ciao for now.... btw seriously r u serious abt bringin jia weii?
     

    
</post>
<date>17,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      arin can't come because his dad is scared tht he will get sick .. so he can't come ... hahahahahaha ok i ll try to get jia weii .. if ur serious :P  heheh  
     

    
</post>
<date>16,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      brian....is arin coming to melacca with us or not? jia weii can come to mallaca with us. he'll make things fun
     

    
</post>
<date>16,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hahahah true jac .. i don't think anyone else even looks at the dam site heheheh.. ok ok ... so we are goin to do plan C ok ok .. so who else u wana ask to come???? i got some ideas..   ppl to come.:::     briana , jacalina , fung anus , arina , jon chay, dawn , em , elanie, fatin, ben teo , jason , menz, verun, jia weii ... hmmm... if u want anyone else or want to cancell anyone out just post it up!! and if u wana come just post something up sayin tht u wana come okok?? bagus.. hmmm wut else ...... its night time and jac is watch 102 dalmatians...    ok my plans for next week if u guys wana know.. which u prob wouldn't :P ok         monday  - nothing               tuesday - sleepin over arins                 wednesday - arin's party, sleeping over                                         thursday - melacca with jac and maybe fung                       friday - come back from melacca          ok i need to fit jia weii in there some way coz i promised him to gosomewhere       anyways ciaow if any ideas plz post :&gt;   cheers mate 
     

    
</post>
<date>16,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      if we take PLAN C, who else will come to paint ball with us dude? neways....the only ppl who are actually typing in this site is brian fung arin chay and me. where's everybody else?
     

    
</post>
<date>16,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      yo guys .. fung and jac.. are u guys goin to sleep over in arin's house on tuesday?? if u are i have A PLAN!!!!!... ok ok .. listen up ..i mean read up!! .. ok  heres plan A: first u guys come over my house and bermain bola sepak then from my house we go to arin's house by taxi.   PLAN B:  go to arin's house and help him move the drum set .. if he doesn't do it on monday..  PLAN C : come over my house and go to the extreme park and do paint ballin ;) so CHOOSE!!.  btw fung .. hmmm if u have paino exam...hmmm... i got a list of stuff ok ok  1:can u put the exam earlier?  if yes go to question 2, if no go to question 3  2: then we go after you finish lar 3: ill try to get my parents to make it later . if i get my parents to go later go to question 4, if NO!! then go to question 5 4: then we must come back later on friday 5: JUST SKIP THE DAM THING OR ELSE ILL KIDNAP U!!! heheheh  ok call me fung  cioaw cioaw
     

    
</post>
<date>16,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      fung, what thing on the right?
     

    
</post>
<date>15,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey evelyone! im damn bored, sitting here in my office... i just wanted to say thanks to the thunder birds for the really really cool, and special keychain they gave me, it really means a lot to me... hope u guyz  enjoyed pirates of the carabiean, and no problemo for the flowers... now ur making me sound gay! it was from my mum! anyway, i said thanks to her many times for u guyz, and.....ya.  Ok, fung, what do u mean it is going to be soo different without me? i mean.. think about how different it will be 4 me, without all of u guyzzzz, :'( and by the way, i am going to miss u ppl... i love u *breaks out into tears* anyway... i haf to go, so ciao for now... ps: sorry for getting mad for trying to figure out what u guyz were doing.. hehe love Barney
     

    
</post>
<date>15,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      and can someone tell me wat da  thing at da right side is supposed to do?.... i dunt really get it
     

    
</post>
<date>15,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hi ppl... hope u like da new title thingi i put in.... any ideas on wat else i can add?... and i could change da title if u ppl dunt like it..=P.. hehe...
     

    
</post>
<date>15,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey guys good morning =)   ok JAC......so therefor i need to do ma add maths hw ..DAm.. heheh jk .. need to do loads of work today.. hey fung finding nemo didn't take 10 yrs hehehehe ooppss took 3 years -2 years for the graphics and 1 yr for the idea ..so DUde Boi hehe.. ok ok wut else do i wana say..hmmm...... can't wait for arin's party :) goin to be great =) and does anyone know when fatin is coming back??  oohh yea if jac doesn't read my blog then i just want to say thank q jac for workin so hard on the thunderfriends blog :) haha and AGAIN I WANA say THank u to arin for the BUNGA BUNGA hhehe ..i know my malay sucks jhehehe... okok so anyways need to eat papaya hehe  ciaow guys 
     

    
</post>
<date>15,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      found a new skin. neways, the thing on te right does not work....nebody noes how to work it?
     

    
</post>
<date>15,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Hi ppl... damn bored.. so decided to post somethin here.... Pirates of carabiean damn cool... got free tickets... so went to watch with brain... sorrie jac... couldnt ask u to come got 2 tickets onli... and arin is on church camp...  anywayz bset week of my life lar this week.... everyday somethin fun... from throwin stuff in da pool to jumpin in and out of LRTs... damn chun =).... And i would also like to thank arin for da very nice flowers he sent us... damn chun...hey arin, be sure to thank ur parents on behalf of my family.... thanx again...  man i cant belive arin is leavin... hey btw hope u like da present we got u... u got damn pissed of tryin to figure out wat we were doin..=P..... life is never gonna be da same next year... cant belive school is startin soon.... gonna be damn diffrent especially without arin... o well ....no more to write... so ciao for now...
     

    
</post>
<date>15,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      brian...we dun haf to cancel. we can go to arins party after add math tuition.  we go to arins thing at arond 12 or 1 lah. hey, i just realised u can u HTML on this  blogger thingy. .......neways....i'm trying to get new skins for this blog.
     

    
</post>
<date>14,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Hey guys..i  also want to say thank you to arin's family and ofcourse arin ..for the flowers.. and i can't wait for ur party heheh.. and  i hope u liked the present tht me,fung and jac got u .. mr kapor,, =) anyways jac..   we need to cancell add maths tution on wednesday coz of arin's party!!!.. so tell ur mummy plz hehehe... anyways thts all for now.. over and out  GF.. u know wut it means right???......... bagus =) 
     

    
</post>
<date>14,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hi everybody. i just wanna thank arin and his whole family for the flowers. their so kind. arnt they? yes they are. i feel like crying. i also want to say lalala pohpoh.
     

    
</post>
<date>14,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      HOWDI HO!!! man i have nothing to do and i m chattin to joel and listening to micheal learns to rock ..and theres thunder and lightin every where its like i am in world war 2 hehehe even if i wasn't alive then,.,,, or was I????!!! :P haha so sup guys any news ????!!! and jokes?!! Or is ur Life just PLAIN BORIN?!!!! IF IT IS CALL ME  ;) esp ..if ur a panas ayam hahahaha .. jk jk 
     

    
</post>
<date>13,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      lalala poh poh. hi guys. i'm feeling bored. theres nobody online. i am trying to past my time wisely. 
     

    
</post>
<date>13,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      yo dudes! its dawn hahaha hope y'all enjoy your holidays! stay cool! =P
     

    
</post>
<date>13,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      HEy Guys this is a promise to ALl of u here... i am goin to make my life intrestin and go for  adventureS,,!!! i don't wana live an ordinary life ..   LIVE LIFE TO THE FULLEST!!!! ADVENTURE!!!!! GO GO GO GO 
     

    
</post>
<date>13,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Hey guys, I just joined into this blog. Hahaha, mine is www.jonchay.blogspot.com Its about my life too! Yea it could be boring for you guys too, catch you up later, i needa update my blog. Cyaz  The LiGhTbUlB Lover
     

    
</post>
<date>13,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      GOOOOOOOOODDDDDDDDDD MMMMMORRRRNING.!!! hey guys for new ppl .. here are our individual blogs .. for the thunderbirds = ) ....  i m not sure if the bold eagle and black hawk has one.. well mine is www.Mxtreme.blogspot.com,     jac's ruffryderz.blogspot.com but guys BEWARE ITS JUST ABT OUR LIVESSSS...sooo might be borin to u guys ; )   Cya Guys ..      GF........hmmmmmmmm tht doesn't look right.... ok ok green falcon ; ) ...hahah cya 
     

    
</post>
<date>13,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Hey ppl.... bald eagle here.... last 3 days damn cool lar... and damn u ppl who threw me in da pool...hehe... =P well hope we do somethin like that again..... damn tired.... but im still up at 1am for some reason... well da fun for me is finally over.... my mom wont let me leave da hse for quite a while..... o well... too bad for me then......
     

    
</post>
<date>13,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      YO MAN... call me the Green Falcon ... i see u already met ma friends the golden phonenix hehehe.. there are 2 others the bold eagle and th black Hawk heheh .. together we make the THUNDER BIRDS!!!!!!!!!!! ooooooooOOOOOOOOOOOhHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH yeaaa
     

    
</post>
<date>12,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hi this is the golden phoenix(jac). for those who are new to this like me.....this is where u just type anything like crap dung shit poo. when u feel like wrting stuff then come write. anyways we hope u enjoy ur stay with the thinderbirds and friends! ROCK ON PUNKS! 
     

    
</post>
<date>12,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      yo guys .. today was COOOLIN .. man first time we did soo many excitin things hahahahah hope there will be more to come ;)  
     

    
</post>
<date>12,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hi, im a new member of this  place, and im like cool surfer dude type... i got long blonde bob marley style hair. i like boobs
     

    
</post>
<date>11,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      testing 123....this is the GENISIS of the THUNDER BIRDS and FrIeNdS!
     

    
</post>
<date>30,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Hey fung could add more links...... like the newcastle site or fhm (just a thought) ;D
     

    
</post>
<date>29,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      fung.....can u figure out a way to make a link to our archives. i wanna look at our previous posts and i'm sure other ppl would want to too. u can edit our archives site by goin to settings if u didnt already noe. only our most recent posts can be seen now.
     

    
</post>
<date>29,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      yea brian....go to low yat plaza....its very cheap stuff there.....hehe. wussup dudes and dudettes. lets add more ppl to this site. but add ppl tht we like lar ook? wut do u guys think. it gets a bit boring here so i guess we add some more ppl. post up ur ideas
     

    
</post>
<date>29,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Brian i see u want to buy a thumb drive, go to low yat plaza instead.... its very cheap stuff there.... i got my 256 usb 1.1 thumb drive for only RM 150...  oh yea and fung do u still want to share the 24 season 2 thing?.... rite nite all :D
     

    
</post>
<date>29,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      today is such a crappy day....crappy crappy crapppyyyyy dayyy!!!!  -eLaniE-
     

    
</post>
<date>29,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hahaha hey chay dude i think thts enough of the jedi..s stuff :P hahah  hey u know arin called me this morning BUT I WAS IN THE SHOWER!!!! NOOO.. what kinda friend am I?!! hey arin sorry mate i was in the shower but thanks for callin ;) hey today is Pitcha's birthday ..happy birthday! hmm.. but first needa invite her.... ahh ok ok and it was greg;s birthday also.. haha cool main.. so wazup guys..??!! hey fung wei u goin to the club right? after gym then me and u can go to pyramid to buy the pen drive for computer studies :&gt;..ahh hey i feel like eatin roti canai..for some reason .. ok ok thts all cya cya  Green Falcon
     

    
</post>
<date>29,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      To all you Jedis out there!!! The code shall be followed to be in the Jedi Academy: There is no emotion, there is peace There is no ignorance, there is knoledge There is no death, there is the FORCE...  hehheheh
     

    
</post>
<date>28,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      ohtayz guyssss...so post and publishhh okiezz..haha...linkin park have gotten kinda weird since thier last album..no offensce to n e one..i mean they are okies and everythinggg but is it just be or did theri first album sound alot better then their second? n e wayss...ARIN!! get u ass back here!! haha...oh well...knock ur selves out guyss...im outttt :D   -LuV- -eLaniE- 
     

    
</post>
<date>28,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Oh yea one more thing.. if u guys have problems just say it lar :P then we can go beat them up MAUAHAHAHAHA jk jk we are peaceful follow the code of the jedi hahaha  cya
     

    
</post>
<date>28,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hahaha yea its true but lets hope we invite only friends and not some random ppl :P. haha u hurt ur back ?! haha so did i the lower part haha well today was kinda  good day.. fatin told me tht they beat the ppl they were playin( no idea who) hahahah.. and i asked one of them ;) THEY ARE HOT DUDES!! ..nah just jokin arin's hotter ;P so anyways they told me tht they were trashed hahah and tht gis have a good team haha so thts good. one more thing lets hope we can beat them again tomorrow and CHAY forget aobut her comon dude feel the facts flow with the force and COMON dude haha cya cya  
     

    
</post>
<date>28,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Hey ppl.... good to know that we r attracting more ppl.... da site is called thunderbirds and FRIENDS =P... emphasis on "Friends"..... anyway... yea man... we won football today... hurt my back... dunno how though... dunt really think it was football..... and arin.. cant wait for december man... we must go melaka this time...=) and chay just forget abt her man... it would be better off.... trust me... and well abt da birds pictured... ill change them this weekend k...  anyway...cya ppl for now....buh bye.. =)
     

    
</post>
<date>28,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Hey ppl....its ben..... i heard that the linkin park concert is only 18 and over... does anyone noe anything?
     

    
</post>
<date>28,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hahah hey elanie u need to press post and publish to post it on the site  JUST REMIND EVERYONE OF U GUYS!! esp ARIN :P hahah wattapp?? hmmm... we won soccer TODAY!!! after a VERy long time... maybe our !0m skill is comin back :&gt; haha yea anyways its a team game.. seems like the site has ppls now so thts kinda cool .hahaha so dudes and dudettes .. whats my name!! haha sorry nothin else to say :P.  u know johan suddenly is actin dam kind to drew haha hey anyways ciao dudes  
     

    
</post>
<date>28,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Hey guyss...eLanie hereee...wattaapp?! can u believe that i couldnt register my name becoz someone already had it?!! i mean!! thats my name!! haha....oh welll... muahz -Luv- -Elanie-
     

    
</post>
<date>28,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hehehehe.....i dunno wut is going on here. anyways.....who wanna go watch linkin park?
     

    
</post>
<date>27,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hahaha yea MAIn and guys remember we still need to plan our trip around the world :P remember we promised and we cant break promises hahahaha.. haha forget about leon lar haha and mel :P.. haha and i m still a long way from playing for malaysia ..DUDE u know whats our problem in soccer every lunch time ??!!!! WHERES THE LOVE?!?!WHERES THE TEAM SPIRIT??!!! thts where we go wrong dude :P we are the 10 M warriors muahaha .. and i think fun will be able to go with her haha so dun put him down and with the prom thing .. guys are really cheap skates lar hahaha no offence guys but seriously we are suppose to buy the tickets hahah but as i said boys are cheap skates hahahaha.. and about the play... hmm.. we must get our star guess ;) kapoor haha  we can call it " JAC STRIKES BACK" muahaha and ARin's our hero ;) and i can be yoda :&gt; :&gt;  haha ok guys gtg cya dudes
     

    
</post>
<date>27,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Thats cool, you guys can get a apartment, live side by side and stuff, sounds really really kewl!!! Yea, it is love at first sight. She likes Leon cause of the accent, looks and stuff lah. Anyway, walaooo i knew brian will be able to represent Malaysia man! I have trust in u man! Brian BOLEH!!! (or tak boleh lah...) I know who fungs gonna ask too. I sense the disturbance in the force..... yesss......... that girl is gonna be asked by sumone b4 Fung.......... fat chance man! Dude, isn't the guys gonna have to pay the tickets for the girls? (thats why most guys go ALONE) At least they can still dance with the girl right??!?! But if ya want it a very magical night. Then u go with the girl lah! Yea man! I like my lightsaber stuff. Brian, this year's play, maybe we can put up a saber fight!!! And I can construct a lightsaber and install a rod on it!!! Sounds intresting eh? Hhahahaha, imagine this man.... Brian, Fung and Jon Chay: Stunt Coordinator/REAL JEDI KNIGHTS!!! Hahahha, anywayz, gotta get back to work man. Ciao dudes! Peace out!!! 
     

    
</post>
<date>27,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      haha dudes we are like a big family ;P hahahahaha.. next time we must get an apartment together guys our own episode of "friends" hahahahaha...  ...yesterday went to em's house was quite cool dude then went to chay's house and had a light saber fight haha ..    so hows everyONE?! tomrrow another week of school ..soo much hw lar. ANYWAYS real madrid lost to velencia ( dun know spellin) haha 2-0 and arsenal beat newcastle 3-2 OH YEA .. haha go arsenal !! u know wut?? we shuold get more good friends to come and write on the stuff .....oh hey arin did i tell u i m playing for a soccer CLUB!!! haha its cool sponsored for adidas and we get our own buss and everything haha.. remember we must bring malaysia to world cup ;) and jac as our coach haha ..  so anyways ppl one more thing.. about mel.. hmmm... i seriously dun get something how can mel like some1 is 3 weeks hmm.. haha maybe love at first sight haha yea. anything else i wana say.....hmm.. nothing much thts all.. OH arin btw WE miss YOu dude!! .. four of us makes up the THUNDERBIRDS !!! haha   and i wana ask some 1 to the prom but the force is tellin me tht she will say no :  ciao dudes and dudettes .. take care and peace out 
     

    
</post>
<date>27,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hahahaha, u obviosly didn't read the blogs last time ;) yea, i'm over meiping now. I'm a new guy man! Jon Chay! Ain't no Jonathan Chay no more!! Thx to brian, fung, ppl who helped me. Brian did the most lah, frankly. And now i'm a new person. If u so happen to find out who i like, arin, plz don't get mad or sumthing. I know it feels weird, or it doesn't sound right. But yea, i can tell u how it happened and all next time man. Leon? He is a pretty good guy. Lets hope mel made the right choice. Anyway, won't u come back b4 prom starts? if you do, maybe u could come to the prom too! I'm sure everybody wanna meet u again.
     

    
</post>
<date>27,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey everyone... im glad to hear from u, jon, uve been quiet, anyway, i  hope that got will answer whyatever u prayed fot.. and who did u ask to prom?? tell me tell me? u over that girl yet... ? k, anyway take care and bye bye haf fun at prom!!!!!
     

    
</post>
<date>26,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Hey ppl, I'm back in track for Blogger ;) Sup guys. Good to hear u again Arin, hope you'll cope with everything there. They're right, the thunderbirds have a missing piece and all. Can't wait to see u again man. Anyway, yeap! Leon is going with Mel. Hahaha, sounds like i'm cursed right? dealing with the fact that got turn down so many times... Anyway, last night i was in church and i prayed to god outside the church. Something happen... when i finished, a bulb just off. All the bulbs except this bulb is off. Sounds weird or stupid but its really cool. You should have seen it man. Anyway, i can't tell u wut i prayed for. But its really magical. Again, can't wait for arin to come back. Hope to see u again. Ciao man. 
     

    
</post>
<date>26,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Dudes!!! i am still here... its just that im not there!! and btw, ill always be here and part of da thunder birds! anyway....u guyz haf to introduce me to leon.... don care bout zaid..hehe, cause leaons going with mel.. and tell him that i will kick his ass if he doesnt treat mel well at prom... hehe..but he has to be a cool guy... and ya, anyway.. what happened to faisal..? hey who are u guyz going to prom with. u know what wud be cool... if fung and em got back together again..that would be sooooooo good! k, anyway... i know like ppl from like mexico, and they are really funny.. hehe.. anyway, i gtg  bye bye take care and stuff
     

    
</post>
<date>26,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey ppl..... yea prom is comin up soon.... and i got no one to ask.... so it kinda sucks.... and brian who u thinkin of askin?.... anyway.. school seems to get more borin everyday.... and its sure diffrent with out arin... onli 3/4 of da thunder birds left.... well got nothin else to say =P.. cya ppl
     

    
</post>
<date>25,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey guys .. and kapor good to hear from u thought u forgot about us :P hahaha hey anyways.. ur welcome jit.. and updates  welll.... its true every1 likes mel.. ok now leon is goin to the prom with mel .... ziad is goin with steph.. and hahah who are u guys goin with???... im thinkin of some 1 but i dun think she will say yes though.. hmm anyways been goin to loads of soccer traning 4 times a week.. hey arin .. u done any fishing over there ???!!! and dude u need to send some pics of ur friends and gurl friends :P hahaha.. ok ok just keep writin stuff. and one more thing chay is pissed of coz mel is goin to the prom ith leon ..hmm... its not a big deal chay ...   anyways cyaq dudes
     

    
</post>
<date>25,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      fung i think the red looks good too. newasy...wussup guys....i just got back from school and i have nuthing to do. i'm going to play football later. ummm.....oh well cya
     

    
</post>
<date>25,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Hey arin... good to hear from u =)... and good to know that ur gettin on really well in school.... we miss u so much.. damn lonely... and hard lar this year... im hardly in any of brian and jac's classes... so im like alone.... da teachers and da homework are also not very pleasent... but overall not too bad... and man u wont belive da number of ppl starting to like mel... damn weird lar.... those ppl include jon chay and menzie.. and others....  Anyway brian, jac adn chay... wat is jit tim tokin abt?... i dont seem to know wat is goin on in da world anymore....  And yea did somemore changes to da site... i think blue looks better though.... okay... cya ppl for now....
     

    
</post>
<date>24,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      yo yo arin. no wonder u didnt come the the site for a long time. anyways....gr8 to noe that u r adjusting to ur skool well. HEY ARIN! so wut changes in ur life haf u made? oh welll.....i've got nuthing else to say other i miss u. hehe. post somore stuff ya? cya
     

    
</post>
<date>24,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hello evelybody...sorry i havenn't posted for so long...busy gone for an out trip(camping) i went saiiiiiling! it was so much fun... like on the boat, if u looked up, u could see thousands of stars up in the sky.... me and some friends were lookin up and talking and stuff bout like how it is good to make a change in life ,because withoput changes in ur life, you wouldnt really get anywhere in life... ya u know.. so its not that bad. k, boarding life isnt that bad.. actually it's pretty cool! u get to hang out withaall ur friends all the time... ya..  and  yesterday was so cool! i was like walking down to the feild with some ppl, to where everybody was... and suddenly someone says Hey Arin! then everyone is like HEY ARIN!!! then i was like .... 'hey cool' ppl know me...hehe, anyway... school is pretty easy, but its boring lah, how bout u guyz... what happened about fais??  hey yong! did u get that mail frop pat saying something bout lay off and three chicks and whores and crap... pretty freaky.. anyway, i gtg now, bye everyone, take care...
     

    
</post>
<date>24,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Hey ppl....just wanna tnk brian for addin me on this site. Well...not much to write abt today..except for the fact that i nearly got 1 damn week detention coz i forgot that stupid info on that village by the sea..well...who cares anywayz.....dunno wut to say when i meet ribena..sigh..brian, jac and jon should noe who i am talkin abt.. Anywayz..write more laterz
     

    
</post>
<date>23,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      yay.. auto bold works.... now everything ppl type nomatter wat it is (bold or not)... would be bold.. =)
     

    
</post>
<date>23,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey ppl....added summore stuff.... nice to know that ppl atually come here.....and brian i think i can auto bold da text.... should i try?..... anyway wassup ppl... not much hw today... so got sometime to do this... and is everyone goin to prom?... and brian who r u thinkin of askin?....
     

    
</post>
<date>23,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
       hahah wah loae soo late dude dude ... haha i didnt know anyone else read the site :P .. ohh well we are more famous than we think ..hahahaha... so anyways its no reason to not write what we feel ..right !! ya MIAin.. hahaha anyways soccer traning was fun.. piggy bank jason :P.. scored 1 goall!! yay.. well not tht happy :P.. soo tired i have like soccer traning like every day :  hahaha and i m still thinkin about prom i dun think the gurl i wana ask out will say yes :  one more thing.. hey fung if we bold our words it will be easier to ready :&gt;   cya guys  
     

    
</post>
<date>23,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      Hahahha! why the hell did u call fais my name in the first place?!?!?!? Nice background u got for this website man. Goodiee! sorry, i didn't post up any messages at all, so yea. Really great effort u put in this web fung. Anwayz, its 11:30 gotta sleep now. Ciao guys
     

    
</post>
<date>22,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey ppl... i actually found out that ppl do read this blog.... like fatin and faisal... cause faisal got pissed at me for callin him chay and he read it bcs fatin was readin it... anyway.... SORRIE FAIS...  and for all u ppl who read... please post soemthing up...   And yea i think my background is too dark.... should i make it lighter....   anyway arin... hope life is cool for u... we r stuffed with work here.... and eya brian is right.. we should at least go out once every 2 week if not every week.... okay gtg now.... ciao ppl
     

    
</post>
<date>22,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      nothing much i have soccer training at 6:30 and i need to finish all my hw quickly.. oh shit i just remembered tht tomorrow is wed .. soccer training under 15's hah anyways wazup?? cya tomorrow 
     

    
</post>
<date>22,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      yo yo sup yall! heheh.....how come only brian and fung comes to the site. there is no point saying tht anyways....cos ppl still wont come to the site and wont read this. oh well....sup brian...and fung. and arin.....come to the site dude. how r u? reply now.
     

    
</post>
<date>20,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
       cool stuff fung " thumbs up" me and fung walked back from sportsunlimited hahah cool lar about 3 - 4 hours walk .. haha had fun  dun wana write everything coz its too much.. well anyways me and fung and the ppl were talkin about school and stuff and i think we should like go out like at least once in 2 weeks and enjoy ourselves .. coz theres soo much pressure and i dun wana be crazy :&gt;.. anyywayss soo much hw to do.. goin to do it tomorrow .and jedi knights 3 is cool been playin it most of the time.. hmmm.. what else .. everyone is in sarika's party thts y there is no one online so tht kinda sucks.. and everyone is talkin about prom .. i know fung is goin but i dunt know if jac is .. hmm.. jac are u goin to the prom this yr ?   anyways got to go.. and fung good job.."soo clever one :P " over and out and one more thing we need to make the font stand out in the background  
     

    
</post>
<date>19,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      fung, the site looks gr8 man. do somemore! heheh......anyways....since the site looks good, wee need ppl to write on it too ok? so post anything u want to post even if it is rubbish. 
     

    
</post>
<date>17,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey ppls.... as u can see... did summore changes... gonna do more later.... but dunt really feel like it rite now.....o well.... we dunt seem to postin much stuff here.... wat happened....???.... and hey arin.. hope u havein fun over there... we all miss u loads.... and i mean loads!!!!.... damn borin nowadays without u... =(... anyway ... ciao for now... buh bye
     

    
</post>
<date>17,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      nvm bout fais....just let him be. yes. uh huh. yea baby. neways.......hey arin. wuusup ma nigger dude guy! how're u? i hope u didnt forget us already. i noe u wont forget us. i think. oh well, how skool dere? is it like a cool surfer dude kind of thing? or is it a boring harry potter skool. take care of urself there ya? eat lots of cabbage there. i heard the cabbage there is very nice. ummmm........post ur reply sooooon. we really misss u. guess wut. its september! tht means ur coming back on december! tht means we only haf to wait for another 3 and a half months! oh yes! ok.....now i gtg. cya ciao avoir cing tao teh WEEE WEEEEEEE!
     

    
</post>
<date>15,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      ya maiN... dunoh whats wrong with him lar... BUt nvm dudes ... so sup guys ,,, so much hw these few days ..and only FIRST WEEK!!!!!!!! hey guys tryin out for under 15's football on wednesday ..and btw what cca's are u takin ?
     

    
</post>
<date>14,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey yea... faisal is turning into chay... nah jk jk...chay is better than him... faisal is just being weird... and hateing da whole world all of a sudden.... and arin... did u get in da football team?... hope u did... wait did u try out in da end?... well hope life is great there for u... school is kinda stressful here.... shit load of hw on da first week... =(... anyway... kinda got to ciao now... so cya ppl..
     

    
</post>
<date>13,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      yo VEE DUDE. how are u ? when are u goin for ur camp ?? hey arin are u the best in soccer over there??!! oh yea arin u need to press post and publish not post.. coz we cant see what u have written :P.. hehe do u have a gf pver then oh yea btw there are 2 new guys in ur class.. ziad and leon.. man i have no idea whats wrong with faisal he keeps havin these mood swings. .. anyways got tot ciao   Cya guys .. keep cool n WHATS MY NAME!!!   i m the coll chi wa wa ..oh yea :P 
     

    
</post>
<date>13,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      dude! im online rite now... hey, u know what... i kipped rugby yesterday cause i had to go and try out for a soccer team... but i didnt go in the end...and ppl here are crap at soccer, not as good as ppl in our school, but the rugby is really good! i mean im probably the crappiest t rugby...hehe, anyway, ill try to mail here as much as i can... and i gtg now, so eeryone take care, and have fun in yr 10, bye bye
     

    
</post>
<date>12,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      yay! arin injured himself! now he can come back to malaysia to see the doctor! YIPEEE!!! neways....hope u recover alin. how e u mian....how come u dun come online anymore. oh yea....u haf skool. neways...i gtg now cya
     

    
</post>
<date>11,September,2003</date>
<post>
</post>
<date>11,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey ppl... its in the middle of school, and im sitting in the library with some ppl using the com... i have nothing better to do! fung.. yea, ill go to melaka, don worry... hehe, i have rugbbby today!  and im gonna get my ass kicked pretty soon.... i already have an injured shoulder, and both my knees are screwed too.... k, i gtg, bye bye take care and all... 
     

    
</post>
<date>09,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hey ppl.... its cool that u got to met loads of ppl there arin... and hot chicks too ;)..  over here... schools starting quite good.... there is 2 new guys in our class and no gurls=(... damn.... o well... scored an own goal today in fottie today =(... headerd it da wrong way.... and we will call u... definately... but we have to get a whone card first.... so maybe next week.. =).. really miss u.... cant wait to december... this time we would make it to melaka okay... anyway... ciao for now... have to go study... and at least get off da pc... cause my dad is scoldin me
     

    
</post>
<date>08,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      helo everyone.... guesss what, i went bowling today! and i got the highest score! 120pts.. hehe, anyway... i met loads of new ppl today, alot of them are from korea and hong kong... thats cool, korean chicks are hot! and i met 2 twins from hong kong in yr 11.. they r cool too, they are bonita and um... something else..  hey pat, how come u dont mail here anymore? i miss all of u like crap... and glad to hear that the bet is still on. hey, brian...post some pics up ok, and ill try too... k, i gtg help my m um do the dinner, bye bye bye ...take care ppl. my phone number is (from malaysia) 0012505197199, thats all, get a calling card, but dont ring from 10-12 in the morning ur time ok, ciao xoxoxo xxx xxx ... bye bye
     

    
</post>
<date>07,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
      hahaha man arin take some pics of the gurls lar..:P hey dawn told me tht will be a new gurl in our school ..hahah... man i was lookin through my sis pics then i found the adverts tht we did :P remember "100 PLUS " hahahah dam funny ... i wana post up some pics on the site ... hey arin btw whats ur phone no. ? need to call u atleast once a month :P  hahaha.. keep informin us about stuff ..and yup the bet is still on ... all the money in our wallets at the time :P hahaha AND THE FEAR FACTOR BET !!!! i won :&gt; hehehe.. got to go look at more pics   hey arin dude.. we all miss u :&gt; so cya in december  and ill see everyone else in school tomorrow :&gt;   Ohhhhhhhhh Chi wa wa   cya guys  \ /                </post></Blog>