<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        I was very upset about something the other day, so I went and bought a slingshot.I have no idea about the slingshot..I can't hit fuck all with it. I can hit whatever I want with a gun though..which makes me immeasurable happy. I so thought I had lost that skill. Honestly, it's about as happy as I am about getting back the ability to play guitar- like I found a peice that has been missing.     Anyway, I got to thinking..it was that damn "Frontier House" program that started me down this road to wanting a house. There is a scene where a guy is building a fence and bitching that he isn't getting enough food- and it turns out he needs to drink more water. Oddly enough, I have had a desire to build a fence or anything ever since that scene. It feels like everything in life that should have hit me at 33 is hitting me now. Damn wreck.    So I am digging into how to build a house, reading books and the internet. I have come to realize that the Jeep can't haul enough of a load to be of use, and that as much as I want some city car..I need another truck. Funny thing, I seem to have a line on a Chevy as of tonight...for about half of what I hope to sell the Jeep for. It's in perfect shape too..a retired air force guy here owns it. Weird stuff. It's like what you need happens if you let it.    Speaking of which, I have been all over the internet lookinbg at alternative buildings..meaning, for the most part, anything that was done for centuries before the lumber barons of the US decided to say it all sucked. I have looked into Solar, Straw Bale, Cob, Adobe, Earth Plaster, Rammed Earth, Log, Slip-form Masonary....pretty much anything that's been done. I am looking for cheap but effiecent with little upkeep.     So Adobe is cool, good for thermal issues, but lots of upkeep. I have stumbled onto Straw Bale construction. It is simply bales of straw, stacked as walls..and then plastered to protect it. You can stucco the outside and make very fluid shapes. Weirdly, a freind mentioned that a friend of his back east built a house this way..and now..it seems like every damn magazine I pick up has straw bale write ups in it!   I mean...mags on living green, mags on home power...its like the world is saying "LOOK HERE DUMBASS!". I have also found colored stuccos that remind me of old Italian villas...so much cooler than normal paint. Anyway....  ...today I was going to drive to Forest Falls..but went past it and made a grand loop all the way through Big Bear. During the drive I was thinking of how much I really don't like the whole "Southwest" type building. It's OK..but not for me. Then it struck me...most of the construction is very much like old Italian villas...! So I began to surmise that for a floorplan and exterior look I could do a straw bale house for many modern reasons, with a villa look to it. Then, I drove past a lot- and had a major deja vu flash from years and years ago..I pictured a villa on this lot near Mentone I think it was- and here I was driving around thinking about how that would fit in to the area well....weirdness. It was like the general area, the lighting, everything, had crawled out of the dream like 15 years ago. The rest of the dream had a wife and a young mistress living under the same roof and about 4 kids. So I doubt it is actually a sign of a true thing that will happen...;</post></Blog>