<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>06,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey guys! You can go here to find out how I am doing especially when you haven't talked to me in a while. I intend to leave a little about how I am doing in with my useless blogs I would like you to comment on. Here is the first useless blog I want comments on. It is a topic that I would like a little help with: I will most likely be asking this really cool girl that I know pretty well now to be my girlfriend. Here is the problem: As Christians, since we will not be doing anything inappropriate, or sexual, if you will, is there any other reason to date in the first place as teenagers except by name only (girlfriend/boyfriend)? Topic: Teen dating, right or wrong; teen dating, useless or full of meaning? Please comment, and have a great day!  God bless!  -Mike
     
    
</post>
<date>06,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Well guys, this is the first entry into my new and progressing blogger thanks to my very very good friend Steve Bergey. I just got back from an extended day of work at Wendy's. You all know I'm working at Wendy's until college, right? I am so tired in mental anguish from all of the hard decisions made, and physical anguish from all of the hard bathrooms cleaned. Unfortunately, they make me clean all of the bathrooms because I do so well... seriously. I was on register today, which is a high step up. It's pretty cool. Well now it is everyone's chance to respond. Hit the little link to make a comment. I will be back AT LEAST once a day to see what is written. Peace!
     
    
</post>
<date>25,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I finally figured out how to use my new blogger. Sorry Guys! Um, nothing much happening today. Since my last message on my former blog page, I have been going out with this really cool girl named Brittany, also a Christian. I see her tomorrow actually. Anyway, leave a message. The next blog I should have something cool to respond to and try to cause conversations! I should post at least once daily. See you all later! E-mail me: OriolesFan2001@hotmail.com
     
    
</post>
<date>18,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      My question about the Dixie Chicks was supposed to include a quote from Martie saying that they believed they were "not supported by the genre," but I didn't include the "not." Imagine it is there. Thanks!  In Christ, Mike
     
    
</post>
<date>16,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Everybody may know that Monday (Oct. 20th) is the happy birthday to me day. Well, my girlfriend Brittany had a huge surprise for me she has been planning for a while, with a romantic dinner she cooked just the two of us, presents, dancing, and all kinds of things. It was so sweet. She and her aunt picked me up at 3:00, and I got home about midnight. It was so cool.   Anyway, here is what I have to ask everyone: The Dixie Chicks left country music because they are "supported by the genre," in the words of Martie, the steel guitarist/banjo player. Now why on earth would the "F.U.T.K." girls think that? Did they think nobody saw the "Without Me" video and the Entertainment Weekly cover? What do you think? Country music is supposed to be more wholesome.  In Christ, Mike  "Wait for the Lord; be strong and take heart and wait for the Lord." - Psalm 27:14 NIV
     
    
</post>
<date>16,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay, I want everyone to comment on my not so normal day. I go to Edgewood High School. After first period in school today I was walking down the hall and I stopped to pick up some trash. Well, I never had trash say "Open Immediately." The curiosity in me made me open it. What I saw when I opened it was a bomb threat to the school. It read, "There is a bomb in the school. It will go off at 11:30. It will be funny to watch you die." After I read it, and went through two periods, I turned it in. The principal, Mr. Schmitz, called me to his office to ask me questions about it. He evacuated the school entirely for almost an hour, from 11:05-11:45 to make sure there was no bomb. It was in fact, a prank, as I knew the whole time. To make sure I was right in the situation, I turned it in anyway. A letter was sent to all the parents of all the students detailing the situation, including all the measures they went through to protect the students and to draw leads as to who wrote the note, and the drastic punishments to the perpetrators. It was kind of embarrassing, but I am glad I did the right thing. What a day, huh? I promise to start writing more.  In Christ, Mike  "Then He said to them all, 'If anyone would come after me, he must deny himself and take up his cross daily and follow me. '" -Luke 9:23 NIV
     
    
</post>
<date>13,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I still need to get used to blogging everyday and checking this thing. Colin, as soon as I am done here, I will look at your page. Any friend of Steve's (AKA Mark lol) is a friend of mine. Keep coming back I guess. Okay, I have a question, friends. If I got into an argument with my girlfriend's friend about how she treats my girlfriend, and I am right, and was totally honest but yet nicer than most people would be, and yet her friend keeps twisting my words and trying to get me in trouble with Brittany, though it doesn't work,  should I apologize to her anyway? Her friend thinks I should, but Brittany thinks I shouldn't, and nobody cares if the friend (left unnamed in respect) and I do not get along. Should I apologize if I am right? What do you all think? More tomorrow. Probably about a different subject.  In Christ, Mike  But the LORD said to Samuel, "Do not consider his appearance or his height, for I have rejected him. The LORD does not look at the things man looks at. Man looks at the outward appearance, but the LORD looks at the heart." - 1 Samuel 16:7 NIV 
     
    
</post>
<date>08,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I finally learned how to work everything. You'd think I was 800 years old, huh, Mark? Well now all systems are go! My next post will be something going on in my life that creates a nice topic of discussion for the day. I will also have a Bible passage of the day under my signature everyday. Please be respectful to others, be brief if possible, and please remember it is not a chat room. Otherwise, have fun. This is as much for my friends as it is for me. I will be back several times a day to respond to what I see. Please comment! Anyway, talk to you all later! Tell your friends this is where I am!   In Christ, Mike  "For the message of the cross is foolishness to those who are perishing, but to us who are being saved it is the power of God." - 1 Corinthians 1:18 NIV
     
    
</post>
<date>28,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      :( No one's commenting. Me sad. Anyway, um, how was everyone's Thanksgiving? Mine was w00t'd as usual! We had all kinds of family over, and more food than anyone will ever eat. We also had a new treat- sparkling apple cider. Now that's the stuff! (No, not Hostess!!!) Anyway, I have had trouble finding really good time to blog all the time. I am starting to budget my time a lot better and I should have the time.  Anyway, talk to you all soon! Blog ya later! Please comment!   In Christ, Mike
     
    
</post>
<date>25,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Nothing to blog about today except the fact that Mark has a new page that we should share. On his old page, www.stephenbergey.com, he has a new chat forum everyone should become a member of. I will spend a lot of time there because I am the moderator of most of the topics. If there is a thread or post I deem offensive, bye bye. I can also talk Mark into suspending your registration. But I am lenient, so have fun! Just don't offend the viewers badly! Insults are okay, just watch it! Anyway, blog ya later!  In Christ, Mike </post></Blog>