<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My internship will start tomorrow.  It sounds like a really intense place, so i'm nervous about the whole thing.  i've always fit in in office enviros really well, and i've tended to do well in those places.  i think i'll be sucessful.  i also don't think its going to be very hard at all.  i'll post tomorrow to let everyone know how it went.
    
</post>
<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      am i in love with you know who?  i think that i may be, though i have never thought about or really fantasized about being with him.  
    
</post>
<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This week was somewhat of a breakthrough in the jobsearch. I even got an offer for a job I had to refuse. On Tuesday I got two phonecalls. One was from Turning the Page, an organization that does professional development for teachers and connects communities to schools. They were calling for a second interview. The other was from Hispanic CREO, a group that advocates for school choice reform. They offered me a (well)paidinternship until something else comes up. I had my TTP interview yesterday, and I think it went really well. I don't want to count my eggs before they hatch, though. I have no idea what my competition looks like!   
    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Priam's coming and I'm excited!  YEAH! 
    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Below you'll find a pic of the place we now call home. Its in Takoma Park - what I consider to be the finest subset of DC. We're in a real neighborhood, with friendly neighbors and treelined streets, but we're still a 4 min walk from the metro, and a 20 min ride from downtown. It comes at a price, though, and there are a few things wrong with the house. In fact, I'm about to go check to ensure the basement didn't flood last night! That said, I couldn't be happier with it. Don't you love our faux stone? 
    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Our new house in Takoma Park. urlLink   
    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Welcome to my blog. My ambition is to record my thoughts and ideas as I find a job, explore dc, and hopefully come across a partner in crime. It'll be more or less unedited... just pure musings. enjoy. 
    
</post>
</Blog>