<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The bump came in today - a day before I expected it. That is good news. I have to pay less apartment late fees and I feel a little better about the whole mess. Still waiting on those letters from the bank to resolve this creditcard fraud mess.  Just listening to the radio in the cold room - ahh - technology - everything I love about it seems to cancel itself out with everything I hate about it.   am ordering the new 7" covers this week, if all goes well. I am looking forward to the end of the line with that shit. Looking back on the last year, all the changes that have happened seem to always have that in the picture - shows have fallen to ruins.  The band thing has run its course with me, never again. That is a stage in my life that I am over with for good. I love art, making things, music too, but I just can't deal with the bull shit anymore. Almost all my friends are from connections in music. I wouldn't trade that for anything in the world. I still enjoy making shirts. I don't really enjoy building websites anymore, not like I used too. I wonder if there is more to come. Have I just not matured enough, have I not found myself like I think I have?   Since Eric is selling a few things, I also have a few things that I will through up for you guys before I take em to my parents for a garage sale:  Glass Dinning table and chairs(the chairs have seen the rath of a kitty) $100 o.b.o.   Time Killers arcade game - $160  Corner Computer Desk: $40  I am moving and I will have alot of other shit for sale. But problably nothing really cool. 
     

    
</post>
<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      hahahaha....the morning has been great so far. Halloween. I came to work looking like a zombie with an afro. I got the fake "bloody scabs" all over my arms. I usually don't do this but latly I have been enjoying this holiday. It's fun...its just a little fake blood, it never hurt anyone. People are jumpy around here, I've just been doing my normal stuff and i get a few jumps here and there.  I guess it looks pretty good becuase i feel like a fucking animal in a cage... people just looking and going, "Hey Mark, check this guy out!" Fuck OFF! Its just a little fake blood, never hurt anyone...
     

    
</post>
<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      just added my interview with myself
     

    
</post>
<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      well.......i guess lunch time is over. I really wish i would get a record or two from someone in the mail... I got an order to No Idea for like 8 7inches and an order for a few SOV 7inches and a Karate 7" i won off of ebay....nothing yet.  I feel sleepy. only 3 more hours of the work and I will be right back here again being retarded and wasting time in front of a PC.
     

    
</post>
<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      it did work! and some how it got rid of my freaking java error on the page...
     

    
</post>
<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      well i just wanted to test out this little blog from AIM thing and if this works, I would have to say very cool.   I'm at home now, eating some leftover birthday cake and drinking a coke....no time flat I will be the biggest, fatest son of a... you have ever seen. haha. nah.....i need to go do some running again.
     

    
</post>
<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      well, im just at work. getting hungry and tired of people bothering me.  I just want to sit here and play with my website. I don't want to fix your email or make your printer work after you jammed it up pretty good.  yesterday was my birthday, i'm 22 now and my ID is expired. i hate going to the DMV.  i'm sure it will be a barrel of fun.
     

    
</post>
<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       SpyAttack goes Platnium  Most of this week has been pretty insane.  The weather was really nice, well it was cold. I find chilling air exhilarating.  Some how the icy air filling up my lungs makes me feel more alive than the smoggy filth that is Dallas summer air.  On Monday the talk in the office was "Oh I hope the roads aren't bad!", and "Well, winter is finally here."  In Dallas, there is no winter.  There are three day periods in the Winter months where it happens to get below 40 F. My decrepit self spent most of the week at home or at work.  Not really talking to much of anyone esp after Wednesday when I lost my front tooth.  I find it very disheartening.  I know I shouldn't care what people think, but it just brings back the insecureities of jr. high and that's really what I hate about it.  I feel exposed, almost naked.  I have found comfort in the pages of William Sutcliffe's second novel "Are You Experienced?"  So far a great book.  I have to stay I really don't like to put it down.  Almost through with the book, when I am done, I will post my thoughts in their entirity.  So far, I am really ejoying it.  I think I am starting to cheer up.  I am totally looking forward to spending the next week with mimi's dad in California.  I think I am gonna go up in the mountians and do a little hiking.  There is a scooter shop in Sacramento called Vespa Haus that I want to check out.  I need to buy a little something for the bike so that will be fun.  Someone other than old man Garner.  And I am totally going to hit the record stores in Berkly and SanFran.  Maybe go fishing at the Delta.   Anyways.....I will try to post on here more frequently.  Till then, all my love.
     

    
</post>
<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
        Welcome to my mind   Ah hell, whatever.  I'm so sick and tired of everything.  I'm pretty  unhappy the last few days, seems that all I want to do is bitch and  moan.  I'm looking forward to this 2-day cold snap coming up. Then sometime in december it will get up to 80 again and make me want to freeze myself through the blistering summer.  Just thaw me out when it gets cold again.  I am getting that itch to move and I'm pretty sure this time next year, I'm going to scratch it. 
     

    
</post>
<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, this weekend went to hell as far as the planned events but I made it worth my while I suppose.  After canceling the show for Lubbock pretty much on the way, pissing everyone off, and wasting about an hour of everyone's time...I went a head and took Brian's drums to him.  I thought it would be nice to eat some dinner with my brother and hang out so I asked him to come along to get some food and I would by him some dinner.  He was down, but he also invited his friends....well, my mind changed because that wasn't really what I wanted to do...so I totally confused him but oh well.  I got on the road wanted to talk to some one about the events, I called up my parents, and then just decided to roll on over there.  I was there for about two hours just talking about this and that.  I invited them to come up this weekend...so maybe I will see them around tomorrow.  I want to take them to this awesome greek place in lewisville that I know they will just love.  Plus, I think my dad is going to bring the Vespa P200 frame that I bought for Brian like almost a year ago.  I think it will be better off in my garage than just sitting in the back of their yard.   Today has totally rocked so far...  I slept till 9 a.m. which was really nice.  For the last month it seems that there hasn't been one weekend that I could just sleep in my bed without doing much of anything.  I would have slept longer but Robert(co-worker) called to let me know they were going to be up at the office going over the Saturday system backup procedures at around 10am.  I needed to be there.  I sat around, checked my email, got dressed and went up to the office. It was a pretty quick ordeal. I spent about an hour there going over all the stuff that needs to be done every Saturday.  New responsibilities...fun.  While I was away, mimi had gone up to Planet Tan to bake herself for a few minutes...she happened to get home at the exact same time I did.  So we went and got some food and went to Target where I bought a "boombox" for the garage.    I spent the rest of the afternoon cleaning up the garage.  I took a whole gallon of bleach and poured it on the floor of my garage.  The fumes where so intense that I couldn't breath or see.  My eyes were watering so bad I had to go outside to get any air worth breathing.  Some how I managed to sweep it all out and I used a fan to help dry it.  After all that mess I spent about 4 hours working on the dismatleing of my Vespa engine. That went Ok for the most part, I had a few problems with a few bolts....some of these problems are still pending.  It was pretty frustrating. I had to go to home depot to pick up a wrench....the real reason was to take a break from the engine. I was about to give my self a heart attack, I just get worked up over shit way to easy.  I feel like I made some head way on the project so that is cool. The real pay off is when I start putting it back together.  That is where I bet it'll get super tough. Around 7pm I am finishing up the laundry and I call up my Uncle Scott who lives right down the street.  His wife, Carrie, was going to a movie so he was going to just be sitting around the house for a few hours with their little baby boy, andrew.  I went over there for a few hours and talked about all kinds of stuff.  I really dig Scott because he reads alot and has alot of interesting view points and I like to hear what he has to say about things.  Anyways, I should be going to sleep soon.  mimi and I are getting up in the middle of the night to go watch the meteor shower.
     

    
</post>
<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, for the last day or two things have been brightening up a bit.  I really can't say how much, but some. 
     

    
</post>
<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Whatever will I do.... I had a very bad day yesterday. I had an appointment to see the Dentist at 3:30 yesterday afternoon. Got off a bit early from work and went over to the dentist office, I didn't have to wait very long to get into a room, which was cool, but i had to wait on the dentist forever it seemed like.  I was going to check and see what could be done with my broken partial, I have it just sitting there and it is  very  annoying.  She told me I need a bridge, fuck, that sucks because that is like 2,500 bucks for a fucking tooth. Anyways, I was pretty upset, walked to my car crying becuase I know it will be a few months before I can get the bridge and that means I have to deal with this broken 'false tooth' for that much longer.  I went home and cleaned up the house real nice for the Art Collective meeting.  No one came.  I laided on my bed for about 40 minutes and read a new book I just got at the library.  the history of buddhaism. It's pretty interesting. I was about to fall asleep, but I finished the chapter and laid my head down.  8pm i was asleep and mimi woke me up at 11:30 and told me to get undressed for bed, i still had my pants on.  whatever..........
     

    
</post>
<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      well i'm at work....thinking of all the shit i need to get ready for another weekend of wuornos shows. first off I want a fresh shower.  my cat pissed all over my clean socks that i had in a basket.  I am really sick of that cat.  I love her, but damn, that is just nasty, she doesn't know.  i think her litter box needs fresh litter. I guess whatever.  We are going to longview tonight to play at the Texas Blues Bar.  I'm stoked about it...first show with brian as our drummer. Hope it goes well. I wont be back until Sunday night.
     

    
</post>
<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       year-end: 2001   Well here I am, trying to think of all the things that have happened in the last year and I really only see the last four months.  I have seen more, learned more, and changed more in the last four months than I have all year.  I really started to expand my worldview more after nine eleven and try to see the world with a different eye.  This led me to a new change in my beliefs on animal rights, corporations, city life, money, health, love, and friendship.  I always loved the urban life, running from street to street and taking it all in.  I still do but there is something different now, I see all these people running around, what for, I find confusion in my new found knowledge.  I don't know about you, but I go through this from time to time like most humans.  What am I doing, why am I here.  Maybe I should help people, but then, maybe not, I need to help myself.  Fuck you and your needs, but this is selfish.  So what am I to do with my time? Should I go through life to make as much money as I can and do all that I can possible dream about?  Sure, why not.    This weekend marks 5 years to the date when I met mimi, Dec 30.  I know that sounds stupid, but that is the day she started work at the Sweet Shop where I was the cook, famous for my perfect Corn Dogs.  haha.  Yeah I made em better than anyone ever.  So they say.  That was a totally different time for me.  I was a very different person 5 years ago, and that is just bizarre to picture in your mind what your were 5 years ago.  I can see myself in my mind, I had this pair of jnco's that were cut off mid-calf.  I still have them, they are in a bag of clothes I'm going to take to goodwill.  I always wore plain white t-shirts and I had a chain wallet, I had hair then and around this time it was bleach blonde and I was still skinny.  Didn't drink then.  Beer did it, that didn't happen for another year.  I was busy, with my fast food job and my bad ass 1972 Chevy pickup.  I had stickers all over the back window of the pickup. Dead Kennedys, supertones, mxpx, the specials, value pac, etc...  I was in between bands at the time, but I had all the equipment to start a band, with my work money I had bought a drum kit, guitar amp, PA, guitars and bass guitars and it was all in my room.  I had a door to the room from the outside, my closet was paneled with cedar and my clothes always smelled so good.  I'm started to feel old, but I'm just glad I can remember sometimes.  Now I'm at the brink of twenty O' two; Happy new year.  What lies in the future is so beyond me that I can't even begin to make a prediction.  I know that the person I am now is the person I think I want to be, it's always that way, but maybe I will become a better person, maybe not as pissed off, maybe I will finish things that I need to finish and move on.  Love you all.
     

    
</post>
<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       x-mas and more of that sort of thing   well, the holidays were more exciting than most so far. I spend a few days before x-mas to take a tour of west texas stopping in little towns that house family of my girl and i.  that was nice, i got a chance to see some family that i havn't seen in about two years, like uncles, cousins and such.  on the day after x-mas i spend holding it down at ssg.  mimi was off work on thursday and we really didn't do anything but hang around the house, hell thats all i've done for the past 4 days, it seems.  glued to the tv playing grand theft auto 3 on the playstation 2 to that mimi bought for me.  i went to a show on friday night, that was a highlight.  i saw a few people that i hadn't seening in a while, all the bands were great: el salvador b-day bash, ...of death, kill the slavemaster, and since by man.  great show.  lots of energy or drunks, can't tell, but it was my first chance to get out my camcorder that mimi bought for me for x-mas.  I owe it to her for sure.  so i have the show on tape and that was fun in itself.  from the desk of john coffman
     

    
</post>
<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Dinner at Monica's   Dinner last night was quit an event.  For the first time in my life, I met some people that I actually found interesting. It's a weird twist on the feeling of meeting new people because I don't really admire these people as much as I just plain find them interesting.   mimi's mom was in town for a meeting and she had invited us out to dinner with a group from her office. I was dreading it.  I just really didn't see it as being fun, but I was hungry, and it was Tex-Mex with a vegetarian menu so I sucked it up.  The place was like a crowded bar, oh wait, it was a crowded bar filled with the cool and trendy.  It was a really cool place and it was half-priced entree night so I could see the reasons for being so busy.  Hell, tonight they have 50 cent margaritas, I can just imagine all the people there then.  We walked into the waiting area and there was this group in the middle that we were meeting up with.  Let me see if I can get this right, but there was Jerri, the old yank woman that moved her giant pear-shaped body around like a weeble-wobble. Her shepardess, Tiffiny, who was the young, repitively defensive and also over weight girl who seemed to feel the need to protect the thought of her open-mind as Fort-Knox.  Next to her was Rose(i think that's her name), not much to say about her except the fact that all of her stories seemed to be very anti-climactic.  Also, the host's of the dinner, Lee and his wife(I forgot her name).  Young, maybe late 20's early 30's, very much caught up in the city life of Dallas.  Into all the lights and sounds of city culture.  I found them to be more inspiring than the other people at the table.  Lee's wife scuplts and paints.  Lee seems to be very sucessful and I could see that his charisma is what got him there.  He really didn't seem that overy interesting but he knew how to deal with people, something I am really not good with.  His wife was able to pull out some very interesting topics and we discussed art, vegan resteraunts, and music; Lee would occational note additions to the conversation. The food was really good, I would go back.  Maybe on a less crowded night.   today  Just going through the same uninteresting things; the life of a computer geek.
     

    
</post>
<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       End of the workday..closing in on 4pm  I've been sitting at my desk for the last three hours trying to stay busy with out much will to get up. Now I am finally to my daily duty of uploading the shipping files to their respected shippers like UPS and the post office.  At least now I have something to do every time I go to work. What will I do with the rest of my afternoon, like I said, mimi is off today so hopeful we can go have some fun.  Christmas has completely left us broke so it seems. I think I have gone a little overboard with the presents but I want mimi and everyone to have a good christmas, its my favorite holiday and damn if I don't see people smiling.    urlLink check out dallas hardcore music   
     

    
</post>
<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Another day...most of this morning I've been reading about how to build a log cabin.  I don't know why but maybe someday I can build my own cabin from the sweat of my brow.  I think I could seriously find that rewarding.  I'm at work, things are alot calmer today.  I'm going to lunch with a finance guy from emerson/ssg and robert is going to.  The guy is taking both of us to lunch for...i guess our help with his bank software.  MiMi is off today.  I hope she is enjoying it.
     

    
</post>
<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      But the bad part was that it wasn't really cold.  We all set forth on the camping trip hoping for a cold weather trip and it ended up being very pleasant.  The rain was not bad until late at night when the fog also set in.  Good thing we were staying in a palace of a tent.  Dad had bought a 10-man tent.  The thing was huge.  It didn't even fit on the pad.
     

    
</post>
<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The forest was dark at the early hour of 6p.m. but this is December.  There were probably a total of 3 occupied campsites in the entire park which made for a very people quiet place to be.  It was really just the nearby road and the forest sounds.  I get there with a headache, which I am totally upset about, but I try to drink away, while at the same time occupying my mind with the duty of Fire Chief, protector of the Flame.  Man was that Fire raging.  I absolutely love camp fires, everything about them, the smell of the smoke, the heat hitting your face while the cold wind slices up the back of your coat.  
     

    
</post>
<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This weekend was adventure number 2 to the Davy Crockett National Forest.  Another insteresting experience to the campgrounds of Ratcliff Lake. I really enjoy that area.  Scott, my mother's youngest brother, and my Dad were my partners in this quest into the woods in search of chilling air and campfires.  We made our way out from Ft.Worth where Scott and I met up with my Dad.  It took us a little longer than normal to get out to Ratcliff because we took I-45 a little longer down to Centerville and from there we crossed over.  The trip was interesting. It rained the entire time, from when we left to just about the time we entered the campsite.  Halfway to our destination the wipers go out on my Dad's Suburban.  That made it almost impossible to see, but we made it to the forest and got to our campsite without slamming into anything.  
     

    
</post>
<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      How shitty all this is!  I had two pretty interesting adventures and my site was down.  David at the hosting server moved some stuff and we all had to re-upload the pages.  Well this one was pretty customized so I had to move a few files.  Luckily I had the files here at work so I can go ahead and start putting it back together.  Looks good, or the same as before.
     

    
</post>
<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       so what it is what it isn't.  I have some super sinky ass farts going on tonight.  oh my.  mimi and i went to a thai resteraunt in dallas called the thai rose. it was really just alright. I had the Evil Jungle Price with tofu and some thai iced coffee and mimi had the asparagus and some sprite.  i enjoyed the time we had just hanging out. it was fun. we tired to go shopping for some family for christmas and saw these awesome new toys....remember the Rudolph the Red nose raindeer claymation cartoons that ALWAYS come on around christmas.  THEY MADE TOYS of ALL the characters and they are off the hook.  I want em all so bad.  That seriously gave me chills when I saw em.  It just rocks.  I mean....i love those shows and I watched em every year, that is a totally good memory of fun at christmas.  Man.....if you get a chance....buy me some....hehe...love john 
     

    
</post>
<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well from my point of view, things don't seem to go anywhere unless you move them.  Cars don't go unless you fill them with dino-blood and start them, lives dont live until you kick them in the ass.  So when is someone going to kick me in my ass.    Thing to start again by the end of the week.   · Lift weights (becuase I need to be mean)  · Study my cisco books regularly and get to the goal of a cert.  · Find a place for wuornos to practice  · Eat better for the fucking sake of staying alive.    I dunno why I just can't do these things.  Fuck it.  Tomorrow I am going to do what I want, not what my weak ass mind gets away with but what I want.   You can't have it all you say, well, I can if I make myself.  Its going to be hard.  But I guess instead of pussing out and getting fat and poor, I'll stop being a light weight and do it!   Updates coming soon!  Man, losing friends makes things go weird....I'm way to dependant on people....from now on its me and I don't care if you don't like me.  
     

    
</post>
<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Holy §moke!   I took a trip to the  urlLink library  yesterday afterwork to pick up some refrence material for the  urlLink DFWAC  meeting.  I had spent some time online researching different sites to find books that I thought might help us come up with some ideas and maybe show us new ways to organize the group to get stuff done. mimi was sick with the cold, so I left her at home, crying and sniffling on the couch.  The  urlLink library  is only a few blocks down the street, behind an Exxon and a dry-cleaners, so it was a short dash to my local branch.    The library was packed with people, but here, the books are the majority and most of the time I would rather take a book with me than a person.  People are to edgy sometimes, and they have problems that they always seem to bring to your front door.  I don't know why, but I'm always greeting strangers on the street with a 'Hello" and "Hey" followed by some sort of nod.  I found my self doing this as I was walking into the library and going, "wtf!" I don't know that person, why do I give a flying fuck enough to say "Hello."  Fuck that guy for making me feel weak and habitual, and now I am saying "Fuck your self for blaming your weak ass on some stranger!"    weird...I had a small fight inside my head..........am I crazy??  I'm crazy, fuck you!   I got my books, and went to check them out and they had some nice calendars sitting on the counter...FREE....wow these are nice.  I picked up two, one for my house and one for the office(a.k.a. the life I am to weak to abandon.)
     

    
</post>
<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I think I have a cold, and I don't like it very much...oh I wanna go back to bed.
     

    
</post>
<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Four A M Lanscape  Wind waves the reeds by the river, Grey sky lids the leaden water. Ducks fly low across the water Three flying: one quacks sadly.  Grey are the sky and the water, Green the lost ribbons of reed-beds, Small in the silence a black shadow Floats upon wide pale mirrors.   year-start: 2002   The first few hours of this year I spent with Nick, Kira, Brian(my brother) and his friend Bryan, and MiMi.  We talked the new year in with a failed attempt to celebrate simultaniously with the rest of the time zone.  Canadian wiskey and potatoe chips where the first food of what will be undoubtedly be the most unpredictable year of my life.  Towards the closing in of sleep i was in the middle of watching Planet of the Apes around 3am.  I started to feel a little sick, like alchohol sick.  I stayed awake for a while longer; trying to get through the movie with out having to lose my chips and "salsa". "Maybe I need to lay down," I told myself.  I went into the room and undressed and slothed my way under the blanket, this didn't help, just made me realize that I needed to take care of this.  I was sober, to a point, and hadn't had a drink for over an hour, why was this belated.  RRAAAAAALLLLPPPHHHHH!.  I feel better now, finished the movie and went to bed.   Its almost like stabing your hand, you know its gonna hurt, but the rush, some say, is worth it.  What a stupid way to start the year.   By the way, Nick and Kira saw the canal rat moster thing last night.  what is that thing! 
     

    
</post>
<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      http://www.museumofhoaxes.com/photos/photos.html some of this are interesting....
     

    
</post>
<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      i wonder if anyone is going to make fun of the image i have up on the main site!  hehe 
     

    
</post>
<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Lets see if they take this olive branch.........  </post></Blog>