<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>31,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
      I just read Elena's thing in my guestbook, again. Me and her have such good times together. She is the coolest girl I know. I really hope she comes to Sprague next year. I wish we could talk to each other more often. I miss her at Judson, even though we really didn't hang out until after I left that place. The fair was so awesome. So was the time we hung out all day, with yea the little ball of light. It was just one day, but I swear that made me feel like we've known each other for like ever. Good times with righty.  Happy new year everyone
     
    
</post>
<date>30,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
      So, I heard some things I guess Hilary said about me today. If they're true or not, we'll find out later. I'm leaning towards truth, because this is the second time I've heard the same things from someone else. I'm pretty well angry about it. It's stupid how she's still going on about all this shit on, "Oh our relationship was stupid" and "I never liked him to being with." Well good for you if that's how you feel. Thanks for lying to me over and over again. Thanks for lying to cover up more lies. Thanks for totally leading me on, and thanks for being a dishonest waste of time. I had feelings for you, real feelings for you. I guess you don't know what that means. I thought I was a nice guy, but that's only up to a point. Just because I'm nice, doesn't mean I'll take in everything forever with a smile. You crossed the line. No one has done that for a long time. I tried to be everything for you, but you didn't even give me a thanks. All you gave me was a slap in the face.  I hope you get my email, and I hope you can find someone good enough for you so you can be satisfied. After all, you deserve it.                    Chris
     
    
</post>
<date>29,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Today I hung out with Tiara and Brittany. It was Tiara's birthday.  Happy 14th birthday Tiara. We hung out and played in the snow and stuff. It was a great day. I had a lot of fun. One of those times where I actually brought out my inner kidness.  Whew, I miss them. It's gonna be icy tomorrow. I hope I can get in contact with Jordan and finally get my amp. I wanna write a song called, "Have you seen my Tiara?" inspired by her little sister's shirt. lol.
     
    
</post>
<date>28,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
      It's late. I get weird when it's late. Like my thought process and stuff. If someone like me was talking to me right now, I'd be freaked. I wrote some poetry tonight. They were a continuation of a couple thoughts I had the other night. They're about Hilary. I'm over her, but the feeling is still there, and I guess it makes for good, sincere, writing.  Oh yea, it's snowing. What a blast. It better continue during school. yaya
     
    
</post>
<date>28,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
      I finished reading Boy's Life this morning. I stayed up until 4:30 am reading it. It was a really good book.   Also, I made a really cool smore. I'll call it the urban smore I think. You melt the marshmallow in the microwave. Gotta be careful though, cuz it will blow up. Then you put chocolate syrup on the grahamcracker instead of chocolate. Yummy
     
    
</post>
<date>27,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Almost halfway through Christmas break I think. I know this half will go fast though. I haven't done anything this break. I haven't hung out with anybody. I want to do something, I'm bored. I got a bad headache right now and it's annoying. Staring at the computer probably doesn't help, but oh well. I don't very much to say right now. Everything is back to plain normal. School and homework.
     
    
</post>
<date>26,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
      I called Hilary today. I'm happy about that. At least I think we'll get to be pretty good friends. After she broke up with me, I think I took her all wrong. I think all my friends have her all wrong, too. She has good intent. I knew that, but was a little stupid anyway. Ah well, that's part of it; I guess.  Christmas is over. I like Christmas, but now I'm bored. I need someone to hang out with. I'll prolly call someone tomorrow. Maybe Elena could do something or maybe Alivia. I never hang out with Alivia that much though I talk to her all the time.  I figured out how to record songs to my computer like off instruments I play. That's pretty cool. I really want to learn how to write music. I think I have the creative lyrical mind, but maybe not the creative musical I want. Well it's not that, it's just that I don't know what I'm doing when it comes to composing music. I'll hit my teacher up about that. I really have a spark in me to become like some famous musician now. Dashboard Confessional all the way.
     
    
</post>
<date>24,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
      This is my poem for the new year, and also I think it's going to be the first one in my new notebook. : )  Another year comes to an end Just think of all the places we've been  Hearts mended and broken Friendships created and lost Lessons learned from your mistakes Reaping the benefits but forgetting the costs  Losing yourself in someone else The first time they walked through the door Wondering as it closed on their way out How could someone so beautiful make you so sore  Finding something new in yourself A strength or weakness you never knew Figuring out when it's time to let go Sometimes there's nothing you can do  Seeing the truth in others The first stain of ugly in your world New pathways come into view As more of the world unfurls  Getting up on your own Putting aside all doubts Locating the light in the darkness Using it to find your way out  Testing your faith And your faith in others Counting on true friends To provide you with cover  New challenges confront you With difficulty never before dealt Realizing the important things in life And the importance of life itself  Maybe it wasn't as expected But just look at where we are Now a beginning of a new day A breath of fresh air, a clean slate, a fresh start
     
    
</post>
<date>23,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
      I found Hilary's present on my doorstep today. She got me a notebook for my poetry. There was a few notes and pictures for me to have. I really want to talk to her about all of this. For whatever reason, I just need to talk to her. I'm going to call her the day after Christmas, even though I'd call her right now if it wasn't christmas eve. There's so much to be sorted out still, but I feel better. Thanks Hilary, for the notebook, the notes, the pictures, and everything you are, you've done, and we've done together.
     
    
</post>
<date>23,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Merry Christmas Eve!! I'm thinking back to what I would be doing this day last year. I think today I would just now finish writing the last page of Brittany's poem and stick in that portfolio and wrap it.   Today is a good day. My second favorite holiday is Christmas next to Valentine's day. As things are going, Valentine's day will be the same lonely day as it's always been, but it's good to see the couples, unless they're breaking up on this day which is the worst thing but it happens a lot I guess. Who knows, maybe I'll have a girlfriend by then. It sure would be nice. I don't think I'm going to chase anybody down though. I know that Erin knows I like her now, and that's always a good thing.  Beats me if she likes me. Not a big deal. She's cool to hang out with, and I like to be around her. She looks really good in her glasses. I say that a lot about her, but seriously! That reminds me, I still need a pair.
     
    
</post>
<date>23,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
      I walked to Audra's today to give her her Christmas present. I probably could have waited for a ride instead of walking out in the cold, but walking is better sometimes.   I'm glad things going on in Elena's life are better. She never deserves to have anything bad happen to her. She is the one of the nicest, funniest, and coolest people I have ever met. I'm so glad me and her are friends. I'd trade any Christmas present to hang out with Elane for a day cause I know we'd have a great time as always.  I've been reading  Boy's Life  lately. Hilary let me borrow a while back. It's her favorite book, and yea it is a really good book. I promised her I'd get it read by the end of the break. I'm going to go. I still hope she's actually making me something for Christmas like she said. I won't be hurt if she doesn't, but if she said she was going to then she should. I'm not going to call her or anything this break. Unless she drops by my house to give me her Christmas present then I won't talk to her until we get back to school.  I went out yesterday and bought the "Maxeen" debut album. Hilary told me she saw them on the Warped Tour so I downloaded some of their stuff. They sounded alright. It's always nice to have a good band that no one knows about, just as long as you don't get mad when people start to learn about them.   I'm not sure if I want to go to the recording studio during the break or not. I don't think I'm ready. I have a few more songs I'd like to get ready so I can record them to. I have Terra on piano I want to record and along with a couple guitar songs I wrote. I wish I was better singer, but I'm not so I'll make do.  I told like everybody who I like now. I'm not like one of those people that are like "Omg if they find out things will be ruined between us." I just think maybe things should have some time before you just go out and tell them you have a crush on them. She'll find out anyway, cause I know her friends will tell her. So Erin, if you're reading this...
     
    
</post>
<date>22,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
      My last past in the voice of a twelve year old kid on AIM:   FIRST DAY OF VACATION YEHAW1!!1! OMG WTF I GAEV 3RIN HAR PRESENT Y3ST3RDAY11!! SHE GOT ME THIS COL HANDS DOWN VINYL!1!1 OMG I THINK TAHT WAS RILLY AEWSOM311111!1 WTF SHAS OF 2 CALIFORNIA ALR3ADY IMM GONA MIS HAR1!!!!1!!   I GOTA GIEV AUDRA H3R PR3SENT 2DAY 2111! IL PROLY WOK OV3R THEIR AND GIEV IT 2 HAR SENG AS I DONT HAEV ANYTHNG ELSE 2 DO AS FAR AS I KNOW!1!1!111 WTF I STIL HOP3 HILARY WIL GET DONE WUT SHES MAKNG M3!1!!11 IMM KIND OF ANXIOUS 2 SE WUT IT IS!!!!!! OMG WTF LOL I WONDAR WUT SHAS UP 2 LAETLY11!1!1! I WAS GONA CAL HAR OVER DA BRAAK SOMETIEM BUT I DONT KNOW IF I WIL!!!1!!1! OMG I STIL HAD A PROMIES TAHT I D FINISH H3R BOK BFORE TEH BREAK WAS UP1!!1!1 WTF LOL IMM GONG 2!!!1 OMG WTF LOL ITS A GOD BOK  WEL11111 LOL I THINK IMM BGINNG 2 LIEK SOMEONA 3LSA11111 OMG TAHTS A GOD THNG I THINK11!!1!1! WTF LOL IT HAPENED FASTAR THAN I THOUGHT IT WUD BUT IT MAEKS SENSE FOR A R3ASON TAHT I CANT TEL U B/C IT WUD GIEV IT AWAY1!11!1!1 OMG I DONT WANT 2 SAY ANYTHNG ABOUT HER JUST YET111!11 OMG IMM ABSOLUTALY POSITIEV TAHT SH3 WONT HURT ME IN A WAY TAHT HILARY DID BY LEADNG ME ON OR WUT!1!1 LOL TAHT IS IF SH3 AVAR FELS TEH SME ANYWAY!1!!111 OMG LOL M3RY CHRISTMAS  CHRIS11!!11! OMG WTF
     
    
</post>
<date>20,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
      First day of vacation, yeehaw. I gave Erin her present yesterday. She got me this cool Hands Down vinyl. I think that was really awesome. She's off to California already; I'm gonna miss her.   I gotta give Audra her present today, too. I'll prolly walk over there and give it to her seeing as I don't have anything else to do as far as i know. I still hope Hilary will get done whatever she's making me. I'm kind of anxious to see what it is. I wonder what she's up to lately. I was gonna call her over the break sometime, but I don't know if I will. I still had a promise that I 'd finish her book before the break was up. I'm going to. It's a good book.  Well, I think I'm beginning to like someone else. That's a good thing; I think. It happened faster than I thought it would, but it makes sense for a reason that I can't tell you because it would give it away. I don't want to say anything about her just yet. I'm absolutely positive that she won't hurt me in a way that Hilary did by leading me on or whatever. That is if she ever feels the same anyway. Merry Christmas.  Chris
     
    
</post>
<date>20,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Alright, today was one of those days. It was one of the days where you just finally come to conclusion about things. Yeah, I am too sensitive; it's true. Not like you didn't know that already, but I am. Not to blame that anybody but myself, I think it's because my dad. For as long as I've been able to see that my dad isn't the nicest guy, I've always said to myself that I wouldn't be like him. Well sometimes I am like him and I get short fused, but I think because I try so much to not be the angry guy he is, I turn into a over sensitive, maudlin freak. It hit me today that I need to seriously stop being so serious. I'm always going on about how I want to live up these 4 years of high school and getting crushed by at fourteen by a fourteen year old girl isn't how to do it. She can do whatever she wants.   Don't get me wrong about my dad. As much as I hate him sometimes for being such an asshole, I know he has it rough. This life is definitely not how he wanted things to work out. No one plans on struggling through the end of every month, and not being able to afford the finer things in life. It makes me sad sometimes when he talks to my brothers and I about how important it is to do good in school so we don't end up like him. He's so insensitive a lot of the time, and it's just really crazy when he starts to talk about his feelings about his life. I wish I could make him happy. Someday I just want to be rich so I can buy him all those things he wanted, and so he didn't have to work like hell just to pay the bills. I feel sorry for him. I feel like things should have been better for him. Just everything he's been through and is going through is what makes him such a bitter person. I know I get frustrated and angry with him all the time, but I need to remember that he doesn't want to be that way; that's just how he is. I love my dad.  If you're actually this, thanks. I love you. If you actually took the time to read and want to know how I feel that means a lot to me really. I don't know, just thought I needed to say that to you. Have a merry Christmas, or Hannukah, or Kwanza, or Birthday, Thanksgiving whatever.  Christo
     
    
</post>
<date>19,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Talked to Audra again today, about Hilary or whatever. It's kinda making me mad actually. I don't do that a lot. She wanted to break up with, and she did. So she just needs to move on cuz she did what she wanted to. She keeps talking about all these things that she doesn't like about me or whatever like she's trying to reassure herself or whatever, I don't know, but it bugs me. I still like her I, but I'm not coming back to her and I don't expect her to come back to me. If she wants to talk about all the things she doesn't like about me she should tell it to me so I can at least stick up for myself.  Chris
     
    
</post>
<date>18,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
      this is supposed to be at the beginning of the last post. I didn't get put in for whatever reason:  I found her. I gave her her shoes. I had a poem on a heart to go along with it. I took it off before I gave it to her. I had a note to give her though. She said whatever she was making me was really cool, but she said that I probably wouldn't like it because I hate her. That confused me a little bit. I wanted to tell her that I didn't hate her, and that if anything I still was in love with her. Instead, I just said merry Christmas and walked away. 
     
    
</post>
<date>18,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
      She makes me sad still. I know I'm over her. I know things are through, but I still can't help but wish we were still together sometimes. I got a SnoBall picture of me and her today. It's a good picture. She was smiling. Whether it was a real smile or a fake one, I found her. I gave her her shoes. I had a poem on a heart to go along with it. I took it off before I gave it to her. I had a note to give her though. She said whatever she was making me was really cool, but she said that I probably wouldn't like it because I hate her. That confused me a little bit. I wanted to tell her that I didn't hate her, and that if anything I still was in love with her. Instead, I just said merry Christmas and walked away. we looked good as a couple that night.  At least the guy I think she's after is a nice guy. She told me she couldn't do relationships, and that she'd be like single forever. Well, she's already looking at someone else. I don't know if they'll get together, but things like that seem inevitable sometimes.   That's how things go right? I don't know why I still keep going on about Hilary. Man....make it stop, lol. I need some good friends.  It's Christmas break finally, yay. I guess I'm going to the recording studio sometime after Christmas to record some piano, and I'm wondering if I should record some guitar too. That should be fun.
     
    
</post>
<date>18,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
      I said Hi to Hilary today. She said hey. I guess that's somewhat of a good thing. I asked her if she wanted me to meet her at lunch so we could still exchange gifts. She said that whatever she's making me she's not done making yet. I'm still going to give her the shoes tomorrow. I don't know if she's telling the truth about not having them done and dropping them off at my house. For whatever reason, I'm having my doubts about believing anything she says. It could be that she won't get me anything, but I really don't think she would lie like that. I'm just not sure what to trust about her now. I'm pretty sure she was telling the truth though; so that's good.  Chris
     
    
</post>
<date>17,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
      I had a weird dream about her last night. Come to think of it, I've had dreams about her for the past few nights, err. Well last night, she was like all over this one guy that I think she has a thing for (nameless). We were in a classroom, and we met eye to eye. I said hello, but she didn't say anything (kinda like what really happened yesterday). The dream the other was that, she was in my house or whatever just doing regular things. I was following her trying to get her to notice me, but she didn't. I reached out and tried to touch her, but my hand just fell right through.
     
    
</post>
<date>17,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Yes, there'll be others.
     
    
</post>
<date>16,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
      I didn't get to talk to Hilary again today. At least I wanted to say hi, just to show her I'm not mad or anything like that. I'll talk to her tomorrow for sure, well pretty sure. Hmph, I don't know what I feel about her. On one hand I tell myself that she lied and I don't need her. The other says that I still get I guess a little jealous that she doesn't hang out with me anymore. I shouldn't be jealous or whatever. I just miss having her around. Time will tell where this goes.  Chris
     
    
</post>
<date>16,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
      I didn't talk to Hilary today. I waved, but she didn't wave back. She looked so cute today with her glasses on, but she's not mine anymore and that's okay. She was cool. Her and I will get to talking again sometime.  I feel bad for missing Elena's concert tonight. I told her I would go a few weeks ago, but I forgot. It's happening right now. If I could drive would totally make an entrance through the double doors, but I don't so here I am. I'm sorry Elena.  Chris
     
    
</post>
<date>15,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
      If you still feel the same way Why are you quitting on us now Put the past behind us We can still make it through somehow   Empty       Broken
     
    
</post>
<date>15,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
      I saw Hilary today. We just walked right past each other. I'm still in a good mood despite the fact that it still does bother me some. I have history with her tomorrow. There's a few questions I want to ask her about the time she burnt the picture of me and her because "it was a bad picture" and all those times she said, "I didn't see you!" But still, heart break is worth the risk.   Christo
     
    
</post>
<date>14,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
      I went to church today for the first time in a long time. It's part of a deal with my mom since she bought me the guitar I wanted. It's not so bad if you don't pay attention. The only hard part is finding a way to occupy yourself for and hour and a half. I still am not totally positive that God exists. All the theories and philosophies have their "gaps."   I'm feeling a little better again about Hilary. I was off and on yesterday. Who knows what I'm going to do at lunch now. I realized that I really don't have a whole lot of close friends anymore. It's hard to find someone to talk to about things. Ironically, it's times like these where I wish I had a girlfriend. I'll find someone to hang out with.
     
    
</post>
<date>13,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
      I wanted to see the parade tonight, but I didn't get a ride. I really needed to get out and do something otherwise I would start thinking about Hilary again. That's exactly what I ended up doing. I cried a little; I tried not to. Oh well, all I need is time. I feel fine, but I can't help it if it hurts.
     
    
</post>
<date>12,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
      I felt better last night. I talked with some friends. It was suprising to me how I didn't take it so hard. I didn't cry after I got off the phone with her, and I didn't cry when I went to bed. I feel good right now, for the reason I don't know. It's sad of course that it's over, but I feel fine. Audra said that I can be "clingy" to people I like, and I totally understood that. If I saw myself through someone elses shoes, I know how someone could get that feeling about it. I don't think it's so much that I cling to someone I like, I think it's that my emotions are pretty strong for some people like that. Hilary's gone now and I'm not begging her to take me back. I think that would be clingy. Maybe I just need to stop showing my emotions so much and just live it out. That would be better for everyone.
     
    
</post>
<date>12,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
      I called her. We broke up. She still likes me, though. I hope she does anyway. She said so. It could be one of those things where you have to tell someone you like them one more time to finally get over them. She said  she "drug this out too long." That kinda hurt when she said that. We weren't acting much along the lines of boyfriend-girlfriend anyway so our relationship remains the same for the most part. Well this is a bummer. I don't know what else to say. She is the greatest. We're still friends, that's always good. She said she just couldn't do relationships....I get that a lot. Maybe it's an overused excuse that doesn't really have any true meaning to it. There won't be any relationships in the near future. I'm done for now. Hilary was worth everything that I did for her. Nobody else is going to be able to make me want to work, think, and try so hard for them. She wrote me a note though for monday about this before I called her. She won't give it to me now since we already broke up;that's what the note was about.. I told her if she would just do one thing for me that I wanted her to give me the note still. She said no. Still as stubborn as ever, lol. I love her soooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo ever much. Maybe one day we'll get together again, because that would be nice.  Just Chris
     
    
</post>
<date>11,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
      It's the weekend now. Hilary wasn't at school today, so I still don't know how things are going. I might have to wait until monday before I talk to her again. I wish she would call me and tell me what's going on. It could very well be she's just been in a mad mood this week.   I'm thinking about calling her right now, but I'm not quite sure if I should. One part of me says that, she hasn't called because she needs some time. The other part says that if she had good news to tell me she would have told me already. I don't know what I'm going to do yet. I don't like to worry and wonder at the same time. All I've been lately is mopey. She's the most wonderful girl I've ever met. I just wish I knew how she felt.  Hilary's Guy
     
    
</post>
<date>11,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
      It's friday, finally. The week has gone by kind of slow. When I get to school today I'll find out what Hilary's feeling. Wow, hope for the best.   Hilary's Guy...  
     
    
</post>
<date>11,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
      You and me  We used to be together  Everyday together always  I really feel  That I'm losing my best friend  I can't believe This could be the end  It looks as though you're letting go  And if it's real  Well I don't want to know   Don't speak  I know just what you're saying So please stop explaining  Don't tell me cause it hurts  Don't speak  I know what you're thinking  I don't need your reasons  Don't tell me cause it hurts  Our memories  Well, they can be inviting  But some are altogether  Mighty frightening  As we die, both you and I  With my head in my hands  I sit and cry   Don't speak  I know just what you're saying  So please stop explaining Don't tell me cause it hurts  Don't speak  I know what you're thinking  I don't need your reasons  Don't tell me cause it hurts   It's all ending  I gotta stop pretending who we are...  You and me I can see us dying...are we?   Don't speak  I know just what you're saying  So please stop explaining Don't tell me cause it hurts Don't speak  I know what you're thinking  I don't need your reasons  Don't tell me cause it hurts  Don't tell me cause it hurts!  I know what you're saying  So please stop explaining 
     
    
</post>
<date>11,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
      I got a new one of these now. I don't know what happened to the old one. Well, here it is, tada!  Today was kind of rough. I don't really understand Hilary lots of the time, and it worries me. From all the experience that I've had, it would seem as though she didn't want to be with me anymore. She's different from anyone else I know though. I sat with her today at lunch, like always. She didn't say much, like always. She looked sad or bothered or something, like always. I wrote her a note last night. It was about everything that we've done together and how weird things are right now. I wasn't so sure if I should give it to her, but I did. I haven't talked to her since. I told her I was going to put my books away, and I asked her if she wanted to come with, but I knew she didn't. I came back hoping maybe she'd still be there by any sort of miracle. She wasn't. I figured if this was the last time we might be together that I want to find her and walk her to her class. She looked rather occupied when I found her, and I just walked away. I don't know about all of this. She could just be in one of her bad moods. She is a strange girl, but I love her with all my heart.                                                                        Hilary's Guy 
     
    
</post>
<date>31,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Today was cool. I went over to my Grandma's and I got her old polaroid camera and my uncle's old turntable. My other uncle is a repair guy and he said he'd fix the turntable for me, and I think all the camera needs is some film. I listened to my dad's old Jimi Hendrix LP's! That was pretty spiffy. I listened to them on my grandma's old turntable deal thing. It's like this huge like thing that sits on the floor. I used to think it was just a counter or something, but you lift the top and it has a radio, 8-track player, and a turntable. I was like whoa! Then I had spaghetti with my grandma. It was good. Oh then we stopped by my aunt Lauries and got some cookies, haha. My grandma rocks. 
     
    
</post>
<date>30,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      So this love won't let me go again. It's strange how it manages to leave me and hold on to me at the same time.
     
    
</post>
<date>29,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Yup yup, three day superbowl weekend! End of the semester too!? That's just too much. I'm gonna go watch the neighbor kids tomorrow for a few hours and earn some cash...I'm not a babysitter. I just look after the neighbor kids alright? so don't call me and be all "hey chris...I heard you babysit [hehehe]"lol  Life is good huh?
     
    
</post>
<date>28,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Phew, the hard finals are over. They weren't even that hard come to think of it. I better stop talking about it; I'll jynx it. I saw Hilary today...why do I always talk about her even if I just see her once? She had a cool dress/skirt deal on, I can't remember. Seriously, she has like the coolest sense of style I have ever seen.  I've been writing a lot lately, like all the time. Not really anything completed though. I've been writing down little lines and phrases that come to mind.   I hope I do something cool this weekend. It's the end of the semester. A brand new start. I want to hear someone play some music. I've never been to a concert before. I want to go to a show or a gig or something.     Elena has a boyfriend! I'm happy for you.
     
    
</post>
<date>27,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Geesh, where did everyone go all of a sudden? Everyone that used to say hi to me doesn't anymore. Then when I say hi to them, they just don't really pay attention. Ironically the last time I had a real good conversation was on the phone with Hilary on Saturday. I still don't think I should call her that often, just because I think she would get annoyed of me. Everyone I try and talk to someone though... they just doesn't seem interested. I am at a loss.
     
    
</post>
<date>26,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Yesterday went pretty well. I went downtown with my mother because I wanted to get one of those old/golfer hats, and I found one, but I ended up changing my mind. I got a tee shirt though, so that's cool. On the way back, I stopped at Erin's to give her present/mission/scheme. She got this cool acoustic guitar! It's exactly the one I saw in a magazine the day before and was like, "That's the one I want!" She said she felt guilty for having and doesn't know if she wants to keep it, because her parents said they wouldn't get it cause of their budget. I thought it was pretty nice of her that she'd be considerate of her parents like that. Happy birthday Erin!  I went to sleep happy last night. I'm so excited about writing music now. I know that this is something I want to do. I know it's going to take me places I've never been, and that makes me so happy. wow. I really want to do this. I think I might be getting an acoustic guitar for my birthday too. My style fits more of an acoustic tone so it should make things a lot better.  Finals week this week. Hopefully I can stop at Judson this week since we get out earlier than they do. I'll bet the people are still uptight and won't let me in. 
     
    
</post>
<date>24,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I was feeling tired so I thought I'd take a walk and get something to drink. I went to the "Sun Market" and picked me up a Rockstar. While I was out there, I thought I'd just go ahead and go all the way to Walmart. I picked up "The Swiss Army Romance" woohoo! They had an PO box to write to, so I wrote them a letter. I won't get to mail it to them until monday though, but I hope they write back. That would be so cool.  I called Hilary after I got home from Walmart. I was nervous, but she was actually happy to hear from me. :) I feel so much better now. We talked for a couple hours or so, I mean we talked! haha, we haven't  really  talked since November. I think me and her will get to be good friends. I know it this time. That is such a nice thing to know. That makes me so so glad. :D whew. All is okay again.  Tomorrow is Erin's birthday! I gotta stop by her house sometime. I don't know when. I'll ring her up tomorrow or something.   ahh man, I still haven't started studying for finals yet....I still need to clean my room.   I'm just jabbering on this whole entry, but I guess the real jist is that I'm incredibly relieved that Hilary isn't mad at me, and that I think we're going to be friends after all.
     
    
</post>
<date>23,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I've decided to name myself Tuxedo. I mean if I ever get band, that's what it'll be called, but for right now, Tuxedo is me and a guitar. If I wasn't so bad at singing, I'd say that Tuxedo is alright, lol.  Here I am; it's Saturday afternoon, and I'm home. I was supposed to go out at get my hat and look at glasses, but my mom didn't keep her word like usual. She said we might do it tomorrow, but dag nabbit I have stuff to do tomorrow.
     
    
</post>
<date>23,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I saw Hilary today. I was walking to health. I went down the stairs and around the corner; she was right there. I know it's not a big deal, but I don't know, something about her just...it was weird. She saw me; I think she smiled, but I don't know. Do you ever have the feeling where you heart just stops? Well I got that feeling, and I guess still miss her. Whether I like her or not still, I'm not sure. I just miss her. I think just talking to her is all I need. I saw her again at lunch. She didn't look at me this time. I know it's not that she didn't see me, because I could tell she was looking away on purpose. I don't know how she feels. I guess I'll find out tomorrow.
     
    
</post>
<date>22,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Alright, I'm gonna try to not be so stressed today. There.  Anyway,  On Saturday, I think I want to find one of those old fashioned hats. The ones that have a short bill and the top kinda folds over all "newsie" like. I wanna get one that matches with my suit, so I'll have the whole "newsie" look. Anyway, I saw some at Nordstrom's, but I think I'll try Goodwill and Value Village first. Somehow I think they could probably beat the price of a Nordstrom's hat...  Also, I'm probably going to call Hilary on Saturday just to see how she's been doing. We actually looked at each other yesterday! Wow! Amazing!!!! lol, actually it kinda is...geeze, I really do miss her smile. Well not just her smile, I mean the way she used to look at me when she smiled. Now I'm all reminiscing and I'm sad. I'll just call her. I just want to get us back to talking again. I shouldn't lose her completely you know.
     
    
</post>
<date>22,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Dang it. I've been really stressed lately. I have bad luck or something. I just spilt some nice red cranberry juice all over the computer desk and carpet. My dad will really love that.   I think I already blew my new years resolutions. This sucks. I wish it was summer. sigh. give me something to hold on to.
     
    
</post>
<date>21,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I went to sleep at 1 last night. Pretty crazy that I'm not tired this morning. I'm sure when I get to school the tiredness will hit me flat on my back. It was my Grandma's birthday yesterday. Both of my grandparents don't look very old, so that's cool. I hope I'm not a crippled old man when I get old.  It's Thursday already. That means tomorrow is Friday, yay! I really want to get final's over with. I don't think they'll be too hard. I just want them over with so I can forget everything I've learned this semester. I think things will get easier next semester, plus we get to start all over. I guess biology is going to be easy second term which is good cause it's my hardest class right now. I'm still planning on switching out mech tech II for drama. I'll take mech tech II next year. I kinda miss acting.  I haven't played guitar like at all this week, because my room is too messy to even take out my guitar, lol. There's things all over the ground from the "scheme," but I can clean them up since I'm done. Phew, finally. The scheme is good I think. I did a lot of craftier stuff I've never done before. I hate trial and error.  Well, off to another A day. A days are the best.
     
    
</post>
<date>21,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Wow! I'm so happy right now you don't even know. I finally finished the one things....haha, my little brother said he saw Erin at like Roth's or something. Good thing I got dropped off before that or I would have been screwed!lol.  Boy, finals are coming up. They shouldn't be too bad. It's actually alright since I don't have homework anymore, just studying.   So mr.ice cream and mrs.cake has a computer. It has everything. That place is so cool. You can even "write on the walls."
     
    
</post>
<date>20,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Alright, it's another school day, and here I am getting ready for school. I can't wait until after school today. I might be able to totally accomplish the rest of the "scheme."  I have to go to Walmart today, but I don't have a bike. So the next door neighbor kid is really cool, and imma ask him if I can borrow it for an hour or so. Man I can't wait. Walmart is the coolest. I hope something bad doesn't happen on the way there. I kinda have a weird feeling about today. Last time I had a weird feeling, some kid tried to pick a fight with me on the corner. He chickened out when I started to get irritated, but he wasn't worth fighting anyway. Some guts that little kid had, lol.  Anyway...S_C_H_O_O_L____N_E_I_G_H_B_O_R____W_A_L_M_A_R_T
     
    
</post>
<date>20,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      The mission/scheme is completed!...for the most part anyway. There's still a few more little "objectives" to accomplish. But nothing can go wrong now! yay!  I totally messed something up today, though. I was like, "Okay Chris, make sure you don't screw this part up," and then an hour later I looked back at it, and sure enough! I screwed that dang part up. Geezus. Oh well.  I hung out with my grandma today. She took me out to the boonies in West Salem to check out her grandpa's farm. She finally found the way, but by the time it was too late to go check it out. Sorry Grandma, another time though.  I got a bunch of homework to do tonight. Better start crackin.
     
    
</post>
<date>18,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      So yesterday was a great day. Elena and I did our little "scheme" downtown. That was a blast. Except after I got the results, "my" part of the scheme was messed up. So i have to find the way make up "my" part of the "scheme." I always have the best time hanging out with her. She's the greatest.  After I got home I went to my piano lesson, and I played a few songs on the guitar that I've been writing. I think that they songs are okay, but I really need to learn to sing louder/speak up. I hate being so quiet. I think it's something that could hold me back. Oh well, I'm off to school.
     
    
</post>
<date>18,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Erin and I don't really talk anymore. Dah, that bugs me. Whenever she's online we hardly IM each other, and when we do we don't say much except for, "Hey, what's up." I don't know what happened, just one of those things I guess. I wonder why that happens anyway. Where you and someone just all of a sudden stop talking. It's weird. :(  Hello Erin, I miss you.  I'm going to call Hilary sometime. We shouldn't not talk. She's still cool in my book. I'm probably not even in hers anymore, haha. I want to catch up with her anyway. 
     
    
</post>
<date>17,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Today is going to be stay home day. That's alright though. I have a lot of things I need to take care of. I'm in the middle of cleaning my room, and then I think I'm going to finish making all those things for Erin.  I wrote some lyrics yesterday. It's hard to find a good guitar part for it though. I can't seem to find the sound I'm looking for. I guess I need to practice more. I put new strings on my guitar yesterday. All six strings once again, yay.  Hanging out with Elena tomorrow! Woohoo!
     
    
</post>
<date>17,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Well I have 14 more to go. I know what I want to do for four of them I think. So that leaves 10. I hope Elena and I can get together this weekend so she can help out with the whole scheme. I'm bored already on my Saturday morning. How bad is that?
     
    
</post>
<date>15,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      It's sad how relationships work a lot of the time. If you could only rewind every day of one and watch it over again, you would see a lot of things you missed the first time. Things like the first sign of one liking another, but also the first sign of one falling away. You'd hear things like, "I love you forever!" and "I'll never leave you!" How many times is that really true? It must hurt to be the person that was told to and then to see the same person say it to someone else.   Love would be a sad movie. It would be depressing to watch how something so great could turn into nothing at all. Sometimes that process is slow and painful, sometimes short and unexpected. It would be sad to see both sides of the story. To see one person move on, but see the other still not having a day without thinking about them.   If I saw love, I would have to turn it off before the ending. If I watched the end, I would weep inside only to find that there was an ending to my love too.
     
    
</post>
<date>13,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I walked to Walmart today to get stuff to finish making Erin's present. I have everything I need; I just need to do it. Elena might help me. I hope she does; It will be some much funner that way. Not mention easier and less awkward as well. Shhhh keep it under wraps k?
     
    
</post>
<date>13,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      My dad totaled his car yesterday. He always said he wanted a car like he that one, and now it's worthless sitting in our driveway as he hit ice on the way to the job he doesn't like. It's not fair, but nothing is. I was going to sleep last night, and I heard him peek through the curtains just as he had when he first bought the car. Instead this time, he wasn't looking to see if he had really gotten the car he drooled over so much, he looked to see if the car he had always wanted had actually gotten wrecked.  I haven't heard from Hilary in weeks. I'm over her, but I guess I couldn't say that I don't still have some kind of feeling for her. I miss her. Her picture is still in my wallet, and I looked at it the other night. I felt a lump in my throat so I put it back. Everytime my computer says "you have mail," I'm a little jumpy to see if it's Hilary or not. Everytime I check it though, it's someone else. There's not going to be another Hilary, and the only Hilary there's ever going to be won't even meet my eyes anymore.  I don't care if she's mad at me or hates my guts. I just want her to say something. 
     
    
</post>
<date>11,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I've discovered a new way to express emotion, music. Well, maybe it's not new, but it is for me. It's like poetry and a melody, good stuff. After wrting Elena a song, it made me feel better than writing a poem could ever have. I think songs can hold more feeling than poetry, because the lyrics can also be poetic. So yea, I wanna start writing more music.
     
    
</post>
<date>10,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I was up for like five hours last night writing Elena a song to make her feel better. I called her today and played it for her. I've never sang for anyone before, and I'm really bad. I was all nervous and my voice was all shaky, lol. I hope it made her feel better though. : )
     
    
</post>
<date>09,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      It's one thing to be hurt yourself. When you see someone you absolutely love hurting, it hurts more than a pain that's your own could ever hurt.  A pain you have is one you can deal with, one you can surpress, one you can get out, one you can rationalize, one you can fix. To see your only best friend hurting, can rip you out because no matter if you'd die trying to make them feel better, you just can't. There's nothing you can say or do. You can't get them to think it out like however you think you may have.  You can't, you can't. All you can do is wait hoping that the pain you feel is somehow taking away from the bleeding feelings in them.  The worst feeling of hopeless, the worst feeling of helpless, the worst hurt you could ever have is hurting for someone else.   I love you Elena Grace Crowson, always, always, always. If you want to wipe your tears off on my shirt or scream at me until my ears bleed, I'm here for you, always, always...always.
     
    
</post>
<date>08,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I think that's like the first time I've ever not wanted to like anyone. You can't really help liking somebody if you do, but I don't know what I'll do. Just drop it I suppose.
     
    
</post>
<date>08,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      hmph. I don't think I like (don't want to like) anyone anymore. I think my liking Erin just kinda flopped our whole relationship. We don't really talk that much anymore.  That sucks when that happens. So I'll just give that whole thing up.  Here I go again own my own.
     
    
</post>
<date>08,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      It's been awhile since I've done one of these     Time now: 9:10 pm 1.Full Name: Christopher Andrew DuBois 2.Birthday: March 10 3.Sign: Pisces 4.Parents Names: Paul and Sonia 5.Any Siblings: 2 brothers 6.If so,their name(s)and age(s): PJ, 16, Ryan, 10 7.Any pets: Two Labs, a chocolate one and a black one 8.If so,their names: Hershey  Feisty 9.Your Eye color: Brown brown brown 10.Your Hair color: Black black black 11.Height: Taller than Elena and taller than Julia. Shorter than a basketball hoop  &gt; 13.Color: Orange, Dark Red, Blue 14.Food: Foreign 15.Drink: Strawberry Milk 16.Movie: Radio 17.Show: Friday Night Stand-Up 18:Radio Station: 97.9, 105.1 19.Music artist/group  Actor/actress: Dashboard Confessional...Actor: Matt Seely 20.Place to relax: Sunset 21.Place to hang out: Somewhere with friends 22.Store: Big Lots 23.Book: Boy's Life 25.Candy: Star Bursts 26.Chocolate: milk chocolate. 27.Animal: Toucan Sam 28.Holiday: valentine's day 29.Day of the week: Thursday, so Thursday 30.Season: winter.  &gt; 31.Is(Are)you best friend(s): Elena Steven Brittany Audra Corey. I'm still low on close friends 32.Is(Are)your worst enemy(s): Myself 33.Have you know the longest(that your friends with now): Corey 34.Makes you laugh the hardest: Elena hands down 35.Makes you weak at the knees: You're smile and those eyes. Long gone, but I still know them. 36.Do you have the most inside jokes with: Cori. I don't do inside jokes. 37.Do you have the funniest inside joke with: Cori 38.Do you have the most recent inside joke with: Cori 39.Can you rely on no matter what: I find myself alone a lot 40.Is your crush: Honey Bucket 41.Is your boy/girl friend: I lost her 42.Do you"love": My love is empty. Fill er up 43.Do you "luv"(friend way): Everyone 44.Can you trust with all your secrets: Elano 45.Can't you trust at all: psssh, what if they read this drrr </post></Blog>