<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Here's to the nights we felt alive, Here's to the tears you knew you'd cry, Here's to goodbye, Tomorrow's gonna come too soon. -Eve 6, "Here's To The Night"    #50 - Everything fun that I forgot on here... Sorry guys, I'll write everything down this year!    #49 - The Shining... The Ring... Silence of the Lambs.   #48 - Everything that comes outta Tiana's mouth.   #47 - Britnii London dressed as a cow.   #46 - When Alec did "The Fag Jump."    #45 - Tessa's "family reunion".    #44 - Everything involved with sexual education.   #43 - The drive over to Valley Fair.  #42 - Tina's lipgloss.   #41 - Watchin' SNL with Nathalie.    #40 - The Kiss    #39 - After the Fireworks!!   #38 - Hittin' Elena with a phone book.. (I'm still sorrie for that!!)   #37 - Modelling with Joce in Abercrombie.   #36 - Patrick's "Snot".   #35 - Michele and Santa Claus.    #34 - Halloween Costumes.   #33 - Stephen's "coming out".   #32 - When Nathalie got hit on during the DC Trip!   #31 - Loren and the Laxatives.    #30 - Mesha and her monkey!    #29 - The Corn Maze.   #28 - "Ice The Irish!"   #27 - Mrs. Locke and the Locker Room!   #26 - Elizabeth's "Knock-out"    #25 - Playin' piano with the Annie.   #24 - MONEY!  #23 - My first purchase from Abercrombie.  #22 - My "Christmas" Presents  #21 - Hawaii~   #20 - Telling Nelli anything and everything.   #19 - Scoring 100% on that Standford Test!  #18 - Tina givin' Amy a piggy-bag ride.  #17 - The "Sugary" Name Tag  #16 - Every one of Suzie's Parties!   #15 - Buffy and Angel   #14 - Late Night Phone Calls  #13 - The Night at the Cabin!!  #12 - Meeting Bryan~  #11 - The Twelve Boys.   #10 - Jaye's voice. (Only Chris gets it)   # 9 - NATHALIE AND TINA!!  # 8 - Romeo and Juliet  # 7 - The Humanaties Academy  # 6 - After Christmas Sales   # 5 - The songs I sang.  # 4 - Friendships  # 3 - AIM.  # 2 - Soquel  # 1 - Coming out. 
     

    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If you believe, That we've got a picture perfect plan, We've got you fooled, 'Cause we only do the best we can. And sometimes we make it. Sometimes we back it. But we get one step closer each and everyday, And we'll figure it out on the way. -Lizzie Maguire, "The Lizze Maguire Theme"   the first day back from break was amazing. it made me realize how much fun school had become. we worked more on our research reports and fam. tree projects, and english was fully devoted to romeo and juliet.  on monday we got a pysco bomb threat and they came in to shonicks class (A3) and they were like "kitty" or thats what chris remembers hearing. and then on tuesday (the day of the first fight of the week) we found out there was a bomb threat. bleh. it was some shitty teens who were trying to rob a bank and like i dunno.. it was in the paper.. i guess i shoulda read it..  wednesday (i think) was lisa's birthday and her, kate, emily and tessas dropped into the library during my break. we sat around and talked and lisa had this HOTT shirt that tess made! jorden stopped by too. oo yeah, since they ditched they all had fake names.  lisa- marie porter jorden- nathalie green tess- elizabeth kate- can't remember..  it was awesome. the history homework had been lightened because Mr. Shonick wanted us to devote time to our research reports. the next day, in english, we performed the opening to romeo and juliet. chris was tybalt and i played benvolio and that BITCH STABBED ME!! i think my dagger was defective... but i got him back, in the begininng ot the party i was capulet and he was tybalt again and i hit him in the back of the head for wanting to kill romeo. freak. kidding~ chris hastings is the coolest. alyssa was romeo tho! shes sooooo skinny.. and lisa was juliet...  on friday i went to math as always, at 7:40, then i had my open so i went into the library and had to sit thru the dancers dancing. bleh. eric watson was in there... and a bunch of girls.. LIKE THE MISSING ONE!! oh yeah, this chick went missin on wednesday and there were 2 more fights that week... so i wrote nathalie a 10 page note which took the whole entire period...  well anyway, after my break i skipped PE cause i really didnt feel good so i went with christina (who has an open B3) and so we walked around soquel village in the rain. she shared a bunch of personal stories with me and i shared some with her.. it was a bonding experience. we went to this like "Lion Park" and there was rain and stuff.. and we went to this yoga place and i almost died laughing!! it was great! then we went to the baglery and ate and we started walking back to school so i could get my camera (not that i had anyone to ake pictures of at harbor!! bleh!!) and we saw christina's mom and so we went to try and get crystal and nathalie outta class but they wouldnt come... so christina and i got my shirt and my camera from my locker.. and then stopped my longoria's room to wave at katy, matt, carson and chris... oo i think alec was in there too...  well we got in christina's car and drove to harbor. the bell hadn't rung yet so we decided to go walk down to the bus stop to check the times but then we got to mud and i was like "nuh uh!" and so we walked back up to the school and we talked with matt and tina and elena and fidel and NAOMI BRADFORD!! she is my harbor lover! i swear, if it wasnt for her i would have tottally had a shitty time. but yeah..  while naomi was off somewhere i was talking with elena jin and nathalie called so we went to go find her and steve saw me and he was like "BEN! BEN!" and i thought he was talking to me but i guess not! cause im not BEN! SORRY STEVE! :-(  with crystal + nathalie there it was a hell of a lot funner! christina and nathalie and crystal and i tottally shined! it was awesome! i would do it all again.. except i would've looked for jaye.. and maybe talked to michael and tell chris albrect (dominic's butt buddy) that i wasn't gonna beat him up.. ha thats funny...  so the bell rang and i went up to tina and hugged her for like a minute and she was like "get off me!" and then we started to walk down to the bus stop. it was shitty and muddy and i called jack vidnovic to try and get a ride but he had already left. stupid A days.. we got down to the bus stop right as the bus pulled away. "oh well, only 15 min." we thought. so we sat. and waited. and there was still no bus. so we sat and tapped our thrid eyes like that chick from Rich Girls. and STILL NO BUS CAME! so we were just about to start walking when this bus came around the corner and we all got on and paid money. i sat with christina and across from us sat nathalie and crystal. this girl new gabi, nathalie's cousin, and she talked to us for a little bit.  we decided on that bus ride that the next time we went to harbor we would PLAN IT OUT waaay ahead of time!  that weekend i got some early christmas presents like NOW 14!!! its a great CD!! luken is the awesomest!! and on saturday i drove up to SF with Andrew Galvez and his two friends, Kathy and Veronica. it was cool! and we went shopping EVERYWHERE!!  banana republic, urban outfitters, abercrombie, american eagle, victoria's secrets, fcuk, macys (OO IT WAS SOOOO FUCKING PRETTY!!), and i acctually think that was it.. hmm.. mebbe there was more... there were a lotta gay guys! and it was super fun cause andrew was there and he bought me in the zone and i bought myself the missy elliot CD. it was one of the BEST days of my life!!  on monday it was a pretty normal C day.. until english. our counselors came in and talked to us about college. i had a lotta questions and so fromnow on when anyone asks "any questions?" chris turns to me and says "brandon?"... yeah.. we also got our schedule options for next semester, but i didnt wanna change anything... well the whole talk was really exciting... it really opened my eyes and that night i searched online for college resources and academic standards.. and i was talking to JACK about it and he said that i didnt EVER come across as the INTELLECTUAL type! psh!! i guess its true then, he REALLY doesnt noe me!!  on tuesday and wednesday i was in full college over achiever mode. i asked questions (like chris knew i would) in all my classes and my french teacher said i was too much of an acheiver and that i would prolly end up killing someone one day. :-D oo i also met micheal over the phone monday and he was pretty awesome. thanks for transferring my calls dominic! even if you did have a shitty weekend and got drunk without me FOR THE SECOND TIME i still love you.. except not. on wednesday i even went to a french club meeting!! it was sooo cool!! we're having a french club party in january and spencers house! spencer the guy, not the girl!! he's soooo hott! tess and tiana and nathalie and naomi and kate are gonna be there too!! its sooo cool!  thursday was rainy. i dont like the rain. but at the same time i love it. we traded rough drafts in shonick and everyone who read mine said that it was good but no one could give me feedback. blah... that day after school while ellen and i were waiting for our ride, i danced with annie under the eaves and then hannah and i talked about starting a club.. lol we came up with funky names.. it was hilarious!! but then my dad came so we left~  friday was boring. nothing fun happened EXCEPT I BEAT hannah and elizabeth and emila and ivy in knock out! hahaha! can't touch this! it was really fun! but yeah when i got home i worked hard on my report and thats basically what i did all weekend.. i slept a lot on sunday and i finished my french family tree project that day... and on saturday (with help from juntado) i started THIS BLOG~!! and on saturday i also watched BUFFY SEASON FIVE~ HELL YEAH IT KICKED ASS! i cried at the end of "The Body" but, of course, dominic was there to kinda cheer me up.  monday i brought my family tree project. we worked more on rough drafts in shonick and thankfully it was so short tat we didnt work THAT long... bleh~ monday was lame.  tuesday was better. we had a sub in math and we did book work the whole period... it was easy and i finished early so i wrote a note to nathalie. piano was awesome and i passed a bunch of songs and got my grade up to a B.. all i have to do is pass 3 more songs and i get an A!! we played this really fun game and i was on a team with the lockewood sisters and ellen and angelica and umm... some other people who are REALLY cool but i dont noe their names. HAHA we brought briana, sara and lisa (not biancalana)'s team DOWN TO CHINA TOWN!! it was great!! the funniest part was annie was sick! the one day we have loads of fun she gets SICK!  well in shonick we did rough drafts for the last time.. the report was due on thursday. oo yeah katherine read mine and SHE DID A SUPER JOB~~ seriously!! she was the only one who could like.. correct it at all!! she is tottally my next pick for proof-reader... ooo in english we watched a scene from romeo and juliet and he had to pants on :-o !! it was.. magical.. as stephen would say.. oh yeah, him and i stopped fighting that day!! it was cool i guess...  wednesday we played knock out again.. its such a fun game! we also tried super knock out which.. i guess.. is where if the person who gets you out gets out by soemone else you're back in. so you win by beating EVERYONE~!! we didnt really finish.. but elizabeth and i talked a lot about.. mm.. stuff... mostly candy.. and during my open i hung out with tiana andkate in the library cause tiana needed to finish her family tree project. she has a really cool family.  thursday i wore abercrombie pajamas! they have mooses on them. we had a sub again in math and we played pictionary AGAIN.. oo we did that on wednesday too.. i forgot to write it tho~ anyone, my pajamas caught everyone's attention and yeah! it was fun stuff. we turned in research reports in history and watch the simpson's odessy and the simpsons hamlet!   "Now when people get wood they'll think of Trojans.." haha flanders...  anway, it was nice having a relaxing day in every class. i wished everyone i had A days with a Merry Christmas before it was over.  friday was the best! i got flooded with gifts.. and i talked with marissa and cloey (shoreline people) in the library. haha i tottally thought of the perfect april fools joke!! thanks marissa~!!  in pe ivy and i made up funny stories while running around the gym. HAHA bird in telephone wires~! there were some other great ones.. but yeah~ we talked about rumplestiltskin too.. i never got that story... we played SUPER KNOCK OUT the WHOLE rest of the period!! our one game NEVER ended!! it was great!! we had like 12 people playin, it was crazy~   at lunch new brighton kids came over and the got ready for a play in our gym. ooo evan was there~ hes a cutie!! it was haha ivy was trying to get me to go meet him and she was like pulling me into the emmy room and we like fell and i ran to tara it was so funny!! michele and i were gonna watch the play but we decided we'd rather hang out in french. french was acctually kinda fun! i sleep during the family tree presentation and then we sang christmas carols like this one about how santa claus saved 3 little kids from a butcher who chopped them up and stuff.  BUT FINALLY THE DAY WAS OVER~ IT WAS WINTER BREAK!!   winter break:  saturday: i sleep for 11 hours and went to the mall with nathalie, tina, amy and lily. i bought them all christmas gifts! a pac sun bag, a volcom wallet and an a shirt. it was a lotta fun and it was super cool to see amy again since i hadn't seen her since the thanksgiving weekend. lily is the awesomest!! oo i also set up luigi and dominic but it didnt last long. ha.  sunday: i seriously slept all day and it felt so good! i was refreshed and ready for winter break!  monday: chores at a friends house.. there was even a cameo appearance by steve (not to be confused with stephen).  tuesday: i got my braces tightened in the morning! it didnt hurt at first and my mom took me to surf city and got me a smoothie. stoked strawberry like always. thats when they started to hurt.. so i choked down the advil and got online. i didnt expect jaye to IM me.. but he did.. and we talked. at first i didnt think it would last more than a few seconds.. but the minutes turned to hours and it was acctually a lotta fun. jaye's a sweetheart, i've always known that. but on tuesday everything just.. changed... :-)  wednesday: oh goodie, christmas eve! today i rushed around getting last minutes gifts for my parents while they were prolly doing the same for me. in the evening i went out to dinner with my grandparents and my folks like always. i got money tho, so it wasnt too bad... that night i stayed up really late waiting for "santa" and i watched the nightmar before christmas and the grinch! both awesome movies.  thrusday: mErRy cHrIsTmAs! today was sooo cool! i got a bunch of money and Cds and DvDs and i even got a new computer for my room (after the remodle tho) and so yeah! it was great. but then it just kinda dragged on and i wanted it to be the day after cause thats when all the fun sales are!  FRIDAY: I HAD THE FUNNEST DAY EVER with nathalie! i woke up kinda late and then called her and we went to the mall. at macy's we saw A BUNCH of clothes on the clothes return table and there were people rushing everywhere. we went to a lot of stores. i got a bunch of stuff from abercrombie! gina, amy's sister, was working and she was really nice. oo and i got a bunh of stuff from american eagle too.. nathalie bought me a present and i bought her another one! lol it was a really soft belt. i saw nelli and anchor blue and i promised to call her so her and i could hang out over the break. we walked around and at wet seal we saw crystal and her sisters and then we saw jocelyn and lindsey. we walked to styles and nathalie saw this REALLY cute shirt and she got excited just to find out there was shit on it. but eventually we found on that was shit free, cause there were like 5 with shit on them, and we boguht them along with this candy fish that look like a toliet. oh yeah! there was this big belt that looked like a wand cause there was a huge star on it! seriously. it was big. like monica big. anyway, we walked to jamba juice and saw britnii and maria and mayra and other people comin' into the mall and britnii was like "brandon, too good to talk to us now?" and so i hugged her and nathalie and i were like "jocelyn's in styles if you wanna see her!" and they were like "screw that bitch!" so nathalie and i laughed all the way thru the parking lot and across the street. after seeing crystal's sisters again, at j.j., we went to choice so nathalie could get a bunch of tank tops and then we went to fresh choice and then my mom came and nathalie fell into a trash can! it was hilarious!. well i called nelli but she wasnt home so i called tara and we had a nice conversation...  saturday- i worked for more cash.. i made 50 bucks! oo and then dominic called.. he called on friday in the morning too but i was still asleep.. he wanted to go to the mall but i think he tree like fell down or something and so he couldnt get a ride. instead he and chris "hung" out.   sunday- i made a lot more money! it was really fun! cause i got to get rid of a bunch of old stuff and make space for new stuff! it feels good to get rid of... well it was lots of fun. i talked to jaye more and more! he's such a sweetie~ that night i talked to tina and nathalie until like 2.. well tina left at 1.. but i watched the shining which was REALLY scary but really good... nathalie told me the end and i yelled at her and then she said that everyone died which was the end and yeah! she confused me.. oo after that i watched Mystery Men and X2 and then i fell asleep... the shining was such a SCARY MOVIE!! but it was so annoying cause that chick coulda like killed that guy a bunch of times. and what was up with that freak, tony!? and REDRUM!! puhleeze~ why not just say "'MURDER' BACKWORDS"! wendy is supposed to be a horror fiction addict, cant she take a little real life ghost stories for a change? and those little girls will have me traumatized for life. AND THE NAKED LADY~ BLEH~!!  monday- jaye left me for tahoe! wow it rained a lot today.. i woke up at 2 and jaye said his goodbyes. so i went to the mall with amy and tina and we went into so many stores!! they got me some presents, my favorite was the MOOSIE BOXERS from abercrombie!! it was so much fun! in the arcade we raced each other and they one. by a second. wow. its only cause tina killed that cow instead of swerving like i did. it was a lotta fun and we should do it again sometime!  tuesday- i woke up at 2:30 cause i watched jerry maguire the night before.. i love that movie! "show me the money!" "shut up! just shut up! you had me at hello!" "sorry, im a little pregnant right now." ok yeah well i woke up at 2 ish and then suzie called and said she was having a small party (like 20 close friends) and so i got dressed and went. my fourth suzie party. it was acctually a lotta fun! i love her new house, even if it isnt as big as the other one.. ok, i loved her other house a lot.. what can i say? im materialistic... yeah.. well i got home and nathalie said her goodbyes and said shed talk to me in 2004~ then she left for reno!! woo hoo... well it got late and i went to be early  wednesday- TODAY! well it's basically almost over so heres what i did: i woke up at 9 because of loud remodlers and so i did a bunch of chores for more cha-ching. then i went to my aunts and ate cookies.. it was kinda lame.. everyone was down at first night and i was stuck at home with another cold. bleh~!! its so lame...  WELL I HOPE EVERYONE HAS A HAPPY NEW YEARS! 2004! WHAT WHAT!
     

    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If at first you don't succeed, Dust yourself off and try again. You can dust it off and try again. -Aaliyah, "Try Again"   this was a really fun month. it starts on the saturday of kassie's birthday party.   Kassie's friend rachel (this really funny girl from scotts valley, who i hung out with in jully...? sometime around then, we anyway, she) had a friend named luigi who came out and was all gay and stuff. well he gave rachel a book and an invite to the party he was having the next week at his (WOOT WOOT) BEACH HOUSE!! so like yeah.. i was thinking about going but they all said he was ugly so i kinda reconsidered..  anoways the party was really fun! we all were playing ddr and then it was like pizza dinner or something.  rachel+ kassie shared a seat and going left there was: stephanie, cali, kayla, cody, jourdain, ellen, kalie, teena, me and monica. well i kinda sat on the edges of both teena and monicas chairs. BAD idea. i almost fell... twice. and i was wearing my nice sweater...  well yeah after presents (wow, there were alotta animal stuff!) we got ready to leave.. and then we left for THE CORN MAZE~!! the ride up kalie and i sang country songs cause kassie's mom really like the western station.   so we get to the maze and like we go in the entrance and this guy tells us aboutthe maze and its all cold and dark and we can hear music from the haunted ranch place and so we like go in and we wander around finding different things and yeah... we end up all getting seperated, me with cody young. cody and i kinda kissed akwardly and yeah.. we continued on and kassie, teena, rachel and all of them jumped out and scared us. but no one was as scared as monica. i felt bad for her... but anyway, i was with her and then the chain saw guy was like somewhere and we ran and it was so scary.  From the windoooow To the kitchen!  Put some hot sauce on that chicken, Damn yo breath is kickin'!  So eventually we got bored with the whole "wandering-around-the-maze" thing and we decided to go str8 to the haunted ranch. now when we got to the entrance it was kinda creepy but it didnt seem scary at all!! teena was scared so since kalie had gone already, her and teena went out of the maze and waited for us at the exit.   in line, the actors (who were in costume), would try to scare us. first it was this vampire lady with big boobs. she scared me and kassie was like "don't worry, he's gay!!" RIGHT when she said that word a bunch of guys turned around and kinda looked at me. they were really cute, but yeah i figured they were red necks or something...  so we waited in line and i would ask all the actors if i could have a hug cause i ain't 'fraid of no ghost *wink* and then we got ready to go in and we annoyed this bunny man. a lot. so we went in the maze.. kayla, kassie, rachel, cali, stephanie, cody and i. everyone else went after us. it was really creepy in the begininng and cody fell and he was like "leave me! leave me!" and i was like "you are not being left behind!" and i piggy backed him thru the rest of the thing.. oo and i met a really cute vampire who was flirting with me and he was REALLY cute in his vampire make up. so we get outta the place after passing this scary girl who looked like she crawled outta a hybrid of the ring and the shining, we got to the CHAIN SAW GUY! and he like chased us it was soooo cooool!! and then we like left and on the way home teena and kalie were talking about the boys that had turned around when kassie called me gay, and kalie was like "they were touching each other and stuff... tottally fruity!"  so yeah.. i called jorden richardson (the jourdain that was with us was different then the other jorden..) and jorden and i talked and yeah... kassies mom dropped me off and teena promised to give me the book on monday at school.   so i got home at 1 and fell asleep pretty fast... on sunday i slept all day.. i was so tired!  monday started with high hopes of the soon to be 4 day weekend. the library was FINALLY reopened after an awesome renovation. and stephen (this guy i met in october) left school do to independed studies. anyway, on wed. night stephen "came out" and by friday the whole school knew so he was pretty pissed at me. but whatever.. he was kinda lame.  OO annie ross's birthday was on thursday! it was so great i got her a monkey and she got a bunch of other shweet presents... oo yeah, mesha and i wore the monkie on our legs and made it look like it was humping us.. :-D annie got these balloons from tanya and while mesha and i were watching her stuff, one of the balloons blew onto the grass and POPPED! and then annie came back and mesh and i were like "noo!! it was the grass!" and annie didnt believe us and so i took the other balloon (she got 2 small ones and a big.. um.. shiny one) and i was like "noo!! the wind popped it!" and i shoved the balloon against the grass and it popped and i was like "like THAT!" and mesha started crackin' up! it was great! HAPPY BIRTHDAY ANNIE BANANNIE~  saturday was suzie's SECOND party. in the morning i went shopping with teena and kendra and got some shweet pajamas. i was gonna meet dominic there and get my shirt back but he got their too late and we left. then the PARTAY~ i met some.. "new" people and it was a lotta fun! im even glad the rowland went dispite the fun we all had. no more vodka for ANY of you! tess is the my best sober friend! lol.. and yeah.. that party was cool but then the cops busted it at like 1 or 2 o'clock. i wasnt there tho but tess was upstairs and like the police told everyone to come down but she didnt so hahaha! i bet it went on their perm. record.   well the next day i hung out with matt and andrew galvez, old friends from cazedero! andrew is REALLY HOT and he's so sweet but he's kinda old.. and now we've decided to be friends until im older.. you noe how it is.. oh yeah, hes 20~ but that night was alotta fun and a lotta laughs! poor matt's prolly trumatized now tho :-) !  the monday of my fourday weekend i stayed home and worked for cash~! it was a lotta fun despite how it sounds, especially cause i watched the first two seasons of angel.~!! and tuseday i hung out with nathalie at the mall-o. i think christina and tina and sarah went too... mm? yeah. i got a sweater and um... i think i bought tina panties :-p  the 3 days that we were in school were kind lame. we didnt really do much in any of our classes except a test in shonick. but that wasnt too hard. i didnt do anything that weekend either. just homework and chores. cha-ching.  so the next week was the last full week of november. wootie woot! we started romeo and juliet in english, our fam. tree projects in french and our final research report in history. we learned how to use athena, this book search thing, in the library, and i got a bunch of nifty books on Joan of Arc.   that weekend i did more chores! i had made/saved 200 and was tottally ready for my shopping spree at valley fair after thanksgiving. on saturday i went to tinas house and she tried to kill me so i hid in her bathroom. but anyway, her and i talked with nathalie from 5 to 12 ish BEATING my record with DOMINIC~!! ha you lost! it was great but then i fell asleep and it kinda ended...   the last two days of school were crazy! i wished everyone a happy thanksgiving and in english we did this REALLY COOL shakepearean dance and like SOMEONE touched my ass!  patrick and i were the last ones outta mrs. miranda's class on the day before break.   Brandon- What are you doing over break? Patrick- Eating. Brandon- Fun... You're gonna get fat, you know...! Patrick- I never said what I was eating.. *wink*  Here's what my Thanksgiving Break looked like:  Wednesday- Went with Nathalie, Crystal and Tina to shoreline were we saw all the little people! it was so fun! but then we had to elave cause i wanted to go to the mall~ Thursday- THANKSGIVING! I had a huge family thing and I ate alotta food and i felt fat so i took laxatives but that just fucked up my aunt's toilet... Friday- I was planning on hangin' with Jack Vidnovic and Luigi but i was feeling under the weather and i was hyped for my V.F. trip the next day and so I just stayed home and watched some of the West Wing. then I went to suzie's THIRD party when i felt better. it was cool and we played fun truth or dare, except my dare wasn't the greatest :-/ ... Saturday- VALLEY FAIR TRIP! I picked Suzie up first, then Tess who lives close to CARSON! Carson's bro's car was TP-ed!! then we got Ivy from Watsonville and we drove and chit chatted all the way to Valley Fair. it was alotta fun and I got a REALLY cute shirt and nice cords. it was really fun cause we're just fun people :-D! omg there was this really nice watch at this one store. but no... It would have looked really ncie on Tina tho! but yeah.. Tess and Suzie got lost in the girl's part of Macy's and Ivy climbed on my back so we could find them! it was sooo much fun! then we went home and i felt really sick.. Sunday- stayed home sick and watched the rest of the first season of the West Wing. i learned a lot from it tho...  Well YEAH~!! that was the end of november cause of the thnxgiving break and all but coming up next was the BEST MONTH so far!! DECEMBER~!!!  LATO BRANDON~!!
     

    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Voulez-vous couche avec moi, ce soir. Voulez-vous couche avec moi. Yeah yeah uh. -Moulin Rouge, "Lady Marmalade"  haha, the month started out great! school was awesome and everyone was so yeah..   but of course my history caught up with me and I began hearing and thinking more about dominic.   i saw him for the first time in 2 months at the mall (of course) and i kinda walked past him. he really pissed me off with his little pissy-ness but whatever. it was a fun day with janis, sally and monique. OMG! we saw ellen in the car on the drive home it was HILARIOUS!   school went on as usually... not really much change. alec was kinda acting weird and chris and patrick were a lil on the alert mode too... i think chris was stoned one day..   annie was lots of fun to hang out with and mesha as well.. and ivy was great.. i met tess in october at aldos. she was really fun and we got to be friends really really fast. michele was cool too and i talked to her and katy quite frequently.   first sat.: can you say kaboom? it was the anual monte carlo fireworks. nelli scored free tickets from kathryns mom.. lol.. even tho i bought a bunch from chris hastings..   i ended up going with kathleen and planned on meeting carolyn, nelli and katy there. i saw chris and carson (really funny guy from the h/a) there with alec. alec kinda gave me the glare and i talked to carson and chris for a little bit but continued looking at the really awesome booths.   Dominic came later... after carolyn and nelli and katy had arrived. lol! carolyn's dad is awesome! well back to dominic~ i let him borrow my shirt for no reason since he had a sweatshirt but whatever. i didnt noe i wouldnt get it back until 2004!! &gt;:-o!   well he ditched us for other harbor people WHILE WEARING MY SHIRT!  so we wandered and i saw elizabeth and naomi and jorden and alyssa and even van dyk! the coolest math teacher from shoreline!!   the fireworks were magical. it was sooo pretty. and i wasnt that far from the rest of the soquelians.... so yeah.. it was great. :-)   lol! this is the best part~ ok so the roads were all closed cause of like some fucked up drunks and we walked to the gas station to wait for kathleen's mom. on the way these cars honked at us and i slapped my ass!! and then at the gas station i swear something was in those bushes!! well at like 11 kathleen's mom and really funny sister darlene got their and we drove to the bank and then BK to satisfy those midnight munchies :-P!   the fireworks weekend was great.   second weekend: snooze! i slept all weekend.. it was great!!   school was getting more and more fun! i was getting closer to everyone.. even patrick and i found common ground~ This is halloween, this is halloween...  the thursday b4 harbor homecoming i called dominic and he was too drunk to talk to me.. so he HUNG UP!!   thrid weekend: Harbor Homecoming go pirates! go pirates! bleh~ this weekend was kinda lame. i met tara at the frosh game and sat with tess and ivy and tara and katy. it was all good. then nathalie and tina and crystal came. after the frosh game i took a quick pic of luken! damn he transferred outta my pe class :-(! well yeah, then ivy, tess and the 3 shorline chicks all went to the deli with me and we ate food. lol.. then i farted.. BUT IT WAS TINA'S FAULT!! tess and ivy left and so i went with kalie and naomi back to the game. that was the first time i saw chris albrecht, dominic's fuck buddy. YUCK! well he was.. um.. "alrite" as nathalie put it.   well i saw dominic a lil bit before the half time of the Varsity game. annie and aby were there too! god i love annie! shes so funny.. and aby changed it this really gross porter potty... half time was kinda weird.. there were dancers.. enough said... i stole tina's lip gloss and almost O.D.ed on it! yay... i stole her soda too..   well then i went and sat with naomi and talked to this really hot guy (who turned out to be taylor!) but i doubt he remembers me.. he was REALLY hot!! oh and i saw jack.. yeah.. no comment :-/  tina had to get a ride home with nathalie and crystal so we wandered around trying to find them but ended up getting really really lost... and yeah... we found them in the end and tina was like "BYE!" and she ran.. and then i talked to dominic and he was kinda iffy but he left with chris to fuck and get ready for the dance and fuck. thats like all they do. well at least hes HAPPY~!!! :-D  yeah well i left with kalie and naomi and it was alotta fun and i was sooo gonna go to the bon fire with jack rodriguez (from french) and a bunch of santa cruz fags but i got sick :-( ...  well school that week was lame cause i had the sniffles.. but i didnt have to swim... so boo ya! elizabeth and me chilled in the gazebo, or how ever you spell it, by the pool!  on thursday i went into the girls locker room for the THIRTEENTH time and like they invited me in and shit and then mrs. locke like fucking grabbed me and hauled me to waddel's office. i got detention, but still it was better than suspension which it woulda been if mrs. locke had her way. &gt;:-o!  the rallies leading up to our homecoming were great! and the homecoming rally was awesome. everyone wanted jeff gill to win (pshyeah~!!) but to rouse support ivy and i made up some poems  Mirror Mirror on the Wall, Damn Jeff is fine!! If I were homecoming crown, I would want him mine!  When you see him on the floor, Ooo la la, you gasp, VOTE JEFF GILL FOR KING.. Or we'll kick your ass~!!  the last weekend: OUR HOMECOMING~!!  it was sooo fucking awesome! so it starts out at the church place with naomi and we watch the parade and jeff and calire throw candy at us and its awesome! and corey was the head cheerleader and it was so cool! so naomi and i met ivy and michele and we walked up the long trail to campus. we see the parade and the band coming up the drive, and then michele and me and ivy go in early for the frosh game. we walk in and see tara and patches sitting up in the stands. so we all hang out during the frosh game and we buy food and patrick gets this little sugar packet and hes like "i think you dropped your name tag.." it was so funny and adorable! after the frosh game we went and chilled at surf city and i got a stoked strawberry.. my soon to be favorite drink!   we got back for the second half of the game and nelli came running over all frantic. "I need help with the freshman float!!" she said, "Will you help?" so patrick is like "yeah!" and we're like "patrick!" and he's like "remember that time.." "NO!!" but we ended up going because nelli is the coolest and patrick is kinda cute underneath it all. so we get to the big orange truck and we're like "no.." but we ended up decorating it and it looked great. tara and patrick ran to berverlys for markers and posters and streamers, and nelli, michele, ivy and i worked on the masking tape and shit."  Rc, the stupid butt hole, and his other senoirs got on their float.. ours was SOOO crappy. it was sad. i shared a sign with michele cause it was really big and when we went in we circled around and we made fun off the irish! ha ha ha ICE THE IRISH!! so yeah and then we went to our side and woot woot! it was fun. but they put ont he brakes and i fell on patrick. it was so much fun! alec and chris showed up and threw candy at us and patrick chucked this thing back at them.. and madalee and heddy showed up~!! they were supposed to be on the floats but oh well...  so after the floats we took down everything and i scored some pretty green shoes.. they were cute. well i went back and sat with naomi engleman this time (before it was all bradford) and amber from my PE class.. (ive mentioned her, right?) well it was great and after the game i went over to carolyn and we talked and then i went with her and madalee and heddy into the band room since naomi bradford was giving me a ride home. well it was fun and we all talked and then i left promising to dance with them at the dance.  i dressed in mardi gras clothing and my new abercrombie hat! i got to the dance and found ivy and michele and we all went in to the dance. ASB stickers really do pay off.... well the dance was fun. lots of freak dancing! the only girl i didnt dance with was ivy cause she didnt wanna with a gay man, and michele kinda danced with me but left. i had fun tho. SLOW DANCE SHOUT OUTS 2: Carolyn! Nique! and... um.. who else did I dance with!? Shit!! I think it was Tara.. but i dunno and I dont wanna be all like mean.. i freaked with everyone including that girl who wants to have fun~ ANNIE ROSS! woot woot monkie style~!! i even kinda freaked with patchy... KINDA.. but eww.. :-)  suzie and kayla were really fun and yeah.. the dance ended and ellen was nice enough to give me a ride home! woot woot! so after the dance i passed out and the next day i got really sick and i slept most of it..  the last week was really cool. it started fun and ended FANTASTIC on halloween when we all went over to suzie's house. halloween was great from beginning to end. i got pictures of everyone including sexy ivy as a bunny outta a hat and amber + naomi the sweedish bar maids! i didnt have to dress in pe cause of the costume. ooo i was LEI BOY! it was great and yeah.. french was crazy and we didnt really do anything. after school i went to suzie's and we went swimming and into a really nice jacuzzi.. wow.. thinking about it makes me wanna pee... so after we went inside and watched movies and listened to music and ate pizza! that was the first of suzie's parties!! yay! i met a lot of people at that party.. it was really cool..  halloween.. the LAST DAY OF OCToBER~!! it feels like somethin's heatin' up!  lates bRaNdOn (Choppin' Broccolli ;-))
     

    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Red red wine, close to me. Makes me forget that I still need you so. Red red wine, it's up to you. -Bob Marley, "Red Red Wine"   so yeah.. its the first month of school. the second day of school was pretty much the same as the first. in all our classes we talked about expectations for the semester and blah blah stuff like that.. the second day was the day i met ivy. she was in the humanities academy. we got to be REALLY good friends REALLY fast!! i met a lot of people in the Humanities academy, There was Adia and Matt and Katy!  Katy showed me her binder of Clay and she was like “this is my husband” so I got my pic. of hott Jamie Martin from all my children and I was like this is mine!  but before that, on the second day of school I found out I had PE with Ivy! While we were getting our clothes i met hannah globus who alsolikes a woot woot!! christine had pe w/ us too and so did emila and majusta from shoreline.  biology was pretty fun but kinda boring. it just lingered on and my only friends were chris hastings and tessa. and this new kid named chris cavero. anyway, i felt like transferring out and dropped my slip in the box in the office.  meanwhile, the humanities academy was getting funner everyday. I met jorden richardson and she is still the SICKEST CHICK EVER!! shes sooo nice and funny! and if shes reading this I LOVE HER MORE!! so ha!!  i also met lisa who was crazy in love with starburst wrappers. she was really nice and REALLY smart.  about mid september i switched from bio to french. it was a great change. french was a lot funner and i met christine and naomi.   i had pe with christine and we had small conversations before but french brought us closer. and i had some classes with naomi but it wasnt until french that i really “met”her. shes awesome, and loves to shop! naomi was great.  patrick was another cool guy i met in the humanities academy. he was really fun and yeah... hes my high five buddy! lol.  Brandon- "Patrick, u got somethin' on ur leg.." Patrick- " *Looks* Snot... *Laughs*" Brandon- "Is that what you call it?" Patrick- "Ur a lil bitch *Smiling* " Brandon- "At least I'm not a whore... Next time tell Alec to aim a lil higher..." Patrick- "Oh my god! Hey, ur the one who likes him!" Brandon- "Um, yeah. I'm gay... me no like women..." Patrick- "Oh, burn!" Brandon- "Well Alec is mad at me so whatever..." Patrick- "With good reason. All the guys hate you..." Brandon- "Do you hate me? *Puppy face* " Patrick- "Of course not...!"  in piano i met annie ross, a friend of aby who i also met in the hum. acad. aby and annie are super fun. tanya is cool too.. and so is Mesha! the monkey! haha! i love them. well annie and i met in piano and we practiced together. i also met brianna and corey and lisa in piano.. fun beans!  math got fun as katia and i got to be better friends. maya and stephanie (from shoreline) were in it and they are fun so yeah. nathalie also transferred in but transferred out after she failed her first test. lol. crystal transferred in. AND ABY HAD MATH WITH ME TOO!! 7:40 classes tho.. they’re bleh...  pe was great! i met elizabeth chuun! shes really cool and she is tottally my advisor. and like when the boys were beaing mean in the locker room she handled everything and i love her for it! jimmy nehrer is a meanie and so is greg nunn but w/e! i met suzie and randi in pe too.. suzie will be important later so yeah~!!  i met alotta people in the hum. acad. just look down there   outside of my classes, i met tara (super fun!) and nelli! nelli is and will always ever be the funnest girl ever! she is so optimistic and she makes us all laugh and she... she just never has a frown! we all love her! she is the same one from graduation who i wanted to be friends with! and she wanted to be friends with me too! yay! tara is really fun too. she is nice and she’s hilarious! at first i thought whe was a sophmore.. lol  that was the best!! ok well not much happened in september, i just met people lol. french was really cool cause NATHALIE and CHRISTINA were in it too!!   more people i met:  cassidy- hum. academy- hes really smart and funny sometimes kathryn- h/a (hum. acad.) – REALLY REALLY smart! shes so cool cause like she could correct my report and i thank her greatly for that! rachie- h/a -shes really cool! and she is best friends with katia! and they’re gonna move to la! alyssa- h/a - friends with jorden and REALLY REALLY REALLY SKINNY!! chrystaline- h/a- really nice and kinda shy carolyn- shes really cool and shes in band! yay! shes really skinny 2! michele- french- long story, i met her in french and i also met her at aldos and basically yeah, shes awesome nique- french- shes really cool and i met her in french! hailey- h/a- really pretty, really smart, really fun! monica- shes pregnant! jk shes awesome! kendra- french – tons of fun kayla- really athletic and yeah...  there are more people that im prolly forgetting BUT I’LL ADD YOU IN OCTOBER~!!  im adding madalee and heddy in october cause of the whole homecoming thing! yay!!
     

    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Fate fell short this time, Your smile fades in the summer. Place your hand in mine, I'll leave when I wanna. -Blink 182, "Feeling This"   the first day of school started kinda like i was expecting. ellen picked me up at 7:20 for the carpool. on the way i had a nervous twist in my stomach... kinda like constapation only less severe.  anyway, we got to school and i opened my locker. 2 - 96. i'd put my combo up here but there are some people reading this who i dont really trust... anyway, i went to my first class. Geometrey. we all stood outside, waiting for Mr. McConnell to show up. That's when I met christine. my first friend at soquel. She came from Holy Cross.. or maybe she got kicked outta there for not believing in god. Whatever, anyway, it was a lot of fun. i learned a lot about her and her fam. WOO HOO! she goes to hawaii every year!! cool beans! so our stubbly math teacher shows up and opens the door. he's already divised a seating chart, alphabetical order, and im stuck between alex baker and brett ackler. Now, alex is pretty cool. hes smart and all that. but brett.. brett stinks... literally... it's called deodorant. well we get our geometrey books and the lesson begins. my mind blanks and i look around the room... holy shit! im the only kid from shoreline! but wait, isnt that chris hastings.  ok, chris hastings, here's the deal.. in May i signed up to be in this intensive humanities course. The humanities academy. the orientation was in the soquel library, in May as well. i wore my spiffy cow boy outfit :-D! I met some cool people there... alec and emily. and, of course, tessa, tiana and kate were there. but back to the story.  so i see chris... and then we talk.. and he's a pretty cool guy. def someone i want as a friend. the bell rings and i look at my schedule... next stop, Piano.  well that was a boring class... i thought when i walked out of piano. all we did was fill out forms. stephanie hammond and ellen are in it with me.. ellen.. little did i know she was going to get way lame, way fast.  so next is my open. i head to the library and i sit down at a vacant table. then, a girl sits down. but not any girl.. it was spencer kaufman. one of the most popular girls at shoreline.  "hey.. brandon right?" she said. i nodded. then she looked at my schedule. "walter for pe..? always dress out and never chew gum. she said. we sat there quietly filling out forms that our A2 teachers handed out.  but pretty soon the bell rang for break.  i met christine and a bunch of other people at my locker. we all had relativley close lockers due to a mishap at orientation... ill get into that later.. anyway, for my first break i headed to my next class. History.. with Mr. Shonick.   i choose a desk next to christine, and pretty soon tessa, tiana, and kate come tortting in. we exchange hugs and "how was your summer?" and then they take seats near me. a bunch of other people come in. there's chris! and emily! oo and crystal! crystal and i have short convo and then she takes a seat next to me. well pretty soon this crazy guy with poofy hair walks in. class starts and we pretty much dont do anything except read and stuff.  the bell rings. my next class is PE.  i walk to the gym with christine and sit in the bleachers. our kinda chubby but happy looking PE teacher walks in. he calls roll and when it all done he gives us some forms. the guy behind me accidently kicks me. "sorry.." he said when i turned around. "hey, im jon luken.." this really skinny kid stares at me with a grin of braces. but whatever. he's cute. lol. we talk a bit but then its over and i head to lunch.  my first high school lunch! you noe what that means.. im going off campus :-D! on the way down with kalie and christine, i run into, GUESS WHO!! NATHALIE! nathalie and i became best friends over the summer.. and it wouldnt have been possible without the DC trip, but i'll get to that after the first day of school.. hmm maybe i should've talked about the summer first.  after buying soda and food at Hernandez, we walk back up the lazy trial (No way I'm going up Sucide Hill!)  English is next. we head back to shonick, cause thats what is says on our sheets, but he tells us to go to miranda. on the way i catch a glance from Alec! boy has he gotten hot over the summer. we fill out more forms in English. there's a lot to do, and we get new notebooks. chris makes a joke about my shirt, but its accepted. Ellen got me my shirt.. another summer story I’ll get to later.  anyway, after English I head to biology with tessa and chris. We have assigned seats and I end up sitting next to.. well.. a big hearted fat kid. Biology breezes by and im out of school. Ellen and I head down to the main parking lot to wait for my dad.   that’s when I saw him.  I was sure he was gay… but whatever the case I felt like I had to find out more about this boy. That’s when I first saw eben.  ok.. so that’s just the first day… there’s a lot more to talk about mainly the summer and stuff.. so yeah..  Later days :-D brandon
     

    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Everybody's workin' for the weekend. Everybody wants a new romance. Everybody's going off the deep end. Everybody needs a second chance. -Loverboy, "Working For The Weekend"   oi.. the end of the summer.. so depressing. august got me addicted to soap operas and text messages. all my children is a really good show for a soap opera. they deal with situations like everyone else. but yeah.. i got over it when school started. my new cell phone tho... that was a big deal. i added every body i knew in, and i mean EVERYBODY.  august is also when i met bryan. he’s really funny but kinda sensitive... anyway, we got to noe each other and yeah.. we were friends.  ooo~ august was the month of the family summer trip. yay hawaii! the trip was a lot of fun, but i wish we spent more time on maui! i was just starting to get a good tan! anyway... we stayed at this really fancy hotel and i met a lot of guys.. you noe me.. :-D my aunt wendy lives in hawaii and i spent a lot of time with her too (no, not kalie’s mom wendy. wendy from my dad’s side)  one night my aunts wendy, debbie and norma and my uncle took us out to dinner at the outback. it was CRAZY~ norma and debbie got drunk and hit on waiters and this one guy hit on ME! plus the scary bus boy watched me potty. and i think the bartender was drunk too.   anyway.. i read a lot of books. the required reading for the Humanites academy was awful. bleh~  i got back on thursday the 14th. the day.. jamie’s mom passed away. this meant jamie would be leaving for washington (the state).. in less than a week..  on sunday the 17th i got a phone call from my “Link Crew Leader” telling me about orientation. lol. i knew from his voice that he was gay.  the orientation was 20th. and of course, nathalie left town the day before.   i picked up ellen, kalie and teena and we drove to soquel. orientation was crazy. my coming out had spread like wild fire. all the shoreliners knew. after a short speech from the president and vice president (my GAY link crew leader) we split into link groups.  the only shoreliner in my group was cloey, but that was enough. we talked about our summer and our ex’s. my link leader was RC (like the soda!). and this other girl... we played a game where we had to remember everyone’s name.. it was fun.   there was one girl in my link group. she was talking about biology and geometry and the humanities academy.. but i didnt remember her from the meeting. when we got closer to school i found out her name was nelli. everyone ran up to her and gave her hugs and she seemed mucho popular. i wanted to be her friend. lol. pathetic, i noe.  after link crew we took pictures. mine SUCKED! probably cause that guy keep telling me to turn my body. OMG! get this! his name – Harry Dong. lmao. well after pictures we got schedules and lockers. locker 2 – 96. everyone one with us got lockers around us. it was really cool.  i looked over my schedule. great. i had a 7:40 class. oh well. not that bad. after we were sure that all 6 of us- me, kassie, kalie, ashlee, teena and ellen- could open our lockers we headed to the parking lot and left. all in all the orientation was fun. oo! i met a guy named stuart saepia. none of us knew he would be kassie; first kiss.  after orientation we went back to my house and watched chicago. it was fun. we sand and danced. speaking of dancing, after the movie we played DDR. but yeah. i had to kick everyone out cause it got late.  that night i was talking to dominic about RC. he asked his ex-boyfriend jack and then jack IMed me and we talked. he seemed really cool.  the last weeks of summer all happened way too fast. the last saturday was kalie’s birthday party. kathleen and i got her CD’s. the party was so much fun. besides kathleen, naomi and lianna were also there. plus kalie’s boyfriend. woo hoo. lianna is kalie’s short but funny friend. she’s tons of fun.  around 5 nathalie called from her trip. i sat down and i started talking to her. the conversation lasted 3 hours. lol. at 8 she left to watch the cheetah girls. she wished kalie a happy birthday and.. blah. it was over.  sunday (the next day) was awesome times 50! it was the day of sally’s birthday. janis, matt, teena and sarah rorvick were there so was tina liang!   ive known sally since 7th grade. shes really athletic. lol.  tina is the coolest girl ever! her and nathalie were my best friends over the summer and they still (more or less) are. tina and matt got in this huge food fight during the party. it was great.  after ,we went back to sally’s house and jumped into her pool. it was awesome. tina wouldnt get in tho.. but i almost pushed her in once or twice... but then she pushed me in... yeah.. good times.  the last day of summer i went shopping (duh!) we saw harry and amy and tessa too! it was so much fun, you have no idea!  but nothing lasts forever. and the summer that i loved so much came to an end.  i went to bed early, but i didnt fall asleep for hours. i couldnt stop thinking about school. oi.  -Brandon!! see yaa
     

    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The tide is high and I'm holding on, I'm gonna be your number one. I'm not the kind of girl who gives up just like that.. Ooooooh noooo. -Atomic Kitten, "The Tide is High"   Woot woot! it's my b-day month!  July was insane, and it all started where June left off. On July second I was outside tanning cause i wanted to look good. the thought of Dominic being gay made me realize there are probably a lot of other gay guys in Santa Cruz too. so i tanned. and then i fell alseep. and 2 hours later i woke up burned. my whole front side was red. ouch.  i took a shower and put some aloe on it... but it didnt really help.  on the fourth I went with Ili to wilder ranch. i pathetically hoped that she'd invite dominic but she didnt. that little runt. jk!!~ wilder was a lotta fun... except i was burned... and the ice cream melted... but i had my stars and stripes boxers on!! mm yeah. then, when i got back home, my grandparents came over and we had pie and stuff. oo! and the fireworks were soooo cool! my dog like wet himself, but he does that every year.  the next day jamie, maya and kristen came over.  have i mentioned maya before? maya's a really smart and really cool person from shoreline. i've known her since the end of sixth grade when we had drama together. shes lots of laughs and shes really smart. her bat mitzvah was soo much fun!  ok~ yeah.. jamie and maya and kristen came over and we watched buffy. :-D! The Hush episode was really scary and my burn was really itching. ooh yeah, and jamie broke her leg and she had to go to the ER room on the second (the same day i got my burn!).  anyway, that was fun and then it was over..  so the next day i went to see Legally Blonde 2 with Kalie, Amanda and Bobbi.   Amanda is adorable! shes funny and cute and no guy can resist that. bobbi's lots of fun too and shes a good advice-giver. anyway, the movie was really good and outside the theater we saw Jake Scruggs, Emily Hasty and CHRIS HASTINGS. coincidence or what! oo i really liked that guy from the movie and i thought he was gay the whooole time.. but then he asked that girl to marry him and it was like "bummer..."  that night all i could talk or even think about was chris. i was talking to gina and she IMed me dominic's screenname. and he wa son. so we talked for 2 hours and somehow chris left my mind. i didnt even think about him again until mid august. dominic was nice and really sweet... it didnt take long for me to fall for him. but i fall for everyone so thats not saying much.  on the 8th we were going out and we talked on the phone for 6 and a half hours! my all time record.. at least until november. :-D. and by the 13th we had our first date. we saw pirates of the carribean and yeah.. it was fun.. :-D! overall dominic's a great guy.. or at least he was at first. but then things started getting shitty and yeah. it ended. THAT COOLEST THING is that ym's horoscope guide said that i would fall for a pisces and it said the 8th and 13th were lucky days, but the 22nd was a bad one. and i broke up with him on the 22nd. freaky.  the week of my birthday was crazy. i went shopping a lot. jocelyn and i got kicked outta abercrombie for modelling and hara fell in love with cheyenne. kathleen and kalie and i had a lotta fun trying clothes on at anchor blue  OH! Kathleen! she's bundles of fun, and she was my best friend last year. for her b-day i got her 20o bucks worth of stuff including DVDs, CDs and 100 balloons!  ellen got me a shirt from American Eagle and i PROMISED to wear it the first day of school. but before that i wore it on my brithday when nathalie and I saw how to deal. that was such a good movie. outside the theater we saw this old guy selling brownies and we said there was prolly pot in them. lol.  july was an awesome month, and the perfect end to the perfect story was my brand new cell phone. woot woot.  yup yup ~Brandon
     

    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I will remember you, Will you remember me? Don't let your life pass you by. Weep not for the memories. -Sarah McLachlan, "I Will Remember"   the rest of June went by pretty fast. my time was mostly devoted to making collages of pictures from the DC trip and watching seasons 1-4 of buffy. as time went on more and more people knew about my sexual orientation. oo i redecorated my room too. anyway, the day.. well more like night was June 20th. Nathalie and I went to Capitola Book Cafe and waited for the release of Harry Potter 5. it was a lotta fun, and the Shoreline band played for a little bit. there were nasty milk and cookies but it was a really fun night. nathalie and i talked and talked about buffy and jamie added some stuff in.  jamie was really cool.. she went to shoreline last year but now shes gone.. well thats another story that ill save for august.  kristen was there too.. she was a grade lower than us, just like jamie. kristen is short, but shes cool.. and her hair is REALLY fluffy.  anyway, nathalie and i bought our books and then i waited around with kalie and naomi until it was time to go.  kalie's my cousin and naomi is one of her best friends... no explanation needed there.  anyway, staying up 'til midnight was a whole lotta fun and i wouldn't have as much fun doing it until kassie's party in november.  the weeks of June lingered on. two days after i got my book we took a trip down south to LA/Oxnard. i met a really nice guy at the hotel we stayed at. his name was Ben. anyway, i spent most of the trip reading and i finished the twice in eight days.  after we got back, my mom and i talked about my birthday which was less than a month away! i wanted a cell phone and she agreed that i should have one.  the phone rang and i picked it up. Ili. she's pretty cool and i've known her for a really long time. her and bonnie were the first people i told about me being gay. anyway, she told me to come see the play bonnie was in cause there was a gay guy there named Dominic.  "Dominic..." the name rolled over my tounge. "Hot name.."  anyway, i declined her offer to go to the play, but she left me one good thing to think about..  "dominic..."  hehe.. ptfo! -Brandon
     

    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's something unpredictably,  But in the end, it's right.  I hope you had the time of your life." -Green Day, "Good Riddance"   there are some things you have to know about the DC trip.   40 eight graders take a trip to DC and NY at the price of $1600 and some other expenses for souvenoirs.    Day 1     at 4:15 i called janis and told her we were coming to pick her up. the car ride was icy cold. i could feel my stomach twist. my skin hummed with eagerness. we met at the airport around 5:30 at the United terminal, San Jose.   my stomach still feels knarly and i take some pepto bismol. anyway, we check in. my partner is teena davis. i�ve known her since like.. 1st grade..? prolly. she�s really cool and i couldn�t have asked for a better buddy. we check our bags and Mrs. Chavez gives us our boarding passes so we head to the gate. teena got stopped in security cause she had 40 hair pins in from grad. night. good times, good times.   we were all sitting around in the gate.  maya brodkey, ryan juntado, sarah rorvick, lisa vechionne, amanda yabarra, des cook, cerena barros, tessa libby, kate kahoano, kevin grassadonia, delia guerrero, nathalie servin, kevin deming, miguel dolores, teena davis, des cuneo, lizette lopez, jessica llanos, angelica solis, neil osterman, stephen mccon, elena rossman, miki burns, augustine perez, aaron melim, janis dinkins, lexi tenney, aly rumpanos, matt starkey, isais dolores, ashlee dominguez, kassie dogherra, ben fisher, jaime sanchez, ashley sanders, scott glass, dan.. um.. something, maddie flood, valerie getts, roxy rafi-tarie, elena jin and michele chelman.   anyway, we�re all sitting waiting for jocelyn zimniki to arrive at the airport.  now dont get me wrong, jocelyn�s one of the coolest people i noe, but at this point we are all a little angry at her.   she shows up and check�s in and before you noe it we�re on the plane, sweeping off the ground. daredevil played on screen and some of the kids (mikaela) watched it in espanol. ha ha. we ate fruit, took pics and when they turned the fasten seat belt sign off we got up and PARTIED! seriously, the walkways were crowded with kids.   it was crazy! we swapped CDs, played cards, read magazines, desiree cuneo (who i sat next to) even broke her chair.. you noe, the normal stuff. (i was also sitting next to teena.)   when the movie ended a blooper/comedy show came on and then NBC was up after that. lexi sat behind me and we were listening to the grease soundtrack, cause she played Cha-Cha in a play. �it�s raining on prom niight!� i brought that CD just for her.   uh oh! we hit turbulence half way into the flight. the second time we all were rushed to our seats. teena ended up with Maya and Matt behind me, and Maddie was next to me. Des still stayed by the window.   we still swapped CDs, and my graduation mix made elena and mikaela cry. aww. i was having tons of fun and we werent even in DC yet! des shuffled cards while maddie fiddled with the air vents.   the stewardess came around with soda. one ginger ale please. maddie and i took turns throwing pretzels at each other :-D.   the captian turned the sign off and we all moved around. Matt ended up sitting next to me. Des was figuring out her new digital camera, and matt played his gameboy.   we�ve landed at our gate, D16, in the Dulles airport. just imagine, 5 hours ago we left gate C2 at San Jose. I wonder if anyone got there bag sent to Cuba.. ha ha.matt and i had the same time on our watches.. and miki said something about making out with her cheek..? oo yeah, those blanket that had been touched by naked bodies!   we got our bags and yummy candy and then we stepped out into the humidity of the East Coast. it was a relief when our AC�d bus drove up.   We drove passed some famous sites, the Potomac, the Washington Monument, Smithsonian, White House, Federal Reserve and the Department of the Interior (don�t ask...)   There was a parade in front of the White House. lots of military vehicles and what not.  we passed more sites, a car being towed, a bus of old people, American History Musuem, the National Achives and the IRS!!   Starkey made a funny quote �Some people are smart, some people are not...�   our chaperones for the trip were Mrs. Chavez, her son and daughter: Mike and... um... the daughter. and also our librarian, Gayle Rorvick! She�s really cool.   we drove into Union Station and peered at the top of the building. Fire, Electricity, Freedom, Knowlegde, Agriculture and Mechcanics. all things that helped man evolve from the primitive beast he once was.   we j-walked to the train station, where we found a REALLY COOL food court. we bought pizza and talked about how Nathalie got hit on!! by an old guy!! that�s when i first met nathalie. well.. not first met, but first had a real conversation with.  Nathalie and and I got gelato ice cream. mm. and then i bought a pint of lemon ice cream for our room. Ahh! Mrs. Chavez said it would melt before we got back. we had to eat it super duper fast. I ate with Matt, Kassie, Nathalie, Janis, Teena and Aaron, but left to go shopping with Jessica and Amanda. I took the ice cream with me :-D.   We looked at books and finished the ice cream. we even saw a really cool train! we met up with Aaron, Matt, Kassie and Teena on the way out. Jessie said she�d she me on the bus and Matt was like �or in hell!� Then Kassie and I walked back to the bus taking pictures along the way.   on the bus we sang �Baby Got Back� and then our tour with Hopi got under way. We drove to the Jefferson Memorial and i got some cute pics of Miki, Elena, Elena and Lexi. there was a really big ledge too.. Jocelyn almost walked off it.   then we headed to the to the Roosevelt Memorial. Hopi (our tour guide) asked �do we need a bathroom break?�, Jaime yelled �NO! We got cups!� and then Miki was like �Not all of us are like Kevin..�   the FDR memorial was really cool. there were a bunch of waterfalls and we got a bunch of photos. it was really hot tho.. if i stayed outside any longer i would�ve friend like bacon. Matt said the Washington Monument looked possesed.. and then he said sweat was good hair gel. lol.   i�ve known matt since preschool.. more or less. he was friends with my cousin Kalie. his mom knew her grandma or something... yeah.. anyway, he was prolly my first best friend.   anyway, there was a bunch of rain and lightning. rorvick and i were gettin� pretty freaked out.. Matt said a bunch of things �Guys take showers so they don�t smell worse,� and �Maybe we could hit the guy who didnt make a california avenue.�   we went to a supermarket to buy stuff for our room. in line, Matt, Aaron and I stood behind a drunk guy in a dress! he was buyin� Burban! lol. then we got back on the bus and it started to pour like never before.   when we got to the hotel, Karen checked us in and we went to our lucky room. 509!! Mike came by and gave matt his medicine, and then we got ice to chill our drinks.   Kassie and Teena and Ashlee came up to see us when this creepy old man came over and said �I will not tolerate loudness, I have two 8 year olds in a bed and I will not have you waking them out. One loud noise and *snap* I�ll call the front desk and you�re outta here.�   we spent the rest of the night talking to everyone on the phone.   some hot gossip?   Tessa, Kate and Cerena got a security gaurd assigned right outside their door.  Des Cuneo, Nathalie and their room buddie have a fridge! They said we could store stuff in it...  Kassie, Teena and Ashlee got their phones disconnected!   kassie came up to get ice and i saw tape on our door and thought mike had sealed it, but he didnt and anyway, teena sealed it and we got ready for bed. Mike came to tuck us in and that�s when we found out he hadn�t put the tape on! he talked to us about tomorrow and about our �traumatizing� run-in with the old red neck.   everyone went to bed and i stayed up, in the bathtub, writing in my journal.    Day 2    we ended up talking until 2 the night before. the red neck was banging against our wall, but we weren�t being loud.. lol.. in the morning we woke up, showered, and went down to breakfast. I had eggs and cereal.   then we walked to the lobby and found a handicapped bathroom! it was so cool! it opened by itself!! and then we rode the escalators. then on bus, we heard about how elena rossman ran into her closet mirror because she thought it was open.   elena is awesome! i�ve known her since 5th grade... maybe longer.. yeah , i think longer. but anyway, shes really nice and fun and friendly. one time i threw a phone book at her and it hit hurt in the head. i bought her candy though! lol..   we headed to the Veitnam Memorial and we all got carnations to put out for soilders. our first stop was the Korean War memorial. 19 soilders lined up on the tundra. next we visted the Veitname Memorial, with 58,226 names cast in stone, the place felt lonely. empty. names. all names.   i left a carnation under Micheal A. Walter�s grave thinking he might be related to Cooper... that kid is so perverted.   anyway, we walked to the Einstein statue and took pictures. there was a rumor that if you touch his nose, you will get smarter. i touced it... twice... just in case. we got back on the bus. woo, that AC relieved me. oh yeah.. miki is goldylocks.. and janis is a hyena? i dunno, those two are crazy. Hopi had a bunch of sweat stains on her butt... lol..   George Pataki and Chris Cox. New York Senator and California Representative. I met them both! We got out of the bus and headed to the front of the Supreme Court building. thats the judical branch. these hairy guys came up to us.. i think they were making fun of people who wore fur cause they were dressed like cave men.   anyway, we took pictures and i told tessa that her family had come to resuce her from civilization. �Smile and say FAMILY REUNION!� yeah.. you had to be there...   then we went to the Library of Congress. there was a naked statue of Neptune in the front. with a 9 incher! Inside the library we saw a bunch of books and there was a really cool zodiac floor! Nathalie and I love it! There was even the first book ever printed!   we walked to the capitol building and I met Chris Cox from New Port Beach! He shook my hand! It made my day. we went in the building and we saw TONS of priceless artwork. it was amazing. De Soto, Columbus, The Pilgrims, Pocahontas, The Declaration, Saratoga and Yorktown were some of the paintings.   we also saw a bunch of statues and learned a lot about the capitol. then we met george pataki. on the capitol building lawn, there was a protest. �Circumcision is wrong! The foreskin is not a birth defect!� boy, that prolly made the jewish boys behind us very happy. oo! alec is jewish!   yeah, back to story. oh we went to McDonalds next and we have to eat EVERYTHING we bought. I ended up eating everything everyone else didnt want too.. Fries, Milkshakes, McNuggest (Nathalie calls them �Muggets�) and more fries. i left them a souvenior the janitor will never forget. Kassie said �we should take a picture of the fries!� and kate was like �just look in the toilet tomorrow!�   Next we stopped at the White House visitor center. I picked p some stuff for Mr. Sullivan AND! i got a coloring book! yay! we walked back to the bus and stopped at the White House. I got a stick from the lawn! it was really cool. and i saw the West Wing! That is a really good show...! there were a lot of squrriels too.. we walked past Alexander Hamilton and the Treasury Building and we even saw a monument to General Sherman! it reminded me of Gone with the Wind.   we then went to the Holocaust Museum and watched a story about a boy named Daniel. it was really sad. there was even a little walk through thing and Lisa V. was my partner. Lisa is really cool.. and really nice too.   then we went to the old post office and went up a glass elavator. it was ok, the veiw was kinda weird, but hey, i had Kevin grassadonia�s booty scrunched close to me for most of it, so it was great. coming down the elevator, teena scared me to death. we left the old post office and headed to..   THE INTERNATIONAL SPY MUSEUM! way lamer than it sounds... i got a cool shirt tho. and i beat kevin g. a lot though at this weird game. ha ha i won. we got to climb through an air duct too! it got really boring.. but then there was this thing where you could see ur house on a satelitte! it was awesome! i bought a sweet t-shirt that says �Deny Everything� yay!   it started to rain and we got back on the bus. soon we stopped at a pizza place. matt got cheese poured in his hair and i made kassie laugh by saying �Cheese Me� when the waiter came around. Well we headed to the Lincoln memorial after that. we took a bunch of pictures and learned a lot about old Abe. He was really tall...   we went shopping at this little place with a bunch of street vendors and the rain began to pour. we got back on the bus and headed to the Kennedy Center for Fine Arts. there were flags from every nation except Lybia, Iran, Iraq, Cuba and North Korea. we also got to see into an opera and we saw a hall of states. then we went up a balcony and took pic.   Next, we drove to the Iwo Jima memorial, where Janis and I were the tour guides. fun stuff. we took a bunch of pictures of the six soilders raising the flag and then we just wanted to go home and sleep.   when we got to the hotel, Janis and I used the phones to try and call Ellen. it as busy, but we met these 2 girls and janis gave them her room number. When i got to my room, the door was open and Aaron and Matt were gone, probably getting ice. Lexi and Elena called and told us to go downstairs to a party.   we brought candy and soda and MM they had cheez-its. we also got to raid Mrs. Chavez�s room and get free food. then we went back to our rooms and tried to get to sleep. but instead we ended up talking until three. we were really tired in the morning.    Day 3    FRIDAY THE THIRTEENTH!!   today was the trip to Arlington national cemetery. after a quick breakfast we were taken into a world of sad sculptures and gravestones. we visited the eternal flame and the tomb of the unknown solider. the hike was a long one, but the changing of the guards was.. for the most part... worth it. it was kinda dramatic.. but it�s to honor the dead so i guess its ok. i liked it.   all in all arlington was good. after the cemetary, we headed for the washington monument. we rode the elevator to the top. well, the 100 floor. the look down was 500 feet! it was really cool, we got to see so much! after the monument we walked to the Smithsonian where we said �Aloha� to our tour guide.   we got to travel around the �Mall� which is the term used for the block on which the Smithsonian museums sit. We breaked and picked buddies. Ashlee and I headed for the Natural history museum and headed all the way down to the food court. we got soo much food!   i�ve known ashlee since kindergarten..? yeah, she�s really cool and funny. and she likes to read a lot, so if i ever read a book then her and i can have discussions about it.. its funner than you think :-D   anyway, after we looked at a bunch of gems and the Hope Diamond. 52.27 karat from India. there were a lot of crystals and stuff and i got a sweatshirt from the american history museum. we went across the street and walked down to the art museum. we bought a few bottles of soda. we took pictures in front of a fountain and then went into the air and space museum. thats where we met up with Janis, Nat, Valerie, Ashley and Lisa.  Nathalie and I ditched Janis and Ashlee and hid behind a fence thing that we thought was tinted (we can see out but they cant see in) Janis and Ashlee were walking aroundon the floor below. suddenly they look up at us and wave. Nathalie screams �I THOUGHT THEY COULDN�T SEE IN!�   we continued walking and we got in a WW2 plane! how fuun!! we checked out some rooms with planets in them and we looked at some space shuttles too.   at five we met matt, ben, aaron, janis, ashlee and everyone else in front of the museum. it was scorching hot but the bus came soon and we drove to the Department of Printing and Engraving. we saw moola being made and we checked out the gift shop.  on the ceiling there were motion censors, and my head almost set them off.   after the money place we drove outta DC. we drove to virgina and stopped at the pentagon mall where we went shopping! ee! ashley sarah and I went to abercrombie and then viki�s. it was so much fun! they had really cute undies in fcuk. then we went back to the bus, running through the rain to get to it.   back at the hotel, we all got dressed in our bathing suits and went down to the pool. i sat outside and wrote in my notebook since the rain had died down. i walked with elena back to the lobby but i realized i had forgotten my key. we went to the front desk to ask for another one, but they wouldnt make one for me.   teena walked me back to the pool and we got aarons key. i went into the elevator and teena said �be right back.� so i held the elevator and this guy came in and was like �going up?� and i was all �yep..� and then a while later he got out and teena came back and got in and he was like �going up?� and she was like �sorry.� by the time i got back to the 4th floor, elena was done showering and we all hung out. it was another hall party! i went in kevin�s room and we talked and yeah, it was fun.   i ran back up to my room and slipped a note under the door for aaron and matt. i also brought candy downstairs. the hall party was gettin� hot and i ran back to my room to get soda right when matt and aaron got back. matt and aaron went down to the party but at 10 we had to get back to our rooms and tuck in.    Day 4    that night we packed and packed and after we had cleaned our rooms we watched drew carey. i fell asleep tho and i slept like a log... or maybe a rock... i would say a baby but i guess babies dont sleep super well. oh yeah! that night i got a call from my mom and thats when i found out she was PREGNANT! the baby�s due February 16th! see ya all at the baby shower :-D!   anyway, the next day we woke up late and i brought a soda down for breakfast. when we were in the lounge i opened the soda and it SPRAYED all over me. i went up to my rooom and changed, and headed back to breakfast, but then kassie ran into me with a plate of eggs.. so i showered and changed again.   then matt came up to the room and we all brought our luggage down to the bus. wihtin a few hours the bus was moving and we had left virgina for good. we watched night at the roxburry and nathalie, matt and i laughed SO HARD! kassie slept in the hallway. crazy. but anyway, i fell asleep during the movie, but nathalie and matt�s talking woke me up.   after the movie we made a pit stop in Delaware. i missed Maryland! we took a bunch of pictures in front of the �Big Guy Restraunt� statue. when we got back on the bus we drove to New Jersey while watching Orange County. I love that movie! We laughed so hard. after the movie we were on the border of New Jersey and after we went through a tunnel we ended up in Manhattan, New York!!   we finally made it! we stopped at our hotel and dropped off our bags. our tour guide arrived at the new york part of the tour started. first stop: Texas and Texas for lunch! after that we bought some stuff from the local street vendors and we spent most of our time walking around and looking at the sights.   we bought some shirts and then we walked to radio city music hall and then to the donald trumpt building. thats when we went in to take a tour of NBC studios. it was a lot of fun and we saw the SNL set and even some previews for Will and Grace! i bought a will and grace shirt from the gift shop.   we headed back to the hotel and the rain started to pour. my bag started to rip and right when we got in the door it fell apart. woot woot. we went upstairs and all got fabbed up. we looked so perfect and we walked to Chili�s in our formal wear. i had this cute brown american eagle umbrella!   anyway, at chili�s we all sat around and talked. ashley sanders and i danced to genie in a bottle, the spanish version. then we walked to the New Amsterdam theater. we got into the Lion King and everything was goregous. the play was beautiful and at the end i cried. it was amazing.   we walkd to times square after the play. i made some jokes about the hookers and then we all got together and took a picture. on the way we saw lisa leslie from the sparks, and before the picture we saw chopper!! he was really cute, and nathalie got a hug! there were a bunch of pigeons.. ee.. i hate birds.. anyway, the picture was good but i look shitty so, no, im not showing you.   we walked back and saw billy joel!! �we didnt start the fire!� that�s like mr. sullivan�s favorite song. anyway, we got back to the hotel and we watch SNL before going to sleep.    Day 5    we went across the street to this greek diner where i got pancakes. yummy. then we walked to the subway! it was so cool! it was all dirty and stuff and we were going really really fast and then it stopped and i fell over.   we got a few feet away from battery park. we saw the globe that was in front of the WTC and it was really emotional. we went and waited in castle clinton for a ferry to the islands. we met a strange but funny guy and played the limbo with him.   then we went to the island ferry and took a ride to Liberty Island. on the way we met a bug named billy and ashlee got kinda pissed off. then at ellis island, i was talking about how chiuahuas were gonna attack miki and i was like �yo quiero taco mikaela.�   miki is awesome! i�ve known her since 3rd grade. we both had calero but switched out to sherwood! tons of fun! shes really cool.. and tottally blonde :-D   anyway, when we got into ellis island i looked for some immigrants from my family. then ashlee and nathalie got me and we went outside and had a picnic. kassie climbed a wall and the security guard told her to climb to the top. she was gonna do it but he said he was kidding so oh well to that.   we got back on the ferry and got back in battery park. we walked down wall street and i got a picture of me on a bull :-D !!! then we walked to this deli and ate. after we went to ground zero. it was a reflective moment and it was an emotional experience.   after that we took a subway ride to centeral park. there were a lot cool plants and picture to be taken. i even say a statue of balto. oh and teena started to get dehydrated..   we went to virgin records and bought CDs and posters and we were gonna go to MTV studies, but we went back to the hotel and got dressed up for our trip to the empire state building.   we took a trip to chinatown and little italy. the restaurant was REALLY fancy and i could barely eat anything it was so fancy. all i ate was the cheese. yummy. i ate nathalie�s cheese too. then we went bargaining in chinatown. i got kassie and teena bags which were originally $30 each down to $28 for both. ashlee also got a cute necklace.   it was really cold out, and the over look from the top of the Empire state building was really pretty. the sunset was so nice. the line town was REALLY long, but kate and i cut and then in the elevator we sang songs, like that one that never ends :-D then i was almost hit by a car.. and the sign said �walk� !   we went back to the hotel and it took a while to fall asleep. it was our last night of the trip and i was kinda sad to be leaving.    Day 6    the last day was perfect. we woke up and went to this huge place for breakfast. teena poured sugar in my hair and then i attacked her with it! good times! kate and tessa started laughing when i did that.   anyway, we walked around more and got to see the today show being filmed. it as a lotta fun. nathalie and i went to starbucks and got really good hot cocoa. did you noe starbucks was named after the guy from moby dick? he drank a lotts coffee.. lol   we walked to a really pretty church and kevin grassadonia prayed. it was so cute. lol  after the church we went to this place and then mrs. chavez said we could go do whatever we wanted for 2 hours. shopping in new york! woo hoo! we went to F A O Schwartz and the Disney Store. it was soo much fun. we were the first customers in F A O Schwartz and they clapped for us! go brandon and kassie! the store was amazing.   after shopping we took a walk past playboy enterprises and down to the Hard Rock cafe. it was the perfect lunch and the ride to the airport was wonderful. teena and dan fell asleep next to each other and they were kissing!! lol!   we waited at the airport and i had everyone sign the back of my times square pic. thenw e got on the short plane ride to chicago. i sat next to a guy writing a porn novel and a fat guy who was really paranoid!! matt was over on the other side and yeah... it was way lame and way creepy, and i took out a vomit bag and the guy next to me freaked out! it was so funny! well, yeah.. i still have that vomit bag..   jocelyn and i went to get mcdonalds while everyone else waited at the other gate. i came so close to telling her i was gay.. but i decided not to. we ended up sitting next to each other on the plane back to San Jose, but i switched with kate and sat next to mikaela and maya.   the flight home was fun.. and sad... �how to lose a guy in 10 days� made me cry.. and then when we were landing miki and i were holding each other and crying alot. it was so sad. but it was the perfect end to eighth grade.   i�m gonna knock on wood when i say this, but after that trip my life was perfect. everything was amazing. i dont noe what happened.. but something changed. at the trip was the best.   i gave hugs to everyone at the baggage claim, then i ran out and met my parents at the car.   �how was it?� they asked  �wonderful..�   later  -brandon!   
     

    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      As we go on, we remember  All the times we had together  And as our lives change, from whatever  We will still be friends forever. -Vitamin C, "Graduation"     the summer was a new beginning. no, no, june was a new beginning. the days leading up to the last day were crazy. we had to get all our work back, and I even got a letter from 5th grade.   it started with bonnie and ili. they were the first people I told. that I liked guys. It was scary at first, but after it felt really good. like masterbating for the first time. ok� that was a little too much. :-) so what started as small got bigger and bigger. graduation practices and.. lol.. joel marshall.. filled my thoughts for the last days. suddenly it was grad. night. everything seemed so perfect� except Mrs. Zahrobsky�s fucked up balloon arch. well yeah it was beautiful.   and the dance was way awesome. the theme was Hollywood, and boy was it a night with the stars. I told a bunch of people that I was.. well� you noe the word. The night was ending.. tears were falling.. and dances were being danced. Shout outs to des cuneo, lexi!, mikki, maddie, amanda and naomi for havin� fun with me on the dance floor.   the night ended, and janis and I ran around givin� everyone hugs and saying our last goodbyes. I still remember elena rossman asking me for a hug even though she knew we would see each other the next day. You noe I never really realized how much I was gonna miss these people until after they were out of my life. But you cant live in the past forever.   I dropped Janis at home, promising to call her before I picked her up the next day. And then I went home and passed out on my bed. it was over. middle school was over. it was finally over.   
     

    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm really really hot, Everytime my record drops, Radio says I won't stop, 'Cause I'm killin' them. -Missy Elliot, "I'm Really Hot"   name: ~*~ BRANDON ~*~   gender: male :-)   height: 6'1" the doctor says   hair color: its brown.. but its prolly gonna change cause nathalie just opened up a concetration camps for insects and she's gonna test repellent on me..   eye color: green/ hazel.. they're so pretty!!   location: ~*SaNtA cRuZ*~   fears: fears? birds, forgetting stuff, spiders and things i cant remember...    Have I ever?   peed my pants: the last time i saw a picture of tina doin' the hokey pokey   cheated on someone: well it never was offical..   fallen of the bed: i fell of a couch.. i've fallen of the couch a lot...   fallen for a relative: yeeah... noooo   had plastic surgery: well that quiz said i got breast inplants... what can i say, im very passionate..   failed a grade: never! woot woot   broken someone's heart: it was an accident... and the heart was made outta clay... but harry had a happie v-day anyway :-D sorry kassie!   had your heart broken: dominic :'-(.. just kidding   had a dream come true: im livin' a dream.   had sex: mm mm, nope   had a lap dance: suzie's party.. the third one..   done something you regret: so many things!   cheated on a test: yeah tinas... WELL NATHALIE CHEATED ON MINE!   been raped: hehe almost on friday...   had a broken body part: my heart!    Currently?   wearing: abercrombie clothes!   listening: to nathalie make plans for monday   eating: orange juice.. mmm   feeling: happy.. like always   reading: nathalie's horoscope   located: santa cruz~~   chatting with: dominic and ryan.. kinda..   craving: you dont wanna noe...   should: work on my reports... or fix my blog... or watch more buffy.. i like buffy!    Do you?   brush your teeth: um.. duh?   like anybody: you'd be surprised   have any piercing: nope   drive: hell yah!   believe in Santa Clause: ho ho ho   wear deodorant: yah, i think it's one of those important things....no one likes a stinky poodle... 'cept.. maybe another stinky poodle   ever get off the damn computer: duh to sleep and go to school    Friends   who have you known the longest: kalie, naomi bradford and nathalie, cause we're family!   do you belong to a crew: mmhm... i belong to soquel!   do you hang out with the opposite sex: mmhm, girls are funny and they have belly buttons.   are you popular: i dont wanna sound concieded.. but yeah... kinda..   do you trust your friends: yup. of course.   are you a good friend: some what neglective... but who isnt?   can you keep a secret: yah, if it's really personal, but if it's stupid i won't.. that's right ellen! i'm telling everyone about your hairy teeth! get new sweaters you fat lil girl! BOO!   The last person you...   hugged: natalie and ivy and people   IM-ed: dominic   talked to on the phone: nathalie, dominic and michael   yelled at: hmmm my computer... hey at least i dont talk to my pants!   checked out: alec   fell in love: 3 guesses...   tripped on something: patrick   turned down: so many...    Personal   what do you want to be when you grow up: bigger   what was the worst day of your life: when i forgot to wear black shoes with my outfit and i wore the green ones, but then i changed to flip flops so it was perfect!   what is your most embarrassing story: i don't remember....and if i did i wouldn't tell u   what was the best day in your life:the past 4 months!   what comes first in your life: money.. men.. and my friends,   do you have a gf/bf/crush: tons   what are you most afraid of: dominic!! jk~ um.. being poor and a loser and unpopular... or having someone close abercrombie!   if you had an extra set of eyes, where would you put them: on my face, moron.   what do you usually think of before going to bed: boys.    Favorite?   Movie: Bring It On! and Orange County...   Song:  -pass the dutch  -milkshake  -me against the music  -lady marmalade   Relatives: nathalie :-D   Sport: volleyball and all sports are fun when ur having fun and not in p.e.   Vacation spot: hawaii or new york   Ice cream flavor: ice cream is ice cream, no matter what the flavor.   Fruit: all berries...   Candy: lollipops   Car: BMW convertible   Class: every class.. especially english   Holiday: christmas.... and summer   Day of the week: friday, saturday   Color: all colors of the rainbow   Name for girl or boy: Girl-Joceyln, Boy-Alec    Do you?   Like to give hugs: to everyone   like to walk in the rain: yes   sleep with clothes: pjs   prefer black or blue pens: all colors   dress up for Halloween: mmm yah   have a job: i want one.. cha-ching   like to travel: yah   sleep on side, tummy, or back: i don't know...all?   think you're attractive: no   Want to marry: when it's legal   ever have the falling dream: falling, like off a building   have stuffed animals: a lot...from New York   go on vacation: yepperz..    What do you think about...   Abortion: if it's nessecary   Bill Clinton: better than bush   Smoking: pointless   Eating disorders: will stop world hunger   Suicide: decrease over population   Summer: tan time   Tattoos: nah.. cause they're permanent.   Piercings: some are hot.. like cartalige peircings..   Make-up: helps   Drinking: mmm   Guys: cuties   Girls: fun fun fun    This or that (Or the other thing)   pierced nose or tongue: i don't like either   be serious or funny: both   single or taken: livin up the single life   simple or complicated: a lil of both   sugar or salt: depends   silver or gold: ill just take anything that glistens   tongue or belly button ring: belly button rings   chocolate or flowers: chocolates..flowers, you keep them around for awhile and then they die...now chocolates u can eat   angels or miracles: miralces, cause they're perfect!   color or black and white photos: both   Sunrise or sunset: sunrise, another beautiful day.   MMs or Skittles: skittles   Stay up late or sleep in: both   taller members of the opposite sex: yah   sun or moon: moon   Diamond or ruby: dunno..   Left or right: right   vanilla or chocolate: i like both   kids or no kids: mmm i guess kids...they move out eventually   half empty or half full: either, as long as it's something tasty.   give or receive: receive   lace or satin: satin   a year of hot sex life or a lifetime friendship: lifetime friendship, cause there are always benefits :-D   happy or sad: happy   wonder or amazement: amazement..   blondes or brunettes: i don't discrimanate.    Girls only   what do you look for in a guy: personality and a sense of humor and cuteness...   sweet or innocent guy: mmm sweet   smart or athletic guy: a lil bit of both   favorite cologne on a guy: anything...   best gift a guy could give: a million dollars? jk...i don't know, i guess like of ppl say, "the thought of it counts" but i guess if i have to answer it'd be his love. that's all that really matters. that and sex.   Flowers, sweet or wasteful: sweet   Sweetest guy you know: dominic? but yeh.. hes my daddy    Other kind of questions   what's your favorite kind of tree: a palm tree   out of all of your friends, who has the coolest room: nathalie! viva la ants!   When you look at a person with lime green tights on...what do you say: i dont say anything... i run away... 
     

    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I know you wanna hit that, I know you wanna hit that hit that. -The Offspring, "Hit That"   I SAVED A BUNCH OF FUNNY and MEANINGFUL andCOOLIO STUFF YOU GUYS HAVE SAID, SUNG AND HEARD,  SO I THOUGHT I'D PUT IT ON HERE&gt;&gt;  ENJOY :-)!   Nathalie- "Don't get slappy, just take this pill and you'll get happy!"  Nathalie- "Ivan, wanna see a trick? Go away and I'll be happy."  Tina- "SHAKE THAT THING MISS!"  Nathalie- "You noe what's scary? Michael Jackson.."  Nathalie- "I think we should all go disco dancing.."  jackorcan: i think about you all the time jackorcan: i see you in my dreams SCnaomes331: really?? SCnaomes331: i thought u wre gay DrPepperChpstick: I actually know that song!  DrPepperChpstick: shake that thing ms kana kana  SCWonderWoman: ahh it's dark upstairs SCWonderWoman: i don't wanna go.....boogy man might get me SCWonderWoman: do u fish? SCWonderWoman: i did, i got a fish and never fished again jackorcan: what song is that? SCWonderWoman: lol.....haha.....it's not a song  Sc cHErrIe bUg11: well you should've used your gay super powers to stop her  AiMsStar125: and you can always...have harry as a bf  me- "I interveiwed naomi and she said "you gotta have connections."  alec- "or they'd just.. you noe.. kill each other.."  christine- "is it girl scout cookie season again? god.. and i wanted to lose weight.."  G_ F_CK Y_ _ RS_LF Would you like to buy a vowel?   Annie... fruit punch! Haha that was a good one.  C'mon pass the dutch baby, Shake shake shake your stuff baby. Pop that, pop that, jiggle that fat! Don't stop, get it 'til your clothes get wet.  jackorcan: SUCK IT BITCH Sc cHErrIe bUg11: lol Sc cHErrIe bUg11: omg i love you brandon  jackorcan: Johnny Sucks Ducks MoonStar4U2NV: not uh!! jackorcan: DOWN WITH THE DEPP MoonStar4U2NV: I love him!! jackorcan: leave me out in the cold then! MoonStar4U2NV: I love you and I dont want u for your sex!!!  jackorcan: if shes that much of a bitch beat her down... jackorcan: even if the shit she says is true! Wut Wut Your Mom: i luv u 2 brandon  jackorcan: when i move, you move SCWonderWoman: just like that jackorcan: when i move, you move rainbowsparkplug: just like that jackorcan: when i move you move... DrPepperChpstick: just like that? Wut Wut Your Mom: hell ya, hey DJ bring that back... Teena9: Stand up! SiMpLyMe115k: stand up... SCWonderWoman: "stand up"!  jackorcan: DO U THINK IM A WHORE!? rainbowsparkplug: yah. i do.  jackorcan: am i a whore? Sc cHErrIe bUg11: hell yeah  jackorcan: am i a whore? MissMichely315: well kinda  jackorcan: am i a whore? SCnaomes331: omg SCnaomes331: yes!!!!!!! SCnaomes331: ur so gross  jackorcan: am i a whore? DrPepperChpstick: ok possibly   jackorcan: am i a whore? CookieKat 482: i dont know CookieKat 482: are you?  jackorcan: can i get a wut wut, can i get a wut? Wut Wut Your Mom: wut wut jackorcan: yay! :-D Wut Wut Your Mom: can i get a wut wut Wut Wut Your Mom: fine no luv Wut Wut Your Mom: its kuz im white huh  this chinese lady was very lonely. one night she was taking a walk on the beach when she met a chinese man. they got to noe each other very well and one night it got PRETTY steamy!! so the chinese lady got pregnant and and the chinese man started to get nervous.. but anyway, they decided to go ahead and have the child. so the lady gives birth and the baby comes out black. the chinese man is like "what!?" and the chinese lady is like "lets name it what what wong!"  word up moooofoooo...! you're so fat you dont have periods, you have EXCLAMATION POINTS! and tomorrow me, god and jesus are gonna go watch a movie.. i love it, i love it, i LOVE it~ cause she got hit by the swing.. and her body is still stuck there.. ew! a seal and that mans naked! i hafta establish my social life before i die..SAY WHAAA? i vill be baach.. what can i say.. im very passionate. is this black history month? im not even being a stupid.. brunette.. i had a DB moment, huh? who is your daddie.. and what does he do? squigals~~ you stupid! no you.. "im cutting you off" "did it hurt?" phone green, i pink it up.. i say "yellow!" i wish i had EATEN something so i could THROW UP IN YOUR FACE! too bad it wasnt a hearttack... ^ ^ ^ ^ ^ ^ ^ ^ ^ ^  nat and brandon jokes  Brandon- "Alec's jewish?" Hannah- "Yup, he's a pure bred, like me. He's going to become *jewish accent* a nice jewish doctor and then marry me." Brandon- "Not if I marry him first!" Ivy- "Jesus, you make it sound like a race!" Brandon + Hannah- "IT IS!"  Mrs. Keplinger- "What did they do on Sundays in France?" Christine- "Burn the witches?"  Mrs. Keplinger- "Why is the king coming to my house?" Christine- "To make fun of you?"   Caroline- "You and rex are such a cute couple! It's like "aw"!"  Alec- "It's gettin hot in herre."  TINA'S REMIX~! Girls just wanna have fun, oh girls just wanna have fun! When the workin' day is done, girls just wanna have fun, they wanna have fun Under the sea. under the sea, darlin' it's better down where its wetter take it from me ;-) ;-) ;-) up on the shore they work all day, and girls just wanna have fun, oh girls just wanna have fuuun. when the workin' day is done, don't cry for me argentina, the truth is i never left you. all thru my wild days. my mad existence, i kept my promise and girls jsut wanna have fun, oh girls just wanna have fun cause oh mickey you're so fine, ur so fine you blow my mind, and girls, they wana have fun!!  mom, r u makin' chicken, cause it smells good - Nathalie  dominic - ill call you back brandon- u never call me back! dominic- todays a new day! and im calling you back!  i heard some guy from AOL got sued cause he kept looking at peoples screennames and changing them.. -monica  mr. shonick- whats colder than russia? tiana- ice cold!  nathalie-- what style do you want? future, rustic, modern, light, squares, misty, special? christina- special brandon- special ed!  nathalie- i dont wanna name it monkey, thats retarded. look at all that marajunana...  ScCherrieBug11: she's in the camera ScCherrieBug11: well get her outta there  jackorcan: he saw me jackorcan: we saw him jackorcan: then katy and i ran away  ScCherrieBug11: and i have a test on it ScCherrieBug11: ughhh jackorcan: if i had a quarter for everytime u said that... jackorcan: i would buy a bakery ScCherrieBug11: lol ScCherrieBug11: you are so funny jackorcan: really? jackorcan: ur not just saying that so i'll help u study, r u?  jackorcan: dude, hes so gay jackorcan: he did the "fag jump" scbuttercup81: what is that? jackorcan: like jackorcan: when gay guys get excited jackorcan: they're all like "yay!" and they bounce up and down jackorcan: and like... yeah... jackorcan: in public jackorcan: (around other people)   ("`-''-/").___..--''"`-._  6_ 6 ) `-. ( ).`-.__.`) (_Y_.)' ._ ) `._ `.``-..-'  _`--'_..-_/ /--'_.' ,'  I'm gettin' ready to pounce...  AND SURVEY SAYS.. Q: Brandon- "You get your test back from your teacher and you get a D, you go up to him and say?"  A:  Nathalie- "Why the hell did you give me a D on this test. You know i did better than this thing!"   Ellen- "Ugh...thanks for another D to add to my collection."  Naomi- "Just because you gave me a D doesnt make you a God or something."  Ivy- "All you teachers are twisted, you laugh at seeing kids fail like this. But i will prove to them all; MWHAHAHAH!!"   Tina- "YOU GAVE ME A D. WHAT IS YOUR PROBLEM. I will conquere the world and own you."  How could anyone ever tell you, You were anything less than beautiful. How could anyone ever tell you, You were less than whole. How could anyone fail to notice, That your loving is a miracle. How deeply your connected To my soul. *to my soul*  ~*~  Sex is good! sex is fine! Doggy-style or sixty-nine, Just for fun or gettin' paid, We all go nuts when we get laid... SO if in life you don't succeed, FUCK the world, then come fuck me!  heres a story of a girl livin in a lonely world a hidden note a secret crush a lil boy who talks too much and im standin in the crowd  and when you smile i check you out but u dont even know my name your too busy playin games and i want you to know if you lose your way i wont let you go if i cut my hair  if i change my clothes  will you notice me if i bite my lip if i say hello will you notice me  whats it gonna take for you to see get you to notice me  ScCherrieBug11: fat rex running with a football ScCherrieBug11: ok..i never said that ScCherrieBug11: shush.  scbuttercup81: it must have been the homework gods... scbuttercup81: sometimes they r good to me.... and sometimes they give me hell scbuttercup81: but i have made my offerings of extra credit scbuttercup81: so they have backed off  Pigeondude: hows it goin' old chap (english accent) Pigeondude: lol Pigeondude: top the evening want to stop in to get a pot of tea  TINA REMIXED IT AGAIN~!! glow! my love is like woah, so dont call me baby. the way you move... mebbe you should think twice... cause whats luv, if you're not the one... Aint it funny? I'm bouncin of the walls again... the thong song is just what i need to rock with you... the smooth criminal is dirrty and he dont wanna try no more, so mintority, get low and hit 'em up style..   Wut Wut Your Mom: my milk shake brings all da boys 2 the yard jackorcan: and theyre like is betta than urs Wut Wut Your Mom: damn rite its betta than urs jackorcan: i kud teach u but id haf 2 charge  MoonStar4U2NV: I said no and she was like who's is it and I said its brandons and she was like is that a girl and I said no and she was like why does she have a will and grace sweater and I was like he's gay and she was all oh jackorcan: lol!!!  jackorcan: golgi apparatus scbuttercup81: si jackorcan: ?? jackorcan: is that like jackorcan: some kinda porn? scbuttercup81: you bet...  Left Behind Chorus: Quaiken4Clay: It may seem like I don't care and you don't mean anything to me but no matter where I go or what I do even if your not there you'll never, ever be left behind  scbuttercup81: i blocked him scbuttercup81: that was sick! scbuttercup81: lol scbuttercup81: breath sarah scbuttercup81: i'm over it now  SLEEPING BEAUTY.. AWW: she is indeed most wonderus fair gold of sunshine in her hair lips that shame the red red rose in ageless sleep she finds repose the years roll by but a hundred years to a steadfast heart are but a day, and now the gates of the dungeon part and our prince is free to go his way off he rides on his noble steed a valiant figure, straight and tall. to wake his love with love's first.. and prove that true love conquers all  God made rivers, God made lakes, God made you, but hey we all make mistakes!!    LET'S REVEIW: MONDAY- Teen Millionaire slips, falls, and breaks 10 thousand dollar nose. TUESDAY- Self-Proclaimed "Pop Princess" picked up for public peeing. WEDNESDAY- A-list actor caught wearing female co-star's costumes. THURSDAY- Cute boy toy rockers lip-locked all night long at awards show. FRIDAY- Married studly sports star canoodles barely legal babe. SATURDAY- Another Sex Tape. SUNDAY- On-again Off-again couple.. On. Karat count now 7. the best week ever. Vh1's look back at the seven days that rocked the world. last week. CATCH IT TONITE AT 11:30!  </post></Blog>