<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>27,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Uh oh, I have ensured the soiling of my reputation (if there is any) at school.  I have submitted not only one.. but TWO pictures of me playing Counter-Strike at a LAN party for the yearbook peeps.  Oh boy.  Why did I do that...? I'm not sure, but I guess it will be funny to look at in several years and say "Why oh why did I do that to myself."  And of course other people will still be laughing when they are middle-aged and still trucking along at whatever career they end up in.  Of course I had to go to "Xtremez II" (a nearby LAN cafe)  to play some CS with my usual buds.  It was awesome.  Although the competition isn't always very good.  It takes me forever to warm up though so I end up doing bad for about 10-15 minutes.  That's impressive for me!  Anyways, no one cares about this so I'll move on to the usual random crap.  You know that guy Macbeth?  I think some Bonespear guy or some (name here)spear or other wrote it... Hmm, the name escapes me... : )  MACTEST! MACTEST! MACTEST! *Banquo raises his outstretched grasping hand towards Macbeth out of the dinner platter*AH!  Not the final Macbeth test... MACFINAL!  *Keyzer slaps Drew and Colin in the chest repeatedly*  *Keyzer laughs far too much for his own actions*  By the way, for you geeks: New roll-up keyboard on the way soon to my humblehome from ThinkGeek.com: http://www.thinkgeek.com/computing/input/keyboards/5a7f/  Que Chevere! Y Que Caliente!  Te amo Justo Lamas!  Boy, that concert was... neat!  What an awesome day, again!  Crew and school? Awesome at the same time? d00d!? I'm a geek.  I need that shirt proclaiming that....  I just have to have it. Someday. Well, either that or a gamer-type one, both links below *props to ThinkGeek.com*  http://www.thinkgeek.com/tshirts/gaming/6119/ http://www.thinkgeek.com/tshirts/generic/6111/  AND! El oh el??? : http://www.thinkgeek.com/tshirts/kids/5ace/action/20ffd07/ 
      
</post>
<date>26,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Whooie! This week is almost over already.  I sure have been keeping busy with homework!  Must have blinded me to the time. Hmph.  Well, it sure is good that tommorow is Friday.  Fridays are always awesome! ALWAYS!  Got a few new games to keep me occupied in my free time:  Beyond Good  Evil -- in progress Star Wars: Knights of the Old Republic -- in progress Need for Speed: Underground -- in progress Deus Ex 2: Invisible War -- beat in 3 days Prince of Persia 2 -- beat in 2 days  Contact me if you want any of the above and I can get you the goods!  And for those of you that have no interest whatsoever, just ask me to yell out something random and it's bound to be... HILARIOUS! AH! Well, you already knew that... I mean Keyzer can only say things that are... AWESOME! Or... HILARIOUS! AH!  iSearch was coolio.  I need to see my grade on it.  Soon.  Now!  Curse you Mr. Webster and your darned baby taking attention from us oh-so-good students and our work! BAH!  Oh, I have to shout kudos! This time to myself!  Kudos to Keyzer for passing out on migraine medication!  Luckily I'd rather be sleeping like a dead man than having that crummy migraine again... I just said crummy. Cool.  Rad!  Later my friends.
      
</post>
<date>23,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, today was mildly interesting.  Not really much out of the ordinary besides a newly found large amount of homework upon arrival back to school.  I've managed to get such an inordinate amount that I am unable to attend crew for the day.  : /  I really hate missing practice although I'm unsure if my coach is there today or not... either way missing practice is no fun, especially on a "row day" (in which we row of course).  The most prominent of this homework is the iSearch paper (boy, that sounds Mac-ish) which entails quite a bit of, well, searching.  Primarily tedious research.  I happened to choose Counter-Strike and some other elements of the online game industry and it has so far turned out fairly informative and interesting indeed.   I just bought a new mouse and i love it to death:  Microsoft Wireless Optical Mouse (Metallic Red).  The metallic red color matches my PC's case quite well.  In addition the scroll wheel (also tilts from side-to-side; Microsoft's tilt-wheel technology) is just major sexah.  Grips well in my hand; very contoured.  I h3arts t3h mu0s3!  Go buy one.  Now!!  And now the homework.  There still remains much to do.  See most of you soon and chat with the rest of you later. Tah Tah.
      
</post>
<date>19,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yarg! Bikeriding is awesome.  I managed to cake about 2 or 3 pounds of mud on me today when I went out bikeriding with a good crew friend of mine.  Afterwards we proceeded to practice and had to work out a whole bunch, as usual.  That was all in good fun, especially when we show up at practice covered in such a rediculous amount of mud.  Whew!  I shall soon have Deus Ex 2 for those of you who know of it.  Should be a decent game.  I'm sure it can't live up to it's predecessor though. w00t.  Deus Ex was awesome!  I heart Kate, again. (Sorry I had to do it)  Boy, what an emotional blog.  I love it.  See most of you back at school pretty soon.  I'm trying not to think of it at the moment! ; D
      
</post>
<date>14,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Boy, this break has been quite good.  Of course I have to send kudos to someone, so that would have to be San Juan School District... I never thought I'd do that but hey, what the heck, they're truly good people in the long run and I'm feeling generous with my positive compliments.  In addition, props to crew for keeping me busy. Heh.  Life is pretty good.  Uh oh, slipping into one of those blogs... Yeck, my blog is better, well as of now.  Although I have been sorta busy over the break with crew and all so I haven't had much of a chance to post...  Yet somehow when I have school I always seem to find some time.  Odd.  I'm really appreciating this break.  It's awesome.  All it needs is a huge LAN party of some sort! w00t! I'm still realizing I'm off from school and how awesome that is...  Although I sure have noticed that I'm much more full of energy at 10am instead of darned 7am in the morning.  The sun being fully over the horizon in the morning is a very good thing.  No more cold.  Anyways,  I have to shout at Christina:  Good luck on the quest for erm... you know ;) May!?!? Geez! Well.  I = Never. w00t. :)
      
</post>
<date>14,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Oh the joys of Valentine's Day.... *sighs*  Love is in the air, everywhere I look around!  (You know that song...)  Well,  today was eventful indeed.  Had a good row in the morning at 7 and then went with all my teammates to have some breakfast at Gold Miners Cafe I believe it was (in folsom)... Dang!  That food was gooooood!  I highly recommend it to those who are interested in a great hle-in-the-wall breakfast and steak joint.  Gold Miners &gt; Annie's  Tons of food for less money.  I spent about 8 bucks on something equivelant to 13 bucks at Denny's or Coco's. Once again, highly recommended.  ALSO, I went out and put together a nice pile of stuff for Kate-o.  That is always fun.  She is also always fun.  Yay.  I heart you again Kate, for whatever 100th time.   Anywhos,  my day was awesome and I'm sure that Hallmark got some good sales this year... I sure as heck saw tons of people running around and buying those last-minute cards... those hosers, eh?  I generally plan it out a couple days before and th</post></Blog>