<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>05,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      From Google News:  Al-Jazeera 'Osama loves volleyball, hates ice' Times of India - 1 hour ago OTTAWA : A documentary about a Canadian family closely linked to Osama bin Laden portrays the Al Qaida chief as a well-meaning family man who banned ice in drinks, loves volleyball and has trouble controlling his children.   He hates ICE?  This is the most feared asswipe on the planet and he banned the use of ice in drinkies?   Well meaning family man ?  Boy did we get the wrong idea about this guy or what?  I got  28 bucks  American  for whoever turns this guy into a stain. E-mail me a polaroid and I'l get it right out to you.  C. Thomas Howell just announced that he regrets making  Side Out  as it may have been partially responsible for Osama's hatred of American culture.  Ooh, C.Tommy, you got a lot of 'splaining to do. 
     

    
</post>
<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      copied: E-Commerce Times Martha's Net Worth Drops $85 Million Forbes - 45 minutes ago NEW YORK - The jury's guilty verdict deprived Martha Stewart of not only her credibility but of approximately $85 million. When she woke up this morning Stewart was worth about $420 million.   I have 28 dollars American.  Martha can blow me.  Enjoy prison sweetie!
     

    
</post>
<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      so then our posts are in chronological order?  we can do that you know 
     

    
</post>
<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      S=Shawn J=Jason (that's me)  S: whats for lunch?  J: food in my mouth that I can chew and then swallow so my stomach can dissolve it into nutrients that my body uses so I don't die cuz dying is bad  S: wow  Inspired by Toby's previous post
     

    
</post>
<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This is the most tired I've been in a long time. But, I guess that's what I get for staying at Justin's so late.  Rather than doing any of the myriad of tasks I have to do relating to my job, I have spent most of the day downloading new fonts. I hope to use one of these in the what I think is the 4th or possibly 5th incarnation of Monkey1.com. I've also been trying to recruite people smarter than me to work on the site. That's how I got SimianCinema to work so well. I want the hiplog to integrate into the site as well as Greg's extremely cool gallery tool. If you've never seen Greg's site you should check it out.  urlLink WWW.TINYGRASSHOPPER.COM .  Anyway, this killed another 5 minutes or so of my day. Let's see what I can find to do next in order to avoid my extremely boring job.
     

    
</post>
<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
            T= Toby, J= Jason     T: so far this day can be cancelled I'll just go back to bed rub one out and call it a day  J: my day has been mostly unproductive as well  T: mine has been counter productivo  J: not totally true. You have internet back   2:35 PM   T: internet was back site is back cannot edit it mailboxes are NOT back and I'm out 90 bucks with nothing to show   2:40 PM   T: so whats going on? just leave at 3:30 excuse yourself to the baño... and Go GO GO MOTHER F****ER!!   2:45 PM   T: hello?  J:downloading fonts spaced out here there  T: leave at 3:30  J:can't   3:00 PM   T: 3:45 my final offer we have to go find Tony   3:10 PM    Gotta love AIM eh?
     

    
</post>
<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Fart philosophy? The people of Norco know why they live there.
     

    
</post>
<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This has got to be the most bored I have been since my third time through Geometry in high school.  There is nothing going on and nothing to do anywhere.  This would be a great time to start that alcohol problem I've always wanted.  So ya know how farts stink (and sometimes sound) as wretched as a Father Dowling Mysteries marathon?  Do you suppose that that (I love when I can legally use a word twice in a row in a sentence) is what our goopy insides smell like?  And for that matter would an operating room/embalming room/autopsy parlour(?) be considered a  free fart zone *?  And for that matter what else, besides ripping incredible cheese bombs while they dig through our guts, are doctors doing while we're under.  For me I know I'd find it hard to resist not doing like a little puppet show with people while they were knocked out.  Then again, maybe that's just the boredom talkin'.  Oooo look - a bottle of whiskey in the pantry....   * free fart zone  - Any area (i.e. - off of the 15 in Norco) where one can freely expel gaseous eminations from their self without reprisal. 
     

    
</post>
<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I have spent the better part of today trying to get the domain name http://www.flickerfactory.com back up and running.  Beginning to wonder why.  I spoke to one of the famously reported 'outsourced' tech support dudes from Delhi.  He wanted to helpful, told me to call my bank.  Listened to The Pixies and shouted "F#%" out loud a few times.  Spoke to my bank (wish they were outsourced to Delhi).  I know someone is having a worse day.  Sorry about that dude.  and... it is FRIDAY.
     

    
</post>
<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Now I know more about Andy's gardener-torture than I do about European history.  While this may not be an inhearantly bad thing, it does give one pause.  
     

    
</post>
<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So we have these outdoor speakers in the backyard (makes sense because that's outdoors and all, anyhoo) that are connected to the computer which has an inordinant amount of music on it, right?  Well I have to confess that sometimes when the gardners show up (and they trample the dog poop into the grass making it virtually impossible to pick up later as they do the gardening thing) I like to blast really odd sound effects out there or just turn on the most obnoxious music I can find, just to watch them freak out.  It's almost funnier than shouting "IMMIGRACION!" while they work - almost.
     

    
</post>
<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
        I'm stoked because I just stole that song that was in Scream (when they pan out with the crane shot showing the kids going home early because of the curfew due to the two guys running around killing chix and stuff, 'member?) and Dumb  Dumber (when he has the big foam hat on and he berates the old lady into watching his crap while he goes to get change for a dollar, ya know...).    It's Nick Cave  The Bad Seeds - "Red Right Hand".  I like this song, in fact I like it so much I think I might go post on the blog about how i just stole it from the 'net for next to, if not as much as nothin'!  Wait a second, I already am posting about it - well crap - nevermind...
     

    
</post>
<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So here I am waiting for the damn gardners to show up.  Every week they show up alter and later.  This has no bearing on anyone else in the world but me, but dammit this is killing me.  Otherwise, I sit here wondering what can I do for free (and there the gardners are) that won't involve any kind of self abuse or driving.  Hmmm?
     

    
</post>
<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Kidsnickers starts of with a post so predictable it was like someone getting hit in the nuts on Americas funniest home videos!
     

    
</post>
<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
       KidSnickers comin' at ya, boyzzzz!!!   Wow, that sounds really gay.  Like rap music.  Doesn't rap music suck ass? I sure think so.   GO, THURSDAY KNIGHTS!!! WOO! 
     

    
</post>
<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Please answer your invitations quickly.  Otherwise I'll have to wonder if this was a(nother) huge mistake.
     

    
</post>
<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Welcome To The New Home of (ahem) SMART PATROL. The blog that is so smart we forgot the password of the old blog.
     

    
</post>
<date>13,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Hi there.  I can't believe that our 25 year reunion is coming up.  I can't wait to meet up with everyone at the Sheraton Hotel in June.  We've got lots to catch up on. 25 years, wow!!  What have I been up to? Well until recently I was working for a privately funded organization known as FLAG, the Foundation for Law And Government.  At FLAG we did lots of cool stuff.  One time I had to chase an armored car through the sewers of North Hollywood before it could steal a rare new element.  Another time I had a mexican standoff against a semi truck made out of the same molecular bonded shell as my 'bitchen' 82 Trans Am, and to top it off, it was being driven by my evil twin ( who had a goatee so you could tell us apart ).  That was two-parter if you know what I mean! My boss was tensed-up European dude named Devon Myles.  I think he was from France or maybe Paris.  He was pretty good guy for a boss but most of the time my annual review would get postponed because he'd been kidnapped by Canadian Terrorists and I'd have to go and ' bring the beatdown ' if you know what I mean ( wink ). His secretary, Bonnie was totally hot for me.  But like my Dad always used to say, " You don't poop where you eat " so I set her up with the guy that fixed the copier, and then dumped her for cheating on me.  Eventually I had to leave the company to pursue my dream of becoming a lifeguard in Malibu.  I'm still waiting to hear back from them, so keep those fingers crossed.  Still no wedding ring, but I should tell the ladies out there that I was married briefly but she was killed by ninjas, it sucked.  But now I'm cool and ready to love again.  I hope that ' Stinky  Poncharello and Sonny" the man " Crockett show up. Those guys were way cool.   Go Van Nuys Huskies!!   Mikey " the Night Rocker " Knight
     

    
</post>
<date>12,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
         GET OUT OF THE KITCHEN!!!!!!! 
     

    
</post>
<date>11,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
         WASHINGTON D.C.  ( Capitol PennyThrift  Coupon Caddy )  In a press conference today, U.S. President George W. Bush declared that America's phone systems were in league with the " Evil, evil forces of evil. ".  " My voicemail is all jacked up and the speakerphone?  Forget about it.  Don't get me started on weekend minutes, what a gyp! " Bush was also heard to complain that " Someone has been calling Pizza Hut ordering up to 10 pies a night delivered to the White House for a 'Miss Juwanna Hugmaballs'...  How much clearer does it have to be America? " Bush spoke while pointing at a photograph of beloved funnyman Dudley Moore and announcing "Osama, we  will  find you".  When pressed the President was not able to reveal any further details.  It is no secret that the President has expressed serious doubts in the " safeosity, strongtitude and securityness " of our nation's telecommunications network; however he has rarely gone on record with his concerns.  Wyoming Congressman Tad Waverley attended the press conference, " This is the least remarkable thing I ever heard. But did you notice those little party snacks by the door?  I gotta come to more of these things!! ", and later added " This is a full size Baby Ruth bar!  All these are full size.  I'm gonna take some with me in case its a long session in congress tonight.  Wait a minute, is that a Clark bar..? ".  Dudley Moore died in 2002 of pneumonia as a complication of progressive supranuclear palsy and could not be reached for comment.  His estate has denied any connection to al-Quaeda and Miss Juwanna Hugmaballs.   
     

    
</post>
<date>11,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
         I wanted a logo too. WEEEE!!!
     

    
</post>
<date>11,March,2004</date>
<post>
</post>
<date>11,March,2004</date>
<post>
</post>
<date>11,March,2004</date>
<post>
</post>
<date>11,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
         COSTA MESA, CA  (AP/Reuters)  Homeowners on the street of Andy  Kate Cauble are divided at the 'new fangled' and 'fancy poop palace' that the couple has erected their back yard.  Construction was done " On the downlow " and " Mostly at night when nobody can see us workin' "       " Hell of a thing " said neighbor Les Fincher, " It puts my outdoor statue of Sean Cassidy to shame.  Bully for them ".       However, not all of the couple's neighbors are supportive, " As a taxpayer I don't see why  they  can have a fancy outdoor bathroom and I have to put up with my cramped indoor bathroom, which I share with my pet llama, Gus " said one neighbor who asked not be identified.       Code enforcement officials at City Hall have few problems with the structure, even though it violates a local ordinance by 96 storeys, and includes a restaurant level and ample parking for 450 vehicles.       " Lets just say, they didn't forget to sign the application with a 'Ben Franklin' if you know what I mean " said  "Friendly"  George Romanetti, co-chair of the city's planning department.  Romanetti is presently under investigation by Orange County's grand jury on an unrelated matter.       " We just wanted something a little special " said Cauble. " And since I spend upwards of 6 hours a day in the can, I figured we should do it up fancy ".       As a conciliatory olive branch, Cauble has invited his neighbors to " come on in an try out the facilities, see what all the fuss is about. " but warned to " bring yer own paper, I ain't made o'money ".
     

    
</post>
<date>11,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      And the Award For Most Dramatic (and yet redundant) sarcasm goes to...    Justin  Jason for  " Toby's phone stopped me from hitting it with an internet chat room vixen "   Thank you and good night.
     

    
</post>
<date>11,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Justin:  You know what woke me up this morning?  Jason:  Your incredibly strong urge for a fifth couch?  Jason:  The "Ya-Whore" that was trying to sneak out before Kira woke up?  Jason:  I don't know. What woke you up?  Justin:  A beeping sound under my pillow.  Jason:  Tobys phone?  Justin:  Yes   
     

    
</post>
<date>11,March,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Everyone can post images to the site.  In your post simply use the following code:  (It's typed funny so it doesn't get read actual code)  Inside the </post></Blog>