<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink iPod: this season's must-have for muggers  
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       新o既企鵝遊戲又o黎啦~   urlLink http://games.coolegames.com/yetisports3.swf  
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Logo Game 好好玩! 目的o係要答出 A - Z 26 幅圖畫入面每一間公司名稱, 例如  I 字:    你就要估到佢o係IBM~  要玩就用以下呢個link  urlLink http://www.logogame.com/game.php?id=8   頭先o個個link o係估科技公司名稱~  以下呢個就估 .com   urlLink http://www.logogame.com/game.php?id=9   Enjoy!  
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Why the objects in the following photos are so special? They are all made from SAND!   urlLink http://www.sculpturesinsand.com/    urlLink           urlLink Mark Anderson - Sculptures in sand   
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    (C)  urlLink Plasgoal   
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink http://www.waxy.org/random/video/lego_thriller.wmv   你都咪話易整! 
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink http://www.gamestop.com/product.asp?cookie%5Ftest=1%5Fid=322028   咁都得? 
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink http://www.deansplanet.com/tongues.html   好多個我都唔識! 
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       切爾諾貝爾(Chernobyl)... 對你來說有什麼感想? 對大部份人來說除了 urlLink 切爾諾貝爾核電廠核災難 新聞一則外就沒有任何感想吧. 但是這 urlLink 網頁 的作者住在離切爾諾貝爾核電廠外130km 的地方, 而因為作者熱愛電單車的關係, 經常會到切爾諾貝爾核電廠附近的區域駕車遊覽. 這 urlLink 網頁 內的照片展示了切爾諾貝爾核電廠附近的區域在二十年間渺無人煙受隔離的情況: 空無一人, 所有東西原封不動地保持在八十年的環境.   最令人印象深刻的是作者的兩段感想:  "People had to leave everything, from photos of their grandparents to cars. Their clothes, cash and passports has been changed by state authorities. This is incredible, people lived, had homes, country houses, garages, motorcyles, cars, money, friends and relatives, people had their life, each in own niche and then in a matter of hours this world fall in pieces and everything goes to dogs and after few hours trip with some army vehicle one stands under some shower, washing away radiation and then step in a new life, naked with no home, no friends, no money, no past and with very doubtful future. "  另一段:  "I wonder how this guy feel, who once went for a fishing trip and who was not able to return home. It is like you life is cut on two pieces. in one is you slippers still under you bed, photos of a first love that left on piano.. in other is you yourself, you memories and a fishing rod. "  試想想... 假如你是那些要受撤離的人的其中一個... 
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink This  is a cool input device. However, does it look like what I am using on my office desk right now? =P 
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       HONG KONG (KNN) -- Due to the introduction of new  urlLink Rummy-O  board game to home this night, Kevin is challenged by his Mom to play against her in one-to-one duel. In only 1.5 hours, Kevin has lost two continuous rounds. "I am totally surprised. I thought I can beat my mom with my good maths. It turns out to be a total failure." said Kevin. Kevin nearly won the first round but he overlooked the last single winning step. In the later part of the second round, he simply cannot figure it out how to play his deck right due to the overwhelming numbers of tiles on the table.  In view of the consecutive success over her postgraduate son, Kevin's mom suggested him to practise more on the game. It is expected his son will challenge her as soon as he has enough practices in front of the computer version of the game. "It's just a game of maths and logic. I can play it well soon." proclaimed Kevin.  Rummy-O is a popular and easy to learn game that the whole family can enjoy.  urlLink The deck consists of 106 numbered and colored tiles . The winner is the player who plays all his/her tiles first. 
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink http://www.pbase.com/accl/best2003   Thanks Lin for sending me the photo album. They are wonderful! The photographer is able to capture the most magnificant scenes in Hong Kong. Personally, I think the  urlLink Ding Kau Bridge  photo and the  urlLink Super Curves  photos are the best. I would like to take such great photos too! However, there is a price to pay... the price of the  urlLink Canon EOS 10D Digital SLR camera  is approximately HKD $10,000. Of course, the price tag is even higher when accessories like flash light and stand are purchased. Anyway, if you are deeply in love with photography, then you are willing to pay this price. Hmmm... not for me now =P  Here are also  urlLink some sample images  from the  urlLink Canon EOS10D official site . Notice the details that the digital camera can capture. 
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       They are bloody... they are violent... but people keep playing them because they are addictive!  Here is the original  urlLink penguin  version. Here is the  urlLink happy tree fans  version. 
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       這間  urlLink SawStop  公司聲稱生產的電鋸能探測到放在電鋸上的是木頭或是手指. 如果是手指的話, 電鋸就會高速(少於5ms 的時間內)收回, 以減少手指的損傷(使用者的手指只會被割傷, 而不會被電鋸切去...).   urlLink Video Demo 示範切手指   不過 Video Demo 示範只用熱狗腸仔代替手指, 如果用真人手指效果必定更佳!!! =P 
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink W.C. stands for Water Closet.   
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       你認為玩  urlLink Neopets  的玩家是成人多或是小童多? 我不知道, 我只知道雖然好像得有趣, 但我不適合玩它 =P 
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Take a look at the following sites:   urlLink http://xicons.com/   urlLink http://interfacelift.com/   urlLink http://graphicsdesign.org/copland/   And you will discover why artists like to use Mac instead of Windows! Oh man, they are really really gorgeous!!!  I wish I have a  urlLink Power Mac G5  with a  urlLink LCD screen resolution 1920 x 1200  in front of my eyes. I will NEVER look at Windows desktop again =P  I promise this is true, my Windows fellows =) 
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       NaDa ( urlLink http://bernardbelanger.com/computing/NaDa/ ) 是一個只有一 byte 的software, 它沒有任何用處, 但仍然有很多人 download 它. It's really amazing... 
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Video-Game Publishers Increasingly Outsource Production   urlLink (http://www.miami.com/mld/miamiherald/business/national/8242740.htm)  
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       原來在美國和法國, 有些提款機是運行 WinXP !!! 所以有時會 hang 機...  Diebold WinXP ATM Spec. (WinXP is mentioned on page 3)  urlLink http://www.diebold.com/solutions/atms/opteva/520.pdf   Hang 機 screenshot:  urlLink http://unworkable.org/diebold/   那麼香港的提款機呢? 香港的提款機大約是  urlLink NCR Persona 84   " NCR Persona 84 Technical Specifications  ELECTRONIC PLATFORM Multiple Pentium® processing "  雖然 Technical Specifications 入面沒有說明是那一種OS, 不過可見 NCR Persona 84 是用Pentium CPU 的 =P 
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink An interesting "Tree growing" Flash game  
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       First, we have software development outsourced to India, now it's content production ( urlLink Builder.com outsourcing content production to India ). What's next? I remembered that there is a comic strip in Times magazine about an American girl outsources her homeworks to India  urlLink Mumbai  =P 
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink CIA World Factbook 2003  
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       (1) 職場裡的人都應該用瓊瑤式的說話方式:  比方生氣的主管或同事對你說：「你這個折磨人的小東西，你怎麼會這麼粗心哪！」然 後你回答：「我知道這一切都是我的錯，我不知道自己怎麼會笨成這個樣子，請你儘管 責罵我吧。」然後對方就會說：「我不許你這樣說自己！」然後，大家都笑倒在地上， 就天下太平了！  (2) 職場裡的人都應該用金庸式的說話方式:  比方生氣的主管或同事對你說: "你這個欠挨刀的小雜毛, 看你壞了老子的好事"然後你 回答: "我知道這一切都是我的錯, 做兄弟的在這裡跟你陪不是了" 然後對方就會說: "今天就是賠了你十跟指頭也濟不得事"然後，大家都笑倒在地上，就 天下太平了！  (3) 職場裡的人都應該用英雄式的說話方式:  比方生氣的主管或同事對你說: "你把一個人想簡單了"然後你回答: "我知道這一切都 是我的錯, 大王你是怎麼發現的."然後對方就會說: "你的殺氣在亂......"然後，大家 都笑倒在地上，就天下太平了！  (4) 職場裡的人都應該用村上春樹式的說話方式:  比方生氣的主管或同事對你說:"事情做成這樣, 我感覺像是在夏日裡把發燙的耳朵貼到 牆壁一樣的感覺,是一種冰冷的回音...."然後你回答: "就像是1978年壞掉的唱盤一樣" 然後對方就會說:"跳舞吧,羊男"然後，大家都笑倒在地上，就天下太平了！  (5) 職場裡的人都應該用港漫式的說話方式:  比方生氣的主管或同事對你說: "口胡! 你這廢柴, 要你仆到大街呀"然後你回答: "想 戰我, 你還未夠班呀"然後對方就會說: "不知所謂的東西, 給我敗了吧"然後，大家都 笑倒在地上，就天下太平了！  (6) 職場裡的人都應該用YA教授式的說話方式:  比方生氣的主管或同事對你說: "因果循環總相隨, 請看職場七要事"然後你: "請您開 示..."然後對方就會說: "一個的勝負成敗, 就在於你埋了什麼因,你在裡面慢慢的澆水 , 我可以告訴你, 總有一天活泉會冒出來,這種耕紜平常是看不到, 是隱性的, 這是你 所命定好的基因, 就會有好的果報出來."然後，大家都笑倒在地上，就天下太平了！  (7) 職場裡的人都應該用霹靂火式的說話方式:  比方生氣的主管或同事對你說: "阮若是心情不爽, 就會想要報仇, 直接送你一筒汽油 跟一支番仔火. ....."然後，大家都笑倒在地上，就天下太平了！  
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       點解Kevin 無啦啦寫blog? 因為佢成日有好多(佢認為)好interesting/無聊/important o既information/idea 想同大家分享, 但係又唔想用ICQ messages disturb 大家, 所以就放o黎呢道啦. 有時間我就會 update 多的, 冇時間我就會訓多 d =P  如果你對我o既posts 有任何意見/投訴, 就send 個email or ICQ message (ICQ: 968194) 俾我啦~ I am looking forward to hearing from you soon! 
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       呢個  urlLink 碧咸新廣告 (http://pepsi.ld.mediawave.co.uk/Pepsi/pepsi_football_2004/PepsiAdvertHigh.asx)  係咪好似Nike o個個足球廣告呢? 
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       這是一個測試 This is a test 
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Last time we have heard "Mario music... in piano", this times we have it done in guitar!   urlLink http://homepage.mac.com/mrspleen/.Movies/ben_mario_piano.mpeg    urlLink keiichi  
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink Shake That Ass!  
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink      urlLink Yetisports  
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Quite interesting... if you have enough patience =P    urlLink http://www.boberil.com/pandafgolf/  
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       It may be a bit silly... but the graphics are nice and the music is good!   urlLink CastleCat 2 - Miami Invasion   urlLink CastleCat 3 - The Vegas Connection     urlLink Mausland  
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink            http://www-personal.umich.edu/~msittig/bento/   
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink                    http://www-personal.umich.edu/~msittig/bento/   
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink http://www.ahsaforum.com/stuff/complain.mp3   相信大家都聽o左啦, right? 
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink http://www.time.com/time/time100/   Are you the next one? 
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Here is a flash game called  urlLink Naked Hero  that is similar to  urlLink Made in Wario .   
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       A nicely animated flash movie by Korean about the love between a male cat and female rabbit!   urlLink      urlLink Sambakza   Here is one more: nicely animated with cool music~   urlLink      urlLink Sambakza   
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Take a look at the following hilarious signs!   urlLink      urlLink Sign Language    urlLink      urlLink Sign Language    urlLink      urlLink Sign Language   There are more in  urlLink Sign Language website ! 
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
         codebase="http://download.macromedia.com/pub/shockwave/cabs/flash/swflash.cab#version=5,0,0,0"  width=600 height=400&gt;           		  		  		  		  		   	      urlLink MONO*CRAFTS3.0   An ingenious  urlLink clock  by  urlLink MONO*CRAFTS 3.0 ! 
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink      urlLink Takagism   Please try to escape from the room! I spent about 20-30 minutes on that. Heehee... 
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink http://homepage.mac.com/mrspleen/.Movies/ben_mario_piano.mpeg   Nice mario game music performance with piano!  If you are a piano player and game player, then  urlLink this site  has more game sheet music such that you may practise and astonish your friends! 
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink      urlLink Edheads   Dear HA friends, may I present you the virtual  urlLink Total Knee Replacement (Px 174.0) !!!  Aaarrrggghhh.. I think I am not suitable to be a surgical doctor... 
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink      urlLink Trickz.com   當你睇完以上呢個  urlLink video  之後, 你就會發現拳霸原來都唔係咁犀利 (當然我冇話自己做得到, 雖然我都想!), 因為video 入面o既男仔都做得到呀~ 
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink      urlLink ThinkGeek   呢個東東叫  urlLink PC EZ-Bake Oven , 你可以將佢 install 落你電腦機箱o既 5 1/4" drive bay, 咁你就可以一路用電腦, 一路用電腦焗蛋糕啦~  你估遲d 會唔會有 1. 電腦洗衣機 2. 電腦雪櫃 3. 電腦微波爐??  其實諗落又真係幾無聊, 做乜要將所有家電塞晒入個電腦機箱入面 -_-" 
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       如果人是DVD, 我希望我是正版... =P   urlLink http://www.asiapacificadfest.com/01welcome/tvc_best.htm  
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink http://boreme.com/bmuk_movies/dont_smoke_in_bed.mov  
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink http://www.neogeopro.com/stuff/mario.htm   Matrix Reloaded Mario 版~ 好佩服作者有咁好心機將  urlLink Matrix Reloaded  入面 Anderson 被  urlLink Agent Smith "S" 圍攻的一幕以Mario Brothers 公仔重新傳神演繹~  我最鐘意 flash 入面的其中兩幕: * 2D Mario 瞬間 3D 化 * Mario 以棍支撐地面作 360 度迴轉踢  Enjoy! 
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink      urlLink Starving Rascal  
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink Easy RPG  is a very simple RPG made in flash... but it's fun!  The creator of this game also made a number of quality flash movies and games. You may find them at the site  urlLink f1ash:room .  I am particularly interested in the  urlLink room flash . 
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink Let Forever Be  
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       A free encyclopedia... better than paying for  urlLink Microsoft Encarta ?   
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink http://www.milkandcookies.com/links/10329/  
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink http://ww4.tiki.ne.jp/~amoh/flash/amoadv.swf  
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       各位駕車人士注意, 以下 urlLink 最新泊 S 位標準方法 將於今年六月一日生效. 有關以上泊 S 位之標準過程單張及小冊子可向運輸處各分區辦事處索取, 多謝合作. 
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       This is the  BEST  site that I have found today!!!   urlLink      urlLink Scamming the Scammer    If you don't read the following pdf file, you won't know why it is totally hilarious!!  urlLink Read the story in PDF format    With my large applause to those who fought this ingenious war! =D 
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink      urlLink Picasa   Its interface is similar to  urlLink Apple iTunes . Browsing and organzing photos are very user-friendly. I like the fact that it can show all my photos on a clean and easy-to-use interface! The slideshow feature is also particularly good!  Give it a try!  Notes: I am not paid for the above. I am NOT advertising. =P 
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink      urlLink BBC NEWS     A Canadian student who ordered an MP3 player over the internet from the US was shocked to receive a licensed handgun instead.    You never know what you will get from  urlLink eBay  =P 
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink      urlLink Nintendo     With its two screens, Nintendo DS instantly shows its innovative face. But capabilities like a touch-screen input, voice recognition and wireless communication set it apart from every other game device, and again demonstrate Nintendo's passion for groundbreaking originality.   
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       OMG! There are a hundred and fifteen Mario Brothers on the screen!!! They look like ants rather than Mario Brothers =P   urlLink http://www.angelfire.com/electronic/dokidoki/index115.html     urlLink 100's Marios  
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink http://myweb.hinet.net/home10/musicbetty/tv/tv.htm  
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink Ray Room Game  
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink Cannot Find Server   Hit it hard please! 
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       The Centamap for Europe?   urlLink      urlLink map24  
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink GameJobs.com   Have you dreamed of a wonderful job in gaming industry? 
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Three new  urlLink logogames  =)   urlLink Brand Name Clothing    urlLink Automobile Logo Challenge    urlLink Fast Food Logo's   
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       咁o既德文page?!? 救命 &gt;o   urlLink Drogenlied  
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well, I think this is cute =P   urlLink QT and Pasootie  
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink      urlLink Popular Science  
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I will be back on 5/7~ 
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink      urlLink clusterballoon.org   A movie clip is available  urlLink here   Wow! Isn't that wonderful? 
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink      urlLink Died Online.com    You login to the system every few days, or whatever time period you set it at. If you don't login within that certain amount of time, the system will email all of your friends with your custom "Hey, I'm dead now" message. You can also display a little dead or alive image on your website, online journals, emails, etc...   咁都得!!! 
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink      urlLink Servers under the sun   Nope, I don't want my cubicle looks like this after I come back from Seattle... 
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Nope, the only relationship between the movie  urlLink Truman Show  and  urlLink Shrek 2  is that I have watched both of them within  these two days. I think both of them worth your time to watch and think about.   We accept the reality of the world with which we are presented.   By the way, if you would like to experience the environment in Truman Show, you may rent a house for days/weeks in  urlLink Seaside Floria  (Ultra expensive &gt;_  ( urlLink Some notes  for the Truman Show)  -- Just my two cents 
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink     The purpose of this game is to control the roller coaster ('S' to decrease speed, 'K' to increase speed) to travel along the track and give as much excitement (represented by no. of hearts) as possible to the passengers.  Be careful not to throw all the passengers out of the roller coaster! Anyway, it is fun to do that, isn't it? =P 
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       其實我地七一遊行係咪都可以整番一個呢? 
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    This is my favourite flash game recently. Nice graphics (I love pixelized graphics =P), especially it is funny to see those pixelized people scorched to dust =P 
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink     我都不明白呢個  urlLink flash  做乜, anyway 都幾有趣...  乜 Kenya 有好多 lions/tigers 咩? -__-"    urlLink Weebls Stuff  
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       How's your feeling if you receive the email after 20/30 years? By the way, I wonder if we will still use email at that time?    urlLink FutureMe.org  
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hard to describe... but I think it's pleasing~   urlLink http://62.210.133.184/melon/cometogether.swf   
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       A great  urlLink Windows 98 blue screen  in a CNN show... hahah.. look how Bill Gates handled the problem~    urlLink kernalpanic  
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       靚~ 
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink http://www.pcpuzzles.com/bubblefun/  
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink      urlLink All Too Fat : Geeky   Of course, you have to enter the search keyword backward.... drawkcab.. 
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Good flash adventure game from the maker of the flash game Samorost   urlLink The Quest for the Rest     urlLink Amanita Design  
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Another good flash adventure game!   urlLink http://nlp.fi.muni.cz/~xsvobod4/amanita/samorost/intro.html     urlLink Amanita Design  
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink http://www.minijuegos.com/juegos/jugar.php?id=2319  
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink      urlLink        urlLink Thanko.jp  
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Some  urlLink gmail  resources that might help:   urlLink gmailusers.com   A hub of information for Gmail users around the world including articles, news, FAQs, forums, tutorials, Web sites, and more about the new Google email service released in beta version by Google on April 1, 2004.    urlLink A list of gmail utilities    urlLink Google GMail Loader (GML)  Import your existing email into GMail!   urlLink GmailerXP   GmailerXP is the be-all-end-all utility app for Google's Gmail service. The program allows users to do anything that they can do online, it also combines all the features of the other programs (GML, Gmailto, etc.) The ONLY Gmail app you'll ever need.    urlLink YoSucker  Access your yahoo web mail account using POP3 mail client   urlLink GetMail   GetMail is a mail forwarding program that started life because of the lack of POP3 availability for Hotmail. From these humble beginnings it has evolved into a flexible Hotmail/MSN/Pop mail directing forwarding program.   
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink      urlLink Mi-24 helicopter in Afghanistan  
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Image by Magigale, b3ta.com 
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink      urlLink Super Mario War    Super Mario War is a Super Mario Deathmatch game. The goal is to stomp as many other Marios as possible to win the game. It's a tribute to "Mario War by Samuele Poletti".    
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
        If you are using bluetooth-enabled device like mobile phone, please beware of "bluejacking" and "bluesnarfing". What are "bluejacking" and "bluesnarfing"?  Bluejacking   An intruder sends messages to your bluetooth device without your authorization.   Bluesnarfing  An intruder obtains data in your device silently via bluetooth without your authorization and attention.    Luckily I do not own bluetooth-enabled phone/device right now, therefore there is little impact on me. =)  References   urlLink Bluetooth phones at risk from 'snarfing' (ZDNet UK)   urlLink 'Bluejacking' hits the mainstream (ZDNet UK)   
    
    
</post>
<date>19,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Since I am busy, thus blogging is a luxury~  Sorry for so few updates in these weeks.  
    
    
</post>
</Blog>