<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       In connection to my previous blog on GDesktop or GInternet.  As we move ahead in the digital world, we will be using more  more digital devices. Today one's office PC, home PC, Laptop, Mobile Phone, PDA act as local data syncs. Then there are resources from multiple service providers on the internet where one's data lives.   The amount of data that we are personally generating is increasing tremendously and as we move ahead its bound to grow bigger  bigger. Mobile phone cameras combined with blogging have already started making an impact in this direction.   In such a scenario, finding even personal information will become a challenge. Google has shown that one can search efficiently in a highly distributed environment by making it centralized very efficiently. The information on which we work personally, has to also lie on the network and the local hard discs, memory data chips will just act like a temporary cache which automatically gets synced back to the network.  For this to happen, we need to look at the Storage Vs Connectivity. Though storage costs have decreased tremendously and memory chips now form a part of wide variety of devices from watches, microwaves and every other device on which one can put hand on. But connectivity hasn't yet become seamless. To have a significant effect for next generation of digital era, connectivity must become as pervasive as memory chips are today where every digital chip is always connected to a network.  And services like google or any other service provider can then make data syncs of personal information on the network from any device. Privacy issues can be handled upto some extent via having encryption technologies, the way unix passwords are stored. Data is synced at the server, but in a secure fashion where like a unix password an administrator or a service provider can't interpret the data.  The next step would be then to apply adaptable techniques to be able to retrieve data in an adaptable fashion depending on the environment.    
    
    
</post>
<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       The title tells it all. Is google going into the desktop space or establishing a wider brand over the internet? Or will the desktop span inside the internet? Or will it master both independently?  Google is slowly moving away from a pure search engine company to a services company where its getting more closer to user needs. The most common things that a user does on the internet are Email and Search. Google has got it both.   With an IPO coming forward, it must have huge plans for going forward.   Google does search on around 4.2 billion webpages which might be a fraction of the internet space. Google has very tactfully managed to work on that amount of data. The desktop data space might be quite huge as compared to the internet but can google master to have a small percentage of this space? A user is then no longer worried about losing his data ever. And google manages it efficiently and enables him to find it efficiently whenever he needs it.  Or will the google tools come closer to the desktop? And therefore one will have a number of tools for each of the multiple devices, a user uses. Or in a true ambient intelligence scenario, google can combine data from multiple data sources for an individual and enable it in the way a user wants, no matter wherever he is, which ever device he is using!  
    
    
</post>
<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       It was quite unexpected when yesterday while configuring my Blogger.com account I got an option to try a GMail account. I was always looking forward to get that. The day Google released GMail account for testing, I posted a message for getting an account. But then didn't get any reply back.   GMail not just only provides you tremendous space but also increases your efficiency. Google has kept its tradition of keeping the interface simple and focusing on functionalities.   There has been much hue  cry about the advertising procedure of google, but I don't see any specific reason which makes me feel negative about that. In my view they have actually created a sound business model based on which they can provide cheap(in this case free) services to large number of users and also earn revenue. And now its upto a user to decide weather he wants to use it or not.  The way advertisements appear along with the mail, doesn't block your view and don't make you feel itchy. The advertisements just appear once only during when one opens an email for reading. On the contrary email interfaces of other providers have a lot of flashy advertisements, pop ups which at times itch a lot.   GMail has made the response for the service quite fast and massively reduced the number of clicks for checking email. Overall its a quite good service, not just because of the 1G space, though its an important part but also in terms of the actual service.  
    
    
</post>
<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       The goal of the project is to visit each of the latitude and longitude integer degree intersections in the world, and to take pictures at each location. The pictures and stories are then posted on the project website. urlLink http://www.confluence.org/   Project Overview : snippets from the original website   The project is an organized sampling of the world. There is a confluence within 49 miles (79 km) of you if you're on the surface of Earth. We've discounted confluences in the oceans and some near the poles, but there are still 13,042 to be found.  History I (Alex Jarrett) started the project in February 1996 because I liked the idea of visiting a location represented by a round number such as 43Â°00'00"N 72Â°00'00"W. What would be there? Would other people have recognized this as a unique spot? Another reason was that my friend managed to convince me to buy a GPS and I had to come up with something to do with it. I also hoped to encourage people to get outside, tromp around in places they normally would never go, and take pictures of it.  Project Stats Primary confluences:  Successful visits: 	4,048  Incomplete visits: 	586  Unique successful: 	3,122  Unique incomplete: 	194  Percent complete: 	19.31%  Total indexed: 	16,164  Indexed - Land: 	14,027  Indexed - Water: 	1,986  Indexed - Ice Cap: 	151   There are already more than 30,000 pictures from around 147 countries by around 4,800 people. India has 290 confluence points of which only 53 have been covered till yet.. See  urlLink map  Any adventurous people around ?   
    
    
</post>
<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       An  urlLink article  at internetnews.com Future of Search Will Make you Dizzy' By Ryan Naraine    That's the word from A9 chief executive Udi Manber, PhD, who insists that full development of search and resource discovery tools remains at least a decade away.  "Think about how the Web has changed your life in the last 10 years. Now, try to extrapolate 10 years forward and you should feel dizzy. We're still in day one of developing and innovating in search. There's still a lot of exciting discoveries to be made," Manber said in a keynote address at this year's World Wide Web (W3C) conference here.  "It's not about speed or size anymore. It's all about quality. It's about delivering the tools that allow relevancy. It's good to make searching faster and faster because that part is well understood. The quality part is not understood and that's the challenge we face today," he added.    Another  urlLink article  on internetnews.com mentions about projects at microsoft.   With the cost of data storage dropping to levels in which a terabyte of space will cost no more than $1,000, Rashid said the time will come when deleting data will be a thing of the past.  "There won't be reason for anyone to throw away any data," Rashid said. "We'll get to the stage where, for $1,000, you will be able to store more than a trillion bytes...More than enough space to store every conversation you have ever had, from the time you are born to the time you die."   With world becoming distributed and data lying not just on PC or web but mobile phones, future networked devices (networked iPod,..) and no delete button - the search wouldn't just imply searching web resources, but searching personal data quick, from any device and with quality results.   
    
    
</post>
<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Some of the companies are pushing hard to have .mobi domain for mobile devices. In one sense it is good for companies as well as users, as people on mobile devices if want to check cnn news, can go to www.cnn.mobi for instance. Finding a wap url for mobile web is a lot more complex today. That is one of the reasons why wap hasn't been able to take off as predicted.  But creating a .mobi domain will create a mad rush for companies with web url's today to have an equivalent .mobi domain. Moreover enforcing TLD's such as .mobi are good in short run, but in long term this will segment the web into small little webs where the mobile web is completely different from the pc web, which is to some extent the case today. Making .mobi domain will just aggravate the problem. What is needed is a mature technology which can make available the existing resources of the internet taking care the constraints of the mobile world.   An article on .mobi domain: urlLink .Mobi's Case For Mobile Domains   
    
    
</post>
<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Developing economies like India face a tremendous challenge in bridging the digital divide. There's a wide gap amongst the rich  the poor and the literate  the illiterate. This is also hugely reflected by the poor PC penetration numbers that are amongst the lowest in the world.  The price levels, poor infrastructure pose huge challenges in the way of increasing these numbers. But more than the price, the real need of a PC for an individual is missing. A PC needs to become a utility like a refrigerator, television, radio or a washing machine where a user can see the need of a PC for himself. Currently a common man cannot find a significant reason to own a PC.   The applications of a PC define the utility for a PC. Internet has emerged as the most hottest application of a PC amongst other applications such as the office tools or desktop games and the like. In the Indian context, the infrastructure for internet is poor, costly, no significant content and very few services available which an individual can make use of.  A Part of being digital is to have access to services passing on the benefits of technology and be able to change the way of living. I am trying to think of a two sided approach for bridging this gap. On the one side we need to decrease cost, improve infrastructure but more importantly also provide content  services which fulfills the need of an individual and affect his way of living.  Secondly to make use of the growing mobile world, where digital devices can be mobilised, even though these cannot provide a rich internet experience but can enable services which can impact the lives of people of bridging digital divide is to stress on mobile technology, data services, improve interfaces, technology and harness it to build a services infrastructure providing services which provides benefits of technology to the user.   The point for building this service infrastructure web is to provide services which a person can make use by himself without being dependent on anyone else. A fisherman when check himself about weather conditions from his mobile phone. Some one's father can buy a train ticket through a voice gateway. A person can have access to information that he needs.  Providing essential services which are usable reflecting a change in a common man's lifestyle will be a significant step forward in this direction. Without building this significant utility, mere increase in penetration numbers is much like running a literacy campaign where an illiterate person who can read/write his name is considered literate even though he is still ignorant and is still left aloof from the benefits of literacy.  
    
    
</post>
<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       RSS and blogging is slowly taking the internet by storm. One can see the orange icons providing RSS feeds on a number of websites (Yahoo, BBC) today. Companies are inventing ways to make use of RSS feeds. As more people move towards RSS, RSS readers and enabling technologies will become a major utility for accessing content.   Today RSS feeds are published mainly in the way a publisher provides them. They reflect the way a particular publisher publishes content, much like the content they publish on their respective website. RSS aggregators mere aggregate these feeds and provide only a basic search facility. As the number of RSS feeds increase, a user will be faced with the same daunting task of which information to see and when? RSS just moves the information overload problem to the next level.  As we move ahead with RSS embracing semantic web technologies, software programs will become a lot more sophisticated. These should be able to aggregate and provide specific content to the users according to their needs, interests and context.   What is needed is a more sophisticated service, which not only just provides a user accurate information, but prioritizes it, provides recommendations, enables sharing of ideas with other like minded people acting like a shared memory and is personalised. A service which could very easily link up an individual's interests with the vast resources available on the internet irrespective of the user's environment.   
    
    
</post>
<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Normally I personally try to keep away from politics like many other young people who think indian politics to be full of corruption. There are no role models and no one to look forward too. Even if at the national level there might be some people, the small constituencies are just empty.  But still I have casted my vote, twice in the last few years. I think when democracy gives us so much - which we take for granted - we must as citizens of a democracy play our role of keeping that democracy intact.  The election results have shocked most indians including me. It never looked that Congress could return to power after what was going with the economy. May be its anti-incumbency or strong campaign of the Congress which tackled weaknesses of the BJP, the fact is democracy and the citizens of india have given their verdict.  What appears more shocking to me after the election that people still making a hay of an indian citizen of foreign origin holding the post of prime minister - as a big issue. We the same people talked tremendously and extended support when people of indian origin earned laurels in foreign lands - Mahendera Chaudhary became prime minster of Fiji, Bobby Jindal ran for Lousiana governor or may be for any other non-political post.   I am not defending any particular person or party but I am trying to have a debate on why a post like prime minister cannot be open for indian citizens of foreign origin. If one finds a person incompetent or lacks experience, then one should tackle it on that front. I myself strongly oppose some policies of the Congress party. But I think the world in which we are living today, we have to grow and be independent and think about competencies rather then an individual's origin. I was never taught at school to distinguish people based on their origin. Let India the greatest democracy, take a step ahead and show what a democracy is meant to be.    
    
    
</post>
<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Crete, Greece a great place for a conference. The week just passed by attending the first European semantic web conference at Heraklion. The place was wonderful, atmosphere was cool and the topic was great. The conference was well attended by around 200 plus people. My congratulations to all the people involved in the organization.  The talks were interesting, some of them stimulating but these are still scratching the surface. And this makes you realize a lot of work has yet to be done and some fundamental problems need to be solved. Semantic Web promises a lot and the road from the problem to the solution is quite fuzzy.  I myself would like this huge effort to succeed but as I started working into the field, I am getting to know the core problems which are as old as of the 80s. The application cases presented in the conference were interesting and did quite a lot but they are in my opinion mere use of RDF and related technologies. They don't justify how using semantic technologies helped as regards to implementing them in simple relational or object oriented technologies of today. And this I think is fundamental to the success of Semantic Web. And that's why I think industry is still keeping away from semantic technologies to a larger extent as of today.  One thing that I understood from the talk by Guus Schreiber, was the difference between ontologies and data models. Ontologies are meant to be fundamentally developed in a shared community. This is what gives ontology its meaning. If one is developing and using his own small ontology in OWL, its still a data model and not an ontology.  Most people have an intuition that semantic web technologies can work and some others are susceptical. Only time can tell which one succeeds. I am myself interested in how technology can be applied in real information systems and solve real life problems.  It will be great to see what the next semantic web conference presents. Its also in Heraklion !!!  
    
    
</post>
<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Its been a few months when I came to know about the world of blogging and started reading blogs regularly. The technology for blogging existed from quite long. But its just now it has started having a ripple effect. Even though technology behind might not be complex, but its merely the simplicity that makes it tick.  I favor the fact that technology has to made more accessible to people rather then people changing their ways to adapt to technology. There might be cases when we humans need to adjust to technology but where ever possible technology should try to seamlessly fit in an individual's life.  Its the simplicity of a technology which makes it appealing to the masses and we as technologists, entrepreneurs need to understand this fact more closely. In technology world, people often talk about having built complex systems but unless one can't simplify the complexity, one is still living in a complex world. The essence is to build systems doing complex tasks in a simple way.   We have moved from the world of huge mainframes, to workstations and now into smart phones. And with each move the number of people getting affected are much larger. The difference between simplicity and complexity will play a much bigger role in the coming world of nanotechnologies. What we need is to understand technology in relation to the way we work, use them in a simple and effective manner - which can then have a far reaching effect on our lives.  
    
    
</post>
<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink Brad Feld  writes in his blog for their rationale behind  urlLink "&gt;NewsGator investment :   The misperception is that NewsGator is only an Outlook plug-in. While the most popular product from NewsGator is currently their Outlook-based aggregator, what really turned us on when we dug into NewsGator as a potential investment is NewsGator Online Services (NGOS). Greg Reinacker's vision is much broader than simply an RSS aggregator - his goal is to provide RSS content on any device. NewsGator currently provides clients for Outlook, the Web, POP email, mobile devices (web-based and wap), and Microsoft Media Center (how cool is it to get an RSS feed on your TV?).   Following are several examples of how NGOS can be used today:  - I use a Tmoblie Sidekick - made by Danger - as my cell phone and wireless data device (web browser, email, AOL IM, wap browser, calendar). Using NGOS Mobile Edition, I can read my feeds via my web or wap browser on my Sidekick. These subscriptions are synchronized with my desktop, so I don't have to do any set up on my Sidekick - I simply access my services.newsgator.com mobile edition account.  - NGOS has a custom search feed capability. I put in all of my companies as keywords (one per feed) and then get feeds for each company. This is similar to Yahoo! Alerts and Google Alerts, but also searches all of blogworld so I get any postings in these feeds also.  - A NewsGator / Gmail interface exists. Using this, you can route all of your feeds into your Gmail account and take advantage of Google's search technology on your personal feed database.  Now - while Greg's vision is broad and his technical skills amazing - he'd be the first to admit that NewsGator hasn't packaged and promoted their various products in the most effective way. We're already hard at work on this - expect a steady stream of product announcements in the next few months as we roll out new products to more clearly package and expose all of the technologies NewsGator has built. Existing NewsGator customers should expect to benefit broadly from this - we intend to be fanatically loyal to all of our customers - especially our early ones. We're also extremely interested in finding out how people are using NewsGator and NGOS, as well as what they are looking for in the future products.   A services model is one of the strongest model for RSS. Pure clients can get lost in the space. Netscape story reminds us of that very well.  
    
    
</post>
<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink SocialText  has a bunch of good links on RSS tools on their webblog. - A list of  urlLink RSS Tools   -  urlLink Secure RSS  - the way RSS is being used for private blogs or feeds using basic HTTP authentication.Silver Orange did an experiment on analysing tools that support secure rss feeds. It can be found here  urlLink http://labs.silverorange.com/archives/2003/july/privaterss    
    
    
</post>
<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Since my university life, I have always been tempted by the Venture world. Having seen the bubble game of the dot com era; rising aspirations, falling hopes - entrepreneurship is not an easy world. Its not for everyone, only for the ones who want to make things happen.   During the dot-com era, everyone used to talk about a "Killer Idea". Few months back I was with some people, they said their intention was mainly towards good ideas. Even though ideas matter but more then the idea, its the "Execution". Ask yourself a question - do you have the capability to execute, do you understand how a business is run? Ideas just come and pass unless someone strong doesn't executes them.   Recently a company called "Auction Drop" got his first funding. The idea is simple, a chain of drop off centers for eBay. People drop off their items for what they want to sell at eBay at some store and rest everything the store handles.  urlLink  You Drop It Off. We Sell It On eBay.   Interestingly this idea has been tried earlier and it failed. A company called "EZSale" founded some years back on the same principle had its fall.  urlLink Link   So will AuctionDrop win or fail or why did EZSale failed - answer lies in execution!I remember few words from a talk by Vinod Khosla, where he said one has to pursue things religously against all odds.   The moral is even if you have a great idea, you might not be successful. Strength lies in building yourself strong, knowing the ins and outs, understand things well and then Just Execute It!  
    
    
</post>
<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Douglas Engelbart - the father of modern day computing systems showed us the way of human computing.  I came to know about this great personality through the hypertext community. I still remember in my university time,I was fascinated by the web when I came to experience it, but I failed to realize the importance of hyperlinking in a wider context. To me it looked to me just like "a href" tag within HTML which I took for granted. But can we imagine the web without links today? They are as synonymous as the web itself.   And from there I made my entry into reading  urlLink Open HyperDocument System  and to Douglas Engelbart.  Can we ever imagine "personal" computing without a mouse, display editing, Outline processing, Video-conferencing, hypermedia, multiple windows, linking, in file object addressing? He is the one who is credited with all and that also way back in 1968!!  In 1968 (an era in which computers were just number crunching machines) he and his team did a landmark demonstration causing shock to everyone. The  urlLink videos and pictures  of this are available and I was myself shocked to see all this in one go. I thought of all these techonologies to have had evolved slowly over a period of time.  Stanford in 1998 organised a symposium on Douglas Engelbart - an Unfinished Revolution. The videos of the symposium are available. Though these are a bit long, but I think they are a must see.  urlLink  Videos    There were a number of interesting talks at the symposium.  I thought everyone would have been blown apart by that demo in 1968. But it's wrong. That era was led by people from Artifical Intelligence and some even thought its just crap, and one should make machines intelligent rather than making machines to be used for knowledge workers. Can we imagine that today?  One of the presenters highligted the effect between fast and slow movements. Fast movements like technology changes fade away fast, Slow changes involving paradigm shifts provide the real continuity on a longer term. We can predict things at 5 year (technology) scale, but can we say how things will be 30 years or 100 years down the line? We can make wild gusesses but it takes a lot to seriously think on that scale!  And the most interesting one was: Can we have a Moore's Law on Organizational capability ?  Douglas Engelbart's aim was not to make technology to show document editing or the like but to make computers in a way which increases the collaborative capability of humans to be more productive. This is what we still miss to a large extent even today.   We live in a world where computing is still data crunching but on a different scale. We live in set paradigms and are bound by set paths. We stil need to work out what do we require for providing intutive interfaces for humans which anyone can use and at the same time increase our productivity.   With more digital mobile devices penetrating our world, we need to work more effectively rather than replicating the PC model on these devices.  
    
    
</post>
<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Last year, I was just sitting lazily on my bed watching news, when a particular news item shook me a bit up. It was one of the most interesting thing that I had seen in robotics. A Robotic Human Head mimicing human expressions of a person who is sitting in front of the head. Today I just tried to find and got it in one go.   The article  urlLink The Man Who Mistook His GirlFriend for a Robot   in Popular Science describes the process in detail. You can also find videos at this  urlLink  link  . 
    
    
</post>
<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       A recent  urlLink article  in bbc news shows sony laboratories in Tokyo enable one to pick and pass information enabling swapping/sharing of information amongst digital devices.   Pick and drop'  Dr Rekimoto's lab has extended the drag and drop technique used in most PC software to create a 'pick and drop' technique.  So the owner of a handheld computer can pick up a file from their device, using a special pen, and drop it onto the screen of another computer, by placing the pen on its screen. 	 These technologies are very interesting for truly intuitive interaction Ian McClelland, Philips. He refers to this approach as 'direct manipulation'. It allows people to visually select and move information in physical space, rather than having to understand abstract concepts of networks and servers.  The pick and drop technique would make it easy for two colleagues in a meeting to exchange files between their laptop computers, new acquaintances to pass each other electronic business cards, or friends to swap references to websites or music tracks they like.  Another technique that the labs has developed is referred to as 'pick and beam'.  This uses displays projected onto tables and walls, using data projectors, that act as extended working spaces.  Documents can be dragged using a special pen from a computer desktop into these spaces. There they can be spread out or exchanged, allowing people to work with them almost as if they were paper documents.   
    
    
</post>
<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Venus made a rare show passing across the sun today. My colleague in office brought special sunglasses today morning. The view was just superb!   Below is a picture and comments from Rediff.com     Photograph: Ian Waldie/Getty Images. Venus made a pass across the sun on Tuesday -- the first time since 1882.  In a rare alignment that has not occurred in 122 years, the planet appeared to move across the face of the Sun -- an astronomical event known as the transit of Venus.  Before Tuesday, no human alive had seen the event. The next transit of Venus is on June 6, 2012. But miss that one and you are out of luck. The next one will be in 2117.  Venus is visible as a black dot as it transits across the face of the Sun as seen from the Greenwich Observatory in London.    
    
    
</post>
<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       1999-2000 were the boom-burst times for the IT industry. It was the time when the mobiles started hitting the campuses, though quite costly for we college goers then.   I still remember with my friends discussing the new buzzword SMS, with some disagreeing that mobile phones are crappy with small screens and too few keys to type. Some one in the crowd said, "SMS will fail". And many in the technology market thought the same and have been taken aback by the success of SMS.  I regard mobility and simplicity to be the two key factors for the success of SMS. Everything from just ringtones, wallpapers, dating, news, airplane updates - any other application of internet has moved to this primitive medium called SMS. The days when we are moving into 3-D visualizations, high tech areas such as nano technology, a simple technology (primitive to current standards) has turned into a multi billion dollar industry. This is what is mobility and simplicity really are.  The current world of mobility is just a beginning. Its still novice - it is at its pre internet stage. There is much more for us to see.   Mobility is getting used to people and People are getting used to mobility.   For mobility to succeed in future, it shouldn't forget the basic principles :  - Provide hit and click services (People need services anywhere anytime, one just needs to provide them in a straight forward fashion). I want to buy a TV, give me the price of TV from the local store. Let the server handle all the complexities and give a user, a hit and click service.  - Simple interfaces which everyone can use (let computing come to people rather than people need to take a course to learn).  - Make Mobility rich but not complex.  
    
    
</post>
<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       For past few days, I was trying to look for people, institutes or companies in India involved in Semantic Web. In Europe it seems to be quite huge effort from some time. I couldn't find much information on these topics earlier.  But today, I found something interesting. NCST (National Centre for Software Technology) Bangalore (now known as C-DAC)has a particular research group called " urlLink Data  Knowledge Engineering " which works on Semantic Web. Its quite good to see indian institutes moving in that direction. They have a number of projects running in the knowledge domain.  - KMap - A Web-based Knowledge Management Application   -  urlLink Viksha  - Knowledge Enabling Devices  Viksha  aims at building a channel through which extraction and addition of knowledge through different data sources existing inside an organisation and combining it with Internet. The whole system is broadly categorized into three parts: -Existing databases, Ontology and then an Intelligent Browser.  -  urlLink VXML  - Visual Document XMLiser  Aim is to convert unstructured text data to structured XML format using a Visual Editor.  - Semantic Web  urlLink Annotation Tool   The Annotation System makes it possible to make/search annotations using a plugin for Internet Explorer. The annotations can be stored both at the client and at the server end.  The screenshots of the available tools look quite good. Currently not available in public domain, but perhaps might be there soon.  
    
    
</post>
<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       A look at few of the blogs ( urlLink Russel ,  urlLink Pheedo ) seems to show the beginning of RSS Advertising. Pheedo recently did a case study on RSS Advertising.    Pheedo reports that by integrating online advertising into an RSS feed, a new online advertising technique, it has achieved measurably better results than e-mail for its client.   The online campaign for a free IT evaluation was conducted through specialist publication InfoWorld, which could offer direct access to IT professionals.   Pheedo said the six-week effort outperformed the best click through rate in email by over 26% as compared to the industry average of 8.7% CTR reported in DoubleClick’s Q4 2003 Email Trend Report. Furthermore, they were able to lower the effective CPM by three times of that over email, saving its client thousands of dollars.   Writing this, I thought about Google AdSense - did someone one integrate Google Adsense in RSS feeds? The answer is YES. Enough smart people around. But its against google license policy and therefore has been put off.  urlLink [Mehack]   And now yet, another activity -  urlLink BlogAds . Some items from BlogAds FAQ   What are Blogads? Glad you asked that. Blogads are classified ads that appear in blogs and other independent web sites. Each "strip" of Blogads is managed by an independent publisher who sets prices and decides which ads appear.  Thank you. Who gets the cash from Blogads? In traditional media, writers and editors earn less than 20% of total revenues, and 80% of revenues go to newsprint, ink, new computers for the ad reps, parking spots, printing presses, lemonade for the publisher's kids... you get the picture. The coin gets flipped with Blogads: 80% goes to the writer, with 20% paying for technology   Will we see publishers now publishing 10 items in every feed which contain nothing but ads? RSS atleast has a big plus that one can remove it quite easily from his reader. So publishers have to be extra careful that they don't publish feeds which cause a nuisance. What will it be for users? Only time will tell, how mainstream this activity becomes. Right now it looks to be going strong!  
    
    
</post>
<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Today's world-wide web consists mainly of html pages which people view using browsers. In the late 90's IE - Netscape war was one of the hottest wars for maintaining authority on the internet. Browsers are till today the main entry point for viewing content on the Web. Content Providers publish content via HTML and big content providers like Yahoo earn their revenue by advertising.   Today's content industry  web based services are to some extent supported by advertising. The google ADSense program took this advertising to the next level by building a store house which can provide advertisements to any small or big content publisher. Advertising has also in some sense become a lifeline even for consumers to have free services on the web.  The world wide web has grown so big, its not possible for people to sneak each and every corner of the web. People are increasingly feeling the need for content to come back to them depending on their interests rather they going and search for it. They would like to divulge certain tedious or repetitive tasks to software agents which can handle them well on their behalf.  I will like all my resources (content I read or services I use) to be adapted according to my own needs. I want an agent to look and inform me of the best deal for a camera. In this world, where software agents work, what role do current business models for advertising play? They appear to me will slowly fade away in the dark. Things are beginning to already appear with RSS, where users are increasingly viewing information via rss readers or directly in their email boxes rather then going on the web. As we go forward with more and more metadata on the web, demand for user adaptable content and services will increase.  In such a situation, where users don't access content the way the content provider provides, but in a way they want; how can content providers sustain themselves? How can users still get subsidised or free services on internet in a future semantic web scenario where agents are brokering on my behalf?  One solution I can think is the advertising itself can mature from just being static (content or images) to be itself a service. My software agents when looking for content on bbc site for me, also check the metadata based advertisements on bbc's site to get recommendations or in other cases might negotiate some deal.   The next question will be to what extent can these "smart advertisements" lure software agents ?  
    
    
</post>
<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Blogger.com added a simple Html editor for writing blog entries. Taking the Gmail efforts further with some nice javascripting, looks like soon we might have full fledged editors via the web. The current  interface provides the basic funtionality of  font ,  size , text alignment, inserting links , back ground colors, spell checking, numbered and bullet point lists.     Even the keyboard shortcuts work!     Here's the  urlLink screenshot  for how it looks.    Blogger. com doesn't provide an image upload service. I just tried at Flickr. I thought it would give me a direct url for an image which I make public, but it didn't do that. So for now I need to look for another photo upload service.  
</post>
<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Edd Dumbill wrote about his analysis of the recently launched Opera Mobile Accelerator. Mobile Phone Users can use a proxy server hosted by Opera through a montlhy subscription fees for getting optimised content saving bandwidth and cost benefit. I had a previous entry on the same topic  urlLink here .  Here is what Edd writes :     I decided to take the Accelerator for a spin on my Sony Ericsson P800 phone, running the Opera 6.31 browser.  Setting the proxy up was simply a case of entering the URL of an auto-configuration page.  Thereafter I browsed as normal.   The speed-up you get will depend on the content you read and how much Accelerator can optimize it. To see if Accelerator lived up to its claims, I performed some experiments. I tried three different sites: my own weblog, BBC News and O'Reilly Network. The latter has adverts on it, which introduces some unknowns into my measurements.    I tested the amount of kilobytes my phone had to send and receive over GPRS in order to load each page. I am charged by total data transfer, so the sum of these is the key figure. I didn't test download times, as there were too many variables involved to get an objective measure.    Here are the download results.                  Site           Normal (KB)           Accelerated (KB)           Improvement                urlLink My weblog            8 + 52 = 60           8 + 32 = 40           33%                urlLink BBC News            59 + 135 = 194           26 + 36 = 62           68%                urlLink O'Reilly Network            27 + 135 = 162           34 + 92 = 126           22%          Note that the cache was cleaned and Opera restarted before every load.    So it looks like I'm getting savings in bandwidth between around 20% and 70%. At the top end, this is definitely consistent with Opera's claim of 70%. At the lower end, however, it looks like Opera's 50% figure is a little optimistic.    The savings afforded by the Accelerator definitely improve when used in conjunction with your browser's cache.  I performed the experiment again for my weblog, but without cleaning the cache:                  Site           Normal (KB)           Accelerated (KB)           Improvement                urlLink My weblog            8 + 36 = 44           7 + 14 = 21           52%          Of course, when browsing on my P800, I don't always start either with no cache, or a full cache.  Neither do I always have image loading on, as I did for this test.  It certainly is the case that I save bandwidth by using Accelerator, whatever the conditions.     Continued.    So, crunch point.  Will Mobile Accelerator pay for itself?  I often use a lot of GPRS data, but more often through fetching my email over a Bluetooth link to my laptop.  Accelerator only works with web content, obviously, so how much do I need to browse to make a saving?  Opera are offering the service at 3 Euros per month.  Given that I might expect to get around 50% data saving, this means the break-even point is 6 or more Euros worth of GPRS in web browsing.      The complete entry is over  urlLink here .       
    
    
</post>
<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       AlwaysOn Network conference (AO2004) took place at Stanford University July 13 – 15. The webcast of the conference is available live.  Thanks to  urlLink Paul Allen  from Infobaseventures for the link.     There are some interesting panel discussions. Just looked through the war between the WIFI and 3G technologies. Came to know about some interesting facts - companies like Tropos Networks using Mesh technologies with technologies such as WiMax can build up a wide area network for a whole city in just 3 weeks. Next year in Asia - WiMAX will be rolled out in some particular cities. It looks to be growing at much faster pace.    The key to all wireless technologies is still - what does a consumer want? What kind of applications - irrespective of any network will provide the kind of mobility a user wants.    The link to all the web casts and the schedule can be had from here .   urlLink http://www.alwayson-network.com/events/index.php      
    
    
</post>
<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       NW Venture Voice has a nice blog entry " urlLink How to Shop for Venture Money " for entrepreneurs.       Rule #1:    Don’t raise money.             What?    A VC saying don’t sell equity?    Selling equity is the most expensive way to finance a company.    Exhaust ALL other options first.    When I left Microsoft in 1997 to start  urlLink Loudeye , the first six months were total bootstrapped.    We begged, borrowed, and squeezed whatever we could out of our reserve cash, friends, neighbors, and even strangers.    The first money into an idea is always the most expensive and it should be your own if you can afford it, your own sweat if you can’t.    If you believe in your idea, run up your credit cards, take out a second mortgage, apply for research grants, go to the  urlLink SBA , borrow money from your parents, whatever you do, put some real skin in the game before sharing with any equity investors. Think about it; future investors will value the personal commitment; if your idea is great, why sell part on the cheap? Here is another trick, put in the early money as a bridge loan which converts at a later financing round.    Let the market put a value on your idea later, after it is worth more!    Necessity is truly the mother of invention.    Less money = more necessity = more invention!        </post></Blog>