<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   “Hey, sleepyhead! Wake up!” Cherie was shouting at her sister in an effort to rouse her. Cheryl did not respond until she received a nasty poke to her stomach. She jolted up, and groaned when she saw her sister’s mischievously smiling face. Just then Matt and Muthu entered the room. Both of them had already changed into their robes and seemed very surprised that Cheryl had just awoken.  	 “Well, hurry up, the carriages are leaving in an hour, and there’s breakfast downstairs...” Matt said impatiently.  	 Cheryl stared, bleary-eyed, at him, before finally getting to her feet. As she walked into the adjoining bathroom and shut the door, she distinctly heard Matt ask, “Is she  always  like this?”  					----------  Forty-five minutes later they were all assembled in the pub below. The Hogwarts students were looking very odd indeed, with their robes and various trunks in stark contrast to their families, who were still in Muggle attire. They were chivvied out by Bill, the innkeeper, who kept on shouting “You’re late! You’re late!” Cheryl thought it was more likely that they were blocking the entrance of the inn and that Bill wanted them out. 	 They made their way out of the inn and walked briskly down the alley. At the end of the alley they turned right, into a lane which led to a large open space – it was about the size of a town square. The space was not as empty, though. There were nearly thirty black horseless carriages there. Hogwarts students were milling around, making it seem as if the space was some shimmering deep-blue sea. After saying their goodbyes to their families (Cheryl was more than happy to leave her sister behind), Cheryl, Muthu and Matt made their way onto one of the carriages. They were soon joined by their fellow Griffindoor fifth-years Minyu, Hu Ping, Barnabas, Yi Fan and Eunice. The carriages had had Engorgement Charms placed on them – though they looked small from the outside, the eight of them could fit inside comfortably. Their trunks went into a separate wagon attached to the carriage.  	 A few minutes later their carriage began to move. “Hold on tight!” Minyu shouted, as the carriages suddenly began to lift off the ground of their own accord – or perhaps there were invisible horses pulling the carriages. Soon they were cruising in the sky, passing so close to those fluffy cumulus clouds it felt as if they could touch them. Cheryl, having taken the seat nearest to the window, was enjoying the view of the Central Business District, slowly moving on to tidy HDB estates, which slowly became more sparse as they travelled westward.  	 “Wonder what’d happen if a Muggle saw these carriages...” Yi Fan mused.  	 Matt sighed. “Muggles  can’t  see these carriages – when the carriages take off, an Invisibility Charm is activated and they all become invisible.” 	 “Cool!” Yi Fan replied, his eyes round with amazement. His shoulders drooped slightly as he said quietly, “I wish I could do magic like that...”  	 No one said anything. They all knew that Yi Fan had barely scraped through fourth year with his poor grades.  	 They all kept quiet for a while, not knowing what to say. The awkwardness was finally broken when Hu Ping asked, “Who d’you think will take the vacant teaching posts?” 	 “My dad reckons they’ll be people from the Ministry. I mean, now that You-Know-Who’s back, the Ministry’s worrying that he can somehow spread his influence here. So they’ll be “implanting” Ministry officials as teachers in order to see that all goes well at school.” Barnabas said darkly. 	 “I say, that’s nonsense,” Eunice retorted. “About You-Know-Who coming here, I mean. In the first place, there’re so few wizards here that he’ll find it hard to find people to bewitch and whatnot. And why would he care about small fry like Singapore anyway?”  	 “Well, hey, he tried to kill Harry Potter, who was a baby...” Cheryl piped up. “And did I tell you how handsome Harry is now…”  	 The rest rolled their eyes. Cheryl continued dreaming, a faraway look in her eyes. 	 “We’re slowing down,” Muthu said, peering out.  	 The carriage did indeed seem to be slowing down – it soon descended and landed on a grass clearing right in front of the castle. All around them carriages were landing. It was a queer sight – this whole posse of black carriages, flying by themselves.  	 “We’re just in time for the feast,” Barnabas said. 	 Cheryl nodded fervently. Having rushed that morning, she had had no time to take breakfast. Quickly, together with her friends, she joined the stream of students entering the castle.   

						
</post>
<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   	 The interior of The Wacky Wizard was – in one word – smoky. Wizards were sitting at tables with rather mismatched chairs, either reading the latest edition of  Transfiguration Today  or the local wizard paper,  The Daily Chronicle . Most of them had a pipe and were smoking. What it was Cheryl didn’t know, but it sure stank. It smelt like burning rubber. 	 The trio edged their way past the crowded tables and to the back of the inn, where all the private parlours were situated. Just as they passed Parlour 1 Cheryl heard a rather familiar voice.  	 “Well, I’m not too sure, Minellus, it’s just so odd...” the voice had a rather fruity note to it. It was so familiar... suddenly it clicked – it was Percival Tan, the Minister of Magic. Cheryl pressed her ear to the door. What business did the Minister have in the Wacky Wizard? 	 “Cheryl! What’re you doing?”  	 Cheryl jumped. Muthu was staring at her. 	 “Nothing... er, tying my laces... you go in first...” As Muthu disappeared behind the next door, Cheryl chanced a peek. As the door had not been closed properly, there was a tiny crack through which she could see. She could see the Minister – he looked slightly puzzled. There was a bottle of wine on the table in front of him – the wine looked abnormally red. Almost like blood... 	 “Why don’t you take a drink, Minister,” another man’s voice said, sourly. Cheryl saw the Minister take a sip of the wine. Suddenly she felt something brush by her. She yelped, only to realize that it was the resident tabby cat of the inn. Breathing a sigh of relief, she resumed peeking, only to see the Minister look rather dreamy, his eyes unfocused. He uttered a nonchalant “Yes.”  	 “So if you’ll just sign here, Minister...” the other man handed over a piece of paper.  	 “Cheryl! Hurry up!” This time it was Matt at the door, staring at her queer stance.  	 “Coming,” Cheryl replied, as she straightened up. She put the scene she had just witnessed out of her mind. It wasn’t her business anyway.  					 ----------  It was a thoroughly enjoyable meal, consisting of many, many delightful dishes whipped up by the resident chef at the Wacky Wizard. They were all sitting back in their comfy chairs, replete and relaxed, chatting amongst themselves. Cheryl finished the last of her durian puff and groaned.  	 “My jeans feel tighter,” she complained. Everyone laughed indulgently, for they too had eaten fit to burst. 	 “Time to go to bed, kids,” Mr. Cheah said, yawning. “You all have an early day tomorrow.” 	 No one argued – the food was making them feel very, very drowsy. Cheryl climbed the stairs up to her room and collapsed on her bed. She had just enough time to close the hangings before falling into a deep sleep, the taste of durian still on her lips...  

						
</post>
<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Cheryl spun round to see a boy of around 15 grinning at her. He had clearly suffered from the ravages of acne – there were still some pimples on his once-chubby face, which was now rather thin. His twinkling eyes were framed by grayish-blue glasses and his fringe hung rather heavily over his forehead. Even as he spoke he pushed it up. Dressed in shorts and a bright orange tee, he looked every inch an ordinary Muggle, yet he was also a wizard, by the name of Matthew Chia. 	 “’Morning, Uncle, Aunty,” he said, turning to Cheryl’s parents, who nodded back. “I daresay you’d like to talk to my parents? They’re in the inn,” he said, winking. Mr. and Mrs. Cheah smiled and went off down the street, dragging Cherie with them.  	 “C’mon, let’s go get our books,” Matt said. 	 The street they were walking on was the only magical one in the whole of Singapore. Small shophouses lined it, filled with a dazzling array of wizarding... stuff. Many of the shophouses were made out of marble, giving the street a white shine that was brought out by the golden sunlight. In fact, the whole street was so white it looked as if everything had been scrubbed clean. The cobbled street was packed. Some wizards were wearing Muggle outfits – others had opted for more ambiguous gauzy shawls, scarves, and robes. A large crowd was gathered round  Quality Quidditch Supplies  – the store was, of course, an enterprising Singaporean franchise of the British original. The crowd was oohing and aahing at the Firebolt in the window – broomstick imports always came in rather late.  	 Meanwhile to their right was  My Magical Best Friend , the pet store. Hoots, coos, purrs and various discomforting squeals were emanating from the dim interior. Walking on, Cheryl and Matt passed  Farquhar’s Freaky Factory  – William Farquhar was the first chronicled creator of a joke shop. Soon they came to  Raffles’ Publishers , where they were to buy their books. The place was overflowing with students – Cheryl recognized Wee Minyu, Chng Hu Ping, Chew Yi Fan and Jaslyn Leong, and waved frantically to them. Meanwhile, Matt was speaking to the shop attendant. 	 "...yes, we need two copies of  Jinxes for the Jinxed and Hexes for the Helpless ... yes, two copies... no, I don’t want to copy them, I want  two copies ...” 	 They left the store a few minutes later, moneybags considerably lighter and bags much heavier. The books this year were unusually thick. And expensive. 	 “Hey Cheryl! Matt! CHERYL!” someone was shouting. Cheryl turned round and saw yet another friend, Muthu. He had never revealed his real name to them and had always insisted they call him Muthu, even though he wasn’t Indian in the slightest. He was rather dark though. Cheryl noticed that he was much taller than when she last saw him the previous year. She sighed. Everyone was growing except herself. 	 “I thought you’d already bought all your stuff long ago?” Cheryl asked. 	 “Well, my parents decided to let me stay the night at The Wacky Wizard… you are too, aren’t you? And Matt?” 	 The other two nodded, and they continued ambling down the street, talking about how they had spent the holidays, about their homework (which had been horrendously difficult and tedious) and the coming school term. They went to the apothecary to get their potion ingredients (Cheryl’s supplies of hedgehog quills and moonstone were running low). Very soon it was evening, and the sun was setting on a blood-red horizon. The shophouses in Change Alley were bathed in gold, orange, pink and purple, and the lamps suddenly came to life, giving out soft yellow light.  	 The trio made their way to a small inn near the end of the alley. A sign hanging at its entrance proclaimed it as “The Wacky Wizard Inn – the best in town!” 	 “Well, obviously it’s the best, it’s the  only  one in town,” said Matt dryly. They passed the large bronze statue of a wizard in top hat prancing about and went inside the inn.   

						
</post>
<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   In one of the rooms of a seemingly-ordinary unit in a housing block, a fifteen-year-old girl lay sleeping. Everything about this girl seemed normal, from her long dark hair down to the tips of her toes. Yet a look around her room clearly showed that she was not what you and I would call “ordinary”. Various books lay scattered on the floor with names such as  Intermediate Transfiguration  and  Charms for the Charmed – An Intermediate Course . On a study table nearby lay several quills, ink bottles, pieces of yellowing parchment, and most mysteriously – a wand. The posters on the walls were of boybands and handsome singers – but unlike normal posters, the people in those posters were moving, flashing their plastic smiles or mouthing lyrics. The clothes spread out on the chair were not your normal T-shirt and jeans, but long, deep-blue robes. 	 Cheryl Cheah was a witch. 	 Even as a solitary ray of light fell on her sleeping form, there was a loud knock on the door, and muffled shouts of “Wake up, sleepyhead!”  	 The girl stirred, and with a yawn, sat up on her bed. Putting on her glasses, she looked up at the clock on the wall. It was 9.30 a.m.  	 Throwing a disgusted look at the door (the shouts were becoming louder, progressing to not-so-subtle insults like “Wake up, you pig!”) she shouted, “Coming!” and got out of bed. She wished she could have slept longer. After all, she had slept at 2 a.m. that morning, having stayed up to celebrate the New Year. 	 After getting dressed and taking a shower, she made her way to the kitchen, finding her family seated round the kitchen table, eagerly awaiting breakfast. “’Morning, sleepyhead,” a man at the head of the table said, smiling. 	 Cheryl grinned back at her father, and sat down at the table. Soon enough she was eating her way through her bacon and eggs with gusto.  	 “You better hurry and get your stuff packed, we’re leaving at 10.30 to get your books,” her mother said, pointing her wand to the plates in the sink. The tap immediately turned on by itself and a sponge started scrubbing the plates. “And, by the way, it’s already 10.15,” Mrs. Cheah said with a small smile. 	 Cheryl choked. Swallowing down the last of her egg, she rushed to her room. She eyed the mess her room was in with horror. Apparently she had not bothered to clear up in the two months of her holiday. Well, she had to pay for her laziness now. Hastily, she threw her robes into a trunk and her books and writing materials into a sling bag. Then snatching her wand from the table, she quickly surveyed the room once again to see if she had left anything behind, before dragging both trunk and sling bag into the hall.  	 “Well, that was quick,” her father said dryly. “Come on, let’s go.”  	 They made their way downstairs and into a car, trying to be as inconspicuous as possible, though how to be inconspicuous with a large trunk and a piece of wood sticking out of your jeans’ back pocket I don’t know. Soon they were off, heading out of the suburban haven of Tampines towards town. 	 The journey was rather quick – Cheryl had barely settled down before they screeched to a halt in front of a tall, imposing building. A sign over the nearest entrance read “Change Alley”. Quickly, they made their way through the entrance and down a rather deserted corridor, stopping in front of an ice cream stall. There was only one person there – a young man of about 20, who was manning the stall.  	 “’Morning, Basil,” Mr. Cheah said briskly. The man named Basil grinned back and waved to Cheryl and her sister Cherie, who were both looking longingly at the many tubs of ice cream on display. 	 “Come on, let’s go before a Muggle sees,” Mrs. Cheah whispered, as the family made their way to the front of a large glass pane at the back of the stall. “Cheryl, you go first.” 	 Cheryl took a deep breath before walking straight through the barrier. It felt as if cool water was cascading down from the ceiling. Yet when she emerged from the other side, she was still perfectly dry. A few moments later she was joined by her family once again. 	 “Welcome to Change Alley,” a voice said.  

						
</post>
<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   400 years ago, Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry was set up in the north of Britain. There it functioned happily for almost 200 years, being one of the few wizarding schools in the world. No matter. 	 In 1819, Sir Stamford Raffles of the East India Company discovered a tiny isle on the tip of the Malayan peninsula. This island soon came to be known as Singapore. Sir Raffles did much for the development of Singapore – changing it from a sleepy, rural island to a bustling trade centre. He set up many schools for the population, and many children benefited from his initiative.          Not many people know, however, that Sir Raffles was in fact a wizard.  	 He had attended Hogwarts when young, and had emerged a fresh-faced graduate with a N.E.W.T in Muggle Studies. As thus he joined the East India Trading Company, planning to carry out the admirable mission of setting up schools for wizards and witches wherever he went. 	 And so, in a remote corner of Singapore, he created a school with the help of a few fellow wizards (one of the most notable was of course, William Farquhar). Having no knowledge of Singaporean names or customs, he named the school Hogwarts, after its British counterpart. He was careful enough, however, to add “Singapore branch” beside the name.  	 He too mimicked the tradition of Sorting students and having Houses. However, having a rather (notoriously) poor memory, he misnamed the four Houses Griffindoor, Huffelpuff, Ravingclaw and Slithering. His colleagues, being too exasperated to correct him, let the names be. And so Hogwarts – Singapore Branch – was set up.   A hundred and eighty-five years on…    

						
</post>
<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Okay, so this is my other blog - for my writing. I don't expect I shall write very often, but when I do I will post here. I don't plan on adding links, but I'll link this from my other blog. I'm not adding a tagboard either - so please use the comments system. Besides, if there's long posts of criticism you can't fit them into a tagboard anyway. =P Or if you're really lazy you can just use the tagboard at my main blog...  It'll be a Harry Potter fanfic - with real characters, i.e. the characters are all people I know. So, erm, any resemblance to people is purely coincidental. =D I know I didn't ask permission to use your names for most people, but I hope you don't mind. I assure you, none of you are evil. And it is never, ever meant to be offensive. It's supposed to be good fun, so I hope everyone's okay with that.   Well, I don't think my writing's very good. But I hope whoever reads will like it anyway.   

						
</post>
<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    As Cheryl trudged down the corridor to her Defense Against the Dark Arts classroom, she felt the brevity of the previous’ night’s conversation dawn upon her. The oily, ominous image of Kiw loomed in her mind. If he could blackmail the Minister, he could do anything. He could take over the school.   As she turned into the classroom, she saw that their teacher wasn’t there yet. Sitting down, she was soon surrounded by a crowd of Huffelpuffs who wanted to hear the conversation she had heard. (Of course, news got around at Hogwarts.)   She was about to begin when the swish of black robes interrupted her. She expected to see Professor Siva but was instead greeted by the face-with-the-mole. She felt her jaw drop, and could almost hear the angry whispers coming from all around her.   “Why the hell does he have to be here?” Jeremy hissed from behind.    Cheryl shrugged. Perhaps he’s blackmailed Professor Siva, she thought dully. That didn’t seem like an illogical conclusion.   “Professor Siva somehow cannot be found in Hogwarts,” Molekiw began with a smirk on his face, “and so I am taking over his lessons. Turn to... page 226 of your textbook. We will be starting on the Reductor Curse, which blasts anything in its path. For example, take a look at this table.”   Kiw rolled up his sleeves and pointed his wand directly at the teachers’ table. “ Leducto !”   Nothing happened. Perhaps it was because Kiw couldn’t pronounce  r ’s and  l ’s properly.    Kiw cleared his throat, and tried once again. “ Leducto !”    Nothing. A few of the girls giggled while the guys withheld snorts.   “Oh, very funny is it?” Kiw asked, but his voice had lost some of its conviction. “How about if I put you in my path instead?”   “His aim’s so bad, I’d be more scared if he were aiming for the thing next to me,” Jeremy whispered gleefully from behind, sniggering. Matt, who was sitting beside him, was rolling about his seat in silent, hysterical laughter.    “I have a meeting to attend now. Er... I want two feet of parchment on the usage of the  Leductor  – er,  Reductor  Curse, to be handed in on Thursday, no excuses.” And with that, Kiw left the classroom.   That shut the guys up.   “Bloody idiot,” Matt swore from behind. “I swear, one day I’ll use whatever curses we’ve learnt against him. Not that we’re learning anything from him at the moment.”   “Priceless moment, that was,” Muthu said, laughing. “ Leducto !  Leducto ! So much for being effectively bilingual,” he continued, stating the fact that Kiw was, of course, extremely Oriental, especially in terms of speech. There was a strong accent when he spoke English – one that caused occasional gaffes such as this.   “Well, it’s still two feet of parchment,” Matt said dully.    “Shut up! I just know you’ll finish it in our next lesson,” Barnabas interjected. He was, of course, right. Matt hid a grin.   “I do wonder though... why he’s here and not Siva?” Cheryl asked thoughtfully.   Everyone else shrugged. Well, most of them. Wan Qing piped up, “Maybe Siva’s just sick!”   They all pondered over this for a while.   “You know, I think that may be the cleverest thing you’ve ever come up with,” Matt said.  ----------  “And they were all  laughing  at me – the idiots!” Minellus Molekiw complained to the girl beside him.   “It’s alright, it’s all over now,” she replied soothingly.    “I can’t get it out of my head! All this time I’m trying to be serious and all they do is laugh at me! I really want this job you know. I like Potions but I want to teach Defense Against the Dark Arts too,” he said childishly.   In her mind, she was cursing at him.  You’re supposed to be my boyfriend, you stupid old goat!  But instead she replied quietly, “Of course you do. And I’m sure the students will all come to accept you in time. Just like I have,” she added, smiling.   He looked into her hazel eyes, and felt all the worry dissipating.   “Of course they will,” he said dreamily.  Just like you have...   ----------  “WHAT?”  “It’s cancelled!” Hu Ping said smugly.   “Woohoo!” Yi Fan cheered.  “The Astronomy test is cancelled? But... but... I’ve already studied for it!” Matt wailed.    “Apparently Professor Huda has something on that evening,” Barnabas added in. “In fact, she says that we may be getting a relief teacher, because she may be going on leave soon,” he added.   “Really? D’you think it’s because we called her... well, you know...  Paddle Pop ?” Minyu asked. Professor Huda had one day worn a multi-coloured outfit to class and had been called by the name of the rather colourful ice-cream. She hadn’t seemed too pleased about it.   “Nah, I don’t think she has such a small temper,” Cheryl said. “Maybe it’s because we’ve been teasing her about Professor Helmi...”   Having seen the two teachers together at mealtimes, between and after lessons, the class had come to the conclusion that they were a pair. This rumour had spread like wildfire round the school and had culminated in Professor Huda giving them a talking-to during one Astronomy lesson.   “Oh my god,” Matt said suddenly from his corner, where he was working on his Defense Against the Dark Arts essay.   “What?” Eunice said.    “I think I know why she’s going on leave,” he said slowly.   “Well, I’ll never!” Muthu and Eunice said in unison. They had been rather affected by a group of old bimbos and had resorted to acting like them.    “She’s going on maternity leave!”  ----------  Dinner that evening was a noisy affair. Of course, with the mysterious disappearance of Professor Siva and the rumour of a pregnant Professor Huda, the students would be anything but quiet. Everywhere there were people shooting furtive glances at the staff table to check if Professor Huda was really donning a maternity dress. Cheryl rolled her eyes. Honestly. If a teacher wanted to get pregnant what did it have to do with the students?   This thought was going through her mind and she was just about to say it out loud to her friends when she bumped into that same Slithering girl from the previous evening.    Yee Tien shot a look of pure disgust at Cheryl and her friends. “So, it’s  you  again,” she said coolly. That girl beside her, Liqin, kept on nodding.   “What’s your problem?” the group said in unison. Most of them were returning the looks of disgust right back to Yee Tien.   “Well, the thing is that  I  am able to take points from Houses now,” she said smugly, holding up a large badge with the words “Molekiw’s Men” on it. The group stared.    “What does...  that  mean?” Muthu asked, puzzled.   “Basically it means that our dear Professor Molekiw wants to have helpers weed out people who break the rules,” she replied. “People like  you , basically,” she continued. “So that’ll be five points for the ankle socks... each,” she said, pointing to the girls, “another five because I don’t like you,” she jabbed a finger at Matt, “oh, and five each for the both of you who have your shirts tucked out,” she shouted to Rachel and Sunny who were coming up behind the fifth-years. She gave them all another superior look before turning on her heel and walking off. Liqin continued staring at them.   “ Liqin !”   She turned, and ran back to Yee Tien, her bimbo traits evident.   "What kind of name is  Molekiw's Men ?" Hu Ping asked.  "Sounds kinda sado-masochistic to me," Matt replied. The rest stared. He cringed.  “Well, I’m not sure I can guarantee I won’t secretly curse her,”he said crossly.    “You’d be doing us a favour,” Barnabas said shortly. “In fact I think she deserves a big slap!”   At that moment, Cheryl couldn’t have agreed more.  

						
</post>
<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    At seven o’ clock that evening, it was the usual stream of students in their white uniforms going into the Great Hall for their dinner. However, in the white there were a few patches of brown and black – the result of the Griffindoors’ Defense Against the Dark Arts lesson.    “He could have just done the lesson in a classroom and given us cushions,” Matt complained.    “Well, grass is healthy, isn’t it,” Minyu said dryly.    “And besides, you look very clean,” Barnabas said suspiciously.    “Oh, it’s very simple really.  Scourgify !” he said, pointing his wand at Barnabas. White foam and bubbles immediately started frothing – out of Barnabas’ mouth.    Matt clapped his hand over his mouth. “Oh NO, er, sorry, bad aiming, er,  Scourgify !” he said once again, and this time the spell worked. The muddy patches simply faded away. Barnabas stopped frothing at the mouth and instead started to strangle Matt.    Cheryl giggled. Just at that moment she bumped into a girl going in the opposite direction, who turned round and glared at her.    “Watch where you’re going,  Miss ,” the girl said snidely. The girl next to her, rather pretty but with a vacant expression on her face, nodded, trying to sneer. Cheryl stared back, but Eunice pulled her away.    “Ignore her,” Muthu said calmly.    “Who’s she?”    “Her name is Yee Tien – and the girl beside her – she’s called Liqin,” Eunice replied vaguely. Her eyes seemed trained on the teachers’ table.    “They’re from Slithering, aren’t they?” Cheryl asked, knowing this was a rather rhetorical question. All Slitherings were rude and bore smirks on their faces. Most, at least. The others might be considered as bimbos.    They sat down, eagerly awaiting their dinner. As they waited, Cheryl happened to look up at the Staff table, where she saw Professor Molekiw apparently deep in conversation with Professor Siva, who had a rather blank expression on his face. The glasses in front of them held horribly red wine. Cheryl shuddered. She did not like the look that was on Kiw’s face now – a mix of triumph and malice.    “Eh, Cheryl! Food’s here,” Cheryl heard Muthu from a seemingly far way off. She shook her head and glanced at the food. There were large platters of sushi and rice and fries – the school was trying hard to have a varied menu. Cheryl shook her head again.    “I’m on a diet,” she said.  ----------  As Matt was returning to his common room from the washroom after dinner, he could not help but hear whispers coming from the classroom next to him. Quietly, he stopped outside the door.    “Well... what are we going to do about,  you know ,” a hushed voice said in panic. The voice had an unmistakable lilt to it – Professor Huda’s.    “I don’t know. It was your fault in the first place! All the fooling around,” a male voice said. This one was once again unmistakable – Professor Helmi’s.    Matt’s eyes widened in horror, but he pressed his ear to the door and continued listening.    “It was your fault! You got me all excited,” Professor Huda replied. “Come on, I can’t hide it forever. It’s already the seventh month! It  has  to come out soon!”    Matt had heard enough. He ran.   ----------  As Cheryl neared the staffroom, she could hear raised voices, obviously arguing.    “Well, Smurf, it’s all very regrettable, and I don’t know what possessed me when I signed the document – but there it is! It’s a legally binding contract!” this voice was all too familiar...   “It is an excuse for Ministry-sanctioned surveillance,” the voice of the Headmaster replied coolly. “I am sure you know, Percival, that I do not allow that in my school.”    “Minellus asked me whether he could be Discipline Master at Hogwarts, knowing you would never allow that – and I allowed him to. I don’t know why I did, but I’m glad I did! Such discipline standards in a hallowed institution simply cannot be allowed. I hear all these rumours about students vandalising school property, graffiti on walls, even  teachers  acting lovey-dovey in front of students –“    “And that is all they are – rumours. Are you so weak as to believe them, Percival?” And then in a much gentler tone, the Headmaster continued. “He is terrorizing the school. Please, cancel the contract.”    Cheryl stopped at the door and pressed her ear to it. If she was not wrong, Minellus Molekiw had somehow become Discipline Master at Hogwarts by the order of the Minister, who didn’t know why he had allowed Molekiw to become Discipline Master in the first place. And now the Headmaster was asking the Minister to cancel Molekiw’s contract as Discipline Master. It didn’t fit in.    “Ah... Minister,” it was another voice, the fruity tone of Minellus Molekiw.    “Please inform me of your decision when you are done, Percival,” the Headmaster said curtly. Cheryl heard the swish of robes and the distant sound of a door closing. Kiw and the Minister were alone now.    “Minellus... these reports that the Headmaster has given me... you seem to be abusing your authority here,” the Minister said rather uncertainly. “I think...I will have to order you to leave Hogwarts,” he finished lamely.    “But you signed the contract, Minister,” Molekiw replied coldly. “I am not under your jurisdiction now. It says so here: ‘Once this contract is signed by the Minister for Magic, the Discipline Master will no longer be underany jurisdiction, and will be the highest authority in the school.’”    “But... but... I’m the Minister!”    “You know, Minister,” the voice of Molekiw said, and Cheryl could almost imagine his lip curling, “I know some things about you. Like how you cannot perform even a simple Levitation Charm...”    The Minister sputtered in anger.    “I’m sure if I released that fact to the press they’d have a field day...”    “Are... are you blackmailing me?” the Minister said weakly. There was fear in his voice.    Silence. Then – “I’m afraid I am, Minister. I trust I will not be removed from this post. A good evening to you,” Molekiw said smoothly.    Just then Cheryl heard it – ten rings. Ten o’ clock. Any student caught outside of their common room after this time would have to do a detention with Kiw. Reluctantly, Cheryl tore herself away from the door and sprinted back to the Griffindoor common room.  ----------  “I just heard,” Cheryl gasped out as she practically jumped through the portrait hole to get into the common room, “Kiw talking to the Minister.”    Her friends stared at her. “What?” Muthu said, nonplussed.    Cheryl proceeded to act out the conversation she had just heard.    “Wait a minute..."Hu Ping said slowly. “You’re saying Kiw somehow deceived the Minister to make him Discipline Master here, but the Minister doesn’t know why he did it? How odd.”    Cheryl nodded fervently.    “And also that now Kiw is blackmailing the Minister so he can keep his job here?”    Cheryl nodded again.    Silence.    And then the torrent.    “What an idiot!”    “Stupid Minister! Couldn’t he have just fired Kiw?!”   "Kiw is such a cunning asshole!”    “Hey, people! Hey! HEY!” Matt roared. Apparently he too had just come into the common room, judging from his flushed cheeks and messy hair.    “Huda and Helmi...” and here he lowered his voice to a dramatic whisper, “are having a baby!”   

						
</post>
<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						        A week later, in their common room, eight Griffindoors were seated disconsolately round a rickety wooden table. None of them looked particularly interested in what they were doing, except perhaps one guy at the corner who was busy with an Arithmancy exercise. The others were staring ahead glumly, propping their heads up on their hands, playing unenthusiastically with their parchment and quills.    “We have  three  tests this week,” Barnabas said slowly.    “Don’t remind us,” Cheryl moaned.    The others nodded and sighed. Only Matt looked up from his Arithmancy graphs and frowned. “Well then, why not just study for them?”    They glared at him, and he fell silent.    “School is crap, honestly,” Hu Ping complained. “Especially with such disgusting teachers.”    Minellus Molekiw had, in about a week, introduced about 10 new school rules, most restricting the way students could dress. The girls no longer dared to wear ankle socks for fear of spring checks. The last time someone from Ravingclaw got caught, they had had to spend an hour in the dungeon disemboweling toads. Yi Fan did not dare to keep his hair long. Matt, of course, kept his fringe in check. Eunice had to resort to changing the colour of her shoes to white – or, as Professor Molekiw put it, 75% white.    Matt stifled a large yawn. He placed his parchment down on the table. “I’m done,” he said through another yawn. “’Night.”    “We’ll return you your essays tomorrow,” Muthu said with a small smile. Matt nodded and went off to the guys’ dorm. His essays – Transfiguration and Astronomy, remained untouched on the table. No one could be bothered to copy them now. They’d rush tomorrow morning, as always.    Cheryl felt a bit guilty. This past week she’d been barely coping with classes. She wasn’t the only one – in fact there were plenty of people doing worse than her. At least she had understood Professor Helmi’s convoluted Arithmancy lessons while Minyu was swimming in her confusion. Her Transfiguration and Potions were only just passes, so far. Her Befuddlement Draught had gotten a C, a grade she suspected she got only because Professor Molekiw didn’t like her. She had been one of the many who had to have extra practice on Vanishing Spells. Though she hadn’t fallen asleep in any more Defense Against the Dark Arts classes, she had a feeling Professor Siva was now observing her every movement in his class, something she hated. She needed to be free. She needed somewhere where grades didn’t matter.    “Kiw has just returned the essays,” Eunice said, sounding remarkably happy. She had been named Griffindoor’s Potions rep, and seemed to be really enjoying the job. Why, Cheryl had no idea. Eunice now proceeded to give out the essays. When she reached Cheryl, she gave a wry smile before placing the parchment in front of her friend.    Cheryl looked down. She had gotten a C. Again.    Quickly, she stuffed the paper into her bag (she had forsaken her sling bag as those weren’t allowed in school) before Barnabas could ask. Before she could do that, however, Yi Fan had already held up his paper for the rest to see. He had gotten an F. An F-, at that.    “It’s a record,” he said proudly.     ----------    The next morning, Rachel Kwan and Sunny Ng, Griffindoor fourth-years, were walking down from their dormitory to the Great Hall. They were clad in school uniform (robes were necessary only on Mondays) which consisted of skirt and shirt. They were talking animatedly, not bothering anyone, when –     “Oh no!!” Rachel squealed, as she tried to pull Sunny and turn around.     “Excuse me, my dears,” a cold voice called out from behind them.     They both winced, and turned round. Slowly.  
</post>
<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Five minutes of hurried walking later, they reached their Defense Against the Dark Arts classroom, where they found their teacher already waiting for them. Professor Siva was sitting at his table, propping his head up, tapping his fingers, looking extremely bored.  	 Cheryl entered the classroom and looked round, trying to find her friends (as this was a combined class with the Ravingclaws, this was understandably difficult). She noticed Professor Siva was staring at her. Looking round, she realized that everyone else was already seated. Quickly, she took a seat beside Eunice, cringing at the embarrassment of the situation. 	 “Now that we are all  settled down ,” Professor Siva began in a pointed voice, “I will begin my lesson. As you all know, you all will be taking your O.W.Ls this year, and your O.W.L results are extremely important as they may determine your future in the magical world. While Defense Against the Dark Arts may appear to be an irrelevant subject, I should hope all of you do well. And I may add, if I do stay on at Hogwarts, I will only take on the best students in my N.E.W.T classes.” 	 “As if anyone would want to take N.E.W.T classes with a teacher like him,” Cheryl heard Jeremy Khong, a Ravingclaw, whisper behind her. She stifled a giggle. 	 “Oh, it’s very funny is it?” Professor Siva directed his glare at Cheryl. “Would you like to share the joke with the class?”  	 Cheryl hurriedly shook her head, while silently cursing and swearing at her teacher.  	 “This year we will be concentrating on spells – jinxes, hexes and the spells that counter them. Though I commonly take a practical approach to my classes, for today reading will suffice. Take out your copy of  Jinxes for the Jinxed and Hexes for the Helpless , everyone, and turn to page 3. Begin reading. There will be no need to talk.” 	 The class put away their wands disappointedly, and took out their extraordinarily thick textbooks.  	 Cheryl turned to page 3 and began to read.  The Difference Between Jinxes and Hexes , the title read, in large, bold font. The words after that, however, were the size of words in the newspapers.  Jinxes and Hexes differ in many ways, but the basic difference between them is in their effects ... 	 Cheryl had no sooner reached the second paragraph when she felt a sudden wave of drowsiness come over her, drawing her in its warm blanket. Her eyes were feeling very heavy... 	 “Cheryl!” A voice called suddenly. Cheryl sat up bolt upright, to find Professor Siva staring directly at her. “What is the difference between jinxes and hexes?” 	 “Er...” Cheryl paused. She didn’t know. She chanced a glance at her book, but no sooner had she looked down than when, with a flick of his wand, Professor Siva Summoned the book to him. He slammed it shut, and returned to glaring at Cheryl. 	 “Er...” Cheryl said again. She could hear Jeremy hissing behind her, “ In the effects ...”  	 “Five points from Griffindoor for sleeping in class,” Professor Siva said shortly. “And another five from Ravingclaw for trying to help a student in the wrong,” he added.  	 The rest of the lesson went on without incident. At the end of it all Professor Siva had given them an essay to do, another two feet on the differences between jinxes and hexes, to be handed in the next lesson, which, unfortunately, happened to be Wednesday. Furthermore, he had also confiscated Cheryl’s book, saying he would only return it next lesson. 	 Cheryl was quietly fuming. It was a really crummy day. She had lost ten points for Griffindoor, got into the bad books of Professors Molekiw and Siva on their first day and now had to do an essay without her textbook. Minyu, sensing her anger, placed one arm on Cheryl’s shoulder. “Cheer up,” she said gently. 	 Cheryl returned the gesture with a small smile.  	 “He’s an idiot, that one is,” Jeremy said contemptuously from behind them, as they walked to their next class. “I should be  getting  five points for helping someone!”  	 They laughed. The girl beside Jeremy, called Wan Qing, said to Cheryl, “Oh my goodness... he was so mean to you... what’s his problem?!”  	 Cheryl shrugged. She didn’t care anymore.  	 “Ah, well... bye then,” Wan Qing said, as the Ravingclaws turned left to go to their next class. “See you at practice!” she called out to Muthu, Matt and Eunice, the three Drama Society members. The Griffindoors waved, before going on down the corridor to their Divination classroom. 	 The windows of the classroom were covered with translucent blue curtains, giving the room an odd blue shine. In a corner there was a pot of herbs bubbling – the smell was thick, and, to say the least, rather disgusting. Cheryl shuddered when the smell entered her nostrils. Though she liked Divination as a subject, the atmosphere wasn’t exactly to her liking. She could see that the guys were taking the smell worse than she was – Muthu and Matt were pinching their noses and closing their eyes in horror. 	 “Good morning, my dears,” a misty voice came out of the corner of the room. “How nice it is to see all of you again. My Inner Eye has informed me that all of you are safe and sound – how glad I am to know that.” Their teacher rose from the armchair she was sitting in, and stood facing the class. 	 Professor Kailini did not exactly have very good fashion sense – she was covered in gauzy scarves and shawls, the colours of which often clashed. Cheryl winced when she saw the red of her teacher’s dress accompanied by the bright yellow of a thick woolen coat.  	 “We are supposed to start on astrology this year,” Professor Kailini said softly, in her deliberately misty voice. “However, my Inner Eye has informed me that you all will be particularly adept at this subject.” 	 Cheryl beamed. She, Eunice and Minyu were perhaps the biggest fans of horoscopes and planetary Divination in Griffindoor. 	 “As such I find that there is no need to commence lessons today. All of you may do whatever you wish – though I pray you will not make too much noise. My Inner Eye needs some repose from the noise and bustle of the school.” 	 She withdrew into a chamber and shut the door, leaving the Griffindoors rather surprised.  	 Muthu broke the silence by giving a perfect imitation of Professor Kailini’s voice, which led to a  lot  of laughter. He then whipped out a packet of Exploding Snap cards and turned to the rest with a gleam in his eye. “Cards, anyone?” he called out.  	 Nearly the whole class flocked to him, clamouring for a turn to play. Cheryl, while jostling for a place, saw Matt bent over a piece of parchment, scribbling. He had already written over an inch in his neat handwriting. In front of him his copy of  Interactive Potions  was wide open, turned to the page on aardvark bile.  	 He sensed someone looking at him and glanced up. For a moment he met Cheryl’s eyes, and smiled. “The master copy,” he said pleasantly. 	 Cheryl grinned back. She turned round, back to her card game. 	 At that precise moment the pack of cards exploded.  ----------  “Your hair looks very good, Cheryl,” Professor Helmi remarked an hour later in the Griffindoors’ Arithmancy class.  	 Cheryl forced a smile on her face. She had been trying to somehow mend her frayed hair after the incident with the cards, but only succeeded in making it look fractionally less burnt.  	 ----------  “Well, you can’t say it wasn’t an interesting first day back,” Muthu said in the Griffindoor common room later. The whole bunch of fifth-years had been lamenting about how terrible their first day back at school was. Cheryl especially had taken a big part in abusing their new teachers.  	 “We already have five assignments!” Hu Ping said shrilly.  	 “One foot for Kiw, two for Siva, two exercises for Helmi and another essay for Mr. Teo. Ain’t that lovely?” Matt chimed in from a corner, grinning. He was now deep into his Charms essay.  	 “Can you stop being so irritating and stop doing your assignments?” Barnabas said. 	 Matt shook his head. “I can’t stand undone assignments,” he said simply. He then held up two pieces of parchment. “Potions and Defense Against the Dark Arts, anyone?”  	 They were snatched away from him immediately.  	 “I think we’re all going to die this year,” Muthu dead-panned. “It’s O.W.L year!” 	 “Well, just study hard and you’ll do okay, won’t you,” Matt replied vaguely, as he flicked through his copy of  Charms for the Charmed . 	 “How can we find any time to study with all this homework?” Cheryl retorted.  	 “Just don’t do it then,” Yi Fan said jokingly.  	 The rest gave him patronizing looks. Yi Fan rarely did any homework.  	 Two hours later, the common room was slowly emptying as students went off to their dormitories. Cheryl yawned and put down her quill. At least she had finished her essay on jinxes and hexes. The rest could be dealt with later, she thought, as she walked up slowly to her dormitory. She hoped for the best.  

						
</post>
<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   The next morning arrived, bringing with it cold gusts of wind and bruise-coloured storm clouds. It seemed rather as if a translucent curtain had been placed across the sun – it shone bleakly on the black horizon of dawn. 	 By the time Cheryl had dressed and went down to the Great Hall for breakfast, all her friends were already there, halfway through their toast, cereal and porridge.  Eunice, her toast en route to her mouth, realized Cheryl was standing there like a fool and beckoned to her. Cheryl saw that she had a piece of paper in her hand. 	 “Timetables,” Eunice said promptly, as soon as Cheryl had arrived at the table and squeezed in between Minyu and her.   	 “Well, how is it?” Cheryl asked as she reached out for a piece of toast.  	 “Doesn’t look too good,” Minyu chipped in. “Double Potions, Double Defense Against the Dark Arts,  Double Divination  – can you believe it? It’s double periods of everything!” 	 Cheryl grabbed a timetable and stared at it for a while. She let out a long groan. Minyu was right – they also had double periods of Arithmancy and Charms.  	 “Two new teachers, one slacker, one gay – what more can we ask for?” Muthu added, shaking his head.  	 Privately, Cheryl agreed. The only good teacher on their list today was Mr. Teo, who was, well, charming.  	 “Have you all seen it?” Two voices chimed from the table to the left. Cheryl turned round, and saw two girls – both members of the school’s Drama Society. The short one on the left with a smiling face and eyes framed with spectacles was called Yvonne, and the other one, slightly taller and much darker, again with a smiling face but with a cleft lip, was called Denise. They were both from Huffelpuff – fifth-years as well. 	 “Seen what?” Matt asked. 	 “The first decree,” Denise said snidely, her voice tinged with impatience. 	 “The one which says ‘Students are not allowed to have fringes’,” Yvonne added in, grinning at Matt. 	 The Griffindoors’ mouths dropped open. It was the first time in their schooling life that they had been faced with such a ridiculous rule.  	 “And just who implemented that rule?” Matt asked, disgruntled. He was one of the few boys in the school who did nothing to their hair – as a result they grew fringes. 	 Denise and Yvonne rolled their eyes again. “ The Kiw ,” they said slowly, with mock awe and wonder. 	 Matt made a funny noise between a curse and a cough. Apparently he didn’t think much of Professor Molekiw. “What if we don’t follow the rule?” he asked a moment later. 	 “The student’s hair will be cut by  the Kiw  himself,” the other two replied, sniggering.  	 ----------  “There’ll be worse to come,” Barnabas said later, as they made their way to the dungeons for Potions.   “Oh, I guess he’ll start banning centre partings,” Hu Ping said in mockery of Barnabas’ neatly parted hair. He received a cold, threatening glare and a poke in the stomach as retribution.  “We’ve arrived,” Cheryl said dully, to stop the guys from bickering. She sat with Minyu and Eunice at a table in the centre of the room, with the guys behind them. This arrangement was convenient as the girls could simply turn around and ask the guys (who were better in Potions) questions regarding the class. No sooner had they sat down than when the hem of black robes swept into sight, soon followed by the rather formidable figure of Minellus Molekiw. He was wearing a most unpleasant smirk on his face. Cheryl wished she could slap him.  He stood in front of the teacher’s table, and looked at the class, the smirk plastered on his face. Cheryl now had a strong urge to throw her cauldron at him.   “Well? I expect to be greeted, you know,” he said, eyes glinting malevolently.  He received a dull chorus of “Good morning, Professor Molekiw.” But Cheryl swore she heard a mocking whisper of “Good morning, Professor  Mole ,” coming from behind her.  “Good morning,” Professor Molekiw replied coldly. “As I am sure you know, I will be your new Potions teacher. Before I start, I must set a few ground rules for this class. First, I expect all homework to be handed in on time. Next, I expect all students to be dressed appropriately and neatly in my classes. Hair is not allowed to grow past the neck of your robes, and gel is not allowed anywhere on your hair. Also, fringes are not allowed to grow past a maximum of 2 cm, something I posted on all House noticeboards today, and something that this student here seems to have ignored...”  At this he pointed his wand to Matt’s hair. A second and a flash of light later, Cheryl saw that his fringe was gone and the ends of his hair looked extremely frayed. In fact little wisps of smoke seemed to be floating out of them. The whole class laughed, both at the sight of Matt’s hair and the shocked expression on his face.  “You think it’s funny, do you?” Professor Molekiw’s voice said, dangerously soft. “You think it’ll be funny if I did the same to you?” 	 The laughter died immediately.  “You will be sitting for your Ordinary Wizarding Levels this year, and I do not want any of you to fail Potions. In fact I would expect all of you to get an E, if not...” he trailed off, smiling evilly.  “Right. Now, today we will be concocting a Befuddlement Draught. The instructions are on the blackboard. You have one hour. Begin.”  The class set about their potion-making quietly, not daring to do anything that their teacher would disapprove of. Cheryl squinted at the instructions on the blackboard and felt her heart sink. She would probably get befuddled by the instructions even before her potion was finished. She tried to concentrate, weighing out her lionfish spine and ginger roots, but soon found herself looking at a potion that was a bright shade of pink, and not the dark red that was required.   “Add more aardvark bile,” she heard Hu Ping hiss from behind her.   “Thanks,” she muttered, but even before she could reach for her aardvark bile she found herself looking at the disgusting face of Minellus Molekiw.  “Trying to cheat on your potion?” He asked, without waiting for an answer. “Five points from Griffindoor,” he said, eyes glinting. “Oh, and another five points for not following the decree,” he said to Matt, who was now looking murderous. Matt returned to his potion angrily, sending dark red drops of it everywhere.  With five minutes left, Cheryl feverishly stirred the liquid in her cauldron. It was still a bright shade of red, but at least it was no longer pink. She thanked her lucky stars she had Hu Ping behind her.   “Your potion should now be ready,” the voice of Professor Molekiw said. “Cork some in a bottle and leave the sample on the table. You will receive your results next week. In the meantime, write an essay on the uses of aardvark bile in potion-making. I expect no shorter than two feet of parchment. Remember, late homework gets a zero,” he said sardonically.  Cheryl quickly left her sample on the table before rushing out of the room, where she was joined by the others, all with ugly looks on their faces.  “The  nerve ,” Matt sputtered. “My  hair ...”   “It looks great,” Hu Ping replied sarcastically, though Cheryl could see that he too had been disgusted by Molekiw.  “I wasn’t CHEATING!” Cheryl shouted. “What’s his stupid problem?”  “Calm down, people,” Minyu said placidly. “No use getting worked up... though... why did he have to give us TWO feet of parchment?”  “At least it wasn’t three,” Eunice interjected in an extremely happy voice.   The rest stared at her as if she was E.T. Then, they all burst out into loud complaints again.  “...totally an asshole!”  “What’s his problem?”  “TWO feet of parchment!”  As they walked up to their next class, Cheryl couldn’t help but feel that Professor Molekiw would soon get worse.   She would soon be proved right.    

						
</post>
<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   The castle, from the outside, looked as if it had been somehow transported from somewhere in England or Scotland to Singapore. Well, that was to be expected. Sir Stamford Raffles was bloody British, for goodness’ sake. He also must have been a person who had delusions of grandeur, for the castle was indeed very grand, though old. There was moss on some walls, which were all solid stone magically put together. In the twilight Cheryl could see the warm glow of candles in the upper towers, which housed the various common rooms and dormitories. Cheryl could already imagine her four-poster bed with the hangings and inviting feather pillows...  As she passed the Entrance Hall into the Great Hall, she noticed something was missing. The hall seemed much bigger than usual. She looked round, wondering, before it came to her suddenly – the decorations were gone. 	 At the start of the Welcome Feast there were always large House banners hanging above the House tables – orange for Griffindoor, blue for Huffelpuff, yellow for Ravingclaw and green for Slithering. They were the centre of attraction at every feast because they usually had “special effects”. For example, Griffindoor’s lion would suddenly roar, or white doves would suddenly appear out of Ravingclaw’s two crossed wands. This year, however, they were conspicuous only by their absence. 	 Cheryl nudged her friends and told them. They were not the only ones to have noticed; people from other Houses were also looking up, their faces puzzled. 	 “What happened to our banner?” Minyu wailed. “I miss it! I miss the orange!” 	 Cheryl rolled her eyes. “Bah,” she said. 	 The rest looked at her. 	 “Nothing,” she replied innocently. 	 She could tell Matt was trying extremely hard not to roll his eyes. To prevent herself from going into a fit of uncontrollable laughter (which was often very infectious and led to stares), she quickly sat down at the Griffindoor table, at the extreme right side of the hall. At the front of the hall she saw the teachers’ table – sitting right at the centre was Professor Smurf, the Headmaster. He was chatting to Mr. Teo on his left, who taught Charms – Mr. Teo had decided long ago to ditch tradition and let students call him “Mister”. Next to them was Professor Helmi, Cheryl’s Arithmancy teacher, who was deep in conversation with Professor Huda of the Astronomy department. Rumour had it that these two were a couple. To the Headmaster’s right was Transfiguration teacher Professor June, who was laughing very hard at a joke that Professor Tweety, the resident Herbology teacher, had just told her.  Right at the end of the table sat a very bored and lonely Professor Lulu, the History of Magic teacher. Between Professors Tweety and Lulu there was one empty seat. The seat at the extreme left of the table was also empty. 	 “And soon we’ll find out who exactly they belong to,” said Barnabas grimly.  	 Cheryl looked up, mouth open. How did he know that that was exactly what she was thinking about?  	 Barnabas looked back down at her, eyebrows raised at her expression of round-eyed surprise. “What?” he said after a pause. 	 Cheryl stared back.  	 “Bah,” she said.  ----------	  Two hours and one hell of a feast later, the Great Hall looked like a repeat of the dinner at The Wacky Wizard, except that this time, it was on a much larger scale. Most of the students were already yawning – after all, eating and talking at the same time required plenty of energy. However, Professor Smurf did not seem to notice any of the students’ lethargy – he stood up and raised his hand for silence. 	 The hall went quiet immediately. The headmaster smiled. “And so we begin another school year,” he began. “But before we begin, I must introduce our two new teachers. Please welcome Sivanesan s/o Makesan, who will be taking the Defence Against the Dark Arts post.”   At this Cheryl glanced once again at the staff table. The two empty seats were now occupied. Professor Sivanesan, a rather broodingly handsome young Indian man, had gotten to his feet and bowed, a trace of a smile on his lips.   “...and also Minellus Molekiw, who will be our new Potions master,” Professor Smurf continued. There was a smatter of applause for the two new teachers. Apparently no one was really bothered.  Cheryl took a hard look at the man called Minellus Molekiw, her new Potions teacher. She did not like his appearance at all. His skin was sallow, and his eyes glinted with a rather crazed light – rather like that of a lunatic. Moreover, there was a mole on his right cheek. It was twitching rather unpleasantly. His face was so oily it was shining in the bright lights of the Great Hall. Cheryl wondered if this man’s character was as disgusting as his appearance. 	 Professor Smurf raised his hand again, and once again the hall fell silent. “However, that is not all,” he continued. “I must also announce that Professor Molekiw will take on the post of Discipline Master in our school. Apparently the Ministry has seen it necessary to create such a post here in Hogwarts...”  	 He trailed off. Professor Molekiw was whispering something into his ear. The headmaster listened intently before giving a curt nod and sitting back down. 	 Now Professor Molekiw stood up. He cleared his throat loudly. Cheryl sighed. What on earth did he want to say? 	 “I am pleased to teach at such a prestigious school,” he began in a distinctly sour voice. “I assure you I will do my utmost best as a Potions teacher. However, I must also inform you that I hold the post of Discipline Master in this school. The post of Discipline Master is something the Minister of Magic deems necessary, given... current events.” A smile flickered and died on his lips, which were pursed into a thin line. They made him look like a horse.   “As Discipline Master I will be in charge of maintaining the discipline standards in this school and ensuring that no student goes astray due to bad behaviour. I will also make sure that the school is a conducive learning environment – my first action has been to take down all the decorations, as they will distract you from your studies. I will give you a full review of the discipline standards I expect in this school very soon. I assure you, any student who steps out of line will be punished as he or she deserves. The school will be run the way I want it. Of course, I hope that all of you will co-operate with me, so that my job will be made much easier.” 	 He sat back down, even as Professor Smurf called out, “All students to your dormitories now!”  	 Cheryl joined her friends as they walked out of the Hall and climbed the stairs to Griffindoor Tower. They all bore looks ranging from disgust to shock on their faces.  	 “He’s really an idiot, isn’t he?” Muthu said. “ The school will be run the way I want it ... he sounds like some power-crazy maniac to me.” 	 “I told you the Ministry was interfering here,” Barnabas muttered darkly. “He’s even endorsed by the Minister!” 	 “ Why  did he have to take down the decorations? The  orange  decorations!” Minyu complained.  	 “Well, just as long as he doesn’t set rules that are  too  strict,” Cheryl said. “And I think he should really do something about his face. Yucks!” She shivered, the image of Molekiw’s twitching mole still in her head. 	 “I thought what he said was okay...” Eunice said rather thoughtfully.  	 The rest gave her incredulous looks, but she didn’t notice. 	 After climbing up the five flights of stairs leading to Griffindoor tower, which was at the north end of the castle, they stood in front of a large portrait of a lady in a rich velvet evening gown. She was certainly pretty. However, she wasn’t looking at all happy, with her arms folded and her eyes trained on something far in the distance. Her stance looked rather like a certain East India Company employee’s... 	 “Hedgehog quill, Lady Raffles,” Matt said to the portrait. “A Prefect told me,” he said nonchalantly to the others gathered round.  	 Lady Raffles gave a prim nod, and the portrait swung open to reveal the warm, cosy Griffindoor common room. It was certainly a large room – there were over ten long tables in it, each accompanied by a collection of mismatched chairs – plush armchairs, wooden, hard-backed ones, and stools. On the left side of the room there were the tall windows, now wide open. On the right side was a long noticeboard. At the end of the room, right in front of the Griffindoors, were the two staircases that would lead to their dormitories.  	 The Griffindoors tumbled in, most of them yawning. Cheryl did not stop by the noticeboard to see whatever notices were there, but instead said her goodnights to her friends and ambled up to her dormitory. There she was greeted by her four-poster bed with the hangings and inviting feather pillows. 	 She could not resist.   

						
</post>
<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   January faded imperceptibly into February, and before the fifth-years knew it, they had already lived through one month of torture and tests (of course, the two were synonymous with each other). February marked many things. It marked the beginning of the Quidditch season. And it marked... well, it marked the beginning of a lot of things.           Cheryl had gradually gotten used to seeing Kiw multiple times a day. She had grown to be more rule-abiding, pulling her socks up (in both the literal and metaphorical sense), paying attention during classes, keeping her fringe short. Her friends, however, were slightly more unfortunate.           “But sir, it’s so hot to tuck in our shirts  completely !” Rachel said innocently, staring at the Man with the Mole. Sunny was finding it rather difficult to keep her feelings inside though, and tried to put on a forced smile while stuffing her shirt in angrily.           “It tarnishes the school’s image. Do you understand that?” he said waspishly.           “As if we care,” Sunny muttered under her breath.           Unfortunately for her, Kiw heard.           “Oh yes you do,” he said, dangerously close to her. She could see the beads of oil on his greasy nose. “Or at least, you will when I’m done with you,” he continued. “Ten points from Griffindoor, and a detention. Ten o’ clock tonight. Be punctual.” With that, he stalked off.           Sunny stared sourly at his retreating figure. Rachel patted her on the shoulder. No words, no vulgarities could ever properly describe the lump of poo that was Kiw.           “What lesson do we have now, anyway?” Rachel asked, trying to change the subject.           Sunny thought for a moment, before clapping a hand on her mouth. “Crap! It’s Defense Against the Dark Arts!”           They grabbed their bags, and ran.  ----------           Five minutes later, Sunny and Rachel stood, panting, outside their classroom. They had run like the wind (actually, no, more like a slow breeze) but had still turned up late. Hesitating at the door, they peeped inside the classroom and saw Kiw already droning on to their classmates. Yihui, the nearest to the door, breathed a sigh of relief when she saw them at the doorway. Glancing at Kiw to see if he had seen her not listening, she whispered, “He’s not in a good mood today. Stupid idiot. Anyway, I thought you two had died or something!”           “Actually, my dear,” Kiw called out from the centre of the classroom, “I had told them to go and make themselves presentable. I have never seen two people who have been such incorrigible rule-breakers. Both of you, sit down. And I seem to remember saying that I do not condone talking in my lessons unless I ask you to.  Silencio .”           Yihui opened her mouth to retaliate, but the spell had already done its work – she had an invisible gag over her mouth. Resigned to fate, she slumped back into her chair and crossed her arms, making a face at Kiw. But he didn’t notice. He was busy sending the class back into a stupor.  ----------  The fifth-years were practising Banishing Charms in the bright sunlight that filled their Charms classroom. Mr. Teo, who was in a rather good mood today, went around humming an old melody, helping those who had trouble with the spell.           “Remember,  concentrate  on Banishing the cushions! And also that nice wrist movement we’ve been practising!”           “Er... the swish and flick?” Muthu said absent-mindedly, as he performed the movement. His cushion, instead of flying away from him, flew up into the air where it hovered for a few seconds, before coming down to fall on his head. The result looked quite like a girl with a pink hat on.           Mr. Teo hurried over and corrected him.           “You know, I think Professor Huda’s really on maternity leave,” Matt suddenly piped up, as he Banished another cushion into the box they were supposed to be aiming at.           Hu Ping stared up at him. “That’s stupid. Maybe she’s just sick or something.”           “But the conversation I overheard! It’s too...  fishy ,” Matt finished lamely. Mr. Teo, who was at Cheryl’s table, turned to look at him for a moment, before he turned back to the girls again.           “What’re you guys talking about?” Yi Fan cut in from the other corner. As he turned he also unconsciously performed the wrist movement they had just learnt, and sent a cushion flying right into Hu Ping’s face.           “Oh... about Professor Huda,” Matt answered, trying not to laugh at the sight of Hu Ping, who had now thrown the pillow off and was sending a few colourful curses at Yi Fan.           “Ah,” Yi Fan said, faking a look of mock awe on his face. “Eh anyway, care to help me with this spell? I just can’t do it,” he said wryly.           “Really?” Hu Ping asked.           “Just look and see,” Yi Fan replied. Turning to his pile of cushions (they all looked in bad condition due to various dirt stains from the floor and walls), he tried to Banish a cushion, but only succeeded in getting it off the table and falling to the floor.           “ Accio cushion !” Matt said, and the cushion flew back up again. He swept the dust off it and placed it back on the pile in front of Yi Fan. “You’re not concentrating properly. Just think of Banishing the cushion. Don’t think of anything else.”           Yi Fan looked doubtful.           “Go on, try it,” Hu Ping cajoled.           Yi Fan scrunched up his face in concentration. “Okay, here we go!” With one fluid motion, he pointed his wand at the five cushions in front of him.           Matt gasped.           “What?” Yi Fan asked, opening his eyes.           For answer Matt pointed to the box on the opposite side of the room. In the box, Yi Fan’s five cushions were stacked neatly, one on top of the other.  ----------  “You’re so good!” Cheryl enthused as the class spilt out of their Charms classroom. Mr. Teo had been so pleased with Yi Fan at the end that he had given him a large block of chocolate. Of course, the chocolate was now making its rounds among the fifth-years.           “Yeah... but I didn’t think I could do it...” Yi Fan said, still quite surprised at himself.           “You just didn’t know you had it in you,” Matt added in.           There was a pause.           “So now you’re gonna beat me at Charms!” Barnabas wailed.           They rolled their eyes, and walked on. And for the first time this year, Yi Fan could see a shred of hope for his studies right in front of him.           ----------  As Cheryl entered the Great Hall for dinner, she saw from afar the figure of Ang Yee Tien – that girl who had been bothering her and her friends day after day. After Yee Tien had been appointed as one of Molekiw’s (Wo)men, she had become even more obnoxious, taking every opportunity to deduct points from Griffindoor for small trifles such as having a speck of dirt on their uniform. Still, Cheryl thought Matt was getting it the worst. Yee Tien was deducting points from Griffindoor simply because she disliked him.           “She’s coming,” Eunice said to the rest.           In a matter of a few seconds Yee Tien had strode up the length of the Hall and now stood in front of Cheryl and her friends.           “What do you want?” Matt said rudely.           “How about deducting more points?” she replied, sneering.           “Because we don’t like you,” said Liqin, who was at Yee Tien’s side.           “Oh, you actually can talk? You look so bimbotic, I thought you couldn’t,” Matt replied.           Liqin paused. “What’s ‘bimbotic’?”           Cheryl had to pretend to cough into a tissue to disguise her snort.           “Oh, it means you’re very pretty,” Eunice said, making her voice as saccharine-sweet as possible.                          Liqin paused again. It seemed she had to take a few seconds to digest anything said to her that was more than a few words long.           “Anyway,  you  don’t talk to her like that, okay,” Yee Tien smirked. “Five points from Griffindoor. I’m  so  sorry. And  you  better watch out,” she aimed her stare directly at Matt, who deliberately started walking towards her, before elaborately stepping past her and going to the Griffindoor table, where he turned and stared coldly back at her.           “Stare you out,” he said coolly.           “I’m not gonna waste my time on a little boy like you,” Yee Tien answered snidely, before whipping round and walking off.           “She’s got an attitude, that one,” Matt said later as his friends sat down. He was helping himself to a large serving of baked potatoes.           “As do you,” Eunice said playfully.           Matt’s temper seemed to have gone down a bit, and he managed a grin.           “Sorry for interrupting,” a voice behind them said. “But would any of you like to try out for the Quidditch team?”           They all turned round to see Desmond Yap, the present Griffindoor team captain and their senior in sixth-year. Sunny and Eunice, both Chasers in the team, waved cheerfully to him. His grey eyes flickered to them for a moment as he smiled. He then looked at the others up and down, his gaze resting on Rachel for a moment.           “Nah, I can’t, I’m commentating this year,” Matt piped up from his corner. He was now on his second serving of Shepherd's pie.           Hu Ping’s mouth fell open. “Really?”           Matt stopped shovelling the potato pie into his mouth for a moment and looked up. “Well, yeah,” he shrugged. “I got through the auditions.”           While the rest clapped and laughed, Hu Ping said again, “Really? But I thought your commentating sucked!”           A round of poking and cursing ensued once again. Desmond raised his eyebrows. “Erm... so... anyone?”           “Me!” Muthu called out.           “And me... ouch!” yelled Hu Ping, who was still being punished for his insolence by Matt.          “Yeah, I’ll go for it,” Cheryl said.           The girls all turned to look at her. “I didn’t know you liked Quidditch so much,” Minyu said. “Actually I’d join... but then the robes aren’t orange!”           Desmond looked oddly at Minyu. “Well, we’re thinking of re-designing the robes this year,” he said.           Minyu pondered over it for a moment. “Nah, I’m not good,” she said finally.           “Well, anyway, the three of you,” Desmond said, his eyes trained on the three who had just signed up (Matt had stopped poking Hu Ping and had gone back to his Shepherd’s pie), “tryouts are tomorrow, 6 o’ clock at the pitch. Got it?”           They all nodded, and he took his leave, moving on to a group of chattering third-years next to them.           “How about you, Rachel?” Sunny asked playfully. “You had this...  lovelorn  look in your eyes...” she turned and took a hard look at her captain’s lean frame, his shock of carefully-spiked hair, and smiled. “Find him handsome, maybe?” she pressed on.           Rachel stared at her friend angrily. “Go eat your dinner!” she said in a commanding tone.           “Anyway, if she joined the team all she’d do is stand at the goalposts and fumble with the ball when it’s thrown to her,” Matt said, sticking his tongue out. “Anyway, Cheryl, why’d you join?”           “Well... I just thought I’d try it out, that’s all...” she said vaguely.           Actually, Cheryl’s mind was buzzing. She had just signed up for Quidditch tryouts. It’d been a long time since she’d done something so offhand, so on-the-spur-of-the-moment. She felt giddily happy. She was trying out for the sport which her idol took part in. She could almost see Harry Potter, flying like a hawk...           And she saw herself, soaring on a broomstick...           Suddenly she stopped. A thought had just occurred to her.           She didn’t have a broomstick.   

						
</post>
</Blog>