<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      of corse the POTC movie will be good because it is POTC. And POTC rocks. 
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       There is no way of telling whether or not the POTC trilogy will be good, until they come out.   
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       I'm not saying that Disney trilogys suck, I'm saying that most trilogys tend to be not as popular as the original, even ones that everyone thinks will be good. For example,  The Matrix  was a ground breaking film, when news got out that there would be a trilogy, everyone got excited. Then the movies came out and the Wachowski brothers' credibility was flushed down the toilet as the movies.... sucked. That is an example of a great movie with trilogys thatweren't as good.  Back to the Future  was a book, but they were written at different times, sothe key issues of thestory changes. But actually,  Back to the Future II  was good, the third messed up on one of the major issues, Don't take it too far, which is what happened, the story went from time jumping to stuck.  Star Wars  the movie was made first then the books were made.   *cough cough* Your kinda missing the point, Lord or the Rings was only good because it was written at the same time by the same person. The actors do not make the story, they tell it.      
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      LOTR made it because it was a good series that won the heart and souls of cridics, directors, fans - you name it. The last one won 11 oscars, 11 !!!!! LOTR was a good series with good actors and a great setup. 
     

    
</post>
<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yes but you have to understand that for people that like disney had to have closure. the whole story of Aladdin is this boy that is alone in the world. The second one had to introduce the genie again and also had to settle the isuee of Jafar. We find out very little about aladdin, so all the aladdin fans had to know about his past, the third and final one. And disney will soon be comming out with a new trilogy... POTC. And if disney trilogys stink then it must refer to the future of POTC and that refers to the first one. Which, as you know, dissing POTC (even future potc) could make you end up mangled and demented and, well not living. Back to the future was a good trilogy and was also based on a book, i believe- so was star wars, and books are always better than movies. 
     

    
</post>
<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Debate, eh? Bring it...   You reallythink so? I'm not a Disney fan,not of the new stuff, anyway. The original Aladdin was good, but it made the fatal error that  Back to the Future  made. Making atrilogy. No trilogy has ever lasted, aside from  Star Wars  and  Lord of the Rings.Lord of the Rings  only lastedbecause, first of all, it was a book, and secondly, it was written as one book, but had to be separated for printing purposes.   
     

    
</post>
<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Xcuse me? There should have definantly been a trilogy for Aladdin. it is the grated disney movie of all time. they set it up for a sequal.  
     

    
</post>
<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      10. It was a pretty good movie, I don't remember any kimono scene, but the fact that they tried to make a TV series out of it ruined it for me,  9. Lion King 1 1/2? Never saw it, but it probably was good.  8. Never saw it again, but antagonist of fire? That doesn't sound like a plot-filled movie.  7. Inuyasha rocks, plain and simple, I'm not too far in the series though. By the way in japanese, hen means strange, hentai means sexually strange/perverted and ecchi is a stronger version of hentai. Unfortunatly, they also have double meanings, meanings that go along with their real meanings. Anyway if you liked InuYasha, you'd love Ranma 1/2, a manga also by Rumiko Takahashi. Ranma and InuYasha have the same voice actor in English and Japanese.   6. Saw this twice so far... Good movie. Docter Octavious rules  .     5. An interesting movie, but I don't like Steven King that much. His writing is too dark. A stunning preformance by Johnny Depp. Love the scene were he finally goes crazy and talks to himself.  4. Aladdin was alright, there should not have been a trilogy.  3.LOTR, always good, doesn't stick to the book though.  2.Two Towers, Same, didn't stick to the book. Tree Beard stole one of Tom Bombadil's lines.  1.POTC, that's what I thought. It was a very awesome movie. 
     

    
</post>
<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Top 10 Movies  with comentary from Weird Kendo Guy     10. My Big Fat Greek Wedding -  this was one of the best romantic comedys I have ever seen. The whole Greek theme was awsome. I love the windex and the kimono scenes. This movie was well writen and is a family favorite.      9. Lion King 1 1/2  - This was sooo great. I have always wonderedaboutTimon and Pumbaa. I like the original songs, xpecially the "dig a tunnel" one. The way the scriptwritersinjected things into the original moviewasplaned well. This, like the former, is a great family movie. Go Disney!   8. Backdraft  - The story of two brothers overcoming life and fire. This is a touching story that takes fire and turns it into a villan. Kurt Russel does and awsome job. Theplot twistsand romance make the story. Besides the cursing, this movie is awsome and ...well...awsome!   7. Inuyasha Movies -I could"sit"(ha ha) and watchthese all day long. They are clasic anime and are very cool. You learn a ton about the Japanese language like hoshi means monk andhentai means perverted ^_^. Also you learn valuble lessons about love, that no matter how much you love sombody, you can still be overpowerd by evil deamonsfrom china andtry to kill yourlove with your bow and arrow.   6. Spiderman 2  - This was so much better than the first one. MJ and Peter's best friend find out who he is and so does an entire train car. it has a ton more action and the kooky news person is back. I dont want to say to muchjust in case.   5. Secret Window  - Stephen King at his worst. This was a good story. Why i say, "SK at his worst" is that he made Johnny Deppa mass murderer. I liked the fact that the only bad word thatwas said is"ship" with a t instead of a p. I liked the plot twist at the end, evern though it was different than the book.The guy who played John Shooter was AWSOME!He really was freaky. All in all a good movie.     4. Aladdin  - Thisis thebest disney movie ever. I know all thesongs by heart. Robin Williams isthe best genie ever!And eago is the greatest parrot ever. GO DISNEY!!!!     3. Lord of the Rings: TheRetern of the King  -In my opinion this was long.I loved all the action and the fact that it was over.The beginning was...odd. I loved it though. The special effects were awsome and i like the dead people.Billy Boyd and Viggo can sing reallygood. It is LOTR, therefore it is awsome!     2. Lord of the Rings: The two Towers  - The fact thatthis was in the middle made it wonderful. Smeigle is awsome! Once again special effects were great. We get to learnmore about the characterswhich makes our compasion for them flourish.The trees are great and the intro of feromer (cant spell) is splendid.     1. Pirates of theCarribean  - This is the best movieever... nough said!  
     

    
</post>
<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yeah, that sucks. I had something like that happen to me, awhile back.  Well, I'm currently in Seaside, Or. I'm on my brother's new laptop. Thank goodness for free DSL connections at hotels.  
     

    
</post>
<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      See, he says accros the country because I currently live in pittsburgh, PA.  I used to live in Cali with all my  fwends but we moved.  Now i live in a place where the sun shines like 100 days out of the year.  it always rains, but i dont care about that, much(untill lightning hits the house and only effects the internet connection making it slower and killing microsoft word so it reads as if uninstalled).
     

    
</post>
<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Greetings, Weird Kendo Guy here, and I would like to welcome you to this modern marvel we like to call the blog with people from two sides of the country. Wierdkendogirl and I will talk and maybe debate or rant, possibly quote... Dude, this is going to be l33t! 
     

    
</post>
<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Those are cool.
     

    
</post>
<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Here's a good quote,  some lyrics from one of my favorite Five Iron Frenzy songs.      "When I was young, the smallest trick of light,   Could catch my eye,   Then life was new and every new day,   I thought that I could fly.   I believed in what I hoped for,   And I hoped in things unseen.   I had wings and dreams could soar,   I just don't feel like flying anymore.      When stars threw down their spears,   Watered heaven with their tears,   Before words were spoken,   Before eternity.      Dear Father, I need you,   Your strength my heart to mend,   I want to fly higher,   Every new day again"   -Every New Day (Our Newest Album Ever)  
     

    
</post>
<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
       POTC   People Of The Crazytown  This is us, this blog is a town where crazy individuals can be free. Just thought i should share that
     
    
</post>
<date>24,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      A little joke.  "An old man living alone on a farm wrote to his only son, Bubba, in prison.  Dear Bubba:  I'm feeling pretty bad because it looks like i won't be able to plant my potato garden this year.  i'm just getting too old to be digging up a garden plot.  wish you were here--i know you would take care of it for me. Love, dad.  About a week later the farmer received this letter. 'dead dad: don't dig up the garden! that's where i buried the bodies! love, bubba.'  the next morning, fbi agents stormed the property and dug up the entire garden. they didn't find any bodies, though, so they apologized to the old man and left.  soon the farmer received another letter. 'dear dad: go ahead and plant the potatoes now. it's the best i can do under the circumstances. love, bubba."           -reader's digest  
     
    
</post>
<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Why Computers Sometimes Crash! By Dr. Seuss. (Read this aloud to yourself, - it's great!)    If a packet hits a pocket on a socket on a port, and the bus is interrupted at a very last resort, and the access of the memory makes your floppy disk abort, then the socket packet pocket has an error to report.  If your cursor finds a menu item followed by a dash, and the double-clicking icon puts your window in the trash, and your data is corrupted cause the index doesn't hash, then your situation's hopeless and your system's gonna crash!   If the label on the cable on the table at your house, says the network is connected to the button on your mouse, but your packets want to tunnel to another protocol, that's repeatedly rejected by the printer down the hall.   And your screen is all distorted by the side effects of gauss, so your icons in the window are as wavy as a souse; then you may as well reboot and go out with a bang, 'cuz sure as I'm a poet, the sucker's gonna hang.  When the copy on your floppy's getting sloppy in the disk, and the macro code instructions all are causing undue risk, then you'll have to flash the memory and you'll want to RAM your ROM, and then turn off the computer and be sure to tell your Mom!   I thought this was funny and it was sent to me by Shannon.  Who would have thunk this was made by Dr. seuss  
     
    
</post>
<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Amanda, in reading your post on my post i say that Figure C said "you love him" not "he loves you". Get that right Figure A. Geez!!! Also, when figure A went up to biology, Figures B and C had a good time talking about how figure D (the squid) is dead and does not feel anything, therefore, figure A should not be squimish of disectinf Figure D. Also Figure C commented to Figure B that she had to watch Figure E (shannon/Bio partner) disect Figure F( the live worm) and how when it was halfway cut open the heart was still beating. Figure B was astonished to learn that our bio clas had disected Figure F and then he went into his german classroom. PLEASE DO NOT KILL FIGURE C  also, this is the best acronymph.  F- Freaked Out  I- Insecure  N- Nerotic  E- Emotional  Never bealeive a person is doing good if they say "Fine"   
     
    
</post>
<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Jenn!  in reading your post i must say one thing, figure A does not know if figure B feels the same way!  he could just think figure A is crazy!  especially after what happened today, miss figure C.  for everyone else, figure C completely screamed "he loves you!" when figure B was right behind us. figure C is a wild one, and i am sure all you californians know this.  who knows what crazy thing she'll do next to mess up my lack of love life.  her and another jen were even plotting to do what jenn did in the steve and christine situation.  i'm doomed. 
     
    
</post>
<date>17,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      IN reading amamda's post i have one thing to say that is a Hazen-nye ism ----- "Love it"  Also just so ppl know, in her little post thing, she is "A"  a certin guy is "B"  and i am "C".  David it is a Steve  and Christine situation, one is afraid to tell the other that they like them. 
     
    
</post>
<date>17,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      as per speaking to my mom, we were discussing how annoying and clueless men are (sorry david) and she said something to me that was one of the more humorous things that  have come out of her mouth.  "Amanda, you must understand that the male species is here to show us how superior we really are."
     
    
</post>
<date>15,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      jenn and i have often referred to ourselves as hobbits, and i was lately contemplating the subject  and of course leading myself in ringlets as tight as my own head's.  being short is usually thought of by figure A, the short one, as being bad.  you cannot reach the high shelves at giant eagle, and you need to look up to everyone.  but those in the catagory of figure B, the tall one, tall is bad. you dwarf even your boyfriend, (of one i wish i had) (Jenn don't comment) (i'll get to this) and you must look down.  except if figure B is a boy, in which case, tall is excellent.  then i decided i rather like being short.  sure, just 2 inches and i would feel a lot happier, but (and think abt it) i don't want to look down to this so called imaginary boyfriend. i like him taller than me, and this is where i twist myself into the ringlet. figure A, the short one, happens to maybe like figure B, the tall one who figure A likes.  yea.  but figure C, the even shorter one, is trying to, hmm, convince figure A to, hmm, do a sydney carton.  which is where i throw myself into the total ringlet, because i am back to thinking short is good.  which by the way my view on this my be slightly twisted because figure B has commented on the shortness of figure A in a cute way.  yea i am crazy, but it's allright.  it's just tale of 2 cities-itis.
     
    
</post>
<date>13,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I found this quote on the internet and i thought it was hilarious.  Comments at end.  Has having children [he has a girl and boy] changed Johnny Depp?   "Oh yeah. I would say that the kiddies give you strength. The kiddies give you strength and perspective and you understand stuff. Things that would've made me sort of upset or angry before, or things about Hollywood, things in magazines or paparazzi or stuff like that, now you can sort of really go, 'Oh, shove off. I'm just going to play Barbies with my daughter."-Johnny Depp   Hahahahahahahaha!!!!! @_@  I love this.  What is so funny is picturing in your mind Depp sitting on the floor with his daughter playing barbies and being yelled at for not putting the shoe on right or something like that.  I remember when i played with barbies with my daddy and yelling him for not putting the clothes on right or not doing what i wanted him to do.  Those were the days, playing with barbies and telling your parents what to do and having them obey instead of sending you to your room.  *sigh*  anyway yea i thought that this was funny.   
     
    
</post>
<date>09,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I am reading A Tale of Two Cities for english, AJ is in my class.  I am thinking about how Jack Sparrow could be a reincarnation of Sydney Carton.  They are both drunks, both are very witty.  Also they are loners.  This, i think will get me personaly interested in reading the story more cause of the likeness between the two.  I love this.
     
    
</post>
<date>09,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Only in America do they have signs in McDonald's in which they say "we have Braille and picture menus available."  Only in America can you get a pizza to your doorstep faster than an ambulance...   Only in America do they have Braille on drive-thru ATM machines.  Only in America - do we put handicap parking spaces in front of skating rinks.  Only In America...Do people order super size fries and cheeseburgers and a diet coke!  Only in America do banks leave both doors open and chain pens to the counter  --this was a profile of a dear friend of mine-- 
     
    
</post>
<date>07,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      hello, my freaky darlings!  jenn, aj is proud to join your blog of craziness!  unfortunately, i am recouperating from a 15 hour drive and therefore have little craziness to share with you now.  however, i do have some wonderful MASH quotes!  "I had a still in Guam in WWII.  One night it blew up.  That's how i got my purple heart."      -Potter  "Stop making fun of my height!" "What height?  You have no height to make fun of.  Go get some height, we'll make fun of it."      -Hawkeye and Radar (I think jenn and i both understand this one wholeheartedly.  it's a great comeback, too)  "I'll stick with gin.  champagne is just ginger ale that knows somebody."      -hawkeye  Luck to everyone in all there hilarious exploits.  i think everyone needs a little craziness a lot of the time.
     
    
</post>
<date>07,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      How many lawyers does it take to change a light bulb?  Such number as  may be deemed necessary to perform the stated task in a timely and  efficient manner within the strictures of the following agreement.    Whereas the party of the first part, also known as 'the lawyers' and the party of the second part,  also known as 'the light bulb' do hereby agree to a  transaction wherein the party of the second part (light bulb) shall be   removed from the current position as a result of failure to perform  previously agreed upon duties, i.e. the lighting, elucidation, and  otherwise illumination of the area ranging from the front (North) door,  through the entryway, terminating at an area just through the primary living  area, demarcated by the beginning of the carpet, any spillover  illumination being at the option of the party of the second part (light bulb)  and not required by the aforementioned agreement between the parties.  The aforementioned removal transaction shall include, but not be limited  to, the following steps: 1.    The party of the first part (lawyer)  shall, with or without elevation at his option, by means of a chair, step  stool, ladder or any other means of elevation, grasp the party of the  second part (light bulb) and rotate the party of the second part (light  bulb) in a counter clockwise direction, said direction being  non-negotiable.  Said grasping and rotation of the party of the second part (light  bulb) shall be undertaken by the party of the first part (lawyer) to  maintain the structural integrity of the party of the second part (light  bulb), notwithstanding the aforementioned failure of the party of the  second part (light bulb) to perform the customary and agreed upon  duties.  The foregoing notwithstanding, however, both parties stipulate that  structural failure of the party of the second part (light bulb) may be  ncidental to the aforementioned failure to perform and in such case  the party of the first part (lawyer) shall be held blameless for such  structural failure insofar as the non-negotiable directional codicil  (counter-clockwise) is observed by the party of the first part (lawyer)   throughout.  2. Upon reaching a point where the party of the second part  (light bulb) becomes separated from the party of the third part  ('receptacle'), the party of the first part shall have the option of disposing  of the party of the second part (light bulb) in a manner consistent with  all applicable state, local, and federal statutes.    3. Once separation and disposal have been achieved, the party of the first part (lawyer)  shall have the option of beginning the installation of the party of the  fourth part ('new light bulb').  This installation shall occur in a  manner consistent with the reverse procedures described in step one of  this self same document, being careful to note that the rotation should   occur in a clockwise direction, said direction also being non-negotiable  and only until the party of the fourth part (new light bulb) becomes  snug in the party of the third part (receptacle) and in fact becomes the  party of the second part (light bulb).  Note: The above described steps  may be performed, at the option of the party of the first part   (lawyer), by said party of the first part (lawyer), or by his or her heirs and  assigns, or by any and all persons authorized by him or her to do sum  the objective being to produce a level of illumination in the immediate  vicinity of the aforementioned front (North) door consistent with  maximization of ingress and revenue for the party of the fifth part, also  known as 'The Firm'.  I thought that this was hillarious.  i dont know about you but this wa really great.  Also i would like to stray away from this happy and light hearted note to make a rant.  Yes, a rant, this is the first rant and it is a Biology rant.  Tommorow i have to disect a worm and that is fine and dandy with me casue certain people at my table will do it. But anyway, I am probably going to be made to disect it anyway.  You may be thinking that that is no big deal.  its just a dead worm that smells bad cause it has been soaked in fermaldahid.  Well, you are sooooo wrong.  We are disecting a live worm, yes ladies and gentleman a live worm!!! This is horrable because when we open the worm its heart will be still beating and its lungs will be working and it will be grose. I mean come on, why disect a live worm.  And with that, why disect a wom at all.  It it a worm for pete sake.  A little worm.  LET THE WORMS RUN FREE!!! That is what i have to say.  DO NOT TORCHER THE POOR THINGS.  Plus that is just sickening.  anyway, we have a biology test on the worm also.  GRRRRRRRR!!!
     
    
</post>
<date>05,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I dont feel like writing anything.  Yet that is how it is in life, you find something to do and you dont want to do it.  Then you just do it anyway because you have nothing better to do.  I wonder why that is.  Are we so wrapped up in our own choices that we forget what we want and dont want?  I have no idea?  
     
    
</post>
<date>03,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I have just come up with one of the coolist things.    IT IS FUN TO BE WIERD.  Wierd people are not held up to0 any standers like nerds or jocks or criminal juvaniles, we are just wacky and crazy.  We do the stuff we do to be who we are, the funny and somewhat sarcastic people we are.  We are here, not to make a lasting impression on the world, but to have fun and be content and take risks.  That is maybe why we are considered "wierd".  It is because we are not the Jocks who are strong, we are not the nerds who do nothing but figure out sqare roots or are in trigonometry in 9th grade, we are not the criminal juvaniles who do anything to get noticed.  We are ourselves and because we are ourselves we are wierd or freaks.  Yet, we hope that one of these years the Jocks and all other types of cliches in schools will relize that they can be freaks and wierd people and bring that out, then the world would be not only crazy, but a good kind of crazy.  Sorry, i just had a wierd moment.  please xcuse.  "NI" (mwahahahaha)
     
    
</post>
<date>02,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Haha!!!
     
    
</post>
<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      This is one of the best quotes in the world and i love it cause it describes me. It is by my main man Johnny Depp. Well, not main man cause The main man is Jesus Christ and one other guy that means a lot to me but, back to Johnny Depp, who I could lavish over for millions and millions of years but i will not succumb to that level...yet (mwahahahahahaha) As you can probably see buy the evil laughing that i am showing on my blog, i am not normal. Yet nobody is normal which makes the world very...well...odd. So insted of my useless rambling, i guess i should deliver my quote.  " There seems to be a constant theme in things I do which deal with people who are considered "freaks" by so-called "normal" people. I guess that would make me a “freak”. Awsome!" -Johnny Depp  I love this quote because it relates to the very astonishingly wierd person that is sitting at the computer. i have no idea who she is...well i do but, yea you get the point. Well i say adu till next time we meet, or talk, or you just read my stupid little bablings without seeing or hearing me but through the passings of my small and scary but non the less full functioning mind to you. (Mwahahahahaha) I make myself laugh. And in the world of me an a few other ppl i say "NI" just to be utterly bizzar. 
     
    
</post>
<date>01,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Hello.  this is my like sixth blog so, yea.  i am going to be inviting people that i think are worthy to wear the crazy crown. Here is a place for them and myself to bestow upon all you peoples of the internet ideas,storys,quotes,rants,thoughts,and other miscilanious stuff that has no meaning in anyones life.  Enjoy!
     
    
</post>
<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Good. ^_^
     
    
</post>
<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Of course not.  Considering I'm in a blog with almost all girls, I would never mean that.  :-)
     
    
</post>
<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Are you implying that women are not as supirior as men?  Cause if you are... that would be bad for you.   Hey Amanda, Sarcasum *drip drip*
     
    
</post>
<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Sal's fine(no offense to birth name taken).  And I'm glad sappy stuff makes women  think  their superior. :-)
     
    
</post>
<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Amanda, i totaly relate.  My friend krystina (whom i met in 2nd grade) still lives in california.  At least you get to see them once in awhile and you live in the same state.  And David, ive known him since i was 9.  All my friends are 3852ish miles away.  I can only talk to them on wekends because i get free minutes on my cell phone.  Sal, i like calling you sal better than zack.  no offence to your birth name.  And the comment was very sappy but that is what boyfriends are for.  Women like to hear sappy things, it makes the feel supirior.  Amanda may agree or disagree.
     
    
</post>
<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Thank you (bow) Thank you (bow again)
     
    
</post>
<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I don't know her, but that's hilarious! I'll remember that if I don't like my English/speech teacher next year!
     
    
</post>
<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Personally I don't think there's anything wrong with you (sappy i know, but o well...deal with it).  I know how it is to lose a best friend too, it's impossible to replace them.  But trust me your nowhere near the bottom of the social standings (trust me I live there :-)  And besides you have all of your new friends at Seneca to make fun of you...uh... i mean make you happy now.  Sorry sarcasm slip (SSS or S^3)
     
    
</post>
<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      fig b, your controbutions to this blog are amazing. haveing the reda-isms inserted brings new life to sarcasm. (jenn, did u put him up to it? no wait, dont' bother answering, i know what it'll be).  anyway....i just wanted to comment on that.  oh, and i think i figured out what wrong w/ me (jenndon'tcomment i know its more than one thing). but...i think i am suffering from friend deprivation. i know i gots tons of frineds at our school, but i cna't help but miss my best friend and my other really close frineds. how crazy is that.  its also kinda major pitiful, but think abt it. if u were best friends w/ the same person for 9 years, u would miss her too! but maybe its' just commonly confused words-itis.
     
    
</post>
<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Awsome!!!!!
     
    
</post>
<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Here it is.  By popular demand.  (Insert drumroll here)  The rebellion against Miss Reda.  For those of you who don't know who Miss Reda is imagine the Wicked Witch of the West in normal clothes minus the green skin and the house on her head.  Crag-A steeply projecting mass of rock. The crag fell on Miss Reda's head. Reda Comment: lovely  Shroud-A cloth used to wrap a body for burial. The shroud concealed Miss Reda's body after getting hit with a crag. Reda Comment: um, yikes  Apocryphal-Of questionalbe authorship or authenticity Jagoffs in our class think Miss Reda has apocryphal authority. Reda Comment: None  Sagacity-Shrewd and wise; wisdom Those jagoffs think that it is an act of sagacity put on by Miss Reda.  Reda over all comment: not funny  For some reason I got points off for inappropriate content.....
     
    
</post>
<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink Crazyness! Sheer Crazyness! @_@ : "Another Revelation."  I have an answer for you:   Other countries drive on the left side of the road. We drive on the right side of the road. If the other countries don't, they drive on the wrong side.   Problem solved.
     
    
</post>
<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      jenn, that was soo far below the belt. soooo soo far. yep. although i do see where u are cmoing from, i prefer fig b to be more of a different type.  (andnonotaldajenniknowwhatuwerethinkin).  and luck on the concert tonite, sry i won't be there.  i'll insted be contemplating life and how much it stinks sometimes. yep. what a stupid thing to think. ype. not that i'm remotely stupid in any way. but don't ask jenn. once again, she'd disagree.
     
    
</post>
<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I have a revelation to share.  If Amanda is Sydney Carton does that make Sal the Seamstress?  I am so glad that you two are together, i will be in peace.  I have that water bottle for you sal!  And Amanda, how do you like your administrative position?  Its good to be in charge, i am usually not in charge much cause i dominate or i become crazy and cant get a thing done or come up with wierd ideas.  Another Revelation.  It is said that the ppl of other countries drive on the wroreng side of the road.  That would mean that we drive on the right side of the road.  But if we are a small minority compared to them than are we wrong.  But if we are right then the majority or popular vote dosent count.  And if the popular vote dosent count, then i have twisted myself into a slinky (if you do not know what a slinky is than i will feel old).  The slinky is that if the popular vote dosent count and people are going to go against the majority anyways then why vote.  But getting back to the whole driving thing ... mailmen, here they drive on the wrong side of the road so do mailmen of other countries (that have mailmen of course) drive on the right side of the road, but then the whole thing comes back about the popular vote and stuff.  ITS JUST ONE BIG NEVERENDING CIRCLE OF CRAZYNESS!!!!!
     
    
</post>
<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      i let fig b join. so david, now ur not alone. he fully gets all the fig a-f and sydney carton stuff, and is the most sarcastic person i know, so, there wil be no lack of craziness on his part. and this should be fun. hehe. 
     
    
</post>
<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Hey everybody.  Just wanted to let all of you who are in on it know that figure B has entered the blog thingy.  No more secret talk.  That's all. :-)
     
    
</post>
<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Hey, I get to be a figure after all? What about the rest of the lunch table crowd? Three down, four to go? What about the PA-Texan girl?
     
    
</post>
<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      We should invite him to join this blog!!! What is his e-mail amanda?????  And Shannon,  you are figure E, the squid is figure D, and the live worm is figure F.
     
    
</post>
<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      You know, we should invite him to join this. Then we can discuss figures A, B, and C amongst mentioned figures. (Humph. I'm not a figure!)
     
    
</post>
<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Exactly why you shold tell him!!!!
     
    
</post>
<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
         well, shannon, nothing was going on today. he was being particularly amusing is all. and by the way, what "show" did u plan to see? and what abt whyt didi he walk down the staris? i dunno what u do in california, but here that's what stairs are for. (lol).      and u think i should tell him.  hmmm. i actually probably will soon, b/c i almost went crazy when he was on the band trip. think of me during summer if we didin't do stuff together.
     
    
</post>
<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Okay, AJ, what happened with figure B today? I was expecting a show!!! And then he just walks up, the two of you lock gazes, and he keeps walking down the stairs! But why? I got out of reminding Nikki about going to the library for   that?    I think you should just tell a particular figure everything that has been going on already. This particular figure has a dire need to know and doesn't even realize it.
     
    
</post>
<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I know who he is... I just... felt like... Oh, nevermind! You might just push me into a German spree. Hope to see ya later.
     
    
</post>
<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Shannon, who do you think the "one other guy that means a lot to me" is.  
     
    
</post>
<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      AJ, I don't recall ever saying that   dentists   were  Sith spawn. (I really do avoid saying "Spawn of Satan," but Sith isn't so bad, really. I mean, anyone could become a sith!) I'm just of the opinion that   orthodontists   are the real sithspawns.   With dentists, it's not so bad. It's the same thing time after time: scraping your teeth, jabbing down in molars with the hooky thing, pressing nasty stuff into your mouth, etc. But orthodontists, that's another story. Let's just say that you don't usually take two ibuprofin before arriving at the dentist's door. It's practically a given for the othodude's.   Also, though the dentist sticks metal in your mouth, (s)he usually takes most of it out again. (Fillings aren't metal anymore, right?) I mean, it's not like you have to relearn how to eat, drink, and speak after two hours at the dentist's. And you don't have to put scented wax over dental work like you have to when you have pokey things sticking out from your teeth. ("Oh, you'll get used to it. It's not so bad, really.")  Well, let me just share one of my reviews for "Jonas, Anubis, and Your Local Orthodontist". This person sums everything up:  I can't tell you how much I enjoyed this story. I had a 2 hour ortho appt. earlier today and I'm rather pissed at them. I've had the expander along with this evil thing called a herbst appliance that has now broken TWICE. I was in a really bad mood, but I ABSOLUTELY LOVE this story. And for anyone out there about to get braces, or anything of the type, if your doctor says you won't need pain meds, smile and nod and take them as soon as possible. AWESOME story. ~Amanda  Yeah, ff.net. Gotta love them people!  I guess my point is this: dentists aren't so bad compared to the othodontists, who are trying to take over the world.  (By the way, there is now no doubt in anyone's mind that I love writing, correct?)
     
    
</post>
<date>08,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      to all concerned... figure b is back from the band trip and i found out he wears glasses! i am gonna havee to wear mine one day to school to make sure he knows how dorky i really am in glasses. (trust me, it's bad)anyway i am sure you do not want to hear abt my raving so here's what i came to say.  i used to think shannon was way overboard wiht the whole "dentist is spawn of satan", but i had ot experience the torture on saturday, at 9 am no less! i did not enjoy metal objects being mercilessly shoved into my mouth, and when she said "open" i was so surprised i did and she shoved fluoride into my mouth. you know, the big teeth shaped foam thing that tastes awful?! yucK! it's a fact dentists have the largest suicide rate of all professions. i know if i were one i would so totaly jump off a bridge.
     
    
</post>
<date>08,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink Technically, this is written on the same day as my last post, but I didn't want to mess up the prettifulness and seriousness of my... sermon. I just want to share one of my favorite quotes from some really smart person still alive in Germany.     urlLink "Kann es sein, dass man die Vergangenheit veraendern muss, damit die Zukunft so existiert, wie wir sie kennen?" Literally, word for word, it says, "Can it be, that one the past change must, by it the future so exists, how we it know?" So for anyone who wants to learn something, it means,   "Can it be that one must change the past, that by changing it, the future exists in the way we know it?"      urlLink  That is such a philosophical-ish-y quote! Now. For those of you who like Stargate (a bit of free advertising on my part, if I may?), check out the stuff, especially Reeses (AJ?), at the following site which actually consists of this whole post except for the German quote. 
     
    
</post>
<date>07,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Yay! After so long, I've finally been able to join! Okay, to comment on everything I missed... Yeah, I've never seen this blog before in my life, so...    April 2   Hey, wierdkendogirl, if JD's your main man (besides Christ), who are all the others that   aren't   your main men? .... Wierd Kendo Guy...? -- WKG, you make yourself out to be such an insane person! I mean, even you will admit that Bloom and I greatly surpass your mere social abnormailities. At least you seem to take true pleasure in AJ's gossip.    April 3   Hey, look, more ranting for tired eyes. I think I may just go check e-mail and come back to this later, but I've missed out on so much!    April 5   Whoa, philosophical-ish-y stuff! W-ay too tired for that!    April 7   Did I send you that e-mail or did you send it to me? I distinctly remember reading that. And then IMing it to you.    April 15   Excuse me, but figure C didn't ask figure A to pull a Sydney Carton, which is what all Jack/Sam shippers (Stargate fanficdom) want Pete Shannahan to pull. You see, if figure A pulled a Sydney Carton, he/she would confess his/her  love and devotion (and constant thoughts) to figure B so that figure C, who doesn't really give a .... about figure B except where it relates to figure A, could forever be with figure B and make figure B happy, but that's not the case. So figure A should just walk right up to figure B the moment he/she sees her/him back from Myrtle Beach (where he is currently physically near/within ten miles of figure... figure... J!!!) and confess excactly how he/she feels for her/him. JUST DO IT! FIGURE B PROBABLY KNOWS ALREADY!!! Besides, when this event finally occurs, we can move on to someone else and get off your back, figure A.    April 17   So said some people. It just relates. (Sorry kendoguy!) Men were made first. Therefore, they are the rough draft.    May 3   Mexico? Cool! You mean you've actually been to other countries? I went to Canada once for half an hour and the Bahamas for two or three hours, but nothing extensive! That sounds so awesome!    May 6   Okay, AJ, I'm ready to come out with the full story. Y'all haven't heard it. Only a few people know. Nikki, maybe Lisa, probably Lindsay, my mom, and that's about it. So I'll get this over with.   Seventh grade. There was a guy in my purpose reading class *not history* that I kinda liked. He was a smart kid, knew a lot about robotics and computers, and was a major scifi fan. I mean, this guy could probably give you detailed directions on which hallways to take to get from engineering to the infirmary on any Enterprise, 14xx, 1701, A, B, C, D, maybe even E. Anyway, we got along well. A few times, I got up the courage to actually talk to him. He talked back. We had some pleasant conversations. (Keep in mind, figure C, I was just as prejudiced/biased/whatever against teenage relationships as I am now.) So we talked some more. Exchanged e-mail addresses. Then one day, he gave me this note with a cat on it, e-mail, phone number, and a few words. I don't remember what it was, but I still know exactly where it is. (And   definately   not in the garbage!!!) So he dropped by my house a few times since the two of us both lived in the same town. Gave me stuff. Hockey equipment, chocolate, etc. Kept it up for a while. We'd talk on the way out of the building. Then he wrote me this nasty e-mail one day. I got mad at him, avoided him and he me.   Remember I said that he was good with computers? My friends got nasty messages   from my e-mail account   that I had never written. The anger mounts. I forgot about it for a while. At or around the beginning of eighth grade, I realized the whole deal was kind of worthless. We could still have been friends. After all, we both liked scifi, right? Nope. I e-mailed him one last time, asking what his problem was. And he replied that he had used me, a ploy for popularity, apparently. I guess when he realized it wouldn't work, he blew off the idea. Well, ... *nasty words rising in mind, of several different languages* I've got several nicknames for him, including baka, shol'vah (appropriate), and scheissekopf. (I'll change that if it offends anyone besides this guy.)   It's kinda funny, not like I didn't have any foreshadowing. The guy's name was Peter M. I had a neighbor in SC with the same name. (Different last name, but same last initial.) I'd been friends with the SC Peter until we were around five. Then I guess it was "uncool" to be friends with a girl, so he was an idiot. I mentioned this to the other Peter, who commented that he hoped the same thing wouldn't happen again. Scheisse. I think it's kinda ironic that the good baka on Stargate is named Pete.   Oh, what I meant to tell you at lunch, figure A? I was going to comment that during all that time, all I could think about was Peter. What Peter would think. What Peter would like. When I would next see Peter. I guess I'm just trying to say that no matter how much you think you know him, no matter how much you think you like him, it can all turn around. Maybe you guys haven't noticed; as far as I know, your parents are still together. But you have to wonder how two people can love eachother so much that they get married, have a child, stay married for almost twenty-five years and then get divorced and detest eachother. How is something like that possible? Is the human heart so frail that even the strongest emotions can reverse so quickly?   This is all easy to take for granted, read over, feel sorry for me. (Don't do that, by the way. I don't need it yet. Maybe I'll tell you if I do.) But you have to see that it's the same here. The same beginnings of the throwing of the same dice. Just know that there may be more riding on the gamble than you think. 
     
    
</post>
<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Actually i wouldnt dissagree.  you are not stupid you are just wierd and it is good to be wierd.  "I don't try to be Weird, I just am what I am" -Johnny Depp.  this is you amanda, we love you any way (Huggles amanda, then coughs and lets go and streightens clothes)
     
    
</post>
<date>06,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      i just wanted to give major major kudos here to jenn and david.  whoever said absence makes the heart grow fonder had some serious mental issues.  sure it does, but it just about kills you in the process.  i mean, figure b is busy on his band trip, AT THE OCEAN, and i am sitting here contemplating the many ways to survive until monday. yep jenn commented (or asked, as the case may be) how i would feel if i did tell fig b i liked him, we were together, and then i was whipped away to the other side of the country.  after much contemplation of this subject, i have decided i am very proud of jenn for not a)exploding  b)going crazy  or c)taking the next plane back to california.  oh well.  just thought i'd give kudos to the two of you. and find some outlet for missing the object of my affections, but that cannot be helped.  i need a life. or a boyfriend. (jenn dont' comment). i will do something this after he gets back. i can't stand it any longer. sorry for all who have had to read this. i promise i am not always this stupid. but don't consult jenn on that.  she'd disagree.
     
    
</post>
<date>04,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      hello david. welcome to the insane asylum. im amanda jo, aka figure a, aka the one who has romance issues.  excuse me in advance for any jokes about men i may make in the future. by the way, if jenn has not warned you about me i suggest you ask her to at a later date. luck to all.
     
    
</post>
<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      hey everybody  i now officially posted my Rurouni Kenshin fanfic on fanfiction.net, it's called "Past Memories; A New Journey". oh and my church finally has a youth pastor. Tim and Natalie Nellis. they are really cool people. Tim grew up in Mexico. it's pretty cool because he wants to take us on trips to Mexico which we haven't done in a long time. well that's pretty much it... oh right, by the way... I'm David... yeah... that's it... until next time.
     
    
</post>
<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Kennywood was awsome!!!! We should go back, me, you, zack, and jenn.  I might even go on the air 360 thing!  I sent both amanda and zack a funny altenate ending to  a tale of two cities, it is hillariously disterbing.  Anyway, amanda, when i get a reply from you it is oftentimes blank.  How come?
     
    
</post>
<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      at the risk of sounding cliched....duh!!!!!!! ur crazy alright, but its' not a bad thing, don't worry. by the way, did kennywood rock or what?
     
    
</post>
<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      of corse you are!  Everybody is crazy.  some more so than others! (cough cough)
     
    
</post>
<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      pardon me amanda, but are u implying that i am crazy?? :-)
     
    
</post>
<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      fix my speeling?! that's no fun! besides, that takes entirely too much time. honestly. and im gald at least u got it sal. at least im not the only crazy one.
     
    
</post>
<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Spelling, hahahahahaha! 
     
    
</post>
<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Hey Jenn, why can't you understand any of the post.  I got it. :-)  And Amanda, when you write something like this you can always take the time to fix your spelling. :-) Just a thought.
     
    
</post>
<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      huh? i understood none of your post
     
    
</post>
<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      no i talkin abt jen w/ one n. she is conveiced that is y. personally, i thoink she's right.
     
    
</post>
<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      are you talking about me cause if you are i am Jenn 
     
    
</post>
<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      geez...my computer spazes for one weekend and i have me b/f and friend commenting idd htings to eacgt other. i have gotta get htis fixed. and by the way...my lack of spelling skills....not in any way due to the fact htat i am currently tlakin to sal....o no, not at all.  i dont' know y jen mad ehtat prediction..... 
     
    
</post>
<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      @_@This Comment, rant, quote, or other crazyness is brought to you by (Weird Kendo Guy), (Super Geek Extraordinaire)@_@   Anyone else wanna join? I can't start until I have 3 people.  
     
    
</post>
<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      @_@This Comment, rant, quote, or other crazyness is brought to you by (name or pen name), (epithet-remember english class)@_@  oh forget the top!! ill joing the blog.  
     
    
</post>
<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      @_@This Comment, rant, quote, or other crazyness is brought to you by (Weird Kendo Guy), (The eternaly... uh, what's it called. Queless?)@_@  Remember how I said I was an pen and paper RPG geek. Well I started an RPG blog. So if you want to join, tell me.  (RPG=Role Playing Game in case you didn't know, which, you probably did know, but... Ok. I'll stop typing now.) 
     
    
</post>
<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      @_@This Comment, rant, quote, or other crazyness is brought to you by (Weird Kendo Guy), (*cough cough*)@_@   I found a cool feature.  Kenshin: Oro?    \/\/007!!!!     
     
    
</post>
<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      @_@This Comment, rant, quote, or other crazyness is brought to you by (Wierdkendogirl), (hobbit one)@_@  I am definatly not ashamed of being a geek.  I am a geeky person but i dont want glasses.  Although ii do have some amazing combacks for ppl who call you four eyes, but that is not the point.  And once again it is in ths Boyfriends code of honnor to HUMMOR your girlfriend in a bad situation.  Although i thank you for the complement but i just dont see it. Toodle pip!
     
    
</post>
<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      @_@This Comment, rant, quote, or other crazyness is brought to you by (Weird Kendo Guy), (*blank stare*)@_@  Don't be ashamed of being a geek, because geeks are so cool. I'm a geek. I play pen and paper RPGs, you can't get any geekier than that. But, back to my original point... uhhhh... Well, I can't remember what that was, but you would look beautiful in glasses, Jenn.
     
    
</post>
<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      @_@This Comment, rant, quote, or other crazyness is brought to you by (wierdkendogirl), (girl who will soon look like more of a geek than she already is)@_@  GUESS WHAT?!  Im getting glasses.  I am not that thrilled but oh well.  Mom dosent trust me with contacts so i cant get them.  Boohoo *_*'.
     
    
</post>
<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      @_@This Comment, rant, quote, or other crazyness is brought to you by (Weird Kendo Guy), (The Stupid)@_@  Must have misread the meaning of epithet, I read: epithet - the part of a taxonomic name identifying a subordinate unit within a genus. Maybe I'm just stupid. I thought it meant describe the post... Yeah... I'm stupid.
     
    
</post>
<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      @_@This Comment, rant, quote, or other crazyness is brought to you by (weirdkendogirl), (Hobbit girl)@_@  I will join your apologetics blog.  And FYI, and epithet it something thet describes me, like "hobbit girl".  It describes you in some odd way or some whay you act.  Hear ye Hear ye, all ppls of the internet I have meet my match.  I have meet sombody, named Randi, that goes to my church and she knows more about Johnny Depp than i do!  I know more about Jack Sparrow, though.  But she knows more than i do bout JD kinda scary, huh?
     
    
</post>
<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      @_@This Comment, rant, quote, or other crazyness is brought to you by (Weird Kendo Guy), (clarification)@_@  Apologetics are a defence of the faith. The word apologetics comes from the same root as apology, which means to give a defence. Bet you didn't know that.
     
    
</post>
<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      @_@This Comment, rant, quote, or other crazyness is brought to you by (Weird Kendo Guy), (announcement)@_@  Hey, I've decided to start a Christian Apologetics blog. Please tell me if you are interested joining, or if you wish to ask questions that we could answer.
     
    
</post>
<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      @_@This Comment, rant, quote, or other crazyness is brought to you by (Wierkendogirl), (The Dictionary of Captain Jack Sparrow)@_@  "Sarcasm is a foreign language to you, isnt it?" -Timon in Lion King 1 1/2  I thought that this was interesting because i watched it right after we all talked on IM, which works because our conversations are usually sarcastic. ^_^
     
    
</post>
<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      @_@This Comment, rant, quote, or other crazyness is brought to you by (wierdkendogirl), (random person)  The only way to solve bordem is to do something.   Zack is on now.  Its 6:01 PM. 
     
    
</post>
<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       @_@This Comment, rant, quote, or other crazyness is brought to you by (Weird Kendo Guy), (Monkey)@_@  So Sarah, do you want to join the RPG?  
     
    
</post>
<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      @_@This Comment, rant, quote, or other crazyness is brought to you by (AJ), (boredom aficionado)@_@ i am soo bored so bored so bored so bored so bored so bored so bored. now was that a waste of time or what. zack get online during the day or its ur head. dork. is this crazy enough? lol. someone save me. i think i am insane. who knows when we're getting our class schedule?  
     
    
</post>
<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       @_@This Comment, rant, quote, or other crazyness is brought to you by (Weird Kendo Guy), (Tombstone reads: Uhh... That guy)@_@  No, that was not for you, Jenn. That was so we don't repeat the same mistake, and remember, I have ultimate control over that blog as GM. Even if  something  doesn't kill your character, I can (GM's discretion). Not that I would, but I can.  GM=Game Master  
     
    
</post>
<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      @_@This Comment, rant, quote, or other crazyness is brought to you by (wierdkendogirl), (Girl who can now see!)@_@  Amanda, you didnt embarras me.  In fact, i dont think i can be that embarased.   David, you wrote that to spite me didnt u.  i still dont want Kim to die, and she better live rather long. 
     
    
</post>
<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
        @_@This Comment, rant, quote, or other crazyness is brought to you by (Weird Kendo Guy), (Fated Failure)@_@   Well, so far it's not going well, but lets see how many people join before it dies. It is a pen and paper RPG... it's like D, but it is   DEFINITELY NOT DD.   The background story is the same as   urlLink  The Journals of Weird Kendo Guy    (It's a Sci-Fi). Oh, and remember, ALL characters will eventually die.    
     
    
</post>
<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      @_@This Comment, rant, quote, or other crazyness is brought to you by Chani, Sorceress of Stories and Scifi@_@  An RPG blog? Cool! What kind of RPG?
     
    
</post>
<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      @_@This Comment, rant, quote, or other crazyness is brought to you by (aj), (deer valley mourner)@_@  k, im late on the uptake, but that was sooo sweet! now have i realy embarrassed u, jenn? 
     
    
</post>
<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      SARAH:   You consider it dishonorable to attack enemies from the back, and yet you don't consider it dishonorable to manipulate someone else's mind? What kind of person are you? I suppose you already answered that.   Your hobbies include stealing and fighting? That's it? Don't you have anything better to do? Can't you browse the internet for something more... fulfilling... than that?
     
    
</post>
<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        USER PROFILE    Hello, I'm Kuronue.  A strange sadistic demon from Kurama's controversial past who is actually kind of gothic.  I have bat wings and wear mostly black clothes.  Like I said, I'm from Kurama's past.  In fact, I was his partner before I met a terrible fate while fleeing from the Castle of the Demon World.  My hobbies are stealing and fighting.  I use scythe and a pendant that I never cast away to manipulate my opponent's mind and make them believe whatever I wish them to believe.  Of course, I also just use the scythe.  And just to diminish any worries, I don't attack enemies from the rear.  It's very dishonorable.
     
    
</post>
<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        USER PROFILE    NAME: Sarah Anderson  I'm a twenty-five year old gal living in Colorado Springs. I have a black husky mix named Imperial Trainee Theodore Houndini Anderson. (He's as sweet a dog as anyone's ever had!)  Let's see... My job... I find people elligible to undergo a procedure to cure cancer and other terminal illnesses. It's really pretty exciting. I've actually had a couple people say no to it before. I don't really have many hobbies. I mostly just hang out around my house when I'm not working, play with Garshie, help my friend's son with his homework, etc. Sometimes I'll meet some friends at O'Malleys for lunch or dinner, but that's about it. 
     
    
</post>
<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Notice to all participants: You will now take on the role of one of your favorite characters, whether he or she be from some copyrighted media, your own, or any combination of the two. (Please stick to only one. Changing   occasionally   is not a bad thing.) These characters from now on will meet on IM, Blogger IM. Please begin your participation with a bio of some sort. For any sense of sanity, we're leaving out screennames on this; it'd get too confusing for anyone unfamiliar with the shows referenced, which include:    STARGATE: SG-1   (DISCLAIMER: "Stargate SG-1" and its characters are the property of MGM/UA, Double Secret Productions, Gekko Film Corp., Showtime/Viacom and USA Networks, Inc. This story is for entertainment purposes only and no money has exchanged hands. No copyright infringement is intended. The original characters, situations and story are the property of the author(s), and may not be republished or archived elsewhere without the author's permission.  YUYU HAKUSHO   Other than that, I have one thing to say:  Any use of copyrighted material is for the enjoyment of participants and readers only. We are getting paid only in our dreams, ie. not at all, not a penny, not a pfennig, not a pound, not one Euro. This is just fun. Any recognizable characters are the property of whoever holds the copyright or the author.  More will be added if more needs to be said.
     
    
</post>
<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      SARAH:  You kidding? We're gonna have a ton of people to calm you down, Mr. K.
     
    
</post>
<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Kuronue:  This should be interesting.  We should be getting a new member soon, just to give you a heads up.  I have no idea who they are.
     
    
</post>
<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      O'NEILL:  Go first with what? ...I shoot right handed, eat right handed, do most things right handed...
     
    
</post>
<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      SARAH:  Exactly. Did you hear that, Mr. K? A privelage! That means I have to like you enough to know that you're joking.   So. Let's all start off on the right foot, shall we? I don't know anyone here who's a lefty. ... Jack, how 'bout you go first?
     
    
</post>
<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      O'NEILL:  Baka?...oh, wait Danny says it means idiot.  And being able to call Reeses a snake-head and get away with it is a privelage, not a right, Bat-boy. Dead-Bat-Boy. Is it just me that finds that creepy?
     
    
</post>
<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      SARAH:  Excuse me, whoever you are, but I have a deep need to know why you feel the need to up and call me a snake head. I'll have you know that I'm NOT!  ... .... whatever you mean by "snake head" of course...
     
    
</post>
<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      KURONUE:  *glares evilly*
     
    
</post>
<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      SARAH:  Kuronue: Give me one reason not to; you just called me a snake head without any proof. Oh, right. Resurrection. Like I'll believe that! I repeat: What kind of person are you?  Nice save, Jack. It's so great to see that you're on! Could you lend me a hand here? He/she/it called me a snake head. You know exactly how much I appreciate that!
     
    
</post>
<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      KURONUE:  Don't call me a baka!  I don't need a sarcophagus!  And I could care less that you help people.  "I kill the spider to save the butterfly."
     
    
</post>
<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      SARAH:  "Snake head"? Excuse me, but I think I deserve a little more credit than that! You think I'm evil, do you?  How to live your afterlife? Yeah, right. It's called a sarcophagus, you baka!  Have you ever considered that I might be a caring person? Did I mention I help people find a cure for their cancer?
     
    
</post>
<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        USER PROFILE    Well, howdy, campers. I'm Colonel Jack O'Neill, but Reeses already knew that. My job involves lots of things that...well, I'd have to kill you if I told you about them, and I'm sure Batman wouldn't take that too well...  As for hobbies: fishing. When I'm not doing that, it's annoying Danny, pestering Carter, or teaching Teal'c the idiosyncracies of the American language. Wonder if snake baiting counts...eh, the  other  kind of snake; nothing personal, Reeses.
     
    
</post>
<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      KURONUE:  Give me a break, snake head.  Technically, I'm supposed to be dead; I don't need you telling me how to live my afterlife.  Anyway, why do you even care?
     
    
</post>
<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      SARAH:  I wouldn't be so certain, Captain Sparrow. I'm sure that, given the right circumstances, you could die just as many times as Jack. And as he and the rest of my friends from that... company... would tell you, it really doesn't matter in what manner you die as long as there's... a certain piece of technology... nearby.  Sorry, it's just seemed that way, what with the baka and rum and "snake head" discussions and all.  Yeah, I'll try to convince her of that! Wait, you're from, what, the 1800's? And you know about different kinds of peanut butter?  Ah, yes, dark chocolate. The best food-like substance in the world! Too bad it's so expensive. Now, I won't take you up on any offer of rum, but if you're going to be handing out some of that "fine Caribbean dark chocolate", I'll be more than happy to lighten your load of that!  Nah, I'd rather that they were fully conscious and understand exactly how we're gonna cure them. (Though I have to admit, drunk or not, it's hilarious to see their faces when we tell them!)
     
    
</post>
<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      CAPTAIN Jack Sparrow:  Well, unlike you, I can only live once and die once.  Im not afraid to die, love, but I would rather be killed doing something worth while than to be publicly exicuted.  Its to much publicity and i dont like crowds.  Plus if i have to hear my charges over and over again they could at least get my Rank right, savvy?  I have absolutely no negativity, and have not held a grudge since before i killed Barbossa, mate.    Peanut Butter is not even in the same catagory as Rum or Chocolate.  Peanut Butter is like eating sand, so corse and grainy unless you eat the crunchy kind.  Now, I have to say that sitting on the Pearl with a bottle of rum and some nice carribean chocolate is the best way to spend an afternoon at sea, savvy?  I prefer dark chocolate myself, it is a tad bitter, mate. I dont know... make them so drunk that they are oblivious to what they are going through?  Welcome Ava, at least someone around here thinks that Rum sounds good, in fact i shall go and endulge in some minor rum drinking, wouldnt want to be too drunk tommorrow Im sure.  Gooday, mates!    
     
    
</post>
<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      SARAH:  Welcome, Ava. If you haven't had time to get caught up, others here include Kuronue (some anime), Colonel Jack O'Neill (Stargate), Captain Jack(three extra characters here) Sparrow (POTC), and me, Sarah Anderson (Stargate fanficdom).  A noose? A noose?! Hah! You're afraid of dying once! When I go on "buisiness trips", I have to worry about dying several times, which the good colonel here can attest to.  Okay, thanks for that understanding, captain. I suppose we could get to a point without so much negativity between us.  Lemme point somethin' out, Cpt. Sparrow: I was interpreting someone else's message to Jack. And, by the way, she says peanut butter's better than rum, beer, or chocolate. ...Humph. Now, how could any alcoholic beverage   help   with "the whole cancer thing"?
     
    
</post>
<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      CAPTAIN Jack Sparrow:  ( Very calmly) I may not know what it is to be critised and judged because of my anatomy, love but try living your life in fear of a noose.  Nobody understands a pirates mind, most are not just mindless people who go stealing things and killing people.  Did You hear about when i sacked Nassasu Port without even firing a shot.  I did that to avoid casualties, mate.  Also, Im not like Barbossa, savvy.  He got what he want by killing.  Did you know that the cannons on my ship, when i was captain, were not used at all on ports but on the daily firieng against another pirate ship to see which where more powerful nines (usually wagered on a case of rum).  And, love, im sorry about the "baka" comment i realize it is that same as me saying "savvy".  (still calm but with a little more force) Never insult my rum, telling someone not to try rum is...is...blashphamy.  If CJ wants to try it, than he sure can, love.  Also, ever think that it could help with the whole cancer thing????
     
    
</post>
<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hello. i am one of your new members. my name is ava pierce and i am hawkeyes' younger sister (from the television show MASH). i am a "minny hawkeye", having the smae black hair (only longer) and blue eyes. and i am slightly short. i am a captain and a doctor in the korean war.  oh, and we have a still in our tent, so that rum is sounding kinda good...
     
    
</post>
<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      SARAH:  Just get over it, huh, Sparrow? How do I "just get over it"? I find it extremely insulting. I bet you don't even know what it's like to be criticized and judged just based on your anatomy,   sir.   I like "baka." Besides, Mr. K understands it better; it's his own language.  *Visions of drunk demons dancing in her head...*    Humans are indeed confusing, but I would like to point out that they're not impossible to live with.    Jack, you up for keeping to your beer and not touching rum? Miss V says that beer is bad enough (for you), but rum sounds to be even worse.
     
    
</post>
<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      CAPTAIN Jack Sparrow:  Kuronue, what kind of demon are you exactly? Also mate, exactly how much rum would you be needin.  The first  Sparrow Anger teatment  is to get the smell of rum so that you do not get sick.  I've had expiriance with Demons and rum before and, lets just say, it dosent sit well, savvy?  That Inuyasha couldnt stand the taste of it let alone the smell so "he settled for no less than total abstanence from the demon rum".  I say "demon rum" because of the effect it had on him.  If, demon-boy, you do not believe that i have met Inuyasha   you can go on Fanfiction.net and find the story called Pirates of the Carribean meets Inuyasha where  i am writing my adventures with this half-demon-dog-boy, savvy?  CJ, beer is  one  of the alcohalic agents in rum.  you also have the whiskey, burbon, and the vodca.  Your a military man no doubt, defenatly not a pirate because our rankings only go up to captain, but you should be able to handle some fine carribean rum.  And if you can't, mate, its pathetic, it truely is.     
     
    
</post>
<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      O'NEILL  So its more like Kuron-you-ay?  You don't know batman? What planet are you-never mind.  'Lo Captain Jack, I'm Colonel Jack...  I dunno about Rum, but i prefer Beer...a nice, cold beer sat my a lake with a fishing pole in my hand...
     
    
</post>
<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Kuronue:  No, it's not pronounced "Kuronay," it's pronounced "KuronUay."  You can't forget the "u" in there.  Who's this Batman, and what the heck is the Batmobile?    I'm keeping that rum in mind.  I think I'm going to need a lot of it.  *mumbles* Humans are so confusing.  This is why I never left Makai.
     
    
</post>
<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      CAPTAIN Jack Sparrow:            Ello, mates.  Its a strange thing this chat.  Sarah, love, if someone calls you snakehead, you should learn to get over it.  And why must you use the term Baka, idiot will suffice.  Also, demon boy - i would love to help you work out any anger issues you have.  Which, you must have because you got angry at someone typing your name wrong, savvy? Rum works wonders!!            Well for those of you who do not know me, I am The infamous Captain Jack Sparrow.  If you forget the CAPTAIN i might just send Elizabeth Swann after you and that IS something to be afraid of, mates.   adieu, avidosay, aloha, and all those other good-by things                                                           
     
    
</post>
<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      O'NEILL   What's wrong with Batman? He was cool...who doesn't want a Batmobile???  So its pronounced Kuronay???
     
    
</post>
<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      SARAH:  I have a bit of trouble spelling things I can't pronounce. I mean, I can try, but with the changes to this IM(ish) thing, "Kuronuay" is about the best I can do.   Call me "S" if you want to; I really don't care.
     
    
</post>
<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Kuronue:  Will you quit calling me that?!  It's Kuronue!
     
    
</post>
<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I'm sorry,  Captain , but that just seems like faulty reasoning to me. God knows what you're going to do, how you're going to go, what decisions you'll make, but that shouldn't give you an excuse for bad habits. Just because He knows what's going to happen doesn't mean that's the way he wants it to be, "savvy"? (Miss V wishes me to express her skepticism in my belief in a higher power. But that's the way she was brought up to think.)      Ah, yes, Anime. You know, I kinda quit paying attention to that when I found a ton of other things to think about. You know, well-being of my world, how my friends are doing (and what trouble they've gotten into lately), grades and school, etc. But, yes, I suppose I can figure what you're talking about. (Though I'm much more of a Star Wars person. Jar Jar and John Williams all the way!)      C. Sparrow, I think you need to give Mr. K a rather exact definition of the word "savvy". (Remember: proper capitilization can help to convey a clear and concise meaning!)   
     
    
</post>
<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Kuronue:  You know Inu-Yasha and Sesshomaru, I'm that kind of demon.  I agree with Sparrow.  Speaking of Sparrow, why do keep calling us all savvy?
     
    
</post>
<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      CAPTAIN Jack Sparrow:  But love, if God choses when i go then he also knows the exact way i will go.  So maybe God has planed for me to die of liver failure from drinking to much rum, savvy?  So technicly, dying because of rum is not dying prematurly at all.  Though i would prefer a natural cause than a noose.
     
    
</post>
<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      High accumulation of spirit energy, huh? Never heard of it. Hey, that reminds me of something Jonas told me. Did you know that if all the energy in a banana was released at once when you ate it, you'd explode with body parts flying up to a mile apart?  Okay, so you're not a "demon" demon. Got it. Dunno anyone who'd freely admit it to me. 'Course I try to stay away from people like that. They bug me.  You know what, Captain Jack? I'd rather not die prematurely at all! I'll leave this... dimension when the good Lord's good'n'ready for me to!
     
    
</post>
<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      CAPTAIN Jack Sparrow:  Rum has a different effect on me.  Im a pirate, it just is, savvy.  I would rather die of liver failure than from a noose, mate.
     
    
</post>
<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Kuronue:  As I have already pointed out, my eyes glow red, but I believe that is due to the fact that I have a high accumlination of spirit energy.  Also, I am a demon (not in the sense as you are reffering to).
     
    
</post>
<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Schizophrenia? Not really. I mean, in the sense that it's two personalities in one body, I suppose so, but it's not any kind of mental disorder. Much more rewarding than that, really.  Yes, just yellow. So? Eyes can glow another color?    That to which she is referring is neither schizophrenia nor multiple personalities disorder. To reinforce her idea on this, she even researched the two; you can be sure that her analysis is correct.  As for glowing eyes, I am aware of only one chemical which can cause this, and it has a tendancy to cause the eyes to flash in a yellow or golden light. I hold no expectation that there is no other chemical with such a property.  
     
    
</post>
<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Kuronue:  I seriously doubt that I'm a snake-head.  From what I understand from watching it, it seems that what you are speaking of is like schizophrenia.  Also, their eyes only appear to glow yellow.
     
    
</post>
<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Then maybeyou're a snake-head as well?      I'm thinking "run" is always a good option, though Miss V says that if you're really the aforementioned source of evil, by all means, "fight you guys" is the best option.      I can see the immense frustration. When my eyes glow, it's not usually in the dark, mostly because I like light. Halogen lamps are the best next to pure sunlight, though I'll settle for a set of incandescent bulbs. (I think; it's been a long time since eighth grade science!) Or the light provided by computer moniters. That's always good. Ah... the wonders of e-mail! Fanfiction! Star Wars fan sites! All wondrous things to be looking at late into the night! Of course, that's not usually when my eyes glow. In fact, I think my eyes glow the least then and--        I'm sorry. Sarah Anderson has become suddenly unavailable as a result of her unscreened babbling.   </post></Blog>