<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>


     

       It is Antoine de Saint-Exupery’s birthday today.  He would have been 104 years old.  Despite being one of the greatest author’s I’ve ever had the pleasure of reading, he lived an extraordinary life as well.  Most of us know him for  The Little Prince , however, most of his other novels were related to his life as a pilot—an extremely lonely, beautiful, adventurous and strenuous life all the same.  These books show us the fantasy of being a modern-day wanderer while sticking to the reality of flying at the same time.   The wandering theme—something I’ve grown accustomed to throughout the years in my readings of great novels, show us the beauty of being human, the fantastic experience of the seeker, and the desperation of really living life to its fullness.  Going back to  The Little Prince ; we find that this very same theme applies.  However, unlike many adult human beings, the protagonist in question seeks only to find experience with his immediate environment.  He finds every aspect of his surroundings interesting and vitally important.  He looks at the world through the eyes of a true wanderer: he finds beauty in all things.  If only we could also find similar beauty in the things we see and feel and experience in our own lives.  Now wouldn’t that be a most extraordinary happening.  On that note, a quote from The Little Prince:  “Grown-ups never understand anything by themselves, and it is exhausting for children to have to provide explanations over and over again.” Thanks to Richard Howard’s translation.  

     

    
</post>
<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>


     

         quotable  Shaq announces he's definitely leaving the Lakers organization next season because he wants to "play for a team that's willing to win." However, what I found so interesting was his final quote to ESPN.com --    "But can't nobody [mess] with me. I'm like toilet paper, Pampers and toothpaste. I'm definitely proven to be effective."   urlLink full story  

     

    
</post>
<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>


     

       I finished watching this film with a new sense of awe for American cinema.  Notwithstanding the phenomenal cast of characters, this film seems to define--in my opinion--everything good and true in modern cinema.  Filmed in the mid-sixties,  urlLink It's A Mad Mad Mad Mad World  follows a dynamic hodgepodge of men and women who are searching for a recently deceased man's buried treasure of $350,000.  Of course, an awesome display of quarky incidents fill in the blanks between the beginning of this race to the end.  I won't even mention all of the films that have taken on this same theme since this movie.  I am simply posting this in order to beg all of you to see it.  I have never laughed so intensly.  Kudos to  urlLink Stanley Kramer  for directing this fine film!

     

    
</post>
<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>


     

      Unfortunately,  urlLink Lollapalooza  has been canceled due to low ticket sales.  I was fairly anxious for having a chance to see Morrissey live, however, it seems that simply won't happen at this point.        urlLink Morrissey  has been nothing less than a hero in my mind--his music, his lyrics, his complete persona, encapsulate everything good and true in music.  He is honest, sincere and genuine with every lyric.  His absolute sense of reality paves a revolutionary way towards real music.  Music that not only tells a story, not only tells events and actions, but tells them honestly and with vigor.  Morrissey is the reality that we all live everyday.  And he's not afraid to speak about it.  I will miss him in concert.

     

    
</post>
<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>


     

            Is Google's new Gmail system invading your privacy?   I've recently obtained three  urlLink Gmail  accounts via user invitations ( urlLink anonymous.kook@gmail.com , my personal account;  urlLink zshop.sales@gmail.com , my new business account for  urlLink Amazon ; and  urlLink valid.email.address@gmail.com , my account for when I simply need a "valid Email address" to register.) :)  Gmail is still in its Beta phase, meaning, it's not been released fully and is still being tested. The best way to test something is to create a market to do the work for you, so, Google has made an invitation only based system. I've been lucky enough to get three invites so far and will continue to check for more, however, I'm sure the full version will be released soon anyway.   After doing a bit of research on Gmail, I've noticed that it has been the product of heavy scrutiny.Websites such as  urlLink gmail-is-too-creepy.com  have been quite outspoken with their fears of Google's ability to invade our valuable privacy. I, however, agree with  urlLink Tim O'Reilly --a computer book publisher and owner of a large network which discusses topics such as the one we're discussing now!--who basically says that all Email providers have the same ability to peruse our secrets as Google does. Spam filters, virus scanners and other similar anti-hacking technologies do this everyday. See his full story  urlLink here .  So why all the fuss about Google? Gmail introduces a new technology, previously unavailable to Email accounts. This technology allows users to search for multiple prior Emails, or conversations as Google puts it, much the same as one would search for something on Google. Not only can you search for certain ideas and/or certain discussions with specific people, but everything you search for is archived. That way, you no longer have to go through all of your Email with your best friend to find that interesting topic you just have to read again. Not to mention the fact that users get 1000MB of space. I for one, think this technology is revolutionary.   But I hope I'm not the only one asking Google this: Now that we have Gmail, how long until Gchat?  

     

    
</post>
<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>


     

      These are all of my  urlLink Xanga  posts--as I've moved over here now:  I recently submitted this short story to another  urlLink blog  and will receive another  urlLink Gmail  account for it.  The only requirements were the story had to be over 300 words and had to incorporate five words (below shown in bold).              He could not explain the obtrusive commercial element engrossing the television in his environmentally friendly, loft-style suite.  “Always low prices.  Always.”               “Always low prices, indeed!” thought Ralph Nader with a snarl.  “I’ve said it once and I’ll say it again!  ‘Wal-Mart is a cancer on the economy!’”              Ralph quickly left the room in a huff and ventured toward the island in his kitchen—a regular paradise surrounded by a vast array of gizmos and gadgets even Bill Gates himself could not understand.  On top of the center piece, in a ceramic bowl painted red, were three ripe bananas.  Eagerly, Ralph pealed a banana—the plumpest in the bunch—and proceeded to engulf it like, perhaps, a gorilla in the wild, eating under immense pressure.                “Why, I wonder what the ‘Mayor of Baghdad’ would do in a time like this!  This is crucial!  This plague on society will not stand!”  Ralph wielded his half-eaten banana in the air like some dim-witted knight’s apprentice would wield a blunt sword in the heat of battle.  “By God!  I’ve got to get out of here quick!”              Like Batman out of the Bat Cave, Ralph sped out of his garage and off his remote estate in a flash.  He was headed for the airport.               “I have to leave the country,” he thought, as he sped down some highway not meant for human travel.  “Yeah, that’ll be my salvation.”              In his newly acquired H2, Ralph flies down the highway at unclockable speeds.  As the trees passing by become a blur, he pops up his handy-dandy passenger seat laptop and attempts to connect to the Internet.  He wishes to check the latest news at  urlLink RalphDontRun.Net .  Unfortunately for him, however, Internet Explorer seems to be down.               “Damn this thing!  And damn Gates!” he screams as he quickly turns back to the road.  “Ten more miles and I’ll be at the airport!  That’s hardly enough time for Netscape to boot up!  If only there was a browser which was both user-friendly and efficient!”               Ralph hastily shoved his laptop out of the way as he pulled into his less-than-private docking station at whatever airport he was at (we can’t exactly say or the terrorists win).  A dozen or so supporters raised “Nader in 2004” signs high up in the air.  With a smile, Ralph thought “Wow!  Every last one of my supporters all gathered here to see me off!”   The smile faded as he realized he’d forgotten his wallet at his environmentally friendly, loft-style suite.  Fortunately for him, he was wearing his favorite navy sport jacket.  The same jacket he was wearing just a month ago on a flight to one of the top five major cities in the nation (again, we can’t exactly say or the terrorists win).  On this specific flight, a famous ditzy celebrity spotted some dark-skinned foreigner.  She threw a fit and spouted off about all of her eager-for-revenge attorneys and with that, the plane landed at the nearest airport and the poor dark-skinned man was arrested for violation of some obscure provision under the Patriot Act (later that day, some tyrannical Patriot Act Enforcer shoved bamboo shoots up his fingernails).   With a newly acquired sense of encouragement, Ralph waltzed into the airport lobby and rode the moving floor down to the popular airline that gave him a substitute ticket—given his run-in with what must have been a terrorist—on the previous flight.  As he approached the airline attendant, he pulled the neatly folded ticket out of his favorite navy sport jacket and placed it firmly on the desk in front of him.   With a smirk, the airline attendant informed Ralph that the ticket “expired last week.”  “What!” started Ralph, “There’s no way this is an expired flight ticket!  I received it just last month!”  “Sorry Mr. Nader—and by the way, my sister-in-law’s cousin’s boyfriend’s mother is a stocker at a Super Wal-Mart, you insensitive goon—the ticket is expired.  That’s how we do things around here.”  “Oh is it?”  “Yep.”  “Okay, ma’am—and forget what I said about Wal-Mart: I was drunk—how can I purchase a new ticket?”  Suddenly, a ring was heard throughout the airport.  “What was that?!” screeched Ralph with a shudder.  “Oh.  That.  Yes, Mr. Nader, that is our new anti-terrorist ring.  It’s supposed to deter the bastards by reminding them of…uh…something-or-other…  I…I just can’t remember exactly what that something-or-other is.”  “Right.  Can we just move on with the ticket?”  “Yes, Mr. Nader.  Let me just connect us to the Internet.  Yes, here we are.  One way or roundtrip, Mr. Nader?”  “What?  I thought IE was down.  And there’s no way Netscape came through that fast.”  “Well of course not, sir, because we use neither.  The new Firefox is both user-friendly and efficient.”  “Well, bouncing bananas!” shouted Ralph, “I suppose I’ll get that ticket yet, thanks to Firefox!”  “Yes sir, as long as you have a major credit card.”  Ralph’s face became long.  “You do have a major credit card don’t you Mr. Nader?”   Ralph turned pale as he did an about face and briskly exited the airport.  In other news: I might move over to Blogger, as there are simply far more options in utilizing its services.  I will attempt to update this as much as possible and use it as a forum for friends and family--although, I haven't given the link to anyone yet, so none of them--if anyone--will see this post.  lol.  Sunday, June 13, 2004  	Yeah.  So I haven't been able to access the Web at all lately.  I'm now in Missouri and we have a cable connection which is just about twice the speed of the cable at my house in Bedford, though, I have to wait for a wireless adapter card.  Meanwhile, I'm stuck here on a 24" flat panel screen in the office ("boo hoo" -- yeah right!).   Anyway, when I can get my own setup back, I'll keep this thing updated regularly!  Sunday, May 23, 2004  I've been unbelievably busy lately. But for you people who actually look at my thrills and spills, I'll attempt to continue to update it as often as I can. Last weekend I went to Lake Whitney (Whitney, TX) with some friends. Here's a shot from the thirty-foot cliffs we were diving off of (click image for full sized version):   urlLink     Fun stuff. I'm at a loss as to what I did prior to last weekend--it's simply been too long. However, the present weekend--now just ending--has been fun. Yesterday, me and my best friend David hustled a museum (we snuck in) and had lunch at a great restaurant in Fort Worth: Lucille's.During the evening I went to a dance benefit deal which was quite entertaining. I sat through part of the movie Pi at Johnny's today.Although I did roll my eyes at many situations in the film, I must admit the camera work is damn good. Unfortunately, the ideas and philosophy behind it simply aren't as revolutionary as the film seems to think. I might be going to Mexico next weekend, though plans aren't certain at this point. I might also be traveling to Wisconsin for a job that has come up. That's about it, really.  That should be enough archiving...  It's all new stuff from here on out!

     

    
</post>
<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


     

           Alright, so I don't want to have to wait another year to basically say that Aldous Huxley has been an immense impact on my life. His birthday was yesterday, 1856.            Brave New World  impacted me heavily as a child and I think that my current interest in the trends in science--the idea that science has become a conquering machine (alla Descartes; cf. his  Discourse on Method  Book Six), i.e., technological and ultimately sophistical rather than simply inquiry. Aristotle noted that science should be in the form of an attempt to understand the physical world (cf. his  Physis ), however, that idea has long since gone awry and most noticeable of this is the idea that technology is somehow equal to science.     But this is going away from the subject. Huxley means a great deal to me and because he touched me so early in life, I will share with you an essay I wrote about  Brave New World  waaaay back in ninth grade (freshman year of high school) for my English GT class. I will note that I recovered this essay a few years ago from a disk I used in high school from an old Macintosh machine. Evidently, I did the cover page at home (I tended to print very lavish cover pages as opposed to the minimal textual norm) and have since lost it, given there have been several new machines flowing through my house since then. Anyway, so to make a long story short, I don't have any recollection of what the essay was called. So, I'll just call it "Huxley Essay." Yeah. And here it is:    "Huxley Essay" -- circa 1995                      What separates human beings from other mammals?    Both have minds, instinct, capacity for knowledge, and most distinguishing, choices.    But man began with a little something extra, something that delegates guilt, expresses powerful emotional feelings, restores faith, and creates a conscience; that something is the soul.    Through technology and science, man uses his drive for knowledge to create mechanical and chemical objects and science related formulas, all this to ease the difficulty of life.    Once this is done, man begins to get selfish desiring machines called computers to do all the work for them, programming the machines to do as man wills.    Once man has developed enough technology, his leaders begin to hold back information, because with knowledge comes power, and to keep this power, man must restrain man; is technology the pathway to digression?                                    W  A  R                                     During World War Two Adolf Hitler seized control of Germany as a whole by keeping the Germans at distance with the truth.    Hitler controlled the BBC radio lines throughout the entire country, filling it with Nazi propaganda and false news reports that always favored the Germans.    This increased Hitler's political power and the morale of his soldiers, giving him the upper hand in the war.    George Orwell published this same theory fictionally in his future-fantasy classic,  1984 .              "And somehow or other, quite anonymous, there were the directing brains who coordinated the whole effort and laid out the lines of policy which made it necessary that this fragment of the past be preserved, that one falsified, and the other rubbed out of existence" (Orwell 38).                                 Orwell used this same basic principle to not only give false news reports (of a false war), but also to falsify life itself, erasing history and creating a history in accordance with  Big Brother .     1984  used the motto; "War is peace…    Freedom is slavery…    Ignorance is strength" quite frequently in the novel (Orwell 7).    Orwell used "War is Peace" to support the nature of power over the weak in the novel.    Explaining that with a constant state of war, there is greater peace in the community as everyone unites to become one strong force and forget any petty arguments.    The state can also control the public easier and ration their needs.    "Freedom is slavery" gives a need for control and "Ignorance is strength" strives on stupidity to control.                                 U            T            O            P            I            A              An overwhelming drive exists between the thoughts of the common man and the nobility of the exceptional, through which an entire realm of absurd intelligence that is marked by the futile as insolence and ambiguity is compensated.    Social class and physical stasis embellish the thoughts of the weak and degenerate.    The idea of inferiority surpassing the physical superior is beyond insipid and falls under the inane category of impossible.    This is all considered by our standards to be an absolute absurdity, but it occurs currently; has occurred in the past, and will most definitely dominate the future as we know it.    The path to digression is absolute, for with the growth of man comes the growth of mentality.    This drives man to corruption, for there is an underlining climax to the growth and definition of mentality: corruption.    The denouement is only the end of mental salvation, however.    It is the beginning of menial civilization.    "BNW is a benevolent dictatorship: a static, efficient, totalitarian welfare state" (Pearce, 8).          Power under any circumstance involves the progression of the mind, the mind being human, and the human being instinctually selfish.    In this post-Darwinian society that we live in, mankind has realized that there is something more to life than evolution,    that something happens to be the soul.    And, as modern scientists have come to theorize, the soul is but a gateway to the mind, and the mind has overwhelming potential for brilliance.    Thus, the conquering of the mind can only be rendered by the mind itself.         To conquer the mind takes absolute precision.    Aldous Huxley, author of  Brave New World,  seems to do a brilliant job of describing just how to do so.    In his world, life begins with the chemical manipulation of the brain.    This tampering of the mind is the simplest solution.    Although Huxley takes it further, utilizing basic manipulation and the theory of collectivism to establish unity in his world.    They are taught to need one another, to want what they've got; they are  taught  happiness.         Once the mind has arrived at a certain point, it searches for power.    To gain this power involves conquering the feeble minded.    Once this is done, the mind moves on to  creating  the feeble minded, and then it has total control.    Once it has reached this point, it must retain stability and ensure the succession of future generations to follow in its footsteps.    This is the point at which (the only conceivable) Utopia is met.    However, upon realizing this, Utopia seems not to be the perfect community, but only a lie.                         </post></Blog>