<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>29,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I’m not like previously now.  Just only last year, people said I’m bluffing them when I say to them I’m in form 4………………………………………………………………... It was a rainy day……………after tuition, I need a bus to send me home………………   Paying the bus fee ...............with casual wear….   ‘Malay bus driver’: pergi mana? &gt;&gt;he asked me after I put 60cents into the box…….DBH  ‘MR.MY’(me): pergi Satapak Jaya!  ‘Malay bus driver’: bukan 60sen! RM1.20 (WTF………………then, searching for another 60cents……………….OMG!OMG!.my wallet is empty!@#$%^*()_+ how the hell to leave the bus without any money&gt;&gt;my only 60cents already inside the ‘stupid’ box………………………I must think in order to solve this matter think-think-think!!…………………Ah!! I have an idea…..)  ‘MR.MY’: &gt;&gt;pretending&gt;&gt;huh??bawah 12 tahun bukan 60sen sahaja meh??  ‘Malay bus driver’: awak 12 tahun ke? (he began to show his bloody face and he was reluctant to give me the 60cents ticket&gt;kanak-kanak berhawa dingin&gt;hohoho!!    ‘MR.MY’:oooooo (Then, I stop before my usual bus stop…………….not stupid, just for safety only…………. Otherwise, he will recognize me……………………..)   WOW! SO CLOSE!@#$%…………………………….how brilliant am I!!!…….hahaha!   
     

    
</post>
<date>28,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Today, the ‘kayu’ taught like usual…………………..copy, copy and COPY.  Aiyoh……….don’t know what she had taught……..better ask her to ‘balik kampung’.  We have done our BIO PEKA today……………..huh! What a relief!!!!………..planned so hard to buy those silly bougainvilleas………………………..I have had tried so hard to bring  ‘Jesus’ the bougainvillea but I didn’t hear a ‘thank you’ from him but just -----  ‘Jesus’:  Wah 5 ringgit so expensive ah ……you con me ah!  And why just got a few amount of flowers only………………….  HEY !@#$%^*()_+ now I owe you meh! 
     

    
</post>
<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yesterday, 5S2 guys did a gotong-royong………….. we started from 8 am and eventually finished at 2.30pm.  Well, that was not an easy job to clean up the ‘millennium dirt’.  After we complete our jobs , we have had our lunch at ‘Hwa Yuen Restaurant’……that was my first time having fried rice there because I usually go there for Tom yam…………….we chit-chatting there for more than an hour……….all about those spooky affairs…………ooh!! ‘popet’ is crazy…………………………………… Then, I have had my first time riding on a motorbike.  Wow! That was quite thrilling and exciting……dangerous oh……………that is why my mum did not allow that………………….nvmlah, just a very short distance only………WK want to fetch me mah, if not how oh! Then, in the bus………………that bloody Indian bus driver……………that bloooooooooooooooooooody…………..so rude ……….just like never study before………………………….damn him. 
     

    
</post>
<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
       KFC, RAIN, FLOOD, FLOATING SLIPPER AND COCKROACHES.   After school or I should say after the torturing lesson of Ambika, we (HK, Goldsheep, TTP and of course me) went to KFC&gt;Jln Genting Klang………to have our lunch there.  We indulged in pieces of ‘TOMYAM Chicken’.  For not a while, EE cames with her friends&gt;&gt;&gt;well, that’s not so important…………………………………………        There was a heavy rain outside but I didn’t notice it at that time, maybe my concentration was only upon the ‘TOMYAM Chicken’ in front of me---till………………. I heard an astoundment from the thunderstorm.  Then, I only know that there was a heavy rain.  That rain caused a slight flood but it was almost 4 to 5 inches from the ground.  Those pedestrians who wear slippers seems to be a bit silly at that time……………..I felt a bit guilty to see their slippers floating above the water with my mind scoffing to them …… hehehehehe…  after the rain gone ‘mild’ and the wind gone ‘tame’ a little………we walked out from KFC toward our bus stop respectively…………TTP goes with HK while Goldsheep goes with me…….In that time, cockroaches also took a refuge under the roof of that little bus stop ……. If not I think the flood will drown them……………….. 
     

    
</post>
<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      It has been a shocking day………………………………………………………………. My uncle fetches me to school every morning. Today he cames as usual as before &gt; 6 o’clock and a half.  He rushed to my school by right I am not in a hurry.  He droves like drunker or like a worm searching for a hole to burrow itself.  He rushes, rushes and rushes till…………. suddenly there comes a horn&gt;&gt;puuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuu………….. when I tossed my head to the right, I saw the big front lamp of a massive Four Wheel Drive-‘Ssang yoong-REXTON’, several centimeters beside my skull just separated by a thin glass window………DBH &gt;damn shocking………  Today is also an election day for ‘Student Union’ in my school.  The Headmaster acted like a ‘Doraemon’ when he is cordially invited to start the opening ceremony.  Then, the last two years AJK of ‘Student Union’ was invited to vote for candidates.  Some of them were so stupid, give a chance for Pn.Lily to condemn our Chong Hwa’s students……….they came with their blonde colour-tinted hair.  When I reach home, my maid cooked me a big bow of  ‘Bi hun soup’ and……..my tongue ‘detected’ foreign objects again---sand.  !@#$%^*()_+ _)(*^%$#@!……….!! 
     

    
</post>
<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
       ‘Counting’ on my maid   I think I have a terror of eating my maid’s food……..or even eating in my house.  I ate a lot despite her badly cooking, but she act too much……… till I’m going to become dejected to put her food into my stomach.  She often ‘adorn’ my dinner or lunch with foreign objects like plastic and………….I still remember that last month when I found two small stones shape like bubbles inside my bottle.  I almost swallowed it………….dunno what will happen to me if I didn’t spit it out immediately.  Besides that, she often grinds at night……..no, I shall say midnight&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;that noise(maybe is a lullaby) disturbs me to deep into slumber.    One thing I can say is&gt;she was keen on washing toilet…………..1 hour everyday in toilet doing washing jobs but the toilet still not seems to be very clean……….....
     

    
</post>
<date>16,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
       JOKES  hehehehehe.....................haha...... .  5 presidents are on a plane     Five presidents are on a plane: George Washington, Abraham Lincoln, Thomas Jefferson, George W. Bush, and Bill Clinton. George Washington says, "I will make someone happy!" and throws a dollar bill off the plane.  Then Abraham Lincoln says, "I will make five people happy!" and throws 5 one dollar bills off the plane.   Then Thomas Jefferson says, "I will make 500 people happy!" and throws 500 one dollar bills off the plane.   Then George W. Bush says, "I will make the whole world happy!" and throws Bill Clinton off the plane.    
     

    
</post>
<date>13,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
        JOKES AGAIN !!    The President''s Puzzle    Dick Cheney walks into the Oval Office and sees The President whooping and hollering.  "What's the matter, Mr. President?" The Vice President inquired.   "Nothing at all, boss. I just done finished a jigsaw puzzle in record time!" The President beamed.   "How long did it take you?"   "Well, the box said '3 to 5 Years' but I did it in a month!"    
     

    
</post>
<date>13,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Fever is not an illness:  It is simply a raised body temperature,and usually a sign of some form of infection.  But what should you do about it???   "Is it important to keep warm when you have a temperature?" You should not allow yourself to get too cold.  On the other hand, there is no need to pile blankets on the bed or heat the room to oven temperature.  Rest, be as comfortable as tou can, and your body will do what is needed.    "When I have temperature, I shiver one minute and sweat profusely the next.  Why is this?" In a fever, the temperature not only goes up, it swings up and down much more than usual.  As it is on its way up, people experience shivering chills, which may be so intense as to cause uncontrollable shaking attacks, called rigors.  As soon as the temperature starts to fall again, there is a lot of sweating.   
     

    
</post>
<date>13,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
       I ate a lot today……….  During recess time was a hotdog burger, after school was the irresistible TOMYAM&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;Yummmmmmm………………………………... that was extremely delicious till I can’t control my self.  While I’m eating, I sweat ceaselessly and I enjoy thrill although I’m not riding on a roller-coaster or space-shot.  Actually, I have had asked TTP to go and eat with me but luckily he denied to go&gt;&gt;&gt;If not, I think the restaurant have to confront a flood by his SWEAT………hjehehe, just kidding….. hope he won’t be annoyed.  1 hour later after the TOMYAM, I went home and devoured my lunch again&gt;&gt; this time was 'MI HUN KUIH'……………&gt;&gt;oops! My mother just said to me she had bought a ‘ba kua pau’ for me.  HEHE…… I have to feed my mouth again. 
     

    
</post>
<date>12,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
        A Blonde’s Brain At Work     A blonde, a brunette, and a redhead all work at the same office for a female boss who always goes home early.  "Hey, girls," says the brunette, "let's go home early tomorrow. She'll never know."  So the next day, they all leave right after the boss does. The brunette gets some extra gardening done, the redhead goes to a bar, and the blonde goes home to find her husband having sex with the female boss! She quietly sneaks out of the house and returns at her normal time.  "That was fun," says the brunette. "We should do it again sometime."  "No way," says the blonde. "I almost got caught."   Hahahahahahahaha……………&gt;&gt;&gt;……&gt;&gt;&gt;just kidding!!!       Today was a boring day.  Went to school but nothing to do.  By the way, today only got two teachers attended class--add maths teacher and  ??teacher.. I’m only concentrating during Add Maths period.  The ??teacher, Pn.??……..was silly today&gt;&gt;&gt; ordered people to stand up and answer her stupid questions. Not only today, previously she was already like that. I HATE HER&gt;&gt;how about you…….? 
     

    
</post>
<date>11,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yesterday was a crazy……..chat with FREN, WAVES and PANDA till 12 o’clock midnight…….then continue chatting with PANDA till 2 o’clock midnight via msn messenger…we’re totally insane!!! Because of that ‘crazy’, today I got nodded, nodded and nodded all the time&gt;&gt;&gt;not enough sleep….ahhhhhhhh—zzzh   Ah!! Lets see the poem written by Robert Louis Stevenson  &gt;&gt;&gt;dunno whether spell correct or not&gt;&gt;hjehehe……..….          THE LAND OF NOD               From breakfast on through all the day                 At home among my friends I stay,                          But every night I go abroad                       Afar into the land of Nod.                              All by myself I have to go,                        With none to tell me what to do---                               All alone beside the streams                           And up the mountain-sides of dreams.                       The strangest things are there for me,                        Both things to eat and things to see,                        And many frightening sights abroad                       Till morning in the land of Nod.               Try as I like to find the way,                   I never can get back by day,               Nor can remember plain and clear                    The curious music that I hear.    Ahhhhhhhhhhhh……………..zzzzzzhh!@#$%^*()_+still got plenty of damn bloody homeworks to do…….. 
     

    
</post>
<date>10,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
       A Horoscope For The Workplace     ASTROLOGY: tells us about you and your future simply by your birthday. The Chinese Zodiac uses the year of your birth. Demographics tell us what you like, dislike, whom you vote for, what you buy, and what you watch on TV. Well, the Corporate Zodiac goes a step further: simply by your job title, people will have you all figured out...  MARKETING: You are ambitious yet stupid. You chose a marketing degree to avoid having to study in college, concentrating instead on drinking and socializing, which is pretty much what your job responsibilities are now. Least compatible with Sales.   SALES: Laziest of all signs, often referred to as "marketing without a degree," you are also self-centered and paranoid. Unless someone calls you and begs you to take their money, you like to avoid contact with "customers" so you can "concentrate on the big picture." You seek admiration for your golf game throughout your life.   TECHNOLOGY: Unable to control anything in your personal life, you are  instead content to completely control everything that happens at your workplace. Often even YOU don't understand what you are saying, but who the hell can tell?! It is written that the geeks shall inherit the Earth.   ENGINEERING: One of only two signs that actually studied in school, it is said that ninety percent of all personal ads are placed by engineers. You can be happy with yourself: your office is typically full of all the latest "ergodynamic" gadgets. However, we all know what is really causing your "carpal tunnel"...   ACCOUNTING: The only other sign that studied in school, you are mostly immune from office politics. You are the most feared person in the organization; combined with your extreme organizational traits, the  majority of rumors concerning you say that you are completely insane.   HUMAN RESOURCES: Ironically, given your access to confidential information, you tend to be the biggest gossip within the organization. Possibly the only other person that does less work than marketing, you are unable to return any calls today because you have to get a haircut,  have lunch, and mail a letter!   MIDDLE MANAGEMENT/DEPARTMENT MANAGEMENT/"TEAM LEADS": Catty, cut-throat, yet completely spineless, you are destined to remain at your current job for the rest of your life. Unable to make a single decision you tend to measure your worth by the number of meetings you can schedule for yourself. Best suited to marry other "Middle Managers," as everyone in your social circle is a "Middle Manager."   SENIOR MANAGEMENT: Catty, cut-throat, yet completely spineless, you are destined to remain at your current job for the rest of your life. Unable to make a single decision you tend to measure your worth by the number of meetings you can schedule for yourself. Best suited to marry other "Senior Managers," as everyone in your social circle is a "Senior Manager."   CUSTOMER SERVICE: Bright, cheery, positive, you are a fifty-cent cab ride from taking your own life. As a child very few of you asked your parents for a little cubicle for your room and a headset so you could pretend to play "Customer Service." Continually passed over for promotions, your best bet is to sleep with your boss.  
     

    
</post>
<date>08,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Got nothing to do??WHO SAY&gt;&gt;still got lots of homeworks to do...   HOW do you think to the above jokes.....interesting hoh!!!!!!
     

    
</post>
<date>08,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yesterday was Sports Day but unfortunately I didn't go.  Because of this I'm smart today.  I have had slept for more than 12hours...till today, I woke up 'early'  at 8 o'clock in the morning...don't know whether it is early or not.....Today both my parents have gone to Kedah to visit my dear sister.  She has been involved in Nasional Service there.
     

    
</post>
<date>08,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
       JOKES   New Rules For Employment    SICKNESS AND RELATED LEAVE: We will no longer accept a doctor statement as proof of sickness. If you are able to go to the doctor, you are able to come to work.   SURGERY: Operations are now banned. As long as you are an employee here, you need all your organs. You should not consider removing anything. We hired you intact. To have something removed constitutes a breach of employment.   BEREAVEMENT LEAVE: This is no excuse for missing work. There is nothing you can do for dead friends, Relatives or coworkers. Every effort should be made to have non-employees attend to the arrangements. In rare cases, where employee involvement is necessary, the funeral should be scheduled in the late afternoon. We will be glad to allow you to work through your lunch hour and subsequently leave one hour early, provided your share of the work is done enough.   YOUR OWN DEATH: This will be accepted as an excuse. However, we require at least two weeks notice as it is your duty to train your own replacement.   RESTROOM USE: Entirely too much time is being spent in the restroom. In the future, we will follow the practice of going in alphabetical order. For instance, all employees whose names begin with ''''''''''''''''A'''''''''''''''' will go from 8:00 to 8:10, employees whose names begin with ''''''''''''''''B'''''''''''''''' will go from 8:10 to 8:20 and so on. If you''''''''''''''''re unable to go at your allotted time, it will be necessary to wait until the next day when your turn comes again. In extreme emergencies employees may swap their time with a coworker. Both employees'''''''''''''''' supervisors in writing must approve this exchange. In addition, there is now a strict 3-minute time limit in the stalls. At the end of three minutes, an alarm will sound, the toilet paper roll will retract, and the stall door will open.   PAYCHECK GUIDE: The following helpful guide has been prepared to help our employees better understand their paychecks:   Item Amount Gross pay $1,222.02 Income tax $244.40 Outgo tax $45.21 State tax $11.61 Interstate tax $61.10 County tax $6.11 City tax $12.22 Rural tax $4.44 Back tax $1.11 Front tax $1.16 Side tax $1.61 Up tax $1.08 Down tax $1.14 Tic-Tacs $1.98 Thumbtacks $3.93 Carpet tacks $0.98 Stadium tax $0.69 Flat tax $8.32 Surtax $2.23 Ma''''''''''''''''am tax $1.23 Corporate tax $2.60 Parking fee $5.00 F.I.C.A. $81.88 T.G.I.F. Fund $9.95 Life insurance $5.85 Health insurance $16.23 Dental insurance $4.50 Mental insurance $4.33 Disability $2.50 Ability $0.25 Liability $3.41 Coffee $6.85 Coffee Cups $66.51 Floor rental $16.85 Chair rental $0.32 Desk rental $4.32 Union dues $5.85 Union don''''''''''''''''ts $3.77 Cash advance $0.69 Cash retreats $121.35 Overtime $1.26 Undertime $54.83 Eastern time $9.00 Central time $8.00 Mountain time $7.00 Pacific time $6.00 Time Out $12.21 Oxygen $10.02 Water $16.54 Heat $51.42 Cool air $26.83 Hot air $20.00 Miscellaneous $113.29 Various $8.01 Sundry $12.09 ------- Net Take Home Pay $0.02   Thank you for your loyalty to our company. We are here to provide a positive employment experience. Therefore, all questions, comments, concerns, complaints, frustrations, irritations, aggravations, insinuations, allegations, accusations, contemplations, consternations, or input should be directed elsewhere.   Have a nice week.   The Management  
     

    
</post>
<date>07,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      07,APRIL,2004  Today &gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;same as before those teachers have had added our homework.  TTP's mood is now better than before.  I have to do my homework now and so I have no time to write much.&gt;&gt;&gt;
     

    
</post>
<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      06,APRIL,2004 Today got many homework................... Besides that, today I have already had my blood test for Hepatatis B  ABO blood group test.  I have done a stupid thing&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;I have only had my blood test after strenuous exercises..........the stupid nurse can't even take out my blood(all bubbles), may be the bubbles are carbon dioxide because of the oxidation of lactic acid in my muscle an this causes to the producing of water, energy, and of course CARBON DIOXIDE(BUBBLES).............I can't said the nurse was stupid because that is all my fault...............but she constant 'cucuk' my vein&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;that was so painful you know    !!!!  Today TTP still persisted his bad mood, look so desperate and hopeless.......................No one he wanted to talk to,.,.,.
     

    
</post>
<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>


       
      05,APRIL,2004  Today should be a happy day because it is Shan Rong Birthday, BUT  don'n know why TTP looks furious and sulky,&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;some one made up a conclusion that TTP is envy to Shan Rong, someone said he was unhappy because of the matter of A4 papers of the class magazine.  I think all this was stupid view points from someone, it may be something happen to him &gt;&gt;may be someone has had offended him .  Hope tomorrow he will be okey.........
     

    
</post>
<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Just changed my blog style!  Is it more comfortable………….. Give your comments………………!    
     

    
</post>
<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Damn bloody ASTOUNDMENT ! *~*……………….my line broke down yesterday…….but………………..However, it works today!YEAH!……….  Just registered streamyx yesterday…………….but need to wait for the bloody approvement ……………so EZ…………………………….1 week…………and not guaranteed approve ……………………………………….&gt;DBP 
     

    
</post>
<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      WAH!!!the exam is over …………feel a bit happy because now I can sleep early; not like the previous week……….have to sleep late……………….for what……….for God's sake…………. We were not very adapted to the new exam format…………………especially the exam format for BIO, FIZIK and KIMIA, this was because we only have to suffer for one paper for these subjects previously……….and now got three papers…………….think about it also want to vomit….…….got phobia already……….&gt;&gt;&gt;someone can help me to check for the scientific name of the ‘exam phobia’?? However, the torturing exam is over………..as TTP says&gt;&gt;MERDEKA Nevertheless, I just hope to enjoy my time during these holidays.  Hahaha……………………….impossible to believe… I ‘abandoned’ my KIMIA reference book out site my class…………just outside the corridor…………………………That night, I have had worried for it but because of tiredness I went fainted(sleep).  Fortunately, LMF picked it up and kept it in her locker……………………….they think that huge and heavy book is belong to Venessa……….because inside that got TTP’s notes and he recognized it………………..so LMF helped to keep it……………………………luckily I borrowed the notes from Venessa.  If not, no person knows whose book is this and they will just left it…………….then my book which cost RM24.95 will = cool over water = like the Cantonese says………………….. How careless am I…………………….  I really want to thank LMF……………….thank you very much!!!  Huh!@@###$@#!@%#^#$ That NAZRI was so stupid………………fell from the chair………..hahahaha……hehehehe!@#$$^_^     Haha……………first time taking a METROBUS to my destination  Don’t know what had happened to JJ…. when I ask him the bus fees, he says to me this is a bus and he teaches me how to spell “B.U.S” ……………really stupid! Then, there was a fubsy woman…….the bus conducter………….the bus is already overweight and still wants to take more passengers……………..and she constantly shouting—BELAKANG SIKIT&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;.BELAKANG SIKIT…………………so annoying……….then the pineapple muttered ………….’if you leave the bus then the bus can accommodate more passengers’……………..hahahaha that was really funny………….. 
     

    
</post>
<date>09,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yeah! I finished my PHYSICS scrap book already ^_^ !! but the midyear exam is around the corner, so i have to prerare for it .......................... haaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaai...................!@#$%
     

    
</post>
<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      One thing I cannot understand and felt a bit weird……………..Why must my parents always order me not to shout out my younger brother’s and sister’s name when they ask me to call them back to home from the playground…………….WHY? WHY? TELL ME WHY!!!……………………………………..Today, evening time 7.30p.m. my father asked me to call them back to have their dinner………………………….he emphasized that not to shout out their name……………………Then,  I followed………………… I shouted loudly in hokkien: “ooi! 7.30 loh ….tui  lai  zia  peng  loh.”  (Please note that I didn’t shout out their name)………………then, you know what has happened………….nothing happened…………NO response at all…………my brother and sister didn’t answer me……………eerie!@#$$%% WHO or WHAT THING… I have had summoned to come and ‘zia  peng’ ……………….it caused me to shiver a bit…………….....
     

    
</post>
<date>02,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      YEH!!!!! I have had signed up for   GMAIL  . Please send mail to   mingyuen@gmail.com  ......... Thank you very much!!!!
     

    
</post>
<date>01,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Yesterday I have had watched the debate………………..                             CHONG HWA vs. CHONG HWA ………………no need to see also know who will win the debate………………. Why those from other schools so weak, so nancy??……………… If not, I still can enjoy an intensive ‘battle’ between CHONG HWA and other schools…………………………………………………………  Then, there was a lot of ‘colour wolves’…..Aiyah!@#$$% don’t want to say that oledilah!   SHY is awe-inspiring………………………..performed so good till he received the honor of ‘The Best Debater’ in KL region……………….KUALA LUMPUR you know!!!! WALAU!! CHONG HWA BOLEH! SHY BOLEH!!!!  Then, there was a presentation of jumping rope…………quite impressive………… everyone applauded……………. 
     

    
</post>
<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Today my mother met with the “giraffe”………………And the giraffe has had a lot to talk and to say………………………………She is just showing her (*~*) face… she will used to show her (*~*) face before she utter a word……….. ...
     

    
</post>
<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Just ate my lunch (Tomyam) at Hwa Yuen Restaurant……which is very near from our school…with SHY……when we reach there…..what I saw was just no place for us to accommodate …………Fortunately, Daren Ang was there devouring his lunch……and so we joined him……………At that time, he said that he is suffering in pain because he has a gastric…………………..then………..don’t know why he had a lot to talk……………….talking those professional stuff……………….that we cannot understand……………..like talking to himself….I think he enjoyed that………………… And one thing is ……………he has had taken almost half an hour to finish his “peanut pao”………….and we have to wait for him……………….After this lunch……….I found that he is not really bad………………..his general knowledge is not suck………is good………he knows a lot especially those science stuff…………………..
     

    
</post>
<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Just watched "The Day After Tomorrow" at Selayang Capitol with my family since we can't book our tickets for cinemas in KLCC and Midvalley.........................................It is quite thrilling and interesting............No wonder those cinemas which play this movie will always get full with crowded......It is really a hot cake movie.......................people don't want to miss out their precious chance of enjoying this magnificent and fantastic motion pictures of film.....................
     

    
</post>
<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Just went for CITIBANK party or somehow is also a "DURIAN" party....it was just suite to the durian season...........THE party was held at BUKIT KIARA..........from AIR PANAS to there....we lost our way.............then my uncle decided to get help from a motorist who passed over his car....................RIDICULOUSLY ..........my uncle asked the motorist to bring him and he will just follow at his back....... My uncle said "THANK YOU VERY MUCH" before the motorist utter a word(Haven't open his mouth to talk).............................then the motorist cannot say anything and just help us.........hahaha....I can see his face turned black although he is an Indian.......we can learn from that.................."THANK YOU+VERY MUCH" is so powerful...............  After the occasion...........we left and we lost our way again.............This time, we went along the highway till we reached SUNGAI BULOH (out of the border of KUALA LUMPUR)from BUKIT KIARA..........wow!!@ fantastic....................take more than an hour to back home.....sigh!!!!!
     

    
</post>
<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Really don't understand.............this is not the first time.......................those Indonesian.....I think so...that is not natural disaster...It is man-made disaster.........       look!!! what a thick haze...... just from forest fire in INDONESIA   (I emphasized that this is not the first time)  A number of island nations in the eastern Indian Ocean were shrouded in thick haze produced by a large number of fires burning in Malaysia and Indonesia. Hundreds more fires were being set even as the thick cloud of smoke already severely reduced visibility across the region. Officials warned that the level of pollution was getting dangerously high and unhealthy. The fires are being set primarily by plantation owners, taking advantage of the current dry season, to clear forested lands and to burn away the surface peat in swamp areas.  
     

    
</post>
<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      CONGRATULATE ME!! guess what?????? .....my STREAMYX service...........hahaha..................a nightmare............ after waiting for almost a month.............the result is.is .............is what.........is NOTHING...............there is no Streamyx service in my area.............ah
     

    
</post>
<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Flying canons(volleyballs) can be seen easily in my school if you are lucky....then you will be the victim and you will eventually die in pieces........hehehe AND....thare are some police cadets and bomba cadets on duty barricading various entrance but I found that they are just doing silly things and obeying stupid orders ...because I still can pass over by using  another entrance and just wasting for extras 10 to 20 steps only........................really stupid.... the atmosphere is just like living in a war........or some way some how....like "DARURAT" (emergency).............. BUT for me ........there is just one thing for me to worry........just don't know when I will be the LUCKY stars......hahaha
     

    
</post>
<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Got desires to watch movies ???............just go    ......Tanjung Golden Village   at KLCC...
     

    
</post>
<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I started to doubt……….who are my true ...... and real friends ........Previously, I am not very concern about this matter and I just make everyone as my best friend………..but suddenly I have the feelings……………..a weird feelings…….makes me to start thinking………………………..Although I am not very happy these few days(not because of my exam results—so far so good...but of course got a little defect and flaw….but I will try my best to do better in my trial and SPM),  I will not show out my sulky face……..because I really hate that……what is so dejecting……………..the wonderful world is still there……….
     

    
</post>
<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Huh!!!!!………SITI NURHALIZA….huh!!that stupid PN.LILY said she is like her-SITI NURHALIZA…………don’t know why she was so……….YUCKY!@#…………… And she was not teaching what she should teach…………………On the other hand, she is fond of condemning people, especially to the Chinese…maybe this is her only hobby……..I feel nothing but contempt for condemning people ALL THE TIME……In addition, she is a Moral teacher..........don't know how to say......... 
     

    
</post>
<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Really thanks to MIN FUAH.....once again..I have had abandoned my SEJARAH text book in the classroom............fortunately..MIN FUAH is there...she kept it for me .............this was the second time and don't know why she was always the one who...kept the books for me
     

    
</post>
<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Recently, we heard news like ..........."(JOHOR) A clerk being robbed by a stupid robber.  He has had pulled the victim's handbag in such a coarse way till she knocked her head then ...........she died"..........If i am not mistaken, she was enjoying her shopping trip in a shopping complex at that moment...........wow.........shopping also can encounter with the 'door' of LIFE and DEATH...........then not far away in future time ..summons may be given to those who didn't wear a helmet once they leave their house..........hahaha
     

    
</post>
<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Urghh…....I really felt dejected………………but LIFE is always wonderful and life is full of mercy…..so I am still aliving ..haven’t dead……………………
     

    
</post>
<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The weather in Malaysia is damn bloody hot…DBH………every time when I wake up from my siesta …….I may have to suffer for headache………..I have had tried so hard not to fall asleep in the damn hot afternoon….but what to do …….the extreme warm weather act as the sleeping pill and it brings me to slumberland……………
     

    
</post>
<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I am dying………….the environment in my house is totally noisy, boisterous and hectic….it is full of tense…………………my parents often quarrel because of trivial matters……..I also don’t know why??? Maybe they enjoy that………..Maybe it is quite fun to them………….but some times it causes disturbance for me……………. But I am already adapted to that …………………………………….  Two days more …………..ya……………..exactly two days more ……………the boring holidays will over…………………..just in a blink of an eye……………………… We will be back to the school life…………………………have to wake up early……………….AND have to confront the…………the…………….the… day after examination………………..the results will come out soon……………….hope for all the best…………………………… 
     

    
</post>
<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Urghh.............what a dreadful day........my brother had a fever...and my mother suffering for gastric........she vomitted and spitted out colourless liquid.....Guess What??oh........nothing so forbidding.........just some hidrochloric acid.........but don't worry...... all is fine now.... 
     

    
</post>
<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Finally............eventually....ultimately...my eldest sister came back from the torturing 'Kick-mud-Negara'.......but I think she won't feel that..............because she was a bit reluctant of coming back...... Nothing was changed physically.............mum said she was much darker than before but after I saw her ..I think not!! Really....not yet become a brunette........ Hehehe!!!
     

    
</post>
<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Just watched ‘Harry Potter and The Prisoner of Azkaban’………………in KLCC.By right, I will be more pleasure if I enjoy this trip with my friends or with my parents……… This trip is sponsored by Citibank and we have the coupon to redeem TGV popcorn and Coca-cola….my dear uncle decided to bring my younger brother and sister to enjoy these benefits………………………………………and………..I have to go to take good care of my brother and sister………………………………………… However, maybe someone else can ask me to join their trip to watch “The Day After Tomorrow”…………………………….or I hope fervently that my parents can watch this movie with me…………..  Lets say the Harry Potter…………………….there is nothing so interesting …is a bit of comedy and I think the fighting between weird creatures caught my full concentration………….Guess what ???the professor of Hogward School can transform to an awful creature.  Harry’s Godfather (Sirius Black), also a fugitive from Azkaban but he is innocent………………………………………………can transform to a ……..don’t know how to say….err ……a Dog…called Grim?????/forgot already whether is a dog or is a wolf….the shape is there lah………. 
     

    
</post>
<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Wah!!!This time I have had changed the soup and also its ingredients.
     

    
</post>
<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ahh...............my eldest sister(ming hwa) who engaged with the PLKN....Nasional Service or as Dr.Liew said "Kick-mud-Negara" will come back soon from KEDAH............just wait for another 2 days....................
     

    
</post>
<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Go and find out what "eunuch" means!!!
     

    
</post>
<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Just came through a vivid dream...............SHY becomes bald,he is as bald as a coot and he is wearing a toupee.........................Don't know how he crept into my dream!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!11111!!!!!! It is realy a nightmare!!
     

    
</post>
<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      If you want to lead a nancy bookworm to become neglect from his/her study or make him/her go mischief........................You may ask him/her to chuck his/her books to the trash because............study=fail.........If he do not believe you, you may prove it to him/her......:  Study = No Fail ---equation 1 No study = Fail ---equation 2   everyone agreed this  ------------------------------ Then,  Study + No Study = No Fail + Fail Study  (1 + No)  = Fail  (No + 1)  Study = Fail              (PROVED)   HAHAHA! Felt a bit guity of doing this stupid stuff!! ^_^ 
     

    
</post>
<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Let's play  this  !!!
     

    
</post>
<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I THINK YOU(Giraffe) DESERVE A POKE INTO YOUR EYE&gt;&gt;&gt;That is what I learnt from Pn.Shanti……………The Giraffe is damn stupid, wonder how she graduated from University…………………Really doubtful! She doesn’t know how to draw the solenoid correctly……………. When I ask her about the electric motor………….She answered me nothing????  Lets see the below conversation:    Bug: CIKGU!! Saya tak faham ini oh! Giraffe: Mana! TENGOK! Bug: NEH! Ini loh……..(showing the book to her) Giraffe:…………..(Can’t even utter a word…Just like her mouth clogged by s**t) Giraffe: Neh !! INI INI LOH!(with her hand pointing the statements in the book but          without direction)  Bug: Saya pun tahu ini ini loh tetapi macam mana ia berfungsi? Giraffe: Errrrrrr….(squeezing her bloody brain to give mandate to her mouth to say something) ini pun saya belum masuk….…Kenapa cepat sangat??(pretending with her face stiffed *~* ) Bug: Tak apa lah!!! (Monologue: BODOHQUEEN !@#$%^*()_+)  OMG! How come there is a teacher like that in the world.....?  
     

    
</post>
<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Thinking why I am so unlogic while doing exercise of the PROBABILITY chapter for Add Maths!!!  The consequence was................... I knocked my head on the toilet door in my tuition center.  I learnt to think more logically..............
     

    
</post>
<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Just came back from a visit to IMR(Institute Medical Research) and FRIM(???) organized by the Mathematics Society.   Firstly, we went to IMR and we saw a lot of plants for the use of medical purpose or herbs as well.  When we reach the herbs garden……………..the first thing we have done was searching for Kacek Fatimah and Tongkat Ali.  Of course, we have had asked for the ways to consume it………..For Tongkat Ali, we just have to boil its root in water and drink it.  The attendant emphasized that one cannot simply consume its powder due to human’s kidney cannot filter those tiny substances.  Then, before we left the garden the attendant gave Miss Phoon an Madam Chan three pieces of  ‘Sambung Nyawa’ for its use of lower the blood pressure and ease migraine.  Miss Phoon and Madam Chan seems to be very curious to those herbs as I saw them discussing and talking about how their grandmother use herbs to ease the illness all along the way…………And they said they wants to get it planted at home for their parent’s sake.  Since the plant is so good at lower the blood pressure…………..we devoured it without washing it……………….THIS WAS MY FIRST TIME TO EAT LEAF……………Impossible to imagine.   At the museum, we have saw well-preserved rats, squirrel, birds, cats, baby tiger, and snakes….There are various types of snakes with weird names………I can remember a one, it is ‘Ular Kucing Bergigi Anjing’……..really cannot imagine why those people is so creative as they created this name for this type of snakes………….. After this, we went for jungle tracking at FRIM.  We can see Miss Phoon’s bag can accommodate lots of things although it is small…………..just like Doraemon’s magic bag.  We saw a lot of giant trees such as Cengal(the hardest tree), Meranti, Kapur,..……..Besides giant trees we saw giant ants……………the guide has had played with the approximately 3 centimeters long giant worker ants………………Think of why was he acted so brave………..this was because that is just a worker ant and not a soldier ant……….If so, then he will sure die in pieces………  We have had climbed up to 1000 feets of height …………..Almost dead………TTP and I have to beware of stepping into “shits”(mud) along the route.  We also saw the IKAN NAGA with its broad-wide mouth……almost 15+ centimeters wide…………….and its long is approximately three of the length of our school desk………………………….We bought a long piece of bread to feed the IKAN NAGA………………….All of us have done it but only TTP.  He has had fed himself with the ‘ROTI’(please keep your hair up TTP).  Along the journey…………..I really cannot stand of the attitude of DS. 
     

    
</post>
<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I went to school today! Wah! what is so surprising!!! STU... BUT......  most of our teachers did not attend class................. Just like doing nothing.................................BUG!  
     

    
</post>
<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Almost get bombarded by Ambika today……..U know?? 4 periods!!……….It was totally a torturing lesson…………………What a senseless woman…….she finished a chapter plus pages of ‘The pearl’ by using 4 periods……….(please note that there is only a chapter++)………………………………she asked me to act as the fubsy doctor and Jesus as the main character of ‘The Pearl’--- Kino……………Then, I started to wonder…..she hoped us to act exactly (I think is just 50% from exact) like the story…………but why she chose Jesus……….he is not as man as Kino…and why she chose me to act as the FUBSY doctor………………Then, her only 50% is vanished ………………..because I’m only 1% of the fatty doctor………hahaha!!! And my voice box is not covered by lipids…………so I can’t groan like a sow.(in Chinese is MU CHU). Miss Lee also came in to our class………..to substitute the “Giraffe” ‘s class…….She had a lot to talk………………….CEASELESS…………………….very noisy…………just wanna choke her……………CYS is the most innocent during that moment…………… After school, I went to 7eleven to buy Chunky Kit-Kats. The guy at the counter is mad….just like his grandmother gives birth……he talks a lot to me.  Well, I’m not very patient to listen to all his bullshits …..just wanna leave quickly because W12 is coming soon.  Next time when I see him in the shop, I will not step in…………..if not he got a lot to talk to………….  BUG BUG BUG BUG BUG!!! Just wanna shout like a bug…….OH! BUGGIN’ YOU!!! 
     

    
</post>
<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       BUGGIN' YOU!  Pitch your speaker to maximum volume!!!   
     

    
</post>
<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      YEEEEEEE!!! How the hell to put those smelly papayas into my delicate mouth........I hate those smells especially while the papayas has been in the tupperware for hours..............Those papayas is soft and emit smells ...put it into my mouth is just like eating shits..........I always try to evade but what to do, my father used to force me to eat......................Really cannot imagine the stench from those rotten papayas in a container.  HF said she has had done before this experiment when she was in primary school..........I think she screamed loudly like a squirrel at that moment while she smells the bad stench...... I REALLY HATE PAPAYAS!!!!  
     

    
</post>
<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Wwah!! Now blogger compose also can upload your file!! But how to use ???What is "Upload Path"?????? 
     

    
</post>
<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Tomorrow I have to visit my sister at UTP.................don't know how is she going on there!!   
     

    
</post>
<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I did a stupid thing today…………..It rained heavily from the time approximately 1.30 p.m. to *.**p.m…………and we (HF,MF,SHY)  have our BM tuition at 1.45p.m. at TY’s house…………………Feel like lucky because both HF got their own umbrella (MRMY do not have a one)…so that HF share an umbrella and MRMY share a one………..Along the journey to TY’s house, SHY is the one who holds the umbrella……….just like the umbrella is for his own.  He left only a few inches for me to refuge…………..Although I know I’m not big-size but how CRUEL is he………And also there is a lot of lower paces(holes) that filled with the rain water……and I just step into it………..not saying that I’m senseless but it is because I’m busying fighting for my right to have the half side of the little umbrella……. One funny thing is…….if you are one who walks beside HF……you can hear screaming sound (AAAAAA!!!) comes out from her voice box.  Once a lorry or a motorcycle or a car as well cross through……….keep screaming AAA! AAA! AAA!   Hahahaha When I reached TY’s house I’m totally wet……….when I turn back my shoes….I saw water dripping out……………it was the same while I squeeze my stocking…………HF screamed frequently while NAZRI talking some *** stuff…….LIKE squirrel………..  ONE thing weird is FSJ kept his stocking in his pocket….with the reason--- It will make the stocking to dry……………..TRY to think……is it logic….. 
     

    
</post>
<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      HAI......the monthly test is over........ But don't know why .....I think i love monthly test..........after this just like nothing that i can do except sleeping.....although the SPM is coming in 3 month+ soon..... What an evil feeling............maybe there is something wrong with me...where got person like me that loves exam....... Actually i must be very happy because no need to burn the midnight oil .....temporary.......because after this monthly test..we will just have to wait for the TRIAL only..and the duration to wait is almost a month+....then next is SPM..... 
     

    
</post>
<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Finally, she decided to go.......go and try!!! HUH!!!
     

    
</post>
<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      WEIRD WEIRD WEIRD !!! Don't know why I am having this feelings........ I found that my house is a bit of noisy ...not a good place for me to study in peace....this may due to the conflict arose within my parents and my eldest sister.....she just got her scholarship to pursue for chemical engineering but...she is reluctant to go...and also hatred to go....I can see this from her emotion and temper......she said she wants to continue her FORM 6 and she said she prefer bio compare to others....she wants her career to be relevant to BIO stuff.....but my parents disagreed that.....then sometime there are some intense quarrel......
     

    
</post>
<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      ...There are too "much"(means uncountable) homework to do........and the monthly test is coming soon..........dying......
     

    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Something serious occured!!  Someone breaks the law.....  co-operate with syndicate and help them to wash out counterfeit RM50..........I think this was detected while the boss of our canteen cannot bank in some of the RM50.... because it is an imitate one...then ....authorities planned to trap the stupid sinner or silly student as well....but   I think only lah  
     

    
</post>
<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Today is my first day to enter the crowd…………….To enter the distinguish KASTURI tuition center.  Well, every thing is just nice but just a little bit problems dealing with the enrolment procedures.  I hate the little fubsy MALAY woman who sat like a bitch or somehow like a sow at the registering counter.  Want to die then go !!!  After P.Hong class, I went home by taking a LRT ride.  Damn, people were as much as mountains.  When the door of the LRT cubicle open, people who wants to leave pushing those who wants to enter the cubicle.  Luckily, I have had hold something. If not, they will push me out.  At that moment, no one is going to tolerate with you!!   
     

    
</post>
<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I really bewildered by something…….I have known something…….something that is bad ………something that I do not know how to say…..or you want to say , it was totally lewd………..The one I adore, but he has done something which the whole of my family cannot imagine………………………..I knew this after my parent told me…. Really, ……..and I have had to pretend as I don’t know everything…………..still have to show my happy face to him, still have to take his car to school………………..He has done something , something that is extremely cheap………makes dirty my house …………….. But I wonder why I still have to pretend………..to give my respect to him……… Damn! My bloody lewd uncle......He deserves a poke!@! 
     

    
</post>
<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      TTP sprained his neck yesterday and he came with his tilted head today.  He said that he sprained his neck muscles while he is watching Sammi Cheng’s funny movies…… What a pity.     WANNA SUE SAMMI CHENG .. AHAHAHA   
     

    
</post>
</Blog>