<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>07,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Haiz... Its been a long time since i last posted.. We have been too busy with that History Drama competition coming up next saturday... rehearsals almost every day! in addition to all that work... I've been coming home @ like 7, 8 pm everyday this week..   Wednesday was nationals... Everyone was supposed to go (for VS!! compulsory) However, on that day, the teacher last minute told us that she wanted to have rehearsals that day, and had also got approval from the relevant ppl already... so we had rehearsals until 2 pm. (we started at 1 pm) After that, erm the 4 of us, isaac, lester, desmond and i planned to go there (we could still make it!!) But that ***** of a jonathan wanted me to accompany him and jeremy to bugis to take a look at the costumes with mrs ng... yah.. screw him... i couldnt go lor...   took mrs ng's car.. maroon toyota corolla. still very new. jona was making lots of noise with jeremy at the back.. playing with little square piggy pillows. ng forced me to sit in front.  -----------------------------------------------------------   regarding the rehearsals, i think we have made quite good progress already!!! especially movement and placement.. hope we win again! its on homeground...  -----------------------------------------------------------   had dental appointment today.. such a waste of time, wasted 2 hours waiting. the person before me had an extraction, and another had gum disease,o_0 so it took an awful long time. :(   mrs jay wasnt here today, she broke her back yesterday and cant walk. poor woman! so mr lai took over 2/5 of her periods. the other 3/5 was spent doing el work she asked a teacher to give us...  -----------------------------------------------------------   next week will be our last and final rounds of full dress rehearsals... X-Country next wednesday too. hmm what else... yah nicole's bright idea is to organise a kindergarten class reunion. what crap is that? i dont think there is anything is it? mark's birthday is next monday (2/8)... 
    
    
</post>
<date>07,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
        RHD today... so boring.. The PRC teachers came to observe our math lesson. We had very early recess. (9 a.m) then followed by 1 period of history. (until 1010)       Then it was followed by stupid kolam designing. You know those Indian decoration thingies that you see on the floor... &gt;_</post></Blog>