<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>27,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      smells like teen spirit. such a great song.
     
    
</post>
<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      sorry, sira nanaman ang freindster. ayaw magsend ng message. im sorry, now at least you know the events on april 24. ewan ko ba. baliw ako sa iyo. and frankly speaking, i dont even know where i stand. iyon lang ang gusto kong malaman. im just so lost in you and... and.. nawala na sa isip ko yung paulitulit na sinasabi ko sa sarili ko kanina. basta. im in love with you. and i just dont know.. wla na.. ewan ko.. in love ako sa iyo. period. and i dont  know what to do. and.. it just sucks to be this way. that i might never get to know you. naalala mo ba nung nag videoke tayo kay paolo. i felt you were someone i could really spend my life with. someone who is real and, true, and happy, and great and beautiful and, and, and then reality hit me, na hindi mo ako gusto, pero ewan ko, i just want to hear it from you, ayokong sa iba nangagaling. sorry. pero i need to. and want to know where i stand. kung ano ako sa iyo. sabihin mo, dont be polite, just tell it to me, blunt, frank. ano ako sayo?
     
    
</post>
<date>24,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
       I want to dedicate this song to you, "thet". you will be loved. you are loved. by me. and you are missed. i miss you, a lot. come to think of it, i never really got to know you.   She will be loved  Beauty queen of only eighteen She had some trouble with herself He was always there to help her She always belonged to someone else  I drove for miles and miles And wound up at your door I've had you so many times but somehow I want more  I don't mind spending everyday Out on your corner in the pouring rain Look for the girl with the broken smile Ask her if she wants to stay awhile And she will be loved And she will be loved  Tap on my window, knock on my door I want to make you feel beautiful I know I tend to get so insecure It doesn't matter anymore  It's not always rainbows and butterflies It's compromise that moves us along My heart is full and my door's always open You can come anytime you want  I don't mind spending everyday Out on your corner in the pouring rain, oh Look for the girl with the broken smile Ask her if she wants to stay awhile And she will be loved And she will be loved And she will be loved  And she will be loved  I know where you hide Alone in your car Know all of the things that make you who you are I know that goodbye means nothing at all Comes back and begs me to catch her every time she falls  Tap on my window, knock on my door I want to make you feel beautiful  I don't mind spending every day Out on your corner in the pouring rain Look for the girl with the broken smile Ask her if she wants to stay awhile And she will be loved And she will be loved And she will be loved And she will be loved  Please don't try so hard to say goodbye Please don't try so hard to say goodbye  I don't mind spending everyday Out on your corner in the pouring rain  Please don't try to hard to say goodbye     
     
    
</post>
<date>24,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
       i am still in love with her. god, why is it hard to stop lovingsomeone that you've loved for thepast three years. i loved her before i even knew i did. 
     
    
</post>
<date>24,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      id always imagine myself with her. that we'd slow dance to "balisong" by rivermaya.  she's just so perfect.. so perfect.
     
    
</post>
<date>24,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Patay  Ilang beses na akong humiling sa Diyos na gumawa siya ng paraan na patayin ako. Ayokong mag-suicide, masyadong maraming nagsusuicide ngayon, masyadong common. Gusto ko iba naman.  Okay lang sa akin ang mamatay, wala naming mawawala sa akin, wala naman akong mahalagang gamit, wala rin namn sigurong purpose ang buhay ko, kung mayroon man, sigurado akong isa itong purpose na kahit sino ayang ganapin.   Naawa lang nga ako sa mga iiwan ko, mapupuyat sila, magagastos.  Medyo gusto ko pa ngang mamatay eh, at least malalaman ko kung may diyos nga talaga, kung may satanas, impyerno, langit at purgatoryo, kung wala naman ang lahat ng iyon, walang diyos, walang satanas, walang afterlife, okay rin. Sana naman, at least, may reincarnation, or buddha or allah or something else. Ayoko lang talagamng paniwalaan na pagkamatay ng isang tao’y tapos na ang lahat.  Madalas kong iniisip kung  ano kaya ang pakiramdam ng patay, yung katulad pa rin ba ng dati? O pag sakalign walang diyos, empty lang ang mararamdaman mo, tapos wala na.  Hindi ko pa alam, hindi pa kasi ako namamatay. Pero kung sakaling mamatay nga talaga ako, nasisiguro ko na hindi sa langit ang bagsak ko. 
     
    
</post>
<date>24,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
        The Lost Soul    urlLink   What sign of the Black Zodiac are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     
    
</post>
<date>24,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
               urlLink   what will your band be?        name:         age:         sex:         do you lke cats?     yes  no  yes, with ketchup  i'm more of a dog person  i hate cats!!  i feel indifferent        you'll call your band:      newxwavexbattlecore        you will sound like:      pedro the lion        lyrics:      the steering wheel, rusted under her tears, became her sun              This   QuickKwiz   by  urlLink  cowboysbecamefolkheros   - Taken 569 Times.         
</post>
<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
              urlLink   what will your band be?        name:         age:         sex:         do you lke cats?     yes  no  yes, with ketchup  i'm more of a dog person  i hate cats!!  i feel indifferent        you'll call your band:      newxwavexbattlecore        you will sound like:      pedro the lion        lyrics:      the steering wheel, rusted under her tears, became her sun              This   QuickKwiz   by  urlLink  cowboysbecamefolkheros   - Taken 569 Times.         
</post>
<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
       nobody made me feel this way before. shes all i ever wanted and more. 
     
    
</post>
<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
       in love with her. she makes me feel like no other person can. she brings me light when no other candle will. she gives me reason to live when there is totally none. im in love with you maria theresa mendiola. and though i may be too drunk, or STUPID to realize what im doing this very instant, know that what i feel for you is true. those four white flowers, they dont mean anything. at all. i prepared this long speech, about you, and love, and things like it, and who your are to me, but you took all the words away. i learned something, it's better to have loved and lost, than never to have loved AT ALL. im in love with you, the whole world and everyone else in it comes second to that. goodnight. 
     
    
</post>
<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      may scroll down button po ag blog ko, just in case you couldn't see them.
     
    
</post>
<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      !@#@#$#@$^$%%*^()  dsad:SAD"SA&gt;</post></Blog>