<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink        Darling, she said, and slipped away.                  He’s been repeating it all morning.             “Darling, she said, and slipped away.”                 He says, and stares at his lukewarm coffee spinning slowly with the microwave plate.    They seem like nice, gentle words and he’d been proud of them all morning, since they came gurgling out in the shower, origin unknown.             Spoken hastily again as he stocked the cigarettes, and again breaking down the cartons and marking the log, and again as he counts change for a customer —              —“excuse me?”     “Sorry, nothing.”       “Did you say something?”     “Nothing.    This heat… make me crazy…”     “Whatever.”              She slipped away.                  They all do.    There’s a second’s contact.    Kind words, a fleeting brush of hands as bills are exchanged, a direct stare, a look away…    Nobody has ever called him “Darling.”    That’s something expensive women said, women from old movies and shows who were so bold and fancy they didn’t know that men were supposed to say it to them.    Women like that came into the store some Saturdays, and tended to smoke Virginia Slims, or 100s, or any stylishly slender cigarette that accentuated their stylishly slender fingers.    They liked mint Lifesavers above all other mints and usually would buy Diet Pepsi instead of Diet Coke, unlike their younger, less fancy counterparts.    He tries to imagine how an entire type of woman all knew to buy the same things.             “Demographics.”    He says, not knowing exactly what it means or why he’d spoken it aloud.    He remembers his coffee, but it’s gone warm again.    Another minute.              Slipped away.                  Almost five already, and already Wednesday, and already July, and only fifty for two more months.    After fifty, nobody cares.    Until you turn sixty, he tells himself, but can’t think of anyone who specifically cares about his being fifty, so he imagines a graceful woman turning slowly and letting her fingers slide from his with the moon reflected off the lake water onto her pale face as she slips away and out of his life.             “This coffee is the most depressing thing I’ve ever tasted in my life,” he explains to a young woman as he takes her bills.    “That’s why I look upset.    I’m not upset.    Just bad coffee.”    She rearranges the bills so all the heads of the presidents face the same way before putting the money in her wallet.    The word “exasperated” whispers across his lips along to the jingle of the door as she slips away.    Outside, the wind whips at her long skirt and he can see the outline of her legs through the fabric.    Hair reels as she turns furiously into the wind and stomps past the front window, headed uptown.               “All that energy’s got to go somewhere,” he tells himself, “I’ll bet she’d make a fantastic lover.”             Nearly five, and time to empty the trash before the rush hour rush.    When he steps outside, the world seems electric and ready to pour.    For a half a moment he stares uptown, bags in each hand, imagination wild, wondering whether to stomp north like the rest of them, but, like always, turns his gaze to the curb and lets the plastic ends of the trash bags slide from his fingers.              Darling, she said, and slipped away                     
</post>
<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
         There’s a mouse under the couch and he won’t leave.  He—she thinks it’s a he—just sits there, always on the opposite end, always as far from her as possible while she watches TV.    If she stands, he vanishes.    If she switches sides, he follows suit.    He’s quite persistent.   For the first eight months, she never even noticed, and would have persevered in her ignorance, if not for an impulsively purchased entertainment center with doors covered in convex mirror tiles.    It was a silly thing to buy, too big for the space and far too Scandinavian-looking amongst her other, more sophisticated, passed-down pieces.    The bright red sides clashed with the soft fern of her walls, and the mirrors, positioned below couch level, reflected the mouse’s distorted silhouette in no fewer than thirty-two separate frames.    He blinked, or she imagined he blinked, and she pierced his extremely sensitive eardrums with her shriek.       The following several weeks she nicknamed “the hunted,” referring both to her unwanted guest and herself, for she felt perhaps even more threatened by this brazen rodent than he felt by her.    First came the “humane” traps, the ones with a chemical bait and a trapdoor, the ones that people buy when they’ve never encountered a mouse before and still retain illusions of this battle ending with a cheerful mammal being released into a field of dandelions, the human victoriously smiling, looking back fondly upon the wacky times the two of them once shared.  After about a week, she wanted his neck snapped.     She wanted to hear its nails scraping at the hardwood floors, aching to pull his disgusting body from a glue trap.    She wanted to hear gurgling, or the swift crack of a trap, the splatter of rodent blood...    She lined the moulding around the apartment with poison and duct tape.    He still showed up as soon as she flipped on the TV.    He didn’t miss even one day.       She sometimes pretended to be eating and casually dropped little poison pellets on the floor next to her, hoping he would think it was food and finally die.    She started to think he might be too smart for her, like maybe he’d escaped from army research, or was specially bred by a former scientist tenant who passed away one lonely night and nobody bothered to do anything about his only pet.    She actually dreamt these visions, and pondered over them, and tried to invent scenarios that outdid the previous ones, and she decided the mouse seemed to favour the news over the Fresh Prince of Bel Air, and the Simpsons over nearly anything.   It became clear that the mouse did have discerning taste.    It would always leave during game shows, or pornography, and in her darkest days she left the Game Show network on all night, and sometimes through the day in hopes of driving the mouse away to another single girl’s studio.    Occasionally, she’d be lucky enough to find a trashy movie on cable to relive the hours upon hours of Family Feud and, on those nights, she’d relish every bared breast with the fervour of a fourteen year old boy.       He always returned.    Not like the other men in her life, she joked periodically, then tended to get a little choked up for about an hour, especially if they seemed to be playing more Maybeline and Special K commercials than usual.    He didn’t run from her sobs, she noted, he always sat still, making his tiny nibbling noises and touching his front paw to his mouth in gentle contemplation of her woes.       “No secrets between us,” she took to saying, even when she wasn’t depressed, and even on those rare occasions of exuberance, like when she caught herself gushing for well over twenty minutes about the subtle way that law student touched her hand when he passed her his number, and what that must mean about him and his gentle nature.    She’d named the mouse Tiny Tim by this point, ever since they’d watched the Christmas Carol together, and told Tiny Tim about all the different ways she’d been imagining that student’s gentle hands.    She peered under the couch at him, looking at him directly instead of in the mirror.    He’d been watching her, not Friends, and seemed much keener on verbal pornography than the video variety.           “We are not friends, Tiny Tim.”    She whispered, “I don’t tell my friends things like that.    I’ve never talked like that in my life, but we’re not friends.    I don’t want you to get the wrong idea.”    She had tears in her eyes and walked out of the apartment in a hurry.    She didn’t come back for several hours, but Tiny Tim was fine because she’d left the TV on PBS for him.     About a week later the law student came home with her.    “Why’s the Game Show Network on?”    She’d been hoping tonight would be the night.    “You don’t like it?    I’ll put on something else,” and she opted for Goldfinger, hoping Sean Connery’s sleazy charm was enough to repel Tiny Tim.    It wasn’t.    He pushed up that loose piece of flooring she’d never discovered and crept out to find exactly thirty-two convex visions of a gigantic man smothering his only friend.    She started moaning, and he grunting, as clothing seemed to fall from everywhere until the two of them were naked and he wasn’t being gentle like she said he would, he was holding her down, arching his back, and slamming against her with grunt after grunt and the rising swell of the Bond soundtrack until a stern and crisp “snap” from under the couch broke their revelry and she shoved him off her and looked and screamed and screamed until the law student had wrapped her in a blanket and taken out the garbage.   “There had only been one left.”    She told him.    “I’d cleared them all away months ago, but forgot that one.    I didn’t see it behind there.    I didn’t know.”   He went home and didn’t return her calls.  
     

    
</post>
<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Skin crawling hands shaking staring down a stack of sheets of names and addresses from Oklahoma City freaking out.  Revulsion at having to type another name.  Sickness at staring at paramedic’s sloppy scrawl and at a simple fact.  This is his life now.  This is every day with no end.  This is where that Bachelor’s degree settles, tapping plastic keys faster and faster until five   when he wishes to turn back into a real person…   with money in his pocket and…   and an itching thirst for something that tastes like real life.  It isn’t there.    Embers.  Ashes and fragments of leases and agreements and business confidences and attendance lists flutter around in his cage of a skull, scraps of names and phone numbers and to-do items, afloat.  Around.  They have a semi-automatic mailing machine  hum-smacking  half-time daily.  Red ink spots palms and at the fingernails, but mountain-climbing, both literal and metaphorical, are all the imagination can muster.   Hum-smack!   The gears are turning.  Red hands hover.   Hum-smack.    What have I butchered?   There’s no corpse.   The only corpse is me.   Struggling around his breezy life.  Comfort food and spas, chocolate and TV, and all sorts of dollar bills—never quite enough but all sorts that flutter away and  what’s so hard about that, you ass?   He asks himself.  He leaves the hall light on and tries to let Beethoven lull him to sleep. 
     

    
</post>
</Blog>