<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The webmaster of Critiquester is in the process of studying for six finals. Look for future updates after June 4.
     

    
</post>
<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The writings posted on this website are not to be copied or used without permission from the owner of this website. Failure to comply with this rule will result in grave penalties for the perpetrator. On a somewhat lighter note, please feel free to make use of the comments button and post any thoughts/suggestions/dislikes of the posted essays.
     

    
</post>
<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       The Legal Strategies of Sir Thomas More and Thomas Cromwell  	In Robert Bolt’s Man for All Seasons Sir Thomas More, the seemingly incorruptible chancellor of England, must clear himself of charges brought against him by King Henry VIII via Master Secretary Thomas Cromwell.  Heading the prosecution is  Cromwell himself, who in the author’s words, “can cradle gross crimes in the name of effective action” (xxiv).  In the play, More seeks to clear himself of the charges of treason without going outside the law or verbally harassing the prosecution.  Cromwell’s plan, on the other hand, it to try to force More to admit he is guilty by denying him freedom, manipulating his family, bribing servants close to More to give damaging evidence, and even instructing a witness to commit perjury.  Essentially, More provides a logical, honest, and controlled defense, whereas Cromwell uses every dishonest and disrespectable method necessary to prove More guilty. 	Sir Thomas More is respected throughout England for his honesty and good record in public office. Even King Henry VIII confirms this claim.  He admits, while fighting with More over his proposed divorce from Queen Catherine, that “you [More] are honest.  What’s more to the purpose, you’re known to be honest” (31).  More doesn’t accept bribes from criminals because he knows the potential consequences of being discovered.  For a man of his position, More’s good behavior is rare, and as Norfolk exclaims: “What! Goddammit, he was the only judge since Cato who didn’t accept Bribes!  When was there last a chancellor whose possessions after three years in office totaled one hundred pounds and a gold chain” (58).  More, even after relieved of his high ranking government position, refuses to accept any donations because he is wary that they may be interpreted as a bribes: “The [church payments] would appear as payment” (64).   More’s honesty makes his testimony more believable in the trial. 	 Sir Thomas More “likes to keep his affairs regular” (67).  While questioned by Cromwell before the trial, More repeatedly makes statements that can be backed up by documents.  In cases where the event could not be written down, More claims that he can verify his statements based on reports from witnesses.  In a number of instances, sources familiar to the case remark that More has been careful in documenting his life.  Even Cromwell, who prosecutes More, mentions that “[He] has been cautious” (67).  Because More can corroborate every one of his statements with written and human evidence, he presents a firmer case than the prosecutor.  In contrast, Cromwell in an abusive manner: “He did accept it, we can corroborate that.  You can go. Go!” (58)  Before dismissing her rudely, Cromwell clicks his finger at her as if she is a servant and tells her to “be quiet” rudely (58).  There is no evidence that More ever mistreated a witness.  Not only does More present a stronger case with corroborated evidence, but the manner in which he collects the facts is polite and easily verifiable.   	Another cornerstone in More’s defense is the method by which he presents his opinion on King Henry’s divorce.  More never gives Cromwell tangible evidence to prove that he committed treason.  More’s message is silence: he never agrees to sign the treaty and he never confides his views in writing or to a witness.  Additionally, More does not use silence to intimidate others, unlike Cromwell. According to More: “You may suppose I have objections.  All you know is that I will not swear to it [the treaty]”(76).  According to a part of a maxim in a law forbidding treason, More’s “silence gives consent” (88).  More’s method of defense is respectful too: “I insult no one” (76).  Cromwell blatantly attacks More, proclaiming that “no King of England has ever had nor could have so villainous a servant nor so traitorous a subject as yourself” (68).  More seeks to offend no one in his tactful defense, whereas Cromwell’s goal is to intimidate More and the trial‘s jurors. 	Cromwell knows from his preliminary interviews with More that More has created a strong case in his defense.  Norfolk thinks that Cromwell's prosecution is a "a horse that won't run" (59).  Cromwell confides to Richard that the evidence they have is not good enough: "Sir Thomas is going to be a slippery fish, Richard, we need a net with a finer mesh" (60).  He goes on to say that they'll need to "weave [a thinner net] for him" (60).  Cromwell is inferring that they must either "find the right law or ... make one" (60).  Clearly, Cromwell tells Richard that they must do whatever it takes to win a verdict on the king's behalf: legal or not.   	Cromwell does not mind playing dirty in his prosecution of More.  He pays off More’s stewards to spy on him, as Rich confides to More.  The prosecutor, Cromwell, even hires peasants to trail More when he lives his residence.  Cromwell brings to the stand Richard Rich, who in his testimony commits perjury.  More makes Rich’s perjury known to the court: “I am sorrier for your perjury than my peril” (90).  An honest prosecutor would not bring to the stand a perjurer, but Cromwell’s methods are not honest or commendable. 	Cromwell confides to Rich that “[More] must submit.  There’s no other good solution!” (79).  When Cromwell gets his chance to force More to give in, he does everything in his ability to make him miserable.  Cromwell instructs the guard to remove More’s books because the “king is becoming impatient” (79).  Removing the books is the first in a series of blows Cromwell deals to him to force submission.  When that ploy fails, Cromwell unleashes his ultimate weapon: More’s family.  Cromwell sends the family to More’s prison cell in a last ditch attempt to try to convince him to give into the decree.  As if that was not enough, Cromwell briefly considers using the rack, an instrument of torture, to force More into acquiescing.  Cromwell’s cruel method of prosecution knows almost no bounds. 	No matter how good a defense More prepares, nor the way  in which he argues, can have save him from his own stubbornness and the king’s desire to have a guilty verdict.  More defends himself honorably, basing his innocence on his good record and evidence of his loyalty to the king.  He does not personally attack anyone or use illegal methods to gather evidence.  There are no bounds to Cromwell’s viciousness , whether it by verbally attacking More, depriving him of rights, or presenting evidence illegally. Although Cromwell ultimately wins the case, More prevails because he does not result to using Cromwell’s dishonest methods to prove his innocence. Work Cited Bolt, Robert. A Man for All Seasons. New York: Scholastic Book Services, 1960. 
     

    
</post>
<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      An essay on  Robert Bolt's A Man for All Seasons  will be posted soon.
     

    
</post>
<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       O akland International Airport will be the hub of Mongoose Airlines. Located conveniently near Oakland, San Jose, San Francisco, and the Silicon Valley, Oakland International provides an efficient gateway to other places. Oakland International Airport has a small-airport feel with large airport services. Mongoose Air plans to operate 32 flights daily out of Oakland.  urlLink      Overview of Oakland International Airport- the future home of Mongoose Airlines  (pending FAA approval) Picture courtesy of photographer Airnikon   urlLink    
     
    
</post>
<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       T  o access the official Mongoose Air survey, please visit:   urlLink Mongoose Airlines Passenger Survey     
     
    
</post>
<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       T ime seems to have gotten away from the founder of Mongoose Air. Fresh back from two weeks in invigorating California, Mongoose Airrelaunches with a new focus. To kick off a new era in our history, Mongoose Air is proud to present the Passenger Survey. Please feel free to browse through and answer the questions. This is your chance to tell us your likes/dislikes of airline travel. Never before has an airline been conceived purely on the basis of passenger opinion! Mongoose Air will end this long, unfortunate streak! Cheers.        
     
    
</post>
</Blog>