<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Part A  On the most fundamental level, we might say that structure is the commingling of space/time and organization.  I assume that it is a commingling in the sense that structure is space/time’s “description” of organization—or rather; it is organization’s manifestation of itself through space/time.  It is organization “through” space/time.      Now without wading though the mire of the “why” question yet, let me simply point out that humans are, if nothing else, organized beings.  Further, we are beings that express this organization in a variety of ways, most fundamentally through language, but I am getting ahead of myself.    Since humans are organized, and since they exist in space/time, all expression of this organization must (if our definitions are on mark) come in different forms of structure.    It seems best to speak of this endeavor of “expressing” in the terms of “building” or “constructing” so that when we say that humans are, at the very least, organized beings, we are also saying that humans are, at the very least, beings that build, beings that construct—building and constructing “structure.”  

						
</post>
<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Part B.  There are different kinds of structures which humans construct.  The statement that they are different seems to need no apology—for is it not readily apparent that social structures (such as families), are of a different kind than the physical structures of skyscrapers? (I am not, of course, intending the two to be unrelated, just different.)    I also do not think an apology must be made for the statement: not all structures are constructed equal.  I would begin to describe this distinction like this: first, it is readily seen that “conceptual” or “non-material” structures are primary and physical structures are secondary.  We might put it in the terms of parent-child; for example, skyscrapers can be seen as the child of social structures: they are “born” out of a vast complex of actors constructing a steel structure by “birthing” their normative structures “into” the physical world.  The building will bear all the marks of its parent-structure or structures—every aspect has been “planned” (constructed) for a “reason” (out of a complex of, in this case—most directly—social norms).    We might label this relationship as a “source”-based relationship—a skyscraper’s structural form can be traced to a “source” social structure(s)—an endeavor far to complicated and esoteric for me to attempt now.  Suffice it to say that I  have correctly set out good reasons for saying that humans are (structure) constructing beings and that unseen structures can be seen as primary to physical structures.    

						
</post>
<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Ok, so I’ve tried making my new home somewhat interesting—an endeavor that turned out to be quite frustrating.  Why, for example, is it impossible to get a simple .jpeg off google images and onto my blog’s photograph space?  Every time I try, the program tells me that I have entered illegal characters.  Illegal characters?!  I’ll show you an illegal character! Anyway, I suppose these are little nuisances that must be endured by those of us who poses no tech knowledge whatsoever.    Oh, and why is the word “blog” not added into the official blog spell checker?!    I know, now would be a good time for me to grow up.      

						
</post>
<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Without too much solo pomp and circumstancing, I must say that I do feel quite powerful to be writing my first official "blog."  Yes, I know that there are quite literally millions of other blogs being written today--thousands at this very moment; but there is still that strange rush of endorphins that seems the eternal bedfellow of publication, no matter how utterly insignificant that publication may be.   Here's to 20th Century fronteerism!  Let us take the ones zeroes by storm!     

						
</post>
</Blog>