<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      holy fucking shit! Dorney Park was Siiiick. I love everyone who i was with. Timmy is the funniest person to ride roller coasters with. Besides Emily whom i love because shes so fucking cool. Ryan S cause he is my best buddy even though he only rode the ferris wheel. dana cause she is sooo funnnny. Klink because he has awesome nipples. Jon cause he is the safari king. jacki clark cause she strikes good bargains. jason cause he tripped balls with me on the Skyscraper. eliza who looks like nala from the lion king. hope i didnt forget anyone. hard to remember caues i was having so much fucking fun.  im typing this right now cause i have no voice whatsoever from screaming my face off on Laser. my god. my balls are still residing in my mouth from the Dominator.  jason is a fun person to ride rides with. the ride back was interesting. lol. womens bus was interesting lol. :: Time Out:: a Red BMW just pulled in my driveway and my dad bought it!!!! wtf thats awesome!! ::time in:: amazingly big thanks too my favorite emily beyer for driving me and ryan around and for just being so awesome! ryans my best bud and best man. lol em aug 3rd ill be home for you. i love everyone!!!!!
     
    
</post>
<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      o man. its the last day of crew. couldnt be happier or saddier.  Love those people with all my sweat. can you say skatahh?  off to there right now in fact. to go sweat my balls off and get tortured one more time. some last words (ian anderson) Really don't mind if you sit this one out.  My words but a whisper -- your deafness a SHOUT. I may make you feel but I can't make you think. Your sperm's in the gutter -- your love's in the sink. So you ride yourselves over the fields and you make all your animal deals and your wise men don't know how it feels to be thick as a brick. And the sand-castle virtues are all swept away in the tidal destruction the moral melee. The elastic retreat rings the close of play as the last wave uncovers the newfangled way. But your new shoes are worn at the heels and your suntan does rapidly peel and your wise men don't know how it feels to be thick as a brick.  And the love that I feel is so far away: I'm a bad dream that I just had today -- and you shake your head and say it's a shame.  Spin me back down the years and the days of my youth. Draw the lace and black curtains and shut out the whole truth. Spin me down the long ages: let them sing the song.  See there!  A son is born -- and we pronounce him fit to fight. There are black-heads on his shoulders, and he pees himself in the night. We'll make a man of him put him to trade teach him to play Monopoly and to sing in the rain.  The Poet and the painter casting shadows on the water -- as the sun plays on the infantry returning from the sea. The do-er and the thinker: no allowance for the other -- as the failing light illuminates the mercenary's creed. The home fire burning: the kettle almost boiling -- but the master of the house is far away. The horses stamping -- their warm breath clouding in the sharp and frosty morning of the day. And the poet lifts his pen while the soldier sheaths his sword.  And the youngest of the family is moving with authority. Building castles by the sea, he dares the tardy tide to wash them all aside.  The cattle quietly grazing at the grass down by the river where the swelling mountain water moves onward to the sea: the builder of the castles renews the age-old purpose and contemplates the milking girl whose offer is his need. The young men of the household have all gone into service and are not to be expected for a year. The innocent young master -- thoughts moving ever faster -- has formed the plan to change the man he seems. And the poet sheaths his pen while the soldier lifts his sword.  And the oldest of the family is moving with authority. Coming from across the sea, he challenges the son who puts him to the run.  What do you do when the old man's gone -- do you want to be him?  And your real self sings the song. Do you want to free him? No one to help you get up steam -- and the whirlpool turns you `way off-beam.
     
    
</post>
<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      dear school,        leave me alone.  how could i be failing math. uggg. thats all i can say. uggggg
     
    
</post>
<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      可以说,这已经是一个被讲烂了的话题.在Blog的世界里,blog的即时性(instant)与独特性(unique)就决定了超过2天的, 超过5个引用的话题那就已经是陈词滥调.更何况这个被上千个blog引用的话题.而我还是要写下一堆废话.  我首先想要谈的是:服务(Service)与软件(Software). MovableType(以下简称MT)是SixApart(以下简称SA)针对个人用户开发的weblog出版软件,而TypePad(以下简称TP)是SixApart针对网络用户提供的weblog服务.这样的定位是相当明确的,MT的流行和逐步成熟直接促就了TP的推出和商业运营.做为一个成功的软件,MT确实做到了最大限度的为用户服务,3年来一直为用户提供免费使用,不断更新的版本,强大的功能,丰富的插件,这些都是MT成功的要素.做为MT的用户应该是深有感触的.  可是MT做得太强大了,这可能也是Mena和ben始料不及的事情,一套MT系统基本上实现CMS的大部分功能,再配合上各种各样的插件之后其威力更甚.基本上,只要有足够强的服务器,一套MT系统完全可以建立起一个强大的Blog服务站点.随着Blog的兴起,越来越多的网络用户开始接触 Blog,运用blog,以MT为系统平台提供weblog服务的网站也越来越多.而且许多个人blog也开始通过MT为朋友架设Weblog.例如我自己就为4位好友在个人网页上架设了Blog, Weciti更是给每一位邀请作者单独开设了blog,这些在MT中实现起来相当方便.也正是简单,快捷,易用的特点使得MT成为最流行的个人出版系统. 作为一套强大的Weblog出版工具,其威力已经完全超越了这个范畴.
     
    
</post>
<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i also dont like this whole school thing.  as of right now im liking crew though. and my sister. she got an effin 1420 on her SATs. fucking crazy. i hope i make it into 10th grade. lol. tonight is the big night. the chorus concert. woopee. ahh so much drama in the choir. this whole who should get the solo thinger. i dont have a prefference personally but ive only heard rachel sing it and i bet that jordan would sing it awesome too. she has a ballsier voice which would sound real good .  hmm whatever. for the record, me and chris sullivan are making a siiick band which will be really really good. he writes the best lyrics ever.  we are gunna be nutttttzzz. this is not taking the panacea's place though. they are still my main priority. i dunno if i have a link on here or not but here.  www.panaceaonline.cjb.net thats the stuff. oo i gotta call mr wilbur. he wants me and ryan to give a show at OCC for his adult guitar class. weds. yeah. come see the panacea (minus jimmy) on june 4th at the school. its gunna be me ryan and jared acoustic. no chance of my amp fucking up which is good. and hopefully emily beyer will add her beautiful voice to the mix on Older Chests. should be a fun night. The Revival too. organized by Joey Vaughn. come on up. peace goin to greenwood lake.
     
    
</post>
<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      fuckin picture doesnt work . doesnt matter. it wasnt me anyway. the dude was hot though. lol
     
    
</post>
<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       98 degrees and rising. a day in which every article of clothing you are wearing sticks to you lick a bug ti fly paper. yeah to quote my really cool sister "Today in school it was so hot that my entire body melted and slid onto the floor and stuck there in this big, gummy mess." shes cool. crew. ugg what can i say.  rowing is beautiful. and it is an amazing thing just to be out on a lake (even greenwood lake) and feel the power of your body becoming one with the water.  but... being on the team sucks. it runs my effing life. i can never do anything cause i have crew. and dr hoverman can be a dick. today he yelled at me for diving off the bridge and said "thats unpermissable!" it was fucking hot out. what an uptight bastard doctor.  but its all good. im happy cause i just remembered the name of the the string orchestra in Waking Life and i burnt their cd. well its really the waking life soundtrack. buts its so goood. i feel like i should be sipping coffe in a cafe in france and sharing my snotty outlook on life with my dog in a sweater.  but thats just me 
     
    
</post>
<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       man... im so sick of school its not even funny. theres only like 4 weeks left or something? w/e its 4 months toooo long. and 3 more years will be unbearable. Im so glad that i have good friends or else there would be no reason to go.  except music class. I love too sing. I dont even really mind old heller woman. she bugs me but at least we sound good.  I skipped engilsh the other day to go to chorus and 3 teachers who have no connection to mr lewis asked me where i was. thats creepy. but w/e. meisters is a fun class. i love those people more than anything. some less than others but nothing serious. man o man am i gunna miss those seniors. there will never be another class like them. yeah and i always forget that jon is a junior so i wont be losing him. actually not many people are leaving. hmm. but w/e. god i say whatever alot. sheesh dont read this.  id delete it but thats to much work. shit speaking of work im late. 
     
    
</post>
<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       intravenously polite it was the walkie-talkies that knocked the pins down 
     
    
</post>
<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yeah that pic isnt me. i dont know the guy. but my pics wouldnt work so i found this cool dude. i wish i looked like him but no. hes a hottie lol  yeah of course im never really going to write in this thing so its worthless for me to spend all this time starting it. but whatever. if u read it u will be greatly diapointed.  hmm  i wish i could write poetry or something cause otherwise these are just going to suck. well im tired from crew right now (cause it runs my life argg) so mebe the next one will be funner* funnerer* more fun ahhh. peace
     
    
</post>
<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Hair flying in the breeze, the boy clung to the last cars ladder. Insired by the music of the night, he let out a gleeful yell. His sounds mingled with the constant rattling of the train tracks, and the gentle, melodic humm of his guitar strings in the breeze. Wind and branches whistling past his face, he looked down at the quickly disapearing ground making way for new earth, every second closer to home than the next.  An sad old man sits in his car waisting precious life waiting for this train. A smile breaks across his nostalgic face as the last car and its human barnacle sing by, waving.   Suddenly the world feels all right.  
     
    
</post>
<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       hmm... maybe one day ill find a real picture of me. 
     
    
</post>
<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      when will the insanity end!  school is just getting more intense as im getting relaxed. no funn. no funn at all. but its crazy hot out. sometimes. the other days its craazy cold. Hmmm. no wonder no one ever posts comments, cause im so damn boring. i just talk about nothing. arg. w/e. Here. Ryan Starks and i are playing an acoustic show at the tuscan cafe on July 2nd at 7 30. Were hoping that ms Emily Beyer will come and perform with us too, cause she makes us sound 10,000,000 times better.(and adds some class too lol) but hopefully jared will hit a couple songs with us and maybe the Jiminator. ol jimmy boyce is pretty pissed i think, cause we always play acoustic shows without him. i dunno, i love the jim but i dont think bass is what you need in acoustic songs.  i wasnt even a fan off the bass part mike G added to our damien rice stuff. but w/e. thats my personal opinion though. i really hope that ryan doesnt want to dump jimmy and use mike, cause jimmy knows our stuff, wrote aloit of the stuff, is really good, and started the effin band. If ryan says anything im gunna give him a peice of my mind. lol but its all cool. i dont think there will be a problem. Whew, im sweatin in here. i wanna go swimming? think my fish ponds deep enough...
     
    
</post>
</Blog>