<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Due to the site being so lag, I decided to move back to blogdrive.com  http://darranonline.blogdrive.com   
    
    
</post>
<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Here are the latest pictures from Maria Sharapova's latest tournament; " WTT 2004 " About her not getting into the Olympics in Athens, I feel its a huge waste of talent, she just beat Venus Williams at the Wimbledon Open and I am sure that proved her ability to compete against the very best.      Maria last night played her first tournament since Wimbledon, a WTT exhibition. The final score was that Maria's team the Newport Beach Breakers beat the Sacramento Capitals 23-16. Maria played 3 matches and won 2 and lost 1. In singles Maria lost 3-5 to Nicole Vaidisova. In doubles Maria teamed up with Nana Miyagi and they beat Anastassia Rodionova and Nicole Vaidisova 5-3 and in mixed doubles Maria teamed up with Ellis Ferreria and they beat Mark Knowles and Rodionova 5-4          Played Football and Badminton today. During my break, we played with some guys who were playing on the field. We won 3-2, I scored 2 goals and Kang Heong scored a goal. A great goal, I might add, dribbled past 1 guy, and got a shot past the keeper at the near post. I scored 2 curling goals from far, and not to forget I hit the shot into the bar once, which denied my hattrick, oh well, time to work much harder. As for the second football session, it was nice, casual playing and relaxing too. Then on to badminton, not much free courts to play on, I guess it was quite a busy day due to it being the last day of the week and everyone wanted to relax. I realised my smashing is getting better and better, hopefully I can reach my best in time to come, but its sure good to play once again.   That's all for now! Will write more tomorrow.       
    
    
</post>
<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        School was pretty normal today, played badminton with staik and at that time, I injured my left ankle again. I don't know why but that part of my leg is increasingly getting weaker, I can't seem to stand balanced on that foot alone. And what's worst, another sprain occurred when the old 1 suffered a week ago hasn't fully recovered. Oh well, I hope to be recover as quickly as possible.   I met Sumitha later on and we watched </post></Blog>