<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A Masters Graduate, with 1 year of work experience in an Industrial Automation and control field. Ability to grasp complex concepts, analyze and implement processes to improve productivity. A team player with strong organizational and communication skills gained through work experience and training.  OBJECTIVE Aspiring for a full time position in a competitive work environment to fulfill professional ambitions and contribute in achieving organizational goals.  ACADEMICS ·	Master of Science Degree in Electrical Engineering  (Expected 2004)       University of Texas, Arlington, USA.						    ·	Bachelor of Engineering Degree in Electrical Engineering   Birla Vishwakarma Mahavidayalaya, Sardar Patel University, India.	  TECHNICAL SKILLS ·	Operating System: DOS, Windows 9x/2000/XP/NT, UNIX, LINUX. ·	Programming Languages: INTEL 8085  8086, C, C++, Fortran, Basic. ·	Application Packages: MS Word, MS Excel, MS Access, MS PowerPoint, Rxlogix (Allen Bradley) MASM, EPS (PLC IP3416), MATLAB, PSPICE, ModelSim, Xilinx and MATHCAD, Circuit Maker, Compiler Design Programming. ·	Automation: Programmable Logic Controller (PLC), Design of digital and continuous control systems, Simulation of high level computer programs and analysis, Computer-based measurement systems, sensor design, signal conditioning, data acquisition, smart sensors, and mechatronics. Techniques for measuring quantities encountered in robotics and automation, manufacturing, biomedical, and other applications. ·	Networking: OSI layer model, TCP/IP, RIP, X.25, PPP, HDLC, ATM, Router Configuration, Queuing Theory, Ethernet, WAN, SNMP, SMTP, VPN, FTP, Telnet.   WORK EXPERIENCE      Graduate Engineer Trainee in the R  D Department, Yash Engineers LTD. Bangalore, India  ·	Review the existing design, suggest modifications, implement the approved modifications in pollution control devices and also the Maintenance  Calibration of it.(Including cases for functionality, integrity, definition of test methodologies and test strategy).    ·	Evaluated test equipment and designed test networks; helped in the development of automated test suites.       Summer Intern at Shree Kamdhenu Electronics Pvt Ltd., Anand, India  ·	Involved in development of Software application for the Dairy Industry, the application automated the process of Milk Collection System and helped in electronically measuring weight of commodities. This product was sold to various top Milk co-operative sectors; involved programming and debugging in C/C++ ·	Designed the website for the company: - http://www.akashganga.co.in     Summer Intern at Shree Electronics, Anand, India ·	Designed a Micro-controller based Electronic weighing machine, to be used as a part of Automatic Milk Collection System     Lab Assistant, Office of Information Technology, University of Texas at Arlington  ·	Managed and supervised one of the finest and latest computer labs in North Texas. ·	Developed skills like Customer Service, Troubleshooting and Problem solving.    PROJECT EXPERIENCE ·	Automation of Thermovac Systems in Instrumentation and Measurements  This project was sponsored by IISRO (Indian Institute of Space Research Organization). Perform the automation of thermo vacuum system using Crompton Greaves PLC  to display the chamber temperature, pressure readings on computer by a software program in Visual Basic and serial data transmission. ·	Project on Cool Mist Roof Cooling System in PLC in Industrial automation    A Programmable Logic Controller (PLC) is used as the Decision-Making Unit. It Senses the Roof Temperature and Compares it with the Desired Limit. If the Roof Temperature of a Particular Zone Exceeds the Desired Value (User Definable: 85 - 95oF), the Water Valve for that Zone Will be Turned On to Spray the Cool Mist on the Roof For 10 Seconds. It also displays Current Roof Temperature of Each Zone Sequentially on the PLC Front Panel. ·	Project on Elevator control System in PLC in Industrial Automation  A programmable Logic Controller (PLC) is used to design an elevator control system for a four-story building. Optical sensors are used to detect the arrival of different floor levels. As a part of the project, I have to develop RLL diagram, Relay circuit and serial data communication between the model and the circuit. ·	Implementation of Transfer Function in Advance Control Systems  The objective of the project is to realize the given transfer function (actual simulation of a existing system), analyze the stability of the presented system, determined steady state error and steady state value by final value theorem. ·	Temperature Meter in Instrumentation and Measurements  The Temperature Meter was designed using BC547 as a temperature sensor and 3-½ Digit LCD display. ·	Paper on Digital Micro Mirror Device (DMD) ™ in Micro Electro Mechanical System  This paper presents detailed information on Digital Micro mirror Device™ (DMD) technology, a heart of the Digital Light Processing Technology (DLP) ™ that is used for high-end projection display systems with superior image quality.       COURSE WORK    PLC in Industrial Automation Advance Control Systems Instruments and Measurements Linear Control System  Micro Electro Mechanical Systems Digital Signal Processing Microprocessors                                                      VHDL     Network Systems I  II SCADA in Industry Computer Networks              C Programming     MEMBERSHIPS ·	Student Member, Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers (IEEE), 2003. ·	Student Member, Instruments and Measurement Organization, 2004.     
     

    
</post>
</Blog>