<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So yesterday was fun and such and I went to James's house right after school and he taught Steph and (somewhat me) the guitar. Me being the impatient one didn't quite listen so I just randomly played. Then we went to Claytons and had fun there and ate and oddly we all ordered the same thing...The waitress was great cause she put up with Chris's antics and we had fun. We walked Steph home and then found a shopping cart and tried to lewer CJ away from Emo ball. We failed so we went to video land and rented  "Better Off Dead"  and that was fun and Chris and James meet my grandparents and saw my little brother amuse them and my room which is cool I guess and Steph came and was scared by Chris and James. That was fun. Today my mom says "your shoes are too small" so we bought some Converse at the exchange that are navy blue and are cool and I also got some cool shirts that my dad owned when he was young and they look like something Gordo would wear so there cool. I'm going to wear them on Tuesday :). This is my life....Cool. 
      
</post>
<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Spanish project due and my hair is cut and i got an extra day cause i said it didnt work but it did  :)  http://www.xanga.com/home.aspx?user=Executive_IMP  look at it on my xanga
      
</post>
<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Spanish project due tomorrow and all needed is editing and woo hoo its pritty much boaring but ok. All ours is is a birthday at a resturant and a commercial of Albertsons. Unlike Collins which is a super good awsome gun fight matrix pariody movie thats cool ours is simple and...simple. All the editing realy needs is a slide show tibit of Albertsons stuff. I really want to see the finishing product on Collins though :)  On another note yester day was my moms birthday and also (drum roll please) my half birthday!!! That means i can get my permit (Technically) and i just realized that when Ryan Jones said "Dont you know you can get your permit now?" and then i write. The first thing that comes to mind is "Road Rage" woo hoo. At our neighbors house we went to eat and for my moms B-Day and we started a conversation about road rage and the whole time i was listening i thought of "Road Rage Brad". I heard stories of Mr. Couture and his road rage and then the conversation stoped due to the stupidity of Kenny (8th grade friend) who climed well tried to over a turned over coucn on its end and it fell and he almost hit tons of Priceless pottery and Mr Couture said "Geise Kenny, why dont you just take a bat and hit the pottery!" It was great! Then we all realized that it was 10:30 so we left.  Im writing a story of Link and his adventures just for fun and its pretty good so far even though its one paage long...its good  adios....i think
      
</post>
<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well "inner bitch" was Hilary and she was talking to me on the phone well now I'm typing with the monitor off monitor off and short term memory are bad together and this post may seem weird (not wyrd like fate ) and lala in world history with Worthington and she has no clue and Hilary says she is sorry to all and I forgive Jon and I tell him not to do that again and listen to my advice sometimes and don't kill the people who help you cause they will kill back and spam :) Ryan Jones who is sitting next to me is sleeping while I'm on this computer typing and did I mention Hillary is sorry reading Hilary is sorry a lot and is or was sad and ya you catch my drift.....6 minutes left so bye for now ill fix it later if you care.....
      
</post>
<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      my grandparents are here and moo im stuck
      
</post>
<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      9.27022% - Geekish Tendencies  Spring fair fun and my toe bandage is gone!!!!  =)
      
</post>
<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
             Which Neglected Mario Character Are You?     http://www.smbhq.com/nc/nctest.html  Toad is like in every game woot woot 
      
</post>
<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      readminification succeeded.
      
</post>
<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Jon is being a blog tyrant and I don't want him as an admin cause WELL HE ASKS ME IF HE CAN BE ONE AFTER ONE COMMENT AND COLLIN ON THE OTHER HAND HAS COMMENTED ON EVERYTHING SO HE IS ONE AND NO JON YOU DIDN'T ASK WELL ENOUGH AND DON'T YOU KNOW THAT COLLIN CAN DO THAT AND YOUR TO BUSY TO DO THAT CAUSE YOUR CAUGHT UP IN YOUR COSTUME THING AND FOR THE PEOPLE WHO ARE LISTENING AND NOT REALLY SURE WHAT'S GOING ON WELL JON IS RIGHT BEHIND ME AND DURING THIS WHOLE WRITING I ACCIDENTALLY PRESSED CAPS LOCK AND IM TO LAZY TO TYPE AGAIN. Ha um so no hard feelings Jon but one helper is enough and if you commented more than just that once then you would have had a fighting chance and such so.....School is dumb. Hunger pains.  Bye.
      
</post>
<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Collin is in the administrator status cause he's smart with this stuff and is the only one who's smart with this stuff who's posted.  If there are any complaints well.....TO BAD!!!  and folks...lookward to the near future in video games for   Metroid Prime 2 Echos   Nintendo DS   The Legend Of Zelda Minish Cap  and  The Legend Of Zelda  unknown name  
      
</post>
<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      my sphere of influence grows daily
      
</post>
<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This is the future and collin already put this up but its so awesome that I'm putting it up.  http://games.slashdot.org/games/04/05/11/217221.shtml?tid=127=186=207=213  I also realized wait Imp there's a spell check!!! My bad spelling days are done on posts and not on comments so.....Moo.  http://www.nintendo.com/gamemini?gameid=54610f14-1826-4d46-9981-8f72874aee2e=1
      
</post>
<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      hahahahahaha steph and the worm was fun and on tape and phils uhh wrong turn slap and smack of head to ground was great and fun and everyone at Rep/Java night was Great.
      
</post>
<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      lalalalalalalala school is mean
      
</post>
<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well I was thinking about using this so I am now and I put the pick of link and I made a different one but it wont go on so and I made my IM thing as:   I_Have_No_IM_Cause_It_Makes_My_Computer_Mad  and the blog so screwed it self up so I took it off. For those of you who don't know that really isn't my IM and it really is RynImp but as I said it makes my computer mad well it does. Add some comments on how to make links if anyone who knows how knows how who views this por favor.(for those who are Spanish stupid out there POR FAVOR means PLEASE)
      
</post>
<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I did this cause you need one to post to others so yah don't count on any updates</post></Blog>