<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hello friends, acquaintances and people who I met when drunk and have no idea what you look like,  I thought it was about time for another group email, since my promise to reply to everyone emails individually… well, let's not go there shall we… Then I discovered this 'blog' thing. I'll hopefully be adding to it every now and again so keep your eyes peeled.  Hope you're all doing well wherever you are in the world. I'm on a high at the moment, because the last 6 months have been good to me!  It all started back in December with the birth of Hana, still as gorgeous as ever at 5 and a half months. See below for photos.  Fast forward to early March when I found out that I got the job I replied for as a Technical Writer for an I.T. company called Daitec in Fukuoka City. I landed the interview by complete random. I emailed a friend for general advice about getting a job in Japan, and it just so happened his company was looking for another foreigner to help with translations etc. The interview was only meant to be a practice for the real thing and I didn't prepare much, but the Jenkins charm (read: bribe) must've worked on them, because I got it :)  Then came the big wedding ceremony on April 10th. In case your wondering, we have actually been married since last August, but we finally got round to having the ceremony last month. 160 people came to watch Chiharu and yours truly get married, god bless 'em. Had a fantastic day. Was so nervous that I couldn't eat any of the 257 course meal, but they put it in a doggy bag for when we finally got back to the hotel room. Needless to say, didn't get much sleep that night ;-) For pics of the wedding and after party, click  urlLink here .   Then by far the most significant moment in any young man's life happened on April the 18th… I won a football tournament!! …or in other words FGU (Fukuoka Gaikokujin (Foreigners) United) won the All-Japan ALT Football Tournament - Western Division!! For details of our glorious victory check out  urlLink Brucey's website . I wrote "We went, we saw, we conquered!"   Which brings us up to the present day. In terms of future plans (if you haven't fallen asleep yet!), I'll be coming home in August with Chiharu and Hana in tow:), but only for a month:(. On Aug 21st we'll be having a little wedding party in sunny Aberystwyth. Those of you who will be in the area at that time are welcome to come along. Just send me your home addresses and I'll send you an invitation. The sooner the better please dudes.  We'll be heading back to Japan in early September to start my new job. We'll still be living in Omuta until about April or May next year so that Chiharu can go back to work at the same hospital in November and work until she gets her summer bonus (a great system in Japan were most workers get about 2000 pounds or more!). This will mean a one-hour commute for me every morning and evening until we can move into the big city. What happens after that is anyone's guess. I don't see this as a job-for-life, so I'll be keeping my eyes open for bigger and better things.  That's all for now. Feel free to add comments, but keep them clean because my mum will be reading this!  Gareth  WELSH: Iawn pawb, sori am yr holl Saesneg yma ond dwi heb siarad Cymraeg ers i fi ddod adre tro diwetha, a ma arnai ofn fy mod i'n dechre anghofio fo! Gobeithio fod pawb a phopeth yn iawn efo chi. Gadwch fi wbod am y parti yn yr haf. Edrych ymlaen at weld chi i gyd cyn bo hir. Jenks / GPH I Llyr a Taf: wnewch i ofyn i Dyl, Ewan ar lads am y parti ar y 21fed. Mae angen cyfeiriadau er mwyn anfon y wahoddiadau. Diolch.  こんにちは、皆さん。 ガレスです。お元気でしょうか？ 以上は英語ばっかりでごめんね。勉強になると思ってね ;-) 私はご存知の通り、もう結婚しました。とても幸せです。花ちゃんは１２月１日に産まれ、元気な５ヶ月の赤ちゃんになりました。この間、初めて寝返りして、今から、さらに大変になるらしい。やべ～！ ４月１０日にやっと結婚式をあげました。写真は上のリンクをクリックしてね。 現在の仕事は７月いっぱいまでです。８月は千晴と花ちゃんを連れてイギリスに帰ります。８月２１日に実家のアベリスイスで第３結婚式をあげる予定です。もし８月にイギリスにいるんだったら、住所を教えていただくと招待状を送らせていただきます。よろしく！ 9月からは博多にあるダイテックというIT会社で仕事が開始します。がんばります！ では、また会える日に楽しみにしています。いつでも連絡してね！ ガレス
     

    
</post>
</Blog>