<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      coptright 2002 John JJ Martin  ...I remember telling my mum when I was eighteen that I was gay and she came at me with total anger and hatred. She said to me after a week of talking about it that she would accept my “choice” but would never respect it. She said afterward that she didn’t want me to tell anyone in the family of my leanings because it would hurt her to know that other people knew about her gay son. I can’t really understand why she thinks this way. It’s odd. She grew up as a member of the baby boomer generation with all the sex drugs and rock&amp;amp;roll but when it came about that her son was a puff, she can’t seem to budge. I guess she’ll have to miss out on my life since she also said that she would never want to see any boyfriends of mine (providing I have them of course) around her. We never spoke about me being gay since. It’s truly an elephant in the living room kind of thing.  ...I do remember one time my father taking me out to a field near our house and flying a kite. A dragonhead printed on translucent plastic molded with a wire in the shape of a circle. The tail was at the very least 20 feet long. In fact I know this is true because I still have the kite in my closet in the original bag it came with. Rainbowed and frayed now, I remember seeing it fly high in the sky in that field with Dad. It’s old and ripped the bag. The kite isn’t in nice shape either, but I can bring myself to get rid of it. When I was England for the first time my Aunt Mary got it for me for my birthday. I had just turned eight. And I loved it. It’s one of the few things I have left from when I was young that brings my nerves to the surface of my skin and warms me to the point that I can cry at the drop of a hat. 
     
    
</post>
<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      copyright 2004 John JJ Martin  I’m feeling good It’s not often that it happens But I’m feeling good.  On days like this I sit Waiting to fee; something more Then, I think What kills me? Noting happens. I think of what you don’t have Me After the year of lacking Me You’ll never see me again If I can help it  I won’t be able to help myself From rejecting You  What you missed from me I will give to someone else If i can  What i missed from you Nothing I will be bitter forever Good  You’ll get in You’ll show your devotion to molding me By never letting me be  One day you will see me If you haven’t already My hand will be cupped with another And you’ll look away  We’ll be local And you’ll remember  I will be looking away And you’ll watch  You will cut his hand And it’ll end  I will know you are there Because you know I’m a hawk Watching everything Noting everything  Basking in what you don’t know I will lock eyes and you will know That you were done Two years ago  You will always know i was looking And laughing But today i feel good. 
     
    
</post>
<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      copyright 2003 John JJ Martin  Heavenly Being, give us the strength to not over compensate with food and drink after having to cut things off with the right guy. With our strength and faith in you dear being, we ask that you bestow this privilege.  Godly Being, be not harsh with our souls when dealing with the loss of that right guy and put our asking minds to rest when we see and speak to them later  Holy Figure, dash away the guilt left behind from the bad choices that we make as gay men. Make us forever sorry for killing the hearts of the sweet ones, and let us mean it.  *To this we pray, dear god save me*  Oh Gay Lord, save us from running into them (the nice ones), when at coffee shops and diners. Please let them not be with better looking guys and be cooing over them.  *To this we pray*  But Gay Father, if we’re wrong, and the right guy turns out to a stalker, and starts showing up at our work, pissed off because we cut it off, please divert their direction into the way of a new love, never to be seen by us again. Keep us safe from phone calls and e-mails, bad run-in’s and awkward conversation when we’re trying to make eye contact with the cute guy in the chair across the cafe.  However, Gay Daddy, since we’re wrong about everything, forgive us of our misleading and hideous thoughts about our fellow gay man, we know not what we think.  But God, please, above all, help us see the error of our ways. Help us love ourselves before we try to love others. Let us see the good qualities in others and hope them for ourselves. Lets us go onward with effort to see the future of our people as one of solid communal peace. Let us be with each other as we will be with you, at one. But allow Mondays and Wednesdays to be lived with kind reflections, and good hair.  Amen 
     
    
</post>
<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      copyright 2003 John JJ Martin  He’s cute, really cute. But I don’t want to be the fool in the end asking some guy out. I don’t want to date a dead beat that doesn’t want to go further now. I don’t want someone like me.  He’s cute, really cute, but do I really want to go for that? Someone that is just looks and no talk, he’s not a big talker and doesn’t know how to converse. I’d be out of my head after one day.  He’s cute, too cute, and I don’t think I’m his match. There are too many people going to be looking at him and making me jealous, it’s not worth it. Guys like him tend to take off.  He’s cute, damn cute, and I think I’ll just leave it alone. 
     
    
</post>
<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      copyright 2003 John JJ Martin  I’m not looking to play the game Not really at least  I want to do things slow and be postmodern I think  I should try to hurry things up I might come in too late  *Stand back from behind the yellow line till the train comes to a complete stop in the station*  I’m been trying to be good about the whole deal but I cant seem to get it right. If it’s not the age, it’s their body, if it’s not that, it’s money, not that, its voice, forget voice, it’s me. When it’s me, it’s because I talk, or think, or expect too much.  *Please stand back from behind the yellow line till the train comes to a complete stop in the station*  I don’t see the problem, I really don’t. I could have love (whatever that is), money, friendship, family, but I can’t move my feet. Cemented in place by my expectations. What I want, what I need, why I want it, is always blurred by what I want all of it to be.  *The train is traveling at high speeds and will not be able to slow down quickly, so please stand back from behind the yellow line till the train has come to a complete stop in the station*  I’m too young to have what I want. It’s not a hard thing to grasp, I just don’t know how to deal with all of the things that come along with being with you. I’m going to need time to test my waters, before I step into yours. Is that sad?  *If the train hits you, we will not be responsible for any injury that may occur. Stand back from behind the yellow line till the train comes to a complete stop in the station*  Without any know how boyfriends work, or how they operate, I need my space to see what moves and steps I have to take. How do i find out? Well, that’s the catch 22. I have no idea. If I don’t try to have a boyfriend, then I wont know how one might operate.  *For god’s sake, please stand back from behind the yellow line till the train comes to a complete stop in the station*  I’m going have to tell you that I’m not feeling it. I don’t feel it because we went too far. I’ve done the sex-first thing, then the date thing, and it’s dead in a month. I know it works if you flip it, remix it, so that’s how I’m doing it from now on. I’ll take the risk after I go through that process, but not before. I want my time, space, and chance to do it my way. No sooner. Never say never says I, but I’ll buy. I want to try guys around my age. I’ve been with guys older. I want to travel; I can’t do that with payments coming out (as much as I’d love to). If someone younger came along, I’d be on you like white on rice. If it’s not an age thing, it’s a body thing, or a money thing, or a sex thing, or a something.  *The doors are now closing, please stand clear, the doors are now closing* 
     
    
</post>
<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      copyright 2002 John JJ Martin  I don’t know you and I don’t think I ever will.   I see you every time I boot up and every time I cross the street, every time I buy tea and every time I read the paper. I see you when I masturbate, I see you when I eat with family, I see you when I drift on the subway and only know I can’t have you.    You’re there with all the passion in the world and I want to fill my arms with everything that is you.    I want to lay with you on the couch, I want your sweat to fall on my chest I want your fists to hit me in the face and dig into my mind and know what makes me laugh. I want your feet in my lap; I want your pain on my hands. I want you to need me and cry when I’m not around. I want to cling to you and have things be better.    You’re so confident and smart. You’re so beautiful and jive.    I want to see your face before you wake up; I want to see soap run down you legs. Your hurt is what I need. Your knees bent over my headboard, my sense of humor warped because of you. I long to have your back pressed to my front and your ears nuzzled by my lips. I want your feet to incite my fetish   How do I love thee? Dose it matter? Do you really want me to lay it out in a blue print? Do you think verbalizing a list from 1 to infinity, displaying from least to most important would show you how I want you? How I want to pull your rib cage open and massage your heart, warming my cold hands with your fiery center. 
     
    
</post>
<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      copyright 2002 John JJ Martin  Go Girl Kick up them heals Strut your stuff  Go Girl Flip that hair, I know it’s yours Show it off Show me what you got Show me your specialty  Click, click click She works hard for the money Click click click  Lucy wobbles Bending ankles, bag swingin’ Lights approachin’  Window 50 to sit the audition 100 for the final 20 I’m in a hurry  Door Crack! snap! Lights Here, stop  Dark Yah! Done  Click click Kick it up Show it off Click click click Lights Go girl!  Click Click Click Click Click… 
     
    
</post>
<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      copyright 2002 John JJ Martin  Click Click Click Click Click click flip Click click Click, girl! Click click click Click click Click click click flip girl "Chaw!"  Click 50 click Click 50 50 click click Click door Click snap! Gag  Click click click Click snap flip Click click click Flip wabble click "Chaw!"    Turn Girl  Click Click Click click click click Click Click Kick it up! Trannie! Trannie!  Turn  Gag dark click Click Click Click Click click click  "Chaw!"  Turn 
     
    
</post>
<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      copytright 2003 John JJ Martin  Gay Cafe Potty Bathrooms are interesting. You can walk in expecting the best and in some cases, you get it. There are times when you can get a palace. However, most other times, you get a moderate cleanness, over the artificial flower sent enticing from the wall dispensers, you get the lingering smell of a really nasty splashy shit, that left a connect-the-dot pattern on the underside of the faded white toilet seat. I always use my foot to put the seat up and push the handle down. I never wash my hands, ever, because I know my hands are cleaner then the sink faucets. I never use public toilets for #2’s.   Gay Cafe Cutie I’m watching him talk to Donny on the other side of the second floor, and man, he’s cute. He looks Dutch. Got a bit of a tummy, but that’s ok, I’m not tossing stones. I’d talk to him, but when it comes to guys my age, I’m the only one that has a brain. He looks like he talks about the circuit and clothes. That’s what the keeps me away. Rejection doesn’t kill me anymore, I’m the good-looking one now. Is that shallow? Great hair, great smile, great bum, damn, where are my condoms when I need them?   Gay Cafe Comfy I’m not really a fan of leather furniture. Leather everything else is cool though. In the summer it’s sticky, in the winter it’s sticky, with syrup, it’s even more sticky, but right now, the cool brown and warm skin is just right. I’ve spent hours on this couch cruising, talking, reading and writing. Any other day, I’m hating the couch but when I’m hear, in the cafe, I’m game. The surroundings might have something to do with it. The bad neo-corporate conditioned murals and coffee colour painted walls? Nahh, it’s the couch. Maybe I should get a leather chair for my playroom, or more importantly, my living room?   Gay Cafe Thinking I like the idea of hurting someone. I want to get a guy to really like me and then jerk his head around. I like the idea of hurting someone as much as I have been hurt. Kevin said “that’s sick”. Is he right? I like the idea of having some guy wallow in his own filth for a while (forever). I like making them suffer when I can. Shwan did it to me 3 years ago, now it’s time to project that built up self-hatred in him, in me, into innocent people. I don’t see anything wrong with this. You think I’m kidding?   Gay Cafe Cruising Damn, I could really go for some of that...Nahhh!  
     
    
</post>
<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ARTISTS and WRITERS OF ANY KIND!!!!! LOOKING FOR A FORUM TO SHOWCASE YOUR TALENTS? Here's your chance! NO work will be rejected. We need creative writers, visual artists, and generally anyone who needs to express themselves, for a 'zine called thing, being destributed throughout Toronto. We at thing, are artists and activists who feel compelled to share our work with others. Submitt drawings, photographs, stories, rants, interviews, critiques, top-tens, documentation, anything!!! A simple sentence will suffice. So have fun with the freedom of knowing you can't lose. It's guaranteed to go in the 'zine.  We accept and print all submissions; any style, any format. Radical ideas encouraged with the exception of fascist propoganda. Get your work out there and have full credit and creative control over it. We want to get your work seen. If you contact us and send us your work we guarauntee it will be on magazine stands in the next issue; unedited and uncensored.  Note to writers: please no more than 1000 words. Nothing is too short. **We are looking for short stories (1-2 pages typed) for our column A Story About A thing. *** Visual Artists are strongly encouraged to apply. Your art work may appear in colour  WE HOPE TO HEAR FROM YOU! You can reach us via e-mail at angelblaze_69@yahoo.com or by phone at 416-532-7581 ask for Deborah Andrea Singh or Karen Darricades 
     
    
</post>
<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      copyright 2003 John JJ Martin  Begging and crying out for the attention I want Grappling Bitching Sketching and retching at the ground Whining and ripping Groping Pawing Snatchin’ and devourin’  Not wanting anything more then to have my cake and eat it too Bullshitting  self-hating Working it and attracting Rejecting Berating Regretting the regrets  My own world and being too damn stuck in my head, and never leaving my four walls. Looking and wanting Cruising and needing Feeling the anti-climatic rejection always hurt in the end.  I run a warm tap when I feel lonely  always forget why I do things in the first place. Losing in the end. Wanting what I can’t have Having everything but still wanting more Wanting what I see and not being happy with what I’ve earned  got already.  Running a cold top when I get my wants, and deny other real needs when they come along. Attempting  failing Wishing and hoping Dying and wanting Never Ever A different me.        It’s better to have lost in love, then never to have loved at all. But what happens when you have lost in love and still, you haven’t loved at all? What then? What now? Does it get better? When do I move? At what point does it get better?! Looking blankly Blurry  blunt Cutting Smacking down Face first, breaking my teeth Starting over.  Uglier then before and not knowing why. 
     
    
</post>
<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      copyright 2003 John JJ Martin  Into the belly, we are starving For uprising of sweets and Carbs. Breads and meats for Our aching gutts; we are starving.  Down our throats we are thirsty For water, cooling the wind dry blisters And cracked lips. Juices flowing and Sugar cane craving. We glug down The punch of alcohol, the warming Of tubes, the filling of holes.  Convulsing and turning, flipping with Digestion, we stuff more through our Mussels and cram into our stomachs Right to the rim. Up to the Opening we fill, with food and drink.  We are content, for now. Pushing back from the trough, Specks on our shirts, goop on our Face, we are happy and full In pain. We rub our flats and Unbutton what has swelled.  We digest, think of what is processing Or maybe not. Regretting the 6 tarts An 5 slices. So full, so hungry in An hour. Turning the corner for the Underground, opening the cupboard, Sitting down on the curb. “Pass the salt”.  Into the belly, hungry and sore. Stuffing again the tarts and slices. Filling with Bread and meat, only now tuna in top Mixed with neopolatin/3 flavors, crackers And chicken, soup and pepper, candy, …oh, sweet candy.  Pushing back from the trough, I get up from the curb. I stagger. I’m full, I’m in agony, more then vicious Ach, an elephant’s thunderstorm, I stagger.   Into the belly I wonder, further in the carved 70’s inferno. Bubbling acid, digesting fragments, into The Bucks to sit and wallow in heart- burn. Cutting my throat, slashing from the inside out. The ulcer from years before. Bleeding in silence, cramping and Churning my hollow, more meat and sweet, tart than Fart. But nothing, but hunger, but fullness, But pain, but gas and cramps remain after The feast at the corner around from the Underground.  Out of the belly I am mulched in the Garden and fed to the flower, I am now The food, but for a more natural being. Less involved with meat and sweet and gas and pain, I am dinner for the Other. To cycle through the veins of a plant, up It’s neck and through it’s petals, then Nourishment.  There might be hope, set free From the pollen and traveling.  Into the belly of the bee I Wait to be vomited into a cone And hardened, and squeezed into a jar by A kind hand. I’m On display (much like back at the corner), But now I have shape. Clear cylinder with A top. I am soft and finally sweet, I’m food once more  Into the belly of you I go. Oh, ode to you, I am in your body, right Where I love to be. Inside you, Rushing with you endorphins, blood bubbles, And I’m not leaving. You’ve taken me in, chosen me from the Shelf, I am yours …until I’m food again. 
     
    
</post>
<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      copyright 2003 John JJ Martin  Every bend, twist and hair From the tip to the follicle, into the skin. Hidden in shoes, exposed in Sandals, I shake, anticipation. New beginnings of wrestling butterflies The nails and bulbous shells. Digits lined, charged.  Clasped Finger for toe and fro. The moisture, the soft pads Like new born labs Pitter-pat on cold floors  Aching arch, Leather, rubber, souls.  Foot Feet Fetish.  Cupped in sockets, The ball  The tendons, Flow to the knuckle  Curling under pressure, Bow back after recline  Dig in, Dragging you under.  Basted in juices Dancing on points Grinding my back  To the rug In the depths Fused to the worship  Arms spread eagle Face in fiber Hard…breathe   Up your leg, Palms to arced rise, Powerless. Traces your veins with my finger. Plump fat tubes of Blood. Upon my knees, I bring your foot in, To my stone. The Trojan horse, the tension in tissue. The submission. Silhouette of five, maybe ten. Viewed, from behind…  I gather myself. Face to face, I’m Together. The defeated heart beat; slow, tongue in movement. I’m ready. Carbon blasts your ravens, divots and dashes. I maintain an even balance, for now. Then you nudge my chin skyward, “look at me” The springs go, snap haywire. My hands quick to the Valleys of your knees, weaken and fall Crashing to my lap, Land and rest, encased in my arms.  Eye to eye, my anger is trigger happy, Frustrated, enamored. Protein starved and light headed. The games are over. You smile and pull back; I’m not Playing this out any further. Either you get out, Or get on top. 
     
    
</post>
<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      copyright 2003 John JJ Martin  It’s come about in years That I can’t hold back the hate And at some point I’m tired I just have to accept my fate.  She tossed me to the ground I was expecting so much more Dreams of parties, tears and weddings Dreams of a full musical score I found myself years later Never speaking of it again She pushed me out wanting fantasy She’ll die lost from the reigned  He slashed me across the chest Leaving me clotted  scared Never have I seen things different After he played part  He was everything to me and he knew it He never said anything but I wish he had I’m the biggest fan of regret But when I try right now To forget his cold hands And cutting words I want him left in my dust And crying for higher ground.  He showed me what it was to be in love Be never gave me a chance I pushed and prodded nothing I wanted nothing more then to be his man  He dashed my hopes and infected my mind And now I can’t see another way.  I’m left hating life and wanting nothing more To run away alone, On the back of a horse with the satchels Full of the hearts I want to burn.  I want to tear out their eyes and hold Them up to the light to see what they Have done  If they knew all the life that they killed Then maybe they could move on (maybe I could move on)  I’m in the coldest place without a trace Of a family in sight It’s all shoes and gel and The smell of nite-rate  I couldn’t even breathe?  The days got long and my clouds came In and it’s so clear where we went Wrong  We don’t give a damn about the young As long as we hear the fierce beat And our arms are strong  I’m left with lonely I’ve given up on love Nothing lasts forever If death come first At least you go out thinking Time was yours and you won.  It’s the lucky few who settle for less And go out with a smile But for the rest of us shmoes We hold on without faith and know That God just smirked for a while.  And I’m one of the runts who just runs Away Hiding under the biggest rock With my mic in hand I blast their town and wish I could come back  I use to love what life threw me I loved the challenge that I faced I was king of my bullshit and I fought till the end  But when I look back now I want my virginity in tact, to turn back the clock... And take everything I said back. 
     
    
</post>
<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      copyright 2004 John JJ Martin  WHEN LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL Everything coming together in A gel of brandy soaked dessert  raspberries. Where the summer days are hot  dry But the heat is bearable because you have a communal Feeling of rhythm over Breakfast in a downtown café. When ashes are accidentally Dropped in your coffee  the pancakes are sponged with syrup.  WHEN LIFE IS BITTER And you’re at a family Gathering of generations lost, Nothing is worth living when Happy sighs and gentle words From older aunts, tell you that Times have truly changed but that everything under That roof, has stayed The same; That grandmothers fall bald, dry up like week old tulips  families drift apart.  WHEN LIFE IS PAINFUL You think of every awful Thing you did. You regret Saying the words you uttered And you crave for your Waistline back. You hate The addictions you’ve made; The colour you dyed your Hair and the shift change last week. When life is painful, You run past mirrors Turn the air-conditioning Off  shut the curtains Because your eyes are puffy. Hoping that the next day will welcome you with open arms, contrasting light not flat like the day before, You never sing your resurrection song for anyone.  WHEN LIFE IS SWEET You run over to the Ex who is still crazy for You and your enthusiastic To see him smile. You e-mail them with your day and check back every hour to see if they have responded. You give in to old memories of rolling over and nestling your head in the nook of their shoulder+.  Passing out for another hour.  Leaving drool on their neck.  Sharing silly jokes in the shower.  When life is sweet, you Take your time in the Morning, rolling around Under your blanket making Sure you have Reenacted old sexual Play before you reset the clock.  When Life is sweet, you Take to your pillow, length Ways, and hold it tight to you till the cool fabric comes up to temperature and you flip it over. Imagining all the time that someone Is about to press their front To your back and breath On your ear.  WHEN LIFE IS HARD  DARK All the roads are blocked And the ground falls in Every time the birds come out. Everything regenerates, or flies, or can live underground, or can do well without. But you, your humans self Will just fall short  Die, or rot, and there is nothing you can do about It.  All of life is a number Where you show your human in capabilities And you never are allowed to live Them up, simply because I say so.  When you cant do anything but frown. When all the lines on your face converge into a tight lipped scowl of plastic smiles  empty well wishing…when the bottom of a bottle gets closer In one sitting.  Ahh, rest away from Everything that you Know, and care to forget 
     
    
</post>
<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      copyright 2004 John JJ Martin  I met him when he was a shell Of something great. Something that encompassed all the ideals of a young romantic Who danced in bed, and was energetic for all that was open to him.  I only knew him when his eyes were dull  hazed. When his thoughts were blurred  hardly decipherable, Where there was once a lush basket of words.  I knew him when his kisses were hardened, sharp  grainy. When he laid back and looked on with pompous gaze. With no participation unless he was in demand.  I ran into him when sex was then, something to do, And after he found out He was pretty. ...when his forehead was smooth without wrinkled expression. Dead still  botoxed without the $500 deposit.  ...when his books were half read and barely spine cracked. Where his CD collection stopped growing and where his good clothes were never worn.     I crossed him one day after his 3rd strike and he was out. When the last one sealed the deal  he now slept Above the covers...when he slept with someone ...when he slept at all.  I know him only as the Guy who plays Russian Roulette And takes it like a man. When his door is always open But the nightstand isn’t stocked.  I only see him when he is willing to go that one step further And forget his revolution. Join the masses to comatose for the evening, and never write about it the next day. 
     
    
</post>
<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      copyright 2004 John JJ Martin  If all human life Everything that matters on the surface (walking, talking, dress, society family, sex, gender architecture and creed…love) Are constructs based on symbolism derived from subjective opinion, Then life, contrary to popular belief in a post post-modernism that relies on spirituality, IS a destination and NOT the journey that all the shrinks and popstars talk about.  In the thinking that all human life is "Surface" Something fake Something constructed Fabricated by humans, Then lets say that nothing in human life, matters Not family, children, poverty money, sex, furniture Nothing…symbolism is subjective  meaningless. If nothing matters in life, then we are all (we, as in all living beings), are just cells and/or tissue and/or matter With no real connection other then biology.  If God is perfect, the be all and end all Everything And He/She/It created everything Earth, man, art Earth wind and fire To His/Her/It’s ideals Then all that God created is perfect Perfect! But! if humans are nature, and are imperfect And are created by God, (who we were modeled in the likeness off), Then God is imperfect as well And we humans are the conceptual  physical construct of a higher being and/or a single cell split that was a fluke from a chance happening.  Biology can be funny that way.  And if we are (on a base level), a construct anything like that of all human life on it’s "Surface" Then we are fake too. Our skin, voice, sexual organs Are all fabricated They don’t actually exist. If we humans feel emotion; love, hate Orgasm, (with all previous things considered), Are just meaningless neurological experiences that are in place because by chance we (we humans) have evolved in a physical way that has allowed the brain to "think".  "Thinking’ has made it possible for humans to feel meaningless emotion in order to survive/exist. In order for humans to limit the amount of physical pain, they must use this tool (their meaningless emotion), to create symbolism in order to apply it to other beings in an attempt to alter the mental state of others/things/beings for the sake of survival. A defense metaphysical mechanism. Physical pain makes life in whole, unbearable and all living things do their best to limit the amount of discomfort so as to make it through the day.  Physical pain leads to mental pain and unless a being has the correct combination of cells to make healthy tissue… that being will inevitably self-destruct (suicide).  Hence, the attempt to construct a Surface of supposed meaningful symbolism to all things in "human life". 
     
    
</post>
<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      copyright 2004 John JJ Martin  EVERYTHING, is Silhouetted hunter green in this still, windless morning of an overcast day. The birds fly  sit solid On pencil drawn phone lines And sing…eventually, When the first cars roll by Who need drowning out.  Meanwhile, behind the Spanish lace And within these four walls The enormous jade leans toward The light. Reaching with his cubby fingers Poking though the window treatment Nose against the glass  Over there on the corner of The Persian rug, (that she has soiled before) lays the floppy dog (whose shedding hair clogs the vents and balls like tumbleweeds)  As we trudge ourselves around the hardwood The floppy dog trumpets our Every move, ahead of us by Every step, escorting us Everywhere, protecting her masters As a cat never would.  Wanting only to please, she spins Plates and tells jokes. Sets up entire productions in order To entertain the crowd  we shove Her out of the way, Because this hairy nuisance is The last thing WE need.  So she curls up on the floor (on her back) and sleeps (with one eye open) ready to guard  protect and jump to the attention anytime there is movement (like the sounds of rustling leaves)  But Jade longs, Aware of what’s going on outside Shooting cut eye to the floppy dog  Can’t she see?  Then leans in (as far as the pot will let him) and grows up the window, slathering his face on the jail cell Leaving his tin cup To rest, knowing no one Will hear him dragging It across the bars, Through the double pained glass. 
     
    
</post>
<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ARTISTS and WRITERS OF ANY KIND!!!!! LOOKING FOR A FORUM TO SHOWCASE YOUR TALENTS? Here's your chance! NO work will be rejected. We need creative writers, visual artists, and generally anyone who needs to express themselves, for a 'zine called thing, being destributed throughout Toronto. We at thing, are artists and activists who feel compelled to share our work with others. Submitt drawings, photographs, stories, rants, interviews, critiques, top-tens, documentation, anything!!! A simple sentence will suffice. So have fun with the freedom of knowing you can't lose. It's guaranteed to go in the 'zine.  We accept and print all submissions; any style, any format. Radical ideas encouraged with the exception of fascist propoganda. Get your work out there and have full credit and creative control over it. We want to get your work seen. If you contact us and send us your work we guarauntee it will be on magazine stands in the next issue; unedited and uncensored.  Note to writers: please no more than 1000 words. Nothing is too short. **We are looking for short stories (1-2 pages typed) for our column A Story About A thing. *** Visual Artists are strongly encouraged to apply. Your art work may appear in colour  WE HOPE TO HEAR FROM YOU! You can reach us via e-mail at angelblaze_69@yahoo.com or by phone at 416-532-7581 ask for Deborah Andrea Singh or Karen Darricades 
     
    
</post>
<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      copyright 2002 John JJ Martin  This is the first draft of my first ever short story. I hope you all enjoy it and I hope your able to see the typos (God knows I don't).  *A young man eyes sad like an empty dinning room table, Percy was the kind of young man who had few friends but knew a tribe. He wasn’t the most academic of people but his social skills were something to be reckoned with. If you wanted to know something you would have to wait for him to come to you. He was the kind of guy that people wanted to know but because of his stand-off-ish style, people never went forward to see what was inside him. Maybe they thought he’d blurt out obscenities to cast them off or they feared he would open up to them revealing something not to be heard by common ears.  Percy stood almost 6 feet tall mid-broadness to his shoulders and a pot to his mid-section. Not the cover model you would see on the New York rag stands. He had a different look about him. Something exotic but still human. Something that wasn’t threatening, something that made you wants to look but not touch. We was that piece of Grandma’s junk jewelry that you wanted to pick up but didn’t because you didn’t know if it would crumble into bits. Breaking at the joints, irreparable. Dark hazel eyes from his father and all other features from his mother. The longest eyelashes you have ever seen were on this one gent. Long and black. A light not so fully developed 5 o’clock shadow shaved smooth each day because he hated the beastie look. Short chocolate brown hair, Ward Clever-like shaped his narrow face, high cheekbones and slightly graying hair. Fair lightly tanned skin-natural Percy was 24 years old. Full lips like his mother and beautiful to listen to.  His dress was nothing too fancy but still pulled together quite nice. Clothes he acquired from his late Grandfathers closet and new odds from high-end stores that made him stand out but not blend with the trendsetters posing behind retail counters. His shoes always warn in to the comfort of his taste, his pants always sitting on the rise of is leather black square off boots and jackets with lapels, a class act but not stodgy. Percy walked like his father. Upright like a Captain of a ship ready to make it’s maiden voyage. Looking about with confidence while he watched for addresses of places he had to go, not letting something go by with out his approval of it’s significant. Burning inside though.  The union of two people brought on this look of his. His father a black Irish/English man (“Black Irish” meaning born of Irish decent but with Portuguese/Spanish history) and his mother of a Spanish/Moroccan background born near the most northern tip of Morocco. They were brought together by they’re want to find more of their lost Spanish lineage. James, his father traveled from the East Coast of the Canadian Maritimes to Spain to trace his family’s roots. Like most young Canadians he was brought up to be proud of his Irish backing but knew nothing about it because he was negligently never taught. Traditions diminishing the longer his family stayed in the new world all fading. Being forced in the face with this idea of his “Irishness” he decided to go off after school and across the pond to Ireland he went. Finding part roots in the county of Manorhamilton and learning of this Spanish side, he abruptly left Ireland for Espana. It was the call to find out something that he had never known about himself, something that he had longed for and a way of getting out of so much damn green. The countryside of Ireland pulled his heart in every direction but the dampness and the icy nights chapped his lips and he wasn’t having any part of it. Natacha his mother, I woman of not the strongest will but of great heart was seen from a bench on the fairy crossing to mainland Spain from the Rock of Gibraltar. The man watching was Percy’s father James. Much like his son, James, a man never to let a chance go by without a good effort moved across the wood planks that were the fiery and started chatting up Natacha. When landed on solid ground and their stomachs settled they had coffee. Learning of her reasons for coming to Spain, James invited Natacha to join him on his hippie trip to find who was. Natacha, brought up in a non-traditional home with a mother who was an out spoken member of several woman’s movement groups in Morocco was bread to think and take responsibility for her actions as a woman coming of age in a time where so much was going on in the western world. However much to her mother crippling dismay, Natacha was a quiet and reserved young thing. Never speaking up and never taking in what her mother was working so hard toward. After being disowned by her mother in traditional Arab form in attempted to bring her head around Natacha left for Spain in a bold move that was far out of character for her. They traveled across Spain to find things that would give them a spiritual home and soon they couldn’t find themselves without each other.  Percy Woodrow was born in Tooting, London England in 1978. His mother was battling breast cancer and he was a breech birth. Post his birth by five hours, Natacha gave in and simply died. From what Percy’s Grandmother recalled his father James was hoping with all his might that Percy would die along side of his mother for he couldn’t handle raising the monster that finally did his “Eve” in. Percy grew up with his father James in London before his hatred took him to a brick wall and he put Percy up for adoption at the age of six. It was only later after Percy found his maternal grandmother, he starting hearing the other stories about other family members that only made him what to be part of the family that he had been away from for the last 18 years. He began to remember people he grew up with before James took away from it. He learned his grandmother Mobina used to call him “Abdy”. She said it was a more Arab name and it suited him better then the one his father bestowed upon him. Anytime however, Percy tried asking about his father and what happened to him after he was given off to another family people would turn their heads in traditional Arab form and maintain silence. Percy’s father gave him off to another family and he never saw or heard from James again. Percy wanted to hear that his father had left a letter with an agent telling him why he felt the way he did so many years ago, but nothing ever came of his efforts. After much pushing Percy’s had his grandmother sit down and told what she could bare. After his father left he went off back to Canada to live and re-married. He had a wife and son who loved him with everything they had. After two years with this new family, James when in a fishing boat off the coast of Seal Cove Newfoundland and never came back. Maritime patrol found his body clinging to the overturned boat by his typically Canadian lumber jacket. Alcohol test came back saying he had downed a bottle of something.  *************************************  The air was colder than what he was use to. Irish weather was getting the better of him and the more north you go the more bitter the air would turn. His lips tight together and arms wrapped around his torso. With his shoulders pulled up and walking like a scarecrow with a coat hanger for a scarf Percy was in Derry. The northern part of the country was beautiful in the summer he reckoned but damn cold and dull in the winter. Percy had arrived on the fairy crossing the Irish Sea, all it’s white caps and nausea were not worth what he was seeing. Everything was brown and not the green wonder that he stereotyped. He would have flown the hour and a half flight from Wales to Dublin but this trip was last minute and he was working on emotion and couldn’t wait the extra day for the flight availability to open up. When he reached solid ground 6 bottles of Perrier and four hours later he got the next chartered bus and went through all the red tape of passing into the north. He stood out so incredibly with his dark skin and fancy corporate dress that it was he who was holding up the bus’s passage at the border. One of the crossing guards boarded to do a routine check he scanned the bus’s occupancy and stopped at Percy. He stared him down and cutting right through, the guard was only doing this for his own enjoyment and power trip. If anyone knows about the history of the North and the death and dismemberment of the culture, they would know that to power hold over someone for just one moment is something to reveal in even for just a moment. This is what the guard was indulging in. A brick through his front window two days before had hurdled passed his five-year-old daughter. He’s been on a trip ever since. Looking out the window the whole time Percy knew just whose attention he had captured. Forcing himself to stare out at the gray dull afternoon, trying not to let his eyes slip from the scenery back to the reflection in his window of the guard standing in the isle. Looked him over, checking the details of his nave suite with sharp lapels, white as snow crisp shirt, gold and yellow striped tie the guard moved on. Knocked his head back on the headrest of the seat, Percy’s chest sunk and he slouched down. All the time looking out the window he now could focus on the sun in the distance trying to pull it’s way through the clouds. His suite shirt was well soaked with sweat now.  Young Percy was in this cold, dead winter place because he was told his father’s family was still living and doing quite well, he wanted to know who this new rich family was. He though of big houses and lots of furniture. Lots of land and green rolling grass, welcoming arms not quite knowing just who this young man was but more then willing to find out. He thought of dinners with candles and wine flowing, laughing and comfortable beds to sink into after a huge feast. Percy’s grandmother (his mother’s mother), told him to go off to Ireland to see what he could find. Percy was about to do it almost blind. Grandma’ had only known his fathers family through what her daughter Natacha told her. As far as Percy’s grandmother knew, her in-laws were in the northern part of the country in the county of Derry. So that’s where her grandson set out set out to find his relatives.  *****************************************  The weather grew milder from day to day and the fog that was too present in London found it’s way to the land of green just to taunt Percy in his search. He hated driving in fog, he hated the limitations it brought and he hated that it frizzed his hair. He would have meetings some days and show up looking like a prize poodle because of it. Walking up a long street encrusted with large stone walls and high over grown hedges Percy came along 10 Bulore road. This was one of about 6 address he fished out of his mother belongings. Through a book of photos and letters of love and longing was this address on the back pages with a photo of James and Natacha and a child cradled in Natacha’s arms that couldn’t have been him. The setting was faded colour quality in front of a house with white steps and a black pipe handrail. Percy walked through a huge arbor and up a few steps just off the street young Percy came to a gate. Over grown and engulfing branches of neglected yard work covered the number of the house on the gate and it was only by chance that he had looked up to see it. Pulling back the branches and walked through feeling the tug of stray twigs at his pants Percy’s dreams of a big house just came to life. Standing before him was nothing he had ever seen. A house three floors high and spanning a good five hundred yards wide the house was a monster. There was nothing but parking space around the front, like nothing that was available in London. Through this sprawling walk he sauntered slowly looking about. The house had ivy growing up two sides of the exterior the crossing over the windows just slightly, white window frames with their own carriage lamps long out of use, dark brick leading around with not a flaw, and a front door that rivals that of the Buckingham Palace. He looked to his left an evergreen stood. Something that made his stop and take it in. From for more then half way up the plume of the branches started in choppy uneven lengths. The bark of the tree was that of upward facing shards like a palmtree bending at the tipped ends. Percy walked to the front door and focused on the doorbell approaching him. The house was so daunting at this point he was almost wanting to turn back but reached out and pulled down on the iron chain linked doorbell before his nerves got the better of him.  Waiting for about fifteen minutes and wondering around the perimeter of the house, quite and old woman came to the door. Older then dirt but pleasant enough. She was small and fair skinned with hair tied back tighter then a nuns commitments. “You must Percy, No one visits me?” “I am and hope I haven’t disturbed you today” he replied. Stating he’d been in the sun far too long today and tanned beyond repair she suggested he should come inside. Abdy’s right brow raised as he looked over his shoulder and thought, “it’s been raining for two days and I’ve been on a bus?” “I’m guessing you’re my grandmother Eva Devilin?” he asked “No no, her sister. I’m one of two girls and my sister Norah died two years ago this coming November. I’m your great Aunt Eva” Eva took hold of his arm and leading him in, the rain that started out as a mist had begun a light beating on the ground and started to cut through the light snow that had fallen. It would be gone soon and he could wear some lighter shoes.  So grandma’ was wrong he thought-about everything so far. Grandma’ said Percy’s father came from a family who had a huge amounts of money and was quite large members of the community in north of Ireland. The money he could see but this woman was clearly isolated. There were no other voices in the house, no children running around, no music playing, no nothing but her as the only living thing in this house. Insisted that he hangs up coat, leave his shoes by the door on the rubber mat and rest his bag she would bring him in to pantry for tea. Percy looked about, his eyes slipping from one object to another while he unzipped his boots; Percy couldn’t believe what this house held. The front staircase by the main door went up a steep twenty something steps and didn’t stop there. He stood in the center of the atrium style layout, the case when up three floors with carriage lamps installed, one on each side of the squared staircase with white sandblasted class covers. Dark wood spindles marching downward with their mother banister cover them with total security. Nobody was going to knock her children down. A shinning single-parent family. A plain burgundy runner from the third floor, thick and flowing like a wine meeting with the burgundy and red rugs that dressed the main floor. The matching wood where Percy stood was high polished like the banister and flowed down the hall and spread around him to the far room’s open for free walking and discovery. Percy trailed Eva down the hall and turned with her at the first right the young mans eyes passed wall scants homing fresh flowers in small vase’s, three sided tables with fancy carved legs. You could smell the fresh furniture polish. The hall was dimly lit and led to their destination. The pantry door was wide open filled with light spilling into the hall. A radio playing soft off the center of the table to the left of the door welcomed them, to the right was a four grill wood burning oven, high back wicker chairs around the room to fill the four corners with a six pained window over the table to the left hand. Right ahead a door leading to the back pantry a doorway a minimum of 12 feet high with no door. Above it nine brass bells hanging in a row all a different size and personality with a molded casing hiding the mechanics. Through to the other room were the sink and counters messed with flower cuttings and empty jars ready to be filled for the winter feasts. Not the place to be taken if you’re a guest. The back pantry was where the staff years ago lived and worked. The architecture from the rest of the house diminished the second you entered these rooms, it was the staff, why worry. To the right of the back pantry was the small dull wood door that entered to the stables.  Striking up the kettle Eva pulled together some biscuits and butter with marmalade. Making little noise and working quiet quickly she was a true tea machine. Working with the old work quality that wasn’t with the wait staff anywhere else in the world. For her age and financial standing she knew her way around kitchen well. “So you’re looking for what, coming all this way from London?” she called from the back room. “It must be something important, I got your letter saying who you were and was a bit taking back by it.” “I don’t know why I came”, He said. “I don’t really see any point. I found out who I thought you were through my mothers mother and she was wrong. This is a bad way of starting out. I wanted to find who I was, maybe”, he finished. “Well if it’s yourself you think you need to find, then you might have to look further west. Darry is the only place where this family has ever had history and most are passed or like me, relics.” She was dismal in what she said but it was pushing him to move forward he thought. A little hurt came through but he managed to put it aside.  Ahold of one of the spoons left for tea and rubbing his thumb in the hollowed dip of the cutlery he took a seat in the wicker chair. Furthest away from the table beside the oven in the main pantry, to the far right of the room. Coming out a bit unsteady with the tea service in hand and placing it just so at the edge of the table for her ease the rattle of the pot and cups was a little unnerving. Percy thought to run over and pour before she spilled everything everywhere. But she took hold of the pot and poured, dribbling the liquid a tad but not enough to cause a panic.  “Most of the family here went off to Canada, some to New York and America,” she continued. Your more then welcome to spend a few nights if you like until you find a way of getting over seas, if that what you want to do?” Eva welcomed “on one condition…” “Yes?” with nerves riding across on his skin. It was driving him mad not know why he was getting butterflies in his gutt. Wondering why this woman talking was putting a shiver down his back. “You have to make the dinners. I get tired of having to stand over that gremlin of a stove trying to keep it lit” she half joked with a smile “it’s a bugger to work”.  Focusing on Eva’s mouth and the way the skin wrinkled when she spoke anything, then to her eyes the way they magnified through her wide framed glasses Percy loosed his grip of the spoon. Still working the tea like a champ Eva poured the milk to her cup then added one sugar cube.  “Just milk, please.” Percy added to the event.  He found a solace for a moment. Being around someone with no conditions or needs for attention he thought this was something he could stand for a while. Well, no conditions other than dinner made and maybe the odd run to the newsagent for milk and the Telegraph. The tea was nice when it finally got to his hand. Moving the cup to his lips he sipped burning his tongue and swallowing quickly.  “After tea, I’ll show you your bed, then the kitchen” Eva looking over with cheek. “Do you like ham?”  Eva’s house shoes made the pat of puppy feet on the runner going up the stairs to the rooms. Her feet disfigured from years of working in places of smoke and dirty floors. To work in times when war was the reality even the rich had to pull their own weight. Her shoulder shuttered with force for such an old woman. It was strange to say the least. She moved one hand slow to her shoulder and collarbone, rubbed it then brought her hand down to her side muttering something to herself about “the blasted pain” out of ear shot. Percy tossed it off.  “So what were Norah and James like? Were they good people at heart? Where they nice to the rest of the family? Is the reason why James gave me away really the reason why he gave me away?” “Oh she was wonderful.” was answered nodding looking down.  She could have gone on to finish more about her sister, his grandmother. She was chatty before but now getting very short. He didn’t know if she was concentrating on the steps as she went up slowly one by one bring the left foot up to rest beside right before the right moved to the next step. He held his arm out for her to hold for extra balance but she looking down and doing fine didn’t notes.  “What was my father like? I heard he was a jolly and laughing kind of guy like Santa before I came along? I heard that even thought he was a skinny little think he knew how to belt it out?” He asked wanting to knew everything he could. Getting all the questions out as soon as he could so they would be out there in the air and they could be answered whenever she saw fit but at least they weren’t burning inside him filling his head and mind with water. Pushing tight to the insides of his gray matter ready to blow out his ears, mouth and nose. “He was sweet when I knew him” was answered.  “Frustrated Percy thought getting info from this woman was going to be like pulling teeth from a rabid dog. He wasn’t going to spend his few nights in Ireland trying to pry stories out of people so he put it out of his head and followed up the case of little soldiers spindles with their mother keeping guard. Percy looked up and listened for nothing he followed Eva while she showed him to his room. She was in a sudden outer space world thinking off to herself and Percy not daring to take her from it. Getting to the first landing there was a Grandfather clock looking down as they passed. The time was 7:20pm and the light was still showing through windows of the main floor and second. To the right of the first landing there was a small power room for people desperately needing to power themselves. The room about the size a coffin’s standard it had blue wallpaper with a tropical fish print that stood out like a sore thumb in this very Victorian monster.  The room that he was going to call home had a voice like no other in the house. Walking in he was greeted with a wood four poster bed ivory painted, a dark navy blue throw rug tucked underneath. Silk padded walls thick with red and gold interweaving Asian design on a dark blue background, an ornate Asian lantern with hand painted birds with long tails dancing in sunlight on it (looking much like the head offices of Chairmen Mao), falling from a gold Victorian crown molding. A deep red ceiling pouring down the walls textured with plaster stopping at the edge of the padded silk. Hard wood floors holding up what seem to be wardrobes weighting a ton, each on either side of the bed. How was he to even close his eyes in this room without thinking something was going to move toward him? He wasn’t going to turn his nose up at the room, he couldn't, he knew of no other place to stay and there were no hotels anywhere closer then Belfast. “I’ll see you down in the pantry in twenty minuets” Eva prompted. Closing the door, Percy started to unload his small bag. Two other changes of pants, a few shirts nothing formal and loads of socks and underwear were all that one needs for he’d have to find a place where he could get hold of a sweater. The weather was damp and he wasn’t impressed. The room had a queen sized bed so there was an up to things.  *********************************************   Not a journal but more a book for thoughts and ideas for work portfolios, Percy wrote; I had a dream last night that I came home after a very long day at school and as I came up the front steps my father met me at the door all exited. “Your mother had the baby!” he said. So I rushed in and saw my mum sitting in the living room holding the baby and I asked her what it was. She said, “it’s a boy” and I all I remember was that wanted to hold the baby so bad. So I picked up the baby and held him tight and had the desire to be the best big brother in the world. I knew in the dream that it was just a dream and that I wasn’t really a big brother so the dream had a bittersweet flavor to it. I remember next taking my little brother everywhere and seeing him grow up to be a strong and willful little boy. I remember being by his side through out the whole dream and knowing that I was going to wake up at some point. As I began to wake up I kept trying to fight the waking hours and get back to see my little brother. I knew I would never see him again after I woke up. He left his book on the nightstand by his bed and started to pack for the trip to Canada. The dream worked his mind for the last few hours. It was the night before that he was wondering what his supervisor was going to say about him having to extend his leave from work. Now this dream knocked everything away.  ************************************************  Hulling out a suite case vintage from his grandfathers positions, (Percy’s grandfather who he knew through adoption, he only real family he had ever knew) the case held it’s self by a clip on the underside and folded in two. Camel coloured with transparent plastic on the inside so to display the nice suite it would hold. Another case, leather, off by a few shades was brought out and filled with socks and shoes, towels brushes, sweaters, a blanket, hair products tooth brush and deodorant. One thing he could not forget was the deodorant; he forgot it once and knew not to do that again. Medication for his shoulder. It was a day for so after he got back from Ireland that his shoulder started up on him. He figured he had pulled it while out for a jog and a swim. He wanted to get one good workout in before he went off to a small town that didn’t have the chances of gym. Lumped together, all just thrown in like rags. Percy regardless of his attention to the same gender, was truly a guy. He scratched himself while playing sports and slob reigned while he had days off. He managed to afford his townhouse by the ad agencies that brought him on board because of his fine art background. Human Recourses knew that Percy knew nothing about the ad world but hired him because the company was looking for a knew demographic in their staff. People who were more creative and looked at things in a way that could change points of view. He didn’t want the job really, he wanted the money. He knew that the art world, which he was trained, wasn’t going to bring him anything other then poverty and bad skin from stress. They were however looking for people who knew computer soft wear but Percy’s charm and wit had won over the HR lady and got in the final interview that brought him the job, that brought him the paycheck, that brought him his nice house in the north part of the city off the northern line.  Nice with no grass to cut was just what he liked. He like that he was a London urbanite with no responsibilities other then work and bills. White exterior with a crack broken front step. The house needed some work but nothing a bit of cement couldn’t fix. Like most houses in London, high and narrow, you walk in to see a tight staircase turning to the right. At the bottom a vanity with hooks and mirror, antique and dark wood. The door to the first part of the house was to the right and opened up to a sprawling living room/dinning room. Following through the dinning room to the back of the house you meet a step and a side backdoor to your right and the only bathroom to the left with its glass door and skeleton key lock. Follow down a shallow hall and you meet the kitchen stuffed with a table and chairs, wrap around counter, stacked washer and dryer, and storage too frightening to talk about. The kitchen was not at all built right for long cooking periods. Beyond the kitchen is the back garden with it’s warn grass sections and all of overgrown. A small strip of grass but it was still too much to bare on days when a hangover and a nameless face were the guest’ staying the night prior.  Pushing his way around his sparely furnished house, Percy pulled his last few papers together and bills he was to drop off on his way to the Gatwick tarmac. Why was he going? Why was he stopping his life of for this? Why did he need to know about his father? He didn’t care to dig for his mother. He could get information now at the drop of hat from her mother. They were on good terms now and Percy was in such love with her now that she opened up and started to talk more about Natcha. He was his grandmothers little Abdy. But why did he want to know about James? The man who just tossed his son aside? Maybe it was the idea that he had a brother? A half brother, but still a brother. Maybe he had wanted to clear up what his grandmother had put forward? Maybe he wanted to grow a backbone? Maybe he wanted to see if this family James made in Canada existed? Maybe his father was still alive? Percy never felt bad about what happened in his life he just always carried a sense of sadness with him. He wanted to see where that sadness came from; he wanted to see if Canada brought on that sadness. The wall of bewilderment had closed in and Percy had no idea why he was doing anything anymore. He was going with it. He closed and locked the front door. The jolt of pain in his shoulder lingered.  **************************************  You walk here Percy thought. You walk everywhere unless you’re in the capital and even then you’re not able to use a subway because there is none but there were busses. They were rusted-dead rolling creatures on crumbling streets so what’s the point? Just walk, he wouldn’t get sick from the stop and go motion of the transit. You could walk all over this town in a few hours. It wasn’t going to help his shoulder any to walk and carry his bags, but he risked it. He wasn’t going to work with the driving of the cabs on the Island.  A shipping port town long out of use Seal Cove was gray cold and the salt in the air was in your lungs so strong you were rusted from the inside out in minutes. Percy pulled up in the back of cab and knew right from the get-go that the suite he brought would be of no use here. The fashion statement was Erin sweaters and ratted jeans. He took a cab from St.John’s to Gander, from Gander, another cab to Grand Falls Windsor, from there to Seal Cove. He got out of the cab and was hit by the air and almost fell over. The day was 3:09pm by his watch and has spent the last 8 hours traveling in cabs. From this point on walking was no problem. The driver of the cab let him out at the point by the harbor. Around him were multi-coloured houses up on rock faces, shops all around where he stood. This was clearly the core of the town. Too much like Ireland he thought. He heard voices pass by with odd irish/scotish accents. The day was still blah with kids dashing through high grass behind houses and shops lower to his eyesight. Typically white children looking typically white with their red and/or blond and/or light brown hair with freckles. Percy’s dark skin and features contrasted in such a way that with the setting, he was a walking silhouette. He walked from shops to the inn he had found on the internet back home he was impressed that even the smallest town no matter how struck down they might be still have the means to connect to the www.com. Percy’s shuttered and twitched like Eva’ but unlike her pain this was a shot through him like a cop killing bullet. Reached around, grabbed his shoulder blade he dropped his case in his right hand he bent forward to shift the pain out. With a flip of pain he moved his head back to see a little boy fly overhead with his arms stretched out straight behind him. His head leading the rest of his body forward. Percy stopped and took in breath, his heart stopped and his body went stiff. He gazed at the boy flying in the sky. Flapped his arms in slow-distanced waves. His eyes followed the boy until the light brown white boy disappeared over the horizon of coloured houses and high grasses. Everything about his father and what he wanted to know drifted slowly until his mind was wallpapered with this boy. Fire balls of pain stopped-for the moment.  The room at the inn here was very nice a big old house with everything you might want. The owners were wealthy that went without saying. They had this house for years and just by the way they kept it you could tell they knew just what they wanted when they wanted it. The older of the two woman, was quite willing to toss him out if he didn’t go by just what she had said when she said it. The bourgeoisie of the town. Lithleana was her name.  The manor was lovely in its presentation. You enter to an oak staircase going up two floors with roman carved spindles and pillars of darkened wood warm with old education. Rugs at every step welcomed you into every room. Pocket doors on the main floor separated the front rooms and dinning room. A Bishop table with the book of check-in adorns with I blue vase with purple swirls wrapping it in ribbon comfort. Two the right of the front door, a stainless window of three red roses. Percy though of his foster mother when he saw these roses. She told him a story that when funeral receptions end most people don’t want the flowers so they would send them off to the wards of hospitals. She went on to say that as beautiful as the flowers were they were never put on the same floor as the nursery. Red roses were one sign of death and that were the last place people wanted to see them.  “Breakfast is at 7:30am and ends at 9:00am on the dot!” was her opener. “No later. We don’t make dinner or lunch, then is a bed and BREAKFAST”, putting all the emphasis on the word breakfast. Which was fine, he didn’t eat in the middle of the day or at night really. “You have to tell us just when you want to eat, we have to know when you’ll be down for breakfast” was her next banter. “Well I might want to sleep in and then come down, I’m not really sure when I might be down” was Percy’s replay and he knew he would hear it right about…now. “You have to tell us! We have to know so we can get the kitchen going! We have to know now!” was thrown in his face. “Oh, ok, well 7:30am on the dot. I’ll set my clock tonight so I’ll be there right on time” was all he knew to get here to lose the scowl on her face. “Well you’re an early bird I see, well that’s good. I’ll see you in the morning” she closed “and we have a 9:30pm curfew. Any later and the door is locked.”  His room was nice. A single room with a double bed, no TV in the whole house, which for him was a good thing. He hated the sound of the tube running on end at friend’s places for hours while parties were in the mix. His room was small maybe 10 by 10 feet with a huge poster window putting down his bags and tried to see if he could see the flying boy. Maybe he would come flying by and smile at him. Percy turned toward the room and looked down the walls with their delicate flower wallpaper and Renoir prints. The carriage lamps on either side of the bed were thankfully electric and sandblasted coloured glass shaped into long narrow flower cups pointing down. The rug lay across wood floorboards with it’s tasseled ends and it’s long rectangle shape. The dresser was high and soon filled with the clothes. His suite hanger was hung on the back of the door. The clock over the bed read 5pm.  *************************************  The jab outward pain was just at a point where he could see it in the mirror when he turned around but couldn’t reach it to feel if something was wrong. From what he could see a bump, small but still notable through his shirt had shown up. Like a cyst crawled on him and set up shop. He would have it looked at when he got back to London. He thought to go down to breakfast and get out the door before the owner who’s name he couldn’t get right gave him grief. Lidia or Lithlia or something along those lines but he knew it wasn’t Lilly or Lilliana. I couldn’t be that simple now could it?  Out the door and after a long breakfast of talking nothing but jabber to a woman who only saw things from the end of her nose, breakfast was over. He hit the street and walked down the road to the next house, which wasn’t that far off. He wasn’t about to get directions from Lithlia she would have directed him right to the craft shops and the wool section of the corner stores. Lord knows she knew them all. As he passed house after house the colours of the homes got brighter. The idea behind this was so that sailors off the coast could see their house from sea and not feel so alone. That was the story his father growing up told him. Jack was a kind man with light hair and eyes with a soul of a saint and the hands with the voice of a bird. Percy went for weeks on end in the summer with him to the cost of Dover when he was a younger. The air was warm and clean and you could see all the way to France some days. The white cliffs stood guard over them as they played in the water and sand. Jack use to say Percy was a good kid with a good heart and something special about him. One day something was going to happen to Percy and you’ll see just how good you really are. Jack had this think about putting his hand on Percy’s back as a child. It was if when he put his hand on Percy’s back warmth when souring through him and he knew all would be well. Jack went away. His mother Anna said that jack had to fly. Already not understanding much about why people went away Percy just ran with it. Hurt but not about to cry again he just put under his hat and when to school.  Walking for a while down and up short hills and over stone streets, Percy came to the front of the shop where he saw the boy flying the day before. He was hoping that he would fly by and wave Percy down. He didn’t know why but he knew that something was going to bring him to that boy. The boy didn’t show that day. Shaking off the daydream Percy turned to the shop and opened the door to see a woman behind the counter with bangs and long straight almost white blond hair hanging limp. Her skin was killed from acne and longed for a pour sucking. She drew Percy in with her eyes. Nothing could unlock their stare. Looking at each other never looking away Percy asked for a bottle of water and moved himself to one side of the counter so the next customer could relive the stress of weight from the basket he was carrying. “Could you tell me where I’ll find a flying boy?” Percy asked out loud, very loud. “We don’t have those here” She blanked. Was this a Stephen King Percy thought? All the time the gent next in line not flinching an inch to the comment. Like people walk in all the time in the place and ask for flying boys. Everyone around just going about their business. He asked the question only because he knew it was real what he saw the day before. He new he saw that boy zoom over him. He had to know if the town was hiding something from him. Everyone just kept on shopping. People grabbing bread, looking at mags, eating at the little dinning set-up by the windows to the end of the store, buying water. He paid for his water and left. What was going on? Why did he not get anything? He knew something was messing with him but he didn’t know what. Something was going around in his head. The voice of Jack. The feeling of his hand on his youthful back. Something was so odd. The there he was. Chugging down the water Percy saw through the rippling glass of the bottle the boy with who he shared an odd connection. His hair looked brown red in the light that was trying to pull it’s way out of the over case sky. Fro a distance he could see the hair but as the boy stood arms at side he turned and ran out of nowhere. Percy followed not thinking of where he was and not thinking of the pain that was coming from his left shoulder. All the time thinking, “I have got to get that boy, I have to see him, I have to talk to him, I have to hold him.” The boy ran and ducked under a high porch, Percy in hot pursuit. No one looking at a damn thing, people not thinking anything of this chase. People going about their lives. Percy flu under the porch to see where the boy when and stop dead. Looking at the child he griped the ground down on his knees. The boy sitting cross-legged straight backed with his head tilted to the side. With an odd look on his face. “You don’t have them do you?” the boy asked. “Have what?” Percy demanded “Your wings, Dad said you had them but that they didn’t show. He said that you were different and that you knew how you hide yours” the boy pondered walking on his knees around pulling at Percy leather jacket putting his hands up under the leather passing the satin lining. The warmth of the boy’s hand killed the pain that was pushing its way through his back. Percy couldn’t move. “Where does it hurt? He said. “Shoulder blade, left” replied. The boy slid his hands under Percy’s shirt and glided his hand across his back hitting ever ridge of his spine. Stopping at the pain as if he had known right where it was. How did he know I was in pain Percy thought. What’s up with this kid. He couldn’t move. He was stuck in this on his knees unable to move to knock the boy out of the way. “I can feel it coming through. One is starting to poke and it’s not going to stop”, the young voice cooed. Looking around the boy was gone, he was able to move, he was able to get up and walk out from under the porch.  *************************************  The pain was back after he sat down to eat at the dinner. The boy had touched his back and taken it away but what did he mean by Dad said he was different? He could hide what? Wings? What wings? The pain billowing inside him he rubbed. Biting into a hamburger filling his mouth with meat he thought to himself. James hated me didn’t he? Was his grandma’ wrong again? Most likely? She was wrong before. At least the pain didn’t kill his appetite The light in the pub was dim and the only light came from the booths and tables where folks sat, ate and drank their night away. It was only until after he finished that he looked up to see that the whole house was looking at him dead quite and blank faced. What were they looking at? What were they wanting now. No one was looking at him with hate or malice, just awe and wonderment. His heart started beating like the light from the moon on a window on a clear eve in the summer. His shirt started to feel tight as the sweat started to wet his sides. “What’s going on?” he demanded. “What are you looking at?” Looking around he saw nothing but eyes on him. More like a stare passed him. Behind him and not really focusing on his eyes but his back. Looking up there it was. High and grand over his head. Hung like a chandelier at Christmas. A wing. Large like an archangels of protection. He sat as still as he could so to look around to see more and there they were. Feathers of white. Crystal and plumed out of his back right where the boy had touched him, right where the pain was, right where the pain was no more. The town was watching. Every night just about everyone when to the pub. “Morgan’s” was the hot spot. Karoke was the Thursday night thing and Fridays was when Sea Side performed. SeaSide was the local band who had quite the following for everyone. They sang the regular Gaelic inspired music with a touch of hard rock. These boys never really moved from the hair metal rock of 80’s. Once something came to the “The Rock” (Newfoundland) it took another huge invasion to kill the last trend. Not even the Spice Girls could knock what 80’s rock did to the island. SeaSide kept right to their rock. Tonight was Tuesday and nothing really happened on Tuesday until tonight when the attraction was Percy and his extension. No one spoke in the pub. Nothing was moving and no ones eyes were moving when Percy looked about. Everyone was in a state of still. He got up creeped by this everyone maintain their gaze from where they were to where he was sitting. He passed couples holding hands and through thick sections of table where large parties where gathered and felt the brush of peoples bodies as he moved past them. His wing wasn’t a hindered him at all. It moved with him like he’d had it forever. He got to the door and took one last look to see everyone still looking as they were at his spot in the pub. The panic started.  To wake the next morning Percy rolled over to see his wing was still tacked not wrinkled by his movement through the night. He shot up out bed to see in the mirror hanging over his dresser the wing was still with him. His heart beated like nothing the night before. He knew it wasn’t going away. What had he started? A knock on the door. “Yes, Lithlia!” he called out with panic in his voice. Nothing. “Lithlian?” calling out again mispronounced. Nothing. He moved his hand toward the door to open and see the boy standing against the corridor. The runners of the carpet following him down the hall to where he stood at Percy’s door. Light from the hall bathroom window fell into the hall behind the boy giving him a glow of a silly cartoon. “Hi!” blurted in his face in a childish way. Trotted in past Percy and hoping up on the bed to sit cross-legged, “How ya doin’!?” in the boys way. “I’m fine I guess, except that I have wing sticking out of my back”, Percy pointed out. “You’ll have another one soon” the boy bestowed. “When! I don’t want another one! I want the one I have to go away!” Percy shouted. “But two wings are better then one and it looks better then having just one and then you can fly better too and then you can be like me and then we do stuff together and then was can play like we never could before, that’s what dad said before had to fly”, the boy ran on. “Stop!” Percy commanded, when you say ‘dad’, what do you mean?” Percy knew this was his brother, knew this was who he was looking for more then anything about his father but didn’t think in his wildest dream that it was going to pan out like this. He didn’t know he wasn’t human. This wing thing was really taking his story on another path. “Do you know why you have a wing?” the boy asked. “No”, Percy enquired. “’Cause you’re special like me, your different” he went on, “look at mine!” With a flop and an unfurling of sheets upon the bed the boy shook his shoulders and twisted a bit and a set of wings came flowing out from behind him like a wave of white milk. Relaxed, one wing over the foot board the other near the top of the bed where the pillows where messed. The room was small as it were but now the room was filled with feathers and bodies almost to the full corners of the room. Two beauties trapped in this coffin. If Percy’s other wing was to pop, this would not be the place for it to happen. “What’s your name?” Percy asked gently. “Johnny” the boy said wide-eyed.    Hand in hand the two walked down the staircase of the inn where Percy had taken up stock on the second floor. Watching Johnny bump down the steps one at a time like a doll with knobby knees Percy held his hand tight. He wasn’t getting away, not right now. Maybe later he would let the boy go home but not right now. Right now Johnny was his. Safe and not just fling around about to hurt himself crashing into clouds and hitting trees. Look down Percy focused on Johnny’s hair how it grew in a double crown on the back of his head. They passed a stain glass window of lilies on the first landing of the case. Johnny had five cowlicks around the shape of his head. Light brown and going to get darker as he got older. You could tell. The boy’s eyebrows were already dark and his eyes were just the same. He with skin like Percy’s maybe a few shades lighter and an upward turned nose that would fill out right as he got older. Just a funny looking little thing. Most kids were. Perfect he thought. Percy couldn’t see anything wrong with him. Looking at his hand submerged in his. Seeing that he had a brother he looked at children most times as crying little animals, not this time. Seeing how Johnny walked in motion with him, leading off on the same foot, swinging the same arm in stride they were brothers even if the mom was different. Getting to the bottom of the inn’ staircase Percy took a look up to see the spindles shinning with smiles down at him. The light bouncing off their medium finish. The banister it self warm with the light waving good-bye to the two as they left for the day. The light from the lilies on the first landing was warm bed silk flowing down the case of steps and filled the floor at the bottom like a pool of oatmeal covering the plush throw rugs in the front hall. Percy closed the front door. “So when do you think I’ll get my other wing?” Percy asked shyly. “I don’t know, I’ve always had mine. My mum says that mine were there all the time. I was born with them” the boy started and stopped. “She said that dad had them when he had to fly. She said that when he flied away he said that you were like me. That I was going to fly away too and so were you if you got wings like him and me”.  Percy looked ahead as while he listen to Johnny’s words. Hearing him say words that scared him. What did it mean when he said “fly away too if he grew wings like the two of them”? What was Johnny trying to say? Percy didn’t really care about his father at this point. He felt a dead end coming and that wall in his mind was rising through the ground of his brain. With a twitch of Percy’s left shoulder he felt the jabbing-out from under his skin. His left shoulder blade was aching and making him hunch a tad. Percy pointed out, “Johnny I can feel it coming through”. “Really!” with glee Johnny stopped and stood in front of Percy. “That’s great! Soon we’ll fly together. This means that we will fly away together.” Percy said nothing, just took hold of Johnny’s hand and walked down the street passing the houses of early 1900 style until they approached the main streets of the town. Crossing the roads and just missing the passing cars Percy walked with a glazed and somber expression of sadness. The ache was a bit worse with every step he took. Knowing that Johnny was going to fly away and not see him again put a hurt through him that only edged the pain in his back further. Every helpless thought put Percy at the mercy of this pain and at this point he was almost walking with a limp. Curving his back while he walked but still not letting go of Johnny, holding on so tight the boys hand should be well crushed by now but still Johnny walked on, head looking about like a curious puppy of the town. Both of them with wings showing full in the late morning sun shards. Percy’s one wing being met with shallow shark-like fin rising from under his leather jacket. “Let me show you where I live!” Johnny shouted. They had walked to John’s house. Walked so far across town past the harbor and the shops. Able to unroll his back enough to see the main road of the town risen high above them while they stood at the bottom of a hill. They were standing with an extended family of high grass and a few distant cousins of houses scatered about the land of rock faced areas of road broken with time and cracked from the cold of winter leading to the fenced backyards of the homes. Johnny braking away out of his brothers grip and running toward the field facing homes to the east until he came to a fork in the road and turned on the left path. Percy rolled back to his position of pain and ache and walked in the direction of where Johnny ran.  RING! RING! and a swoop of air goes by Percy’s ear and shocks him to stand upright and grunt with agony from the shark fin emerging from his back. Johnny had rushed passed him on a bike he snagged from the front porch of his house and peeled around Percy as he wobble hobbled toward the house. “What do you think of my bike?” Johnny called out. “It’s great”, Johnny expecting a bigger reaction and when he didn’t get it he just shrugged and flew up what was left of the path, got of his bike after tossing it to the side of the front steps ran inside letting the door slam. Funny the door made nothing more then a soft “pat pat pat” as it closed. Heavy wood should do that. Still looking down, what seemed like seconds Percy came to the steps of Johnny home. Percy was more the relived and sat down on the first one closest to the ground. Looking up still hunched, Percy looked at the beauty of the water in the distance to the west and the town to the south of the water view. It took him over for a moment. Nice sights always did thought. The ache eased and he was able to sit up a bit straighter but still felt the pain and pull of his skin as the fin-like left wing grew ever bigger out of his upper back. “Johnny are you there?” Percy called out. The sun hot on his face, squinted he thought, they didn’t have sun like that in England. “Johnny are your there, I need you!” Percy said with desperation. “I’ll be right there! I’m getting water!” Johnny shouted back. Stationed at the bathroom sink Johnny was gluging water down. His throat a dry pipe in a desert.  It was taking Johnny forever to get back to the front porch and all he thought was that he flew away without saying good-bye. He thought Johnny was gearing up to make that last big shot into the sky. Forgetting in youthful absents that he had left his guest on the front porch in pain. Aching with every negative thought. Felling the bony form of the wing pushing now harder through the skin. The rawness of flesh rubbing the under side of the shirt was making the situation worse and to boot, the sun was his eyes blinding him forcing his eyes to water. “Need some help?” a voice not Johnny’s. “Um, please.” Was whined back. The voice was welcoming. He wanted it to be his brother but knew that any help was better then no help at this point. A feminine voice. The voice was softer with a bit of grit somewhat familiar but nothing that he could decipher. The way Percy felt, he couldn’t turn around, the pain that was so very present in his body was affecting his neck. Shooting up from his shoulder blades, Locking. Down toward his waist making it hard to twist and his eyes delapited by the sun shards. In his haze, Percy was able to get his arm out of his jacket. He had it strung on one arm and hooked over the rise of the unexposed wing unable to get it over his new limb. So for what warmth in the cooler morning he could attain he wore it half on. He heard the voice from his front and saw her sitting half on the step where he had perched himself. Through the watery condition of his eyes he could see a hand come out to take hold of his good arm (the winged side) and help him to his hunched self again. Helped to the top step Percy was welcomed inside thanks to his guide. He saw nothing of her but her feet at this point, the porch floor boards and lower doorframe moving passed his eyes. Inside his view was still of the floor. Tiles of floral design, soon a carpet as he turned left into what he was guessed a living room, blue. Where was Johnny? Percy was feeling nothing but loss right now. Was this what it was like to be ripped of your child in abduction or still birth? Where was he? The covered wing pursued its search for air; it was even bigger now. Percy’s buttoned down shirt stretching across his chest with tension on the buttons that now sat up on their side. “Let me help with your shirt” the voice soothed. Who was she Percy thought? Must be the mother. The one who married his father? The one who loved him as much as she could. Or at least that’s how his grandmother’s story went. A poke inward for a change. The tip of a knife, cold, ripping through the back of his blue and yellow striped shirt around the unexposed wing allowing air to get to the pink red skin. Strechmarks were now climbing to the peak of the mountain growing on his back. The new air was numbing to his brain in a good way. The mercy relaxed his muscles and straightened Percy’s back and loosened his neck. He was hot, his face red from being bent over for so long in the sun and leather. His exposed wing bent back now relaxed with his new found freedom. Moving his eyes around the room in a drunken hallucination, the endorphins were rushing. He stopped the slip of his eyes at her. It was the woman from the shop near the harbor. The woman with the bad skin and limp hair. She was Johnny’s mother. “My name is Deb,” she said.   ***   The thump of Johnny’s foot on the table’ single pedestal shook and chimed the glasses of water placed in from of Percy and his mother. The water was good. It cooled Percy’s throat. Percy watched Johnny down his water like a camel. How much did he have to drink? He couldn’t need that much water? He spent a good ten minuets drinking when they arrived and left Percy suffering on the porch and now glugging down more liquid. “So you’re here for what?” Deb asked in a less then interested voice. Percy’s eye’s locked on Johnny as he drank. “To find him” he answered. “I came to find you. In the beginning I didn’t know why I came really.” “I know who you are. James told me about you before he flew” Deb was soft in her answer. Percy didn’t know his father and didn’t know his taste in woman other then he liked something different in them. His mother Natacha was exotic and foreign in her looks and voice. This one was a plain Jane at first until she opened her mouth. The first sounds Percy heard from here were ruff but gentle. Her voice sounded as though she had sucked on a bottle of Jameson Whiskey from the time she could swallow breast milk. Her eye’s gray/blue and skin scared from teen acne still red in places where melanin never recovered. She was middle aged he thought. He wasn’t about to ask. You don’t do that. He did have manners. He was brought to up to respect woman even if some of them were the big “C”. Deb drank from her glass. Johnny’s glass seemed never-ending. After taking his eye’s off Johnny for the moment to watch her talk, he looked back at the boy and saw that his head was still tilted back. Glugging and heaving his chest taking in the water. Was he going to try to breathe Percy thought? “So how old is he?” Percy asked. “Johnny should be well into his teens by this time. If James left when I was seven and had a son two years later and died, Johnny should be 13?” “He’s 15 years old” Deb cleared. “He never grew up much after James flew way. He never even grew mentally, he never showed signs of teenhood, manhood, nothing! Johnny still can’t do his multiplication tables. No matter how I tried or how his teacher tried, Johnny couldn’t get it. He’s had the same teacher, school and desk for the past 7 years. Everyone grows around him, everyone dies and everyone is born around him. He’s had the same clothes all this time. We’ve never had to go shopping for him. Every shirt and pair of pants were still in tacked from the time I bought them at the shop where I work. All I had to do was mend slots to get his wings through his shirts. I could pull and stretch his shirts as far as I could to get those wing through but they never tore. They just went back into place. He’s frozen and that’s the only reason why I hate James for leaving. His going away ended his son’s life. Johnny walks around town and lives day to day never knowing what could be there for him. He’ll never know what it’s like to make love to someone, or feel the kiss of a child that could be his, or taste the sweetness of a drivers test passed, or understand why I have to die and not come back.” Deb running her fingers across the table grain feeling the wood under her fingers passed the knots and knife scraps from years of preparing dinners, she went on. “I feel for the kids out there who are like him. Like Johnny they will get to an age and after their parents fly they themselves will just stop in real time.” Deb moved her hands over Johnny’s and rolled them up his arm to his neck rounding his throat feeling his Adam’s apple pump the water down into the tank of his stomach. “When I have to leave him, when I die, he will be on his own. There will be no one to take him to school or help him bath. There will be no one to help get through life. And you, you’re just like him. You’re other father Jack flew. He never came back did he?” “No he didn’t” Percy confirmed. Jack was a good man. The foster parents of three children Jack and his wife Anna took Percy in to make their family an even six. James knew Jack from years before when he visited his family in the English countryside when James was a boy himself. Jack flew away too. “After you found your way, Jack flew knowing you were going to go on your way. He knew you were your own man and knew that you didn’t need him anymore” Deb read his Percy’ life like a book. “But I did need him. I need him now but he’s not there” Percy disputed. The pain in his back was growing. It was creeping back to his neck and the tension in his waist was on the rise. The pain of the memories were gripping his body pulling it back into the hunch that almost killed him an hour before. “I’m sure you did, but how was Jack to know that. He loved you so much and his fathering mind couldn’t see pass your life” Deb went on. Percy, whose body was contorting, eye’s red from Deb’s story. He didn’t want her to talk anymore. He just wanted to watch his little brother drink.  Turning hunched in Johnny’s direction Percy asked with strain, “Johnny said he always had his wings, how old was he when he grew them?” “He was born with them. He moved out of me so smooth I could feel he was like his father and the doctor didn’t flinch an eye when he saw the wings. It was like he and the nurses couldn’t see them like it was normal.” Deb was looking at the shine of the glass rim now. “So what dose that mean? Percy pained. She leaned in with fingers on her glass Deb made the point, “It means James knew his son was like him. That James couldn’t handle knowing his son was going to go his own way weather he like it or not. It means he left you because he saw himself in you and gave you off first. Hoping you would be the last bit of what James hated about himself gone forever”. Deb held a breath then closed, “…and for the record, James didn’t die, he had to fly” Johnny slammed down his glass with a huff, “That was good!”  With a bolt to the top of the kitchen table Percy’s chest crashed with mass force. Everything he heard from Deb was killing him. His eye’s tearing up from the heaving of his back, his bones grinding and bending, his center muscle beating with a speed that would kill and pro athlete. Percy’s second wing was about to make it’s grand opening. Johnny laughed and with a scutter ran down the hall snapping open the front screen door, across the porch and hopped down off the second step to the rocky stoop. He was on his bike before you knew it rounding the house at top speed squealing with delight at his big brothers new evolution and soon to be the best playmate he was ever to have. Deb sat looking on. There was no point in helping him right now. He had to feel it. He had to go through it because that’s just how it went. She saw James go through it and saw how he felt. James’ wings took longer then Percy’s to come through. Like father like son in this case, it takes forever to find things out. But at least you get there she thought. Johnny knew right from the beginning. He was a smart kid, but still a kid and always would be. His wings were in her and on him and Johnny never had to worry about the transition.  Percy took hold of the table edges and bared down. The wing was out. Gray and boned, a giant skin covered skeleton. With a few snaps and cracks, its twin matched the feathered wing. The new addition opened to its full height. Feeling the skin spread from the pores where the small bird hairs bore, he felt the new large feathers of his first wing move out like rapid trick daggers. The bouquet of crystal silk plumage made the crack sound of ice in a thaw while it set into place with the other wing. Percy’s bones shifting harder now. Moving around taking steps only Martha Gram could pull off. His left ear to the table, face blue from empty lungs. Wide mouthed with veins in his forehead packed with blood to their limit. Deb moved further back from the table. Percy pushed with his feet to the floor to gain traction to his chest on the table to control the tectonic movements of his body. With a deep hollow yell, a long grunt and quivering whine, he took in the breath. Air, feeding his muscles and brain, all stopped. The wings fell to either side of table limp, Percy’s body calming, his chest beating through his ribs to the table. Deb was use to this by now. Her son, then husband and now this beautiful young man. Was it ever going to end? She had seen much since her son was born. The town of Seal Cove wasn’t a place where much took place except in her home. No one would ever know or believe what spectacular happening just happened. She wrapped her arms around Percy, the first woman he’s felt since he found his grandmother and she the first woman ver he felt other then that of his foster mother. Deb was strong, her arms tight to the sleeves of her sweater. She pulled the kitchen chair back into place from where he had kicked from his jolt forward Percy was a limp head of lettuce and Deb propped him straight in the chair before she got him to his feet unsteady. She was there for him. Turning down the hall to the front door. Crossed over the wood panels of the porch Deb got Percy to his backend. His legs hanging over the porch hunching still, not from pain or numbness, just tired. “It’s going to take him sometime learn these wings” she thought. Johnny came whizzing around the starboard side of the house with his wings ready and willing. Johnny zoomed, “Is he ready?”* 
     
    
</post>
</Blog>