<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today I spent most of my day at home after my adventure outside my house at 9am. Skipped the Mediquiz training, I did not want to ruin my holiday by not doing things for myself. In view of the SRS project, I searched pet shop after pet shop, nursery after nursery, and I finally found CATNIP! I felt so accomplished after finally finding it, I guess the harder the journey, the more trying the process, the greater the satisfaction, the fanfare and ecstasy when the job gets done.  I spent the rest of the day contemplating, meditating, and shooting the heads off bots in Unreal. The day went by just like that as I thought of the mysteries of life. I thought about why people act the way they do, I thought about what my purpose on this world was, in the big and small picture, I thought of my past, pondered the present, and envisioned the future. In short I did a lot, a lot of deep stuff with myself.  Life has never been easy. If it was, why would some people choose to call it the greatest tragedy? Is it all but a mockery of death? However, why do some people come out of life as successful individuals with smiles on their faces, but the rest just fade away into the darkness, not making a difference.  The secret must therefore lie in the difference. How should difference be achieved then? We are all human, with two eyes, two ears, one mouth, one nose, and basically the same physical traits, though it cannot be said for some of us, of which my sympathies do lie, the larger human population is still very much physically alike, discounting faces. Hence the secret must lie within the heart.  If one looks at life as a hunt, it will be a hunt. The process will become the thrill of the hunt, and the goals will become the prey. If life was a cruise, the journey will be the rests between each trying port and pit stop. I have always firmly believed, that "Man creates, fate dictates", quoting myself, the thing is that destiny always begins, in one's hands.  The sacred Choice. To do or not to do. Very often we blame others for our failures, or we blame the world for being unkind, or we would curse fate and say that destiny is unjust. Are we being petty in this case? Have we actually thought about the choices involved. If one chooses not to come into this world, would we? If one chooses not to embark on the journey, would we? It is all about our own choices and the consequences they bear, not that the world owed us justice.  "The world does not owe you a living, after all it came first." Wise words from Mark Twain. We cannot blame anyone but ourselves for landing ourselves into predicament. To do so means to deny that we believed in our choices. Have we lost faith in ourselves by blaming everyone else? Why not make the best out of each situation? Why do we always look toward the negative, and forget that very often, the positive is within reach, by just stretching out our hands, we may grasp the honey of life?  I do understand that it is tough to look away from the negative, and reach out toward the positive. Though mathematically they are separated by one line, in life, that one line could embody a mile. The journey back may be tough, but it tests one's faith and strength. To hold on to the last moment is not just proving to yourself that you can do whatever you put your mind too, but it also celebrates the strength of the human spirit.  Why were humans not given the speed of the cheetah, the cunning of the wolf, the strength of a bear? We were compensated with something more beautiful than all of that. The mind. The mind is limitless and boundless. It is from there which the light bulb was spawned, it is there where world records are conceived, where theories are developed. Where comes such divine strength as marathon runners push themselves to the limit? It is truly the infinite power of the mind that embodies the true spirit of being human.   Think of light... And you see light.   In a child's mind, we see the beginnings of a destiny. We see hopes, wishes and dreams. Why do we seem to lose those as we grow up? Is it a bane or a boon to lose all those as we find our niche in the modern world?  As we become individuals, it becomes almost impossible to find someone else with exactly the same hopes, dreams and wants. Success is defined a million times by a million people. We try to seek other individuals with similar hopes and dreams, but we often realize that at the end of the day, the person in the mirror is yourself. You have to face your own consequences.  Hence the importance of thinking for oneself. I may sound very selfish here, but if we look into ourselves, we will realize that man, thought gifted with thought, is very selfish by nature. Who would not fight to protect their loved ones or possessions? It is selfishness that causes man to continually improve, to seek higher limits, to fight. To actually talk about universal love would be useless unless one knows how to take care of oneself.  It would be utter foolishness to mention about taking care about others, when one cannot even take care of oneself. Are you being considerate in that case, if you cannot help others take care of their problems in the end, but you give people false hope that you would by showing a helping hand? We see people who are so caught up in caring for others that they forget about themselves. Such is the beauty and the foolishness of the human being.   Do think before you act.   This brings us back to the mind again. With all our ideals, what is the use of determination and the aggressiveness to stand for our ideals when we can't think fulfilling them? We often get lost in this world and we begin to question our ideals as we get to know other people. However why do we find the need to question if belief is all that is and was required? We find the need to think about the ideals that we have, to see them for their realism, not their idealism. What are great ideals if we can't find a facet for them to be transformed into reality?   I feel very sad when I see people reaching out to others, but neglecting themselves in the name of their ideals. As they waste themselves away, I wonder if they would have enough time to see their ideals through.  The world is cruel. If one does not learn to think, then one has truly failed oneself, one's friends and families, one's hopes, and one's ideology.  I see myself 15 years from now, married with 3 children. I see myself with a networth of 30 million. I see myself a overworked, but happy man. I see my wife as a wonderful lady with the sophistication of a aristocrat, but who knows how to enjoy the simpler things in life. I see her as a wonderful cook, and I see many happy hours that I can spend with her in the kitchen, and playing her favourite piano pieces near a fireplace when it is all snowing outside. I see her as an intellectual lady with a beautiful mind of her own, who can give me logic, yet allow me to smother her with emotion.   I see...   Dreams. Hopes. Wants. What are they without making a move to realize them. What are they if one does not live, breathe, eat and drink the dream. What are we if we are not defined by them? Don't tell me two people have the same ideals, because at the end of the day, we are all unique.  Grow up if you have not. As one lets go of the past, roots oneself in the present and then embraces the future, then one can finally say, I am not dreaming, I vision. Clinging on to the insubstantial things, and you will know what they are, will not help you in one bit. Look around you. There are many lights, all you have to do is to reach out and grab one.  We come into this world not finding the perfect person to love, but learning to love the imperfect person.  To Huiwen, EQ, Joy, Deb, Fruz, ET:  My sword and service will lie with all of you, always.  To Ming, Chee, Qadir, Colin:  My good comrades, I look forward to battling alongside you guys, for a long while.   Have faith. Believe like you have never believed before.   </post></Blog>