<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink The Department of Homeland Security has raised the terror threat level today.  Tom Ridge, Secretary of Homeland Security, announced in a press conference today that the terror threat level has been raised because of credible evidence from numerous sources that al-Qaida is trying to attack key financial centers in NYC, Northern NJ and Washington D.C.  So what's different this time? Well several things:        This is not the usual chatter. This is multiple sources that involve extraordinary detail -Tom Ridge        Ridge has stated that the means of the attacks are truck bombs and or car bombs. Previously the means of the attack have not been stated.         Specific targets have been named.       For more information read the  urlLink press conference.     -Nick 
    
</post>
<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I found this interesting article while perusing the usual sites. I find the report similar to the way in which I look at the situation in Iraq. I encourage everyone to read the entire article as the man has been on the ground recently. Here is an excerpt:           These are painful observations for me to make, because in early April, I wrote on this page that the media had been underplaying the good things happening in Iraq, and were missing the potential for a turnaround.   I still believe the first part. But when I returned to Iraq in June, I found that the situation had deteriorated so dramatically that a lot of those good things have become irrelevant.    Entire article  urlLink here.    This article raises an interesting point, and that is that the mainstream media has an inability to accurately report the war in any fashion. The mainstream media has proven itself useless in the past few years, with its live coverage of the "War on Terror" and the wars in A'stan and Iraq. What we see on CNN, Fox, CNBC, or any other mainstream media outlets is not news, it is a sensationalized representation of events. Otherwise known as  entertainment.  What we see on these mainstream  entertainment  channels is not coverage from the "frontlines", no matter how badly Christiane Amanpour wants us to believe. Reporting from the Mustafa hotel in Kabul is not reporting from the "frontline". Reporting from the Green zone in Baghdad, is not reporting from the "frontline". Not to mention that the wars we currently face do not usually involve frontlines in the sense that most of us know. A'stan may be the exception here, but certainly not Iraq. The media would rather dazzle its audiences with footage of "Shock and Awe", than portray accurate reports from the ground, mostly because the "reporters" from the mainstream entertainment organizations are too afraid to report, that job is left up to a small group of real journalists searching for the truth. I must say though, it made for some good entertainment, just like going to the movies, grab some popcorn, a soda and recline. Nothing like watching Baghdad get pounded by precision guided missiles! Reminds me of the Fourth of July! Too bad none of the mainstream entertainment stations have the gall to show wounded soldiers, or wounded civilians. Instead, we may see a 10 second clip of a car-bombing with a 30 second analysis of the situation by someone who has never been in Iraq, let alone ever spoken to an Iraqi.  Part of the responsibility of the mainstream entertainment outlets, and if they want to be referred to as news outlets, is to address the credibility issues that they face. Selling stories through sensationalization is not a credible practice, nor is it respectable. And it should not be considered as either. An excellent example of such practice was the coverage of the Abu Grhaib prison scandal. At the beginning of the coverage the story was a testament to how powerful and important journalism is. However, as soon as the entertainment outlets got a hold of it, they did not let go, and they milked it for everything it was worth. This type of coverage distorts the overall picture of the situation. And does nothing for our troops on the ground. That is not to say the story was without merit, nor is it to say that it did not deserve attention, but what happened here is a prime example of a sensationalism of events.  The best that the mainstream entertainment outlets are good for is opinions, and even at that, they fall short. For an example of this, recall the 'debate' between Michael Moore and Bill O'reilly during the Democratic National Convention. In the 'debate', nothing but pure entertainment was accomplished. As an interesting sidenote, recall the hype that went into selling the Democratic National Convention, namely on CNN. The hype to sell the   Republican National Convention   has already begun.  This being said, it's not all bad.         For those of you who want to know what it is like to read real journalism, here is Daniel Smith's story,  urlLink  Iraq Diary  . You see Daniel was actually on the ground speaking with real people. This is part one of the three part series that will be out on my site. Check back for the next two segments. The story is beyond incredible. Expect an interview with Daniel in the weeks to come.  -Nick  
    
</post>
<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It appears that a journalist in Iraq has been arrested for his harsh criticism of the controversial Iraqi congress, which he said represented the Iraqi people in an "unbalanced way".  Here's a caption from the WP:   Baghdad, Iraq, Aug. 2 (UPI) -- U.S. forces arrested the press official of the Committee of Muslim Ulemas, Iraq's highest Sunni religious authority, after participating in a televised debate.   The whole article can be viewed  urlLink here.   Details at this time are sketchy. More info will be posted as the story progresses.  -Nick      
    
</post>
<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       The war in Iraq has proved to be a distraction from what's going on in Afghanistan. Important to note is that the Iraqis are watching the situation in A'stan carefully. The reason being is this; A'stan is similar in many respects (however, starkly different in some) to Iraq.  Reasons A'stan and Iraq are similar:      Removed two regimes from power     </post></Blog>