<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>


     

      I just wanted to let the world know that a "smashingly wonderful girl" (AKA my girlfriend) has recently posted her blog for everyone to see at the following URL.  Please check it out and leave her lots of nice comments!  URL:  urlLink http://www.laurenwalters.com/blog/blogger.html 

     

    
</post>
<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>


     

      Well, today has been a long hard day--as can be expected during this time of the year with the local governments scrambling to spend their left over budget funds before they disappear at the end of the fiscal year.    Why the government operates this way is beyond me.  You could rest assure that if a business were to operate in this manner, they would have been out of business before they even opened up.  Where is the incentive?  Put yourself in the shoes of a regional government agency's administrator and think about it.  What person in their right mind would  not  spend the left over money?  Why let it go back into the State's general fund when all you have to do is spend the money to keep it local?  I don't know about all of you fine folks out there in the internet ether, but I would much rather the money that I worked hard for--to give to the government--be left alone in my bank account then spent because a government admin "had to."

     

    
</post>
<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>


     

      When I was taking one of my advanced web design classes at  urlLink IS, Inc.  in Sacramento, the person teaching the class--a Mr. Rob Huddleston--directed us to one of his pet internet projects.  His page is still a work in progress, but it has some pretty good content for people looking to pickup some odds n' ends for basic web design and  urlLink Macromedia  products.  For example, on the site you can find some links to older versions of various web browsers, which is very helpful for those of you who are designing your websites to look good in browsers such as Netscape 4.0, etc.  My favorite use for this website is the convenience of checking on when the next  urlLink Sierra Macromedia User's Group  Meeting is.  I can never remember the web address for some reason and it is easier for me to remember  urlLink http://www.universityofhtml.com  then it is to remember  urlLink http://www.sierrammug.org/ ...don't ask me why.  Anyway, check out the website and, if you get a chance, check out the classes that Rob teaches at IS, Inc.  He did a pretty good job at teaching the class and it was definitely worth the time and money.  URL:  urlLink http://www.universityofhtml.com  

     

    
</post>
<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>


     

      How is it that  urlLink Dilbert  can capture the essence of what it is to be in IT so well? Sheer genius--that's all it can be.     

     

    
</post>
<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>


     

      What a wierd format...  Sometimes I wonder who at Microsoft thinks up this stuff.  Today has been such a long day, and I can't wait to hit the sack.  This weekend is graduation weekend here in Chico (Go  urlLink Chico State !) and the bars are going crazy!  Graduating Seniors--and their parents--going crazy at the local bars.  Sometimes when I see this it makes me think back to my last semester at college--last Spring Semester (May 2003).  It seems so long ago now, as I have moved on to the working world.  No more staying up every evening until one or two a.m.  *sigh* 

     

    
</post>
<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>


     

      Well, it’s 5:00pm and lucky for me it has been a pretty low key day.  In the IT industry, Friday’s are a kind of a reprieve from the utter chaos that takes place during the earlier part of the week.  Today, my wonderful girlfriend came by my work and brought me by some delicious  urlLink low carb  sandwiches—which was a really nice surprise, and I had a chance at looking into starting a  urlLink Chico Macromedia Users Group .  For those of you who are into web design and web application development, and are not familiar with  urlLink Macromedia Dreamweaver , you need to check it out!  

     

    
</post>
<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>


     

      Be sure to remember this site!  I am currently working on a redesign of this site for the HRA to take it from bore to  score .  Five years of web design study and I finally land my first job--owwwww!  Lets see if I can pull it off.  *sigh*   URL:  urlLink http://www.hra.co.glenn.ca.us 

     

    
</post>
<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>


     

      Well, it all began when I first heard the word  blog  on  urlLink http://news.google.com/  about two weeks ago.  Then, everywhere I looked it said  blog  this, and  blog  that until pretty soon I couldn’t take it anymore—I decided to get a blog of my own.  So, here it is.  My first blog posting and boy is it ever lame. –lol.  Please bear with me while I try to make this into something pretty cool and try and get as many other suckers—I mean  bloggers —to join the ranks with me.  Stay tuned!

     

    
</post>
<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>


     

      It has been such a long time since I last made a posting to my  blog !  Once again I have proven my realist thoughts correct and I have dropped the ball on keeping an updated journal.  The good news is that I'm a changed man!  Lot's of postings from now on...I swear!  Why do you all have that look on your faces while you read this?  Why am I seeing the look on my readers faces...?  Hmmm... =|

     

    
</post>
<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>


     

      What a great weekend! For the Memorial Day weekend, my girlfriend Lauren, and I went and spent Friday thru Monday in beautiful Monterey, California. The weather was gorgeous, the scenery was beautiful, and the experience is one that I will never forget.   Friday evening, after I got off of work, Lauren, my cousins Jim and John, and I set out for Monterey at around 6:30pm. We didn't end up getting into town there until about 10:30pm as it is about a four and a half hour drive from Orland, plus we stopped and ate dinner--and some ice cream--along the way.   The next morning we got up and ate breakfast at a Denny's that was just down the street from our hotel room. As we didn't book our tickets until Wednesday night, I think we got one of the last rooms in town. We stayed at the Best Western Park Crest Hotel which was located up on a hilltop near the downtown area of Central Monterey. It was a nice and clean hotel--even though I believe it was definitely overpriced for what we got. I know what you're thinking, "What could I expect from a hotel booked two days before Memorial Day Weekend?" Well I tell you, I expected more... =)   Denny's was nice and filling and gave us the fuel we needed to move on and see the  urlLink aquarium  that Lauren had been excited to see before we had even left Chico. It was rediculous how many people were jammed into the aquarium. They must have oversold the tickets by at least double. All and all it was a pretty cool place though.   -------------------------------Fast forwardin time to July 24th, 2004.   OK, so it's been a little while since I've worked on this blog posting. My website stopped working for a while and I just now finally have gotten the chance to get it fixed so this posting is a little our of date. =)   In all, this was a really fun trip and besides the fact that I put the first scratch on my car =( everything went perfectly. Anyway, time to move on to new postings!     

     

    
</post>
<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>


     

         Microsoft has once again pushed back its release date for its new  urlLink Windows Update Service  (better known as WUS), which is soon to replace the current  urlLink Software Update Service (SUS) .  This much anticipated server management software will have all kinds of new features including advanced reporting tools, support to update all Microsoft Products (including MS Office, etc.), advanced network optimization, including a grip of other tools that will make a network admin's job  a lot easier.    urlLink Here is the whitepaper that talks about WUS's new advanced features.   Speculation is still growing as to when WUS will finally be released.  Early reports put its release at sometime late last month but it is obvious that it never occurred.  Now the release date has been scheduled for sometime in the 3rd Quarter of 2004.  This could mean anytime between June and October before we see the first version released to the IT community.  Currently, the beta has been released and for those who don't mind being on the  bleeding edge of technology , this might not be such a bad idea.  For those of us who like to err on the side of caution (especially since it could mean exposing large number of computers to security risks) we may still have a long time to wait until any usable version becomes available.    URL: urlLink http://www.microsoft.com/windowsserversystem/sus/wusbeta.mspx  URL: urlLink http://www.microsoft.com/windowsserversystem/sus/default.mspx  URL: urlLink http://download.microsoft.com/download/d/c/b/dcb4332c-f9b8-4e65-9ce8-d93b3e5323e6/WinUS_Datasheet.doc    

     

    
</post>
<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


     

         It's finally here! The day we have all been waiting for--Friday!  The  urlLink Democratic National Convention  closed with a bang last night with  urlLink John Kerry's speech  which promised big things. The speech was well delivered and definitely worked the convention crowd into a frenzy. I think that the Democratic Ticket is extremely smart for not campaigning on core liberal ideologies but to instead campaign on the mainstream thought.  What I mean by this is that  urlLink Kerry  took the approach of being a patriot, rather than a political dissenter. His message, "Stronger at home. Respected in the world." is an awesome political statement that George W. Bush will have to put down quickly if he wishes to make any kind of progress on the campaign trail in the near future.  The one thing that Kerry's speech lacked was personal accountability for his past actions.  urlLink His campaign promises sounded great; however, the ideas put forward are the polar opposite of what his past actions show.  For example, John Kerry voted for the authorization on the use of force in   Iraq  , and in the first senate debate John Kerry strongly supported President Bush's actions there. He has been quoted as saying, “George, I said at the time I would have preferred if we had given diplomacy a greater opportunity, but I think it was the right decision to disarm Saddam Hussein, and when the President made the decision, I supported him, and I support the fact that we did disarm him.” Now Kerry is running as the "Anti-war" candidate. The Republican Party is right to refer to him as a "Flip-flopper."   urlLink Here is another excellent link that summarizes in a table the issues that Kerry has done a 180 on.   John Kerry is a politician--there is no doubt about that. What I would like to see though is a candidate who campaigns on issues that he/she truly believes in. Not on what might, or might now, get them elected.  I was perusing one of my daily reads (www.wired.com) and came across an article that linked me to one of the  urlLink funniest political cartoons I have ever seen .  Make sure you check it out.  It targets both sides of the aisle perfectly. -lol.  Well, I am going to cut this posting off for now but I will write more to my fellow internet bloggers out there in the ether when I get a chance!   URL: urlLink http://www.dems2004.org  URL: urlLink http://www.johnkerry.com/pressroom/speeches/spc_2004_0729.html  URL: urlLink http://www.johnkerry.com/index.html  URL: urlLink http://www.georgewbush.com/kerrymediacenter/read.aspx?ID=2439  URL: urlLink http://slate.msn.com/id/2096540/  URL: urlLink http://www.jibjab.com   

     

    
</post>
<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


     

         Finally the week is starting to fall in place. The software bugs at work are beginning to work themselves out of the system--who knew that the  urlLink Altiris  software could somehow fix itself over time--and the Helpdesk phone calls are beginning to slow down.    The final night of the  urlLink Democratic National Convention  is starting to wind down and I am definitely looking forward to what the Democratic Presidential Nominee  urlLink John Kerry  will have to say tonight. I am really hoping that he gives a speech of substance and gives us--the viewer--a clear picture of what his presidential policies are going to be. I might not necessarily like what he has to say but I always respect political figures who give the listener something to think about. Those politicians who leave the audience scratching their heads (i.e. most speakers so far at the DNC) leave something to be desired.    I'll definitely have more to say after I watch the Convention tonight...  Stay tuned.     URL:  urlLink http://www.altiris.com   URL:  urlLink http://www.dems2004.org   URL:  urlLink http://www.johnkerry.com    

     

    
</post>
<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


     

       Last night I saw a quick sound bite on the nightly news where  urlLink Ted Kennedy said ,  "In the depths of the Depression, Franklin Roosevelt inspired the nation when he said,” The only thing we have to fear is fear itself." Today, we say the only thing we have to fear is four more years of George Bush. "    What a joke. It seems extremely trendy for people today to bash George Bush based on his stated idioms, and his personality. Instead of meeting the President head on about the issues that are affecting this country the Democrat's tactic has been to target Bush's personality traits.   For example,  urlLink Ted Kennedy compared George Bush to the English  who "ruled by fear, by force, by special favors for the few." He talked of revolution against our nation's current administration who is supposedly holding our country's proud citizens down by instilling fear in each and every one of us.   </post></Blog>