<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      5th round played jeslin then won....6th round played liu yang...then damn farnie..jason waas asking me to draw wif her..then after some persuading, i drew wif her....7th round played FM terry chua(lolx...)n won quickly...8th round played wif a cheap guy....from the start onli play for my time:(in the end two pawns up...then b cos of time,everything screwed up:( n i lost...i was lyk going to cry??i was lyk cannot b lief it...nvm....its over liao...last rd played wif darling's mei n won quite quickly....i think she dont noe the opening well?? in the end tie for 6th wif gabriel, sean n my 8th round opponent RICHARD LEAN...got onli 37$$(suppose to b 37.50!!!)  luckily found my wallet from the front office..but when i open the wallet all the money gone:( the winnings of my tournament not even half of my money lost:( nvm...at least the things r still inside:P...  cool!!!u r oming back tmr liaoz..hope to hear ur voice soon:P
     
    
</post>
<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      tournament sux....1.5 wth manz...won christer, lost shaobin,draw gabriel(arranged) n lost to han wei....wth manx..feel damn screwed....  then afterwards found out that i lost my wallet....(again.....wtf.4th time)this time worst...tmdwtf....feeling so screwed...  in the car, my father was scolding lyk mad.....play so badly still go n lose my wallet......ask me to go n die...:'( i cried silently. feeling damn hurt...i dont think i can go out anywhere during this holiday...hav to mug lyk mad:( my father say my studies sux.....might as well quit everything n gnd....wth manx....its not lyk i screw up exams all the time:(... yah....my father was also saying how stupid can i get..... wtf manx....cannot take it anymore....  feel so hurt....not b cos my father slap me....its the words he use on me:(  wad should i do.....someone plz tell me... 
     
    
</post>
<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      sianz...todae no skool so stsy at home slack.  carn b lief tmr is National Rapid le!!!:( haven prepare well enuff(i think sure die liaoz)must play damn well to meet my target of at least 7!!i think that is quite hard as all the players r damn strong!!nvm...as long as i try my best...i will b satisfied.  no....mr tu still haven tell me who is that..he only hint to me that she played may li in the indivs.....how come mr tu lyk that one??nvm.  when r u coming back....i need to talk to u....dying for ur voice liaoz.... for the past 4 daes i hav been missing ur voice loads...most importantly i miss u lyk mad... xh, i need u!!where r u now??:'(
     
    
</post>
<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      todae last dae of skool....played chinese chess as usual. then suddenly this chinese chess teacher pop in n told me that i m in for the dunno wad tournament!!!wth...its lyk crazy...i dun reali want to play one:( stupid teacher lah...nvm:(   after skool went to play bb at dover...me dary1 alanNO.1 n dt went to challenge some fairfield pple...then in the end got thrashed badly:(  NOOOOOOOOOO....i feel that i cant study anymore...i lost my touch:(...wad  am i doin now???argh...my father was scolding me lyk mad:(  hahaz...my father called u AH HUAN(i think)...i was laughing lyk mad....hehez. it was damn funny!!!damn cool rite???  hope to c u soon!!!
     
    
</post>
<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      xh....i want to talk to you...i miss ur voice.   how r u doing now?? is ur team winning?? dont give up k..."the best is yet to be":P(lolz!)  i really miss u liao...nv get to hear u this few daes, i felt terrible:(....felt very restless...  hope to see u soon!! just wanna tell u....i love u always,no matter wad.
     
    
</post>
<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      xh, u r just in my mind all the time. i cant stop thinking abt u.    *muacks* i love u loads!!!i will love u even more as time goes by....
     
    
</post>
<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      last night was damn farnie...i put on my msn nick "brandon said that someone is damn CHIO...while the others beg to differ" he was lyk damn funny....lolz. This was soon stop when bk put on his msn nick "weiCheng said that he n xh together...wc,change ur nick b4 i complete this sentence" i was larfing lyk crazy....lolz...  school was quite boring today.....spent the whole time playing bb n chinese chess!!! Quite cool...got a few "students" to teach...they all super joker,alwaes make patzer moves....lolz  sighz...school ended juat lyk that. went to KAP wif frenz... soon come home le...  sianz....when will i get to c u again?? so long:'(  i love u loads!!!i miss u lyk crazzyyyyyy!!:(  hope to see u soon...i m looking forward to seeing u.(and my present!!!lolz:P)  
     
    
</post>
<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      cool!!! today after assembly walked to NUS to watch C div tennis finals between acs(i) n RI... damn cool.....while i was walking ard....nth to do, then suddenly i saw my "sworn" brother Sean!!! he was lyk damn shocked...(me also lah!!!)yah then we talk for a while n continued to watch the finals...obviously our school won coz we hav the under 18 1st n 3rd player in our school, matthew n hala tan(lolz).  walked back to school went for recess....not much of a recess actually,was lyk PE......played bb for lyk 1hr++. in the end was late for class:(   after goin to class,greeted the teacher...i sneaked out of my class n went to 2.4 to play chiness chess!!!cool manx...2.4 class teacher was damn blur!!thought that i was one of the student of tt class...i was lyk okok....,i m in ur class...:P hahax!!  after school when going home, i saw ailin on the bus!!!i was lyk huh???quite shocked... nvm...i think she nv see me...soon she alighted somewhere at clementi (sunset way???)i finally reached nanyang...while i was waiting at nanyang for a straight bus home, i saw this chi chess player i played in the last tournament...he just waved at me for a while and continued to look serious???okok....got onto the bus, the bus stopped at opp coronation plaza....i saw jeslin!!!i was lyk omxh...how come today see so many pple one!!!nvm. she was damn dao anywae....  reach home liao....so decided to blog.....  Darling....can u hear me??i want to tell u i miss u!! how r u doin now??   rest well for ur tournament....hope u hav fun there!! rem to buy me sth:P 
     
    
</post>
<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      my results sux.....everything sux....especially me!!!:(:(:(  
     
    
</post>
<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      sianz..tmr is NAG liaoz. very scared that i will screw up lyk anything:( ......
     
    
</post>
<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      joshua loh sux big time......hate him.hate him.hate him.hate him. wanna kill him!!! wad the fuck man...after winning a tyco game against me and my bro....go n boast n boast n boast.....wtf! its not lyk he so pro lyk that.... he sux lorh....if without gabriel, he would be at a total lost position.fuck him....fuck him....GO TO HELL JOSHUA....  later in the "chessu cs competition" me n my bro against nat JOSHUA n jace... joshua lyk tyco tyco kill me or my bro then start calling us losers...also go n boast to nat n jace..."did u guys see that!!!" wad the fuck lorh...its lyk he got the LEAST kills, still go n boast ard....wad the fuck....he think he super noob at cs lorh...normal kill he go n say until headshot....its lyk 90% lorh...i wanted to slap his face n ask him to kiss my asss....wad the fuck siax...   fuck fuck fuck.....joshua is a FUCKER....fuck off n go n die....
     
    
</post>
<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      xiu huan......5201314.......
     
    
</post>
<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      chinese chess tournament sux lyk shit....dunno wad i playing also:( for the stupid team event scored 5.5/7(soso).wasted lyk dunno wad...give free pieces away lyk dunno wad but tycoly manage to get a draw!!! sighz... the blitz thing is the worst....6.5!!!( out of 11 :(  ) wth..,dunno play wad also...tech foul three four times also i never claim....then in the end lose lyk mad:( wth...   y am i so loser????????????????????sian ar....xiuhuan i need u badly:(    龍捲風 Long juan feng  Composer: Jay Chou (周杰倫) Lyricist: Vivian Hsu (徐若瑄)  愛像一陣風 ai xiang yi zhen feng 吹完它就走 chui wan ta jiu zou 這樣的節奏 zhe yang de jie zou 誰都無可奈何 shei dou wu ke nai he 沒有妳以後 mei you ni yi hou 我靈魂失控 wo ling hun shi kong 黑雲在降落 hei yun zai jiang luo 我被它拖著走 wo bei ta tuo zhe zou  靜靜悄悄默默離開 jing jing qiao qiao mo mo li kai 陷入了危險邊緣 xian ru le wei xian bian yuan Baby~ 我的世界已狂風暴雨 wo de shi jie yi kuang feng bao yu  Wu~~~~ 愛情來的太快就像龍捲風 ai qing lai de tai kuai jiu xiang long juan feng 離不開暴風圈來不及逃 li bu kai bao feng quan lai bu ji tao 我不能再想 wo bu neng zai xiang 我不能再想 wo bu neng zai xiang 我不 wo bu 我不 wo bu 我不能 wo bu neng  愛情走的太快就像龍捲風 ai qing zou de tai kuai jiu xiang long juan feng 不能承受我已無處可躲 bu neng cheng shou wo yi wu chu ke duo 我不要再想 wo bu yao zai xiang 我不要再想 wo bu yao zai xiang 我不 wo bu 我不 wo bu 我不要再想你 wo bu yao zai xiang ni  不知不覺 bu zhi bu jue 你已經離開我 ni yi jing li kai wo 不知不覺 bu zhi bu jue 我跟了這節奏 wo gen le zhe jie zou 後知後覺 hou zhi hou jue 又過了一個秋 you guo le yi ge qiu 後知後覺 hou zhi hou jue 我該好好生活 wo gai hao hao sheng huo   http://www.jaychoustudio.com/jaychoustudio/translations.html#
     
    
</post>
<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      sianz...cannot sleep...cant stop thinking.  愛情懸崖 Ai qing xuan ya  Composer: Jay Chou (周杰倫) Lyricist: Vivian Hsu (徐若瑄)  妳說我像一個小孩 ni shuo wo xiang yi ge xiao hai 總愛讓妳猜 zong ai rang ni cai 我說妳才像個小孩 wo shuo ni cai xiang ge xiao hai 總要我說才明白 zong yao wo shuo cai ming bai 有些事太快 you xie shi tai kuai 失去了等待 shi qu liao deng dai 障礙 zhang ai 沒了期待 mei liao qi dai 我們的的愛 wo men de ai 怎麼才自然 zen me cai zi ran 每次溝通不來 mei ci gou tong bu lai 就要離開 jiu yao li kai 就說不要愛 jiu shuo bu yao ai  我掉進愛情懸崖 wo diao jin ai qing xuan ya 跌太深爬不出來 die tai shen pa bu chu lai 下降的速度太快 xia jiang de su du tai kuai 來不及踏上未來 lai bu ji ta shang wei lai 妳的愛反覆徘徊 ni de ai fan fu pai huai 打亂我呼吸節拍 da luan wo hu xi jie pai 該怎麼逃開 gai zen me tao kai 我控制不來 wo kong zhi bu lai 我掉進愛情懸崖 wo diao jin ai qing xuan ya 回想起妳的可愛 hui xiang qi ni de ke ai 傻傻的還在等待 sha sha de hai zai deng dai 以為妳還會回來 yi wei ni hai hui hui lai 妳的臉慢慢離開 ni de lian man man li kai 時間快將我掩埋 shi jian kuai jiang wo yan mai 消失的太快 xiao shi de tai kuai 我負荷不來 wo fu he bu lai 
     
    
</post>
<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      sian ar.....later still hav to go for some chinese chess competition:(....so long never play liao sure get whack lyk dunno wad...  past few daes play bb n golf lyk mad....now legs lyk dead liao/...then afterwards still hav to go play bb wif my bro.  dont care ar....must do as many things as possible....time is veri precious!!!  saw sean n family jes now...talking abt world youth n nat age group:(......i wanted to cry liao....argh....y i lyk that one?????????????   說不上為什麼 shuo bu shang wei shen me 我變得很主動 wo bian de hen zhu dong 若愛上一個人 ruo ai shang yi ge ren 什麼都會值得去做 shen me dou hui zhi de qu zuo 我想大聲宣佈 wo xiang da sheng xuan bu 對妳依依不捨 dui ni yi yi bu she 連隔壁鄰居都猜到我現在的感受 lian ge bi lin ju dou cai dao wo xian zai de gan shou  河邊的風 he bian de feng 在吹著頭髮飄動 zai chui zhe tou fa piao dong 牽著妳的手 qian zhe ni de shou 一陣莫名感動 yi zhen mo ming gan dong 我想帶妳 wo xiang dai ni 回我的外婆家 hui wo de wai po jia 一起看著日落 yi qi kan zhe ri luo 一直到我們都睡著 yi zhi dao wo men dou shui zhao  我想就這樣牽著妳的手不放開 wo xiang jiu zhe yang qian zhe ni de shou bu fang kai 愛能不能夠永遠單純沒有悲哀 ai neng bu neng gou yong yuan dan chun mei you bei ai 我 wo 想帶妳騎單車 xiang dai ni qi dan che 我 wo 想和妳看棒球 xiang he ni kan bang qiu 想這樣沒擔憂 xiang zhe yang mei dan you 唱著歌 chang zhe ge 一直走 yi zhi zou  我想就這樣牽著妳的手不放開 wo xiang jiu zhe yang qian zhe ni de shou bu fang kai 愛可不可以簡簡單單沒有傷害 ai ke bu ke yi jian jian dan dan mei you shang hai 妳 ni 靠著我的肩膀 kao zhe wo de jian bang 妳 ni 在我胸口睡著 zai wo xiong kou shui zhao 像這樣的生活 xiang zhe yang de sheng huo 我愛妳 wo ai ni 妳愛我 ni ai wo  想 xiang 簡！簡！單！單！ jian! jian! dan! dan! 愛~~~~~~~~~~ ai~~~~~~~~~~ 想 xiang 簡！簡！單！單！ jian! jian! dan! dan! 愛~~~~~~~~~~ ai~~~~~~~~~~ 
     
    
</post>
<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      sianx..  try to do lotsa things to keep myself bz...but dont seem to work.i just cant concentrate...   才離開沒多久就開始 cai li kai mei duo jiu jiu kai shi 擔心今天的妳過的好不好 dan xin jin tian de ni guo de hao bu hao 整個畫面是妳 zheng ge hua mian shi ni 想妳想到睡不著 xiang ni xiang dao shui bu zhao 嘴嘟嘟那可愛的模樣 zui du du na ke ai de mu yang 還有在妳身上香香的味道 hai you zai ni shen shang xiang xiang de wei dao 我的快樂是妳 wo de kuai le shi ni 想妳想的都會笑 xiang ni xiang de dou hui xiao 沒有妳在我有多難熬 mei you ni zai wo you duo nan ao (沒有妳在我有多難熬多煩惱) (mei you ni zai wo you duo nan ao duo fan nao) 沒有妳煩我有多煩惱 mei you ni fan wo you duo fan nao (沒有妳煩我有多煩惱多難熬) (mei you ni fan wo you duo fan nao duo nan ao) 穿過雲層 chuan guo yun ceng 我試著努力向妳奔跑 wo shi zhe nu li xiang ni ben pao 愛才送到 ai cai song dao 妳卻已在別人懷抱 ni que yi zai bie ren huai bao  就是開不了口 jiu shi kai bu liao kou 讓她知道 rang ta zhi dao 我一定會呵護著妳 wo yi ding hui he hu zhe ni 也逗妳笑 ye dou ni xiao 妳對我有多重要 ni dui wo you duo zhong yao 我後悔沒 wo hou hui mei 讓妳知道 rang ni zhi dao 安靜的聽妳撒嬌 an jing de ting ni sa jiao 看妳睡著一直到老 kan ni shui zhao yi zhi dao lao 就是開不了口 jiu shi kai bu liao kou 讓她知道 rang ta zhi dao 就是那麼簡單幾句 jiu shi na me jian dan ji ju 我辦不到 wo ban bu dao 整顆心懸在半空 zheng ke xin xuan zai ban kong 我只能夠遠遠看著 wo zhi neng gou yuan yuan kan zhe 這些我都做得到 zhe xie wo dou zuo de dao 但那個人已經不是我 dan nei ge ren yi jing bu shi wo 
     
    
</post>
<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       回到過去 Hui dao guo qu  Composer: Jay Chou (周杰倫) Lyricist: Liu Geng Hong (劉耕宏)  一盞黃黃舊舊的燈 yi zhan huang huang jiu jiu de deng 時間在旁悶不吭聲 shi jian zai pang men bu keng sheng  寂寞下手毫無分寸 ji mo xia shou hao wu fen cun 不懂得輕重之分 bu dong de qing zhong zhi fen  沉默支撐躍過陌生 chen mo zhi cheng yue guo mo sheng 靜靜看著凌晨黃昏 jing jing kan zhe ling chen huang hun  妳的身影 ni de shen ying 失去平衡 shi qu ping heng 慢慢下沉 man man xia chen  黑暗已在空中盤旋 hei an yi zai kong zhong pan xuan 該往哪我看不見 gai wang na wo kan bu jian  也許愛在夢的另一端 ye xu ai zai meng de ling yi duan 無法存活在真實的空間 wu fa cun huo zai zhen shi de kong jian  想回到過去 xiang hui dao guo qu 試著抱妳在懷裡 shi zhe bao ni zai huai li  羞怯的臉帶有一點稚氣 xiu qie de lian dai you yi dian zhi qi  想看妳的看的世界 xiang kan ni de kan de shi jie 想在妳夢的畫面 xiang zai ni meng de hua mian 只要靠在一起就能感覺甜蜜 zhi yao kao zai yi qi jiu neng gan jue tian mi  想回到過去 xiang hui dao guo qu 試著讓故事繼續 shi zhe rang gu shi ji xu  至少不再讓妳離我而去 zhi shao bu zai rang ni li wo er qu  分散時間的注意 fen san shi jian de zhu yi 這次會抱得更緊 zhe ci hui bao de geng jin 這樣挽留不知還來不來得及 zhe yang wan liu bu zhi hai lai bu lai de ji 想回到過去 xiang hui dao guo qu  思緒不斷阻擋著回憶播放 si xu bu duan zu dang zhe hui yi bo fang  盲目的追尋仍然空空盪盪 mang mu de zhui xun reng ran kong kong dang dang 灰濛濛的夜晚睡意又不知躲到哪去 hui meng meng de ye wan shui yi you bu zhi duo dao na qu 一轉身孤單已躺在身旁 yi zhuan shen gu dan yi tang zai shen pang  
     
    
</post>
<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i felt lyk crying after those words... i m at a lost of words....dunno wad to say...  i really cared abt u!!!  nvm....i will love u still no matter wad happens!!!
     
    
</post>
<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      sighz...feeling shitty.i tried my best liaox...stilll just cannot forget....:( WEICHENG SUX BIG TIME!!!  XH....5201314??!!!
     
    
</post>
</Blog>