<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   This is a blog about my thoughts of everything I'm interested. Let's enjoy~ 

						
</post>
<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Got Milk? urlLink    

						
</post>
<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    AB형의 일반적인 성격      AB형들의 기질은 A형과 B형의 혼합이라고도 생각할 수 있지만 단순히 두가지 기질을 나타낸다고 보기보다는 사람에 따라 외면상으로 A형 혹은 B형 기질 중 하나가 나타나게 된다는 점이다. 그리고 그 양상도 A형과 B형이 끊임없이 부딪쳐 새로운 성격을 만들어 내고 있는 것이다.    AB형의 기질을 살펴보면 우선 합리적이다 . 그래서 사회의 의리나 인정 그리고 기타 제도 등에 대해 관심이 적고, 합리적인 반듯함을 선호하게 된다. 또 합리성으로 인하여 분석력이 뛰어나 비판 정신이 강하고, 그 뒤에는 현실을 바탕으로 한 객관성이 있다. 그래서 대부분의 AB형들은 자신의 인생관이 뚜렷하고 자신의 일에 대한 충분한 타당성을 가지고 있다.   그러나 AB형을 1 대 1로 접촉해 보면 의외로 부드럽고 사귐성이 강하게 느껴진다. 또 AB형은 간곡한 부탁을 잘 거절하지 못하기 때문에 친절한 사람으로 보인다. 그러나 시간이 지남에 따라 타인에 대한 거리감이 뚜렷하게 드러나 다른 사람들의 아쉬움을 사기도 한다. 이는 AB형이 사람들을 신뢰하지 못하고 또 자신도 절대적인 신뢰를 받으리라고 생각하지 않기 때문인 것 같다. 전체적으로 AB형들은 다른 형에 비하여 장점을 많이 가지고 있는 편이지만 크게 성공하는 사람은 적다. 이는 AB형이 마지막 순간에 주저앉거나 포기하는 것, 즉 모험을 회피하는 데 이유가 있는 것 같다. 또 이러한 경우 잘못을 남에게 전가하는 것도 AB형의 단점 중의 하나이다.   This is me...so close...that even scares me...-_-;;; 

						
</post>
<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    me, myself  BR31... urlLink    

						
</post>
<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    puss in boots cuty ver. of shrek2  urlLink    

						
</post>
<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Today I’d like to make a short speech about learning Latin. First, how much do you know about Latin? Most of you will answer don't know any. But in fact you already know plenty of them. 'animal, index, rumor, maximum, minimum, arena...' Who isn't familiar with these words? Yet all are Latin words taken over into English without change. Latin was mother language of the Romans who lived in Rome.  Usually we say Latin is dead language (and it can be true in speaking ways.) But the influence of the Romans and their language spread over most of Europe and the Near East.  Many modern languages, including English, reflect this influence. (Some will say again, "O.K. Latin has something connected with English, but the time learning for Latin I may pay more time for studying English!" Yes, that's kinda true. But if you hear the hidden benefits of learning Latin, you'll change your thoughts.) Then what can be the benefits of learning Latin? In first, abbreviations we are using are full of Latin like A.D., AM, PM, Ph.D., e.g., etc… so if you know the meanings of them, you can use those more fluently. There are lots of words in English and it's hard to memorize all of it one by one. Using Latin can make you guess the meaning of the word just by morphemes. For example, let's pretend you don't know the word ‘aquarium’ means. But as you know ‘aquarium’ is constituted with ‘aqua’ and ‘arium’, so if you already know ‘aqua’ means ‘water’ in Latin and ‘arium’ means ‘a place where the thing mentioned is found’ in Latin, you can guess ‘aquarium’ as a place related to water. It also can be used just the same on post(after), sub(under), astra(star), sola(sun) etc…  Like this, to guess meanings which you don’t know, Latin can be used to solve these problems. There a lot more that I didn’t mentioned. I’m sorry we don’t have much time for this.  Well, as we can see even though Latin is a dead language knowing or not we are already using lots of words from Latin. If you realized how Latin makes English more easy to those who want to learn English deeply, why don’t you try learning it? It’s still hard work but it’s worth it. [Gratias vobis ago!]  

						
</post>
</Blog>