<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      For a start I chosed to do General Power  what is the best sport for that other than Bodybuilding...  a program of 6 days a week with 1 day of nagative rest...  I'm enjoing that :D    Day One: Chest/Calves/Abs  Chest • Pushups: 1 warmup set • Incline Bench Press: 4 Sets x 10, 8, 6, 6 • Flat Bench Dumbbell Press: 4 Sets x 10, 8, 6, 6 • Flat Bench Dumbbell Flyes: 3 Sets x 12, 10, 8 • Pushups: Immediately following the last set of dumbbell flyes, finish the chest with one set of pushups to failure  Calves • Donkey Calf Raises: 4 Sets x 20, 15, 15, 12 • Standing Calf Raises: 4 Sets x 20, 15, 15, 12  Abs • Hanging Leg Raises: 4 Sets x 20, 20, 20, 20 • Rope Crunches: 4 Sets x 20, 20, 15, 15 • Dumbbell Side Crunches: 4 Sets x 20, 20, 15, last set to failure      Day Two: Legs  Legs • Bike: 5-10 minutes warmup  • Squat: 4 Sets x 12, 10, 8, 6 • Leg Press: 4 Sets x 10, 8, 6, 6 • Leg Extensions: 3 Sets x 10, 8, 8     Day Three : Hammer Throw  • 7 kg Hammer (12 Throws)     Day Four: Biceps/Triceps/Abs  Biceps • Seated Preacher Curls: 4 Sets x 12, 10, 8, 8 • Standing Dumbbell Curls: 4 Sets x 10, 8, 8, 6 • Dumbbell Hammer Curls: 3 Sets x 10, 8, 8  Triceps • Skull Crushers: 4 Sets x 12, 10, 8, 8 • Close Grip Bench Press: 4 Sets x 12, 10, 8, 8 • Cable Pushdowns: 3 Sets x 12,10, 8  Abs • Cross Body Crunches: 4 Sets x 20, 20, 20, 20 • Decline Reverse Crunch: 4 Sets x 20, 20, 15, last set to failure      Day Five: Hamstrings/Calves  Hamstrings • Bike: 5-10 minute warmup  • Stiffed Legged Deadlifts: 5 Sets x 12, 10, 8, 8, 6 • Lying Leg Curls: 4 Sets x 12, 10, 10, 8 • Standing Leg Curl: 3 Sets x 12, 10, last set to failure  Back • Wide Grip Pull-Ups: 3 Sets x to failure each set • Bent-over Barbell Rows: 4 Sets x 12, 10, 10, 8 • Seated Cable Rows (close grip): 3 Sets x 10, 10, 8  Calves • Donkey Calf Raises: 4 Sets x 20, 15, 15, 12 • Calf Raises on Leg Press Machine: 3 Sets x 20, 20, last set to failure      Day Six: Shoulders/Traps/Abs  Shoulders • Barbell Shoulder Press: 4 Sets x 12, 10, 10, 8 • Arnold Dumbbell Press: 3 Sets x 10, 10, 8 • Front Dumbbell Raises: 2 Sets x 10, 10 • Side Dumbbell Raises: 2 Sets x 10, 10  Traps • Barbell Shrugs: 4 Sets x 12, 10, 10, 8 • Upright Rows: 4 Sets x 10, 10, 10, 8  Abs • Lying Leg Raises: 4 Sets x 20, 15, 15, 12 • Crunches: 3 Sets x 20, 20, last set to failure    By the way I didn't make this training program I toke it from a website so God Bless the internet as I always say :)
     
    
</post>
<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The Season has been over for me too early  I toke 2 weeks of nagative rest...   now back to workout my body parts...  It will be a very tuff summer for me because I'm planing for an intensive program starting August...  Here We Go...  START :)
     
    
</post>
<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm going to extend this program for another week because work status...  I'm going to know if I'll work on shifts during July or not. If not I'll change my training program if yes it will be the same until August.
     
    
</post>
<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Amonth agoit was a dream yesterday was a vision  today IT IS REALITY.   Every human been on this earth should follow his dreams  plan for it so it becomes reality  in between there is vision to see where u r going to be NEXT!   Well today was a BIG day for me  a dream come true but I changed my dream to a BIGGER dream  my vision still see that I can be there sooner or later :)   I'll just   KEEP ON DREAMING KEEP ON VISIONING  MAKE ALL OF THAT TO REALITY.   
     
    
</post>
</Blog>