<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have a new piece... I just finished it a minute ago... I hope all the people that this piece is about know that they are included in my thoughts...   My Friends...  My place is dark… and my sky is gray… But I caught the glimpse of a star today… The void grows smaller… with each moment gone… As twilight ends… just before morning’s dawn… This moment is rare for people like me… Who travel lonely paths to their destiny… Deep down in my soul… I am not so sad For companions surround me… and for this I am glad… Their paths are all different… no two are the same… Except for the fact that they all shout my name… It is them who have given me all of my hope… They have taught me to love… and help me to cope… With the tears in my heart… and the scars in my mind… And one thing is certain… they won’t leave me behind… It is they that I thank for my happiness too… For without them… I don’t know what I’d do… It is you who have shaped what I have become… I have you all to thank for escaping the glum… Not all of them are with me today… Some had left me behind when I drifted away… But the few that I have are my most cherished friends… Who’ll remain in my heart until my end… They’ve given all this hope to me… I’d die for them… So they may see… Another day to glance at the sky… And the ghost of their dreamer flying high… You who stood by me for 8 crazy years… You with your blue coat... always in good cheer... You with your heart in the stars up above… You with your kindness made me fall in love…  You who I teach the Dreamer’s Song… You who I laugh with all day long… All of you gave me the wings to fly… You’ll remain in my heart til the day that I die… I hope that you all will remember these days… That I shared with you… and showed you my ways… 
     
    
</post>
<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Another story to pass on as I continue my journey... Hope you enjoy...   Dreams Will Never Die  The world can turn it’s back to you…  But Dreams will never die… The darkness and corruption can consume your soul… But Dreams will never die… Your hopes can wither and rot… But Dreams will never die… Your life as you know it can drift into nothing… But Dreams will never die… A starry sky can be shattered into oblivion… But Dreams will never die… You may… never be… with the one you love… But Dreams will never die… You can lose your faith in what you believe… But Dreams will never die… You may choose to let go of your dreams… and give up… But Dreams will never die… You cannot forsake the dreams that you make… For Dreams will never die… Even if you wish they did… Those Dreams will never die… They will follow you until the end… That takes a lot to understand… They will follow you till the day you die… There is no use to question why… Don’t ever give up… don’t even try… For those Dreams will never die… You can try to forget them… deny that you know… But deep in your mind… they forever will grow… And they won’t stay in your mind… they will drift to your heart… Where they will open the door… or they will tear it apart… Your Dreams are essential… in your soul they will bloom…  But if they never come true… your mind they’ll consume… They will bring tears to your eyes…As your heart slowly dies… With no one around to hear your pathetic cries…  This is my malediction… my terrible curse… My Dreams pass me by… and the going gets worse… But the world melts away when I look to the sky… With the song in my heart that sings… “I will fly!” And one day I will have it… one day I’ll find love… And again I will see… my stars up above… This is my devotion… This is my ideal… It may not be inst… and it may not be real… But I’ll follow these until my lonely demise… This is the faith that has opened my eyes… A world without boundaries… a world without walls A world without limits… if you answer the calls...  This is the place that I will belong…  On Chronia they sing the Dreamer’s Song… And though it is only fiction to you… In my heart… I know it to be true… That one day it will come to me… Fate’s evil sword… KwaL na’z Theli And with my blood it will shine anew… The Crimson Blade of Dreams… Shi-Teku… So here I stand… alone and apart… Waiting for what lies in my heart… A door to yet another world…. With new thoughts and hopes and dreams unfurled… And so the saying goes along… As I sing my Dreamer’s Song… “No matter how shattered… or broken they are… Your dreams in the darkness… are a shining star… And no matter how hopeless… your Dream’s you’ll achieve… If you hold true to your faith… and in your heart you believe... You’ll drift across oceans… You’ll touch the sky… You’ll pass through the ages… Never caring why… For your Dreams will never die…"  As long as you believe… And I Do… 
     
    
</post>
<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is the beginning I guess... this is the gateway from my world to yours... or at least part of it... I welcome all of you... I might as well begin with the reason why I made this... I need a place to store my writings so that people can see them... since Poetry.com is money grubbing, and has limited space I've decided to come here... Well here are the first 3 pieces to join this maiden voyage...   The Thoughts of A Dreamer  As a dreamer stands tall...  Alone and shattered he wanders... Always drifting in the wind... Always falling towards his fate... Struggling to find his destiny Fighting the loneliness in his heart... What future is there to come…? For one who has seen the pain…. Who’s lost in the eyes of society... And trapped in the void Forever lost in his soul. I must always wonder... Starring up at the stars every night Is there truly a place for me? Will I find my fantasy? Is there truly destiny? Is there truly love for me? Will I ever be free? For many long years I've dreamed of these things... Searching for the truth Yet always finding deceit... Trying to step forward But pushed back so far Where is the place in time...? Where darkness ends... And light begins... The day I find identity... And one day find true destiny... That day shall come to me some time... But for now I must always wonder... When... Where... How... Who...? Such things have always journeyed my mind Yet I feel so broken... Battered down by my past Through the ages I drift... Waiting for the answers I may never find... Hoping for the dreams that may never come... Yet I still stand strong... Never losing faith...   Another Day...  Another day to dream a dream...  Another day the stars don't gleam... Another broken soul to mend... Except my own... it shall not end... And so I look up to the sky... With hopes that one day I will fly... And that one day your world will see... This thing that I call destiny... But it is here I still remain... With fragile dreams that I obtain... Someday you just might understand… The task I put into my hands… Of Chronia you hear me speak… It is this world to which I seek… I pray this world shall remain safe… For in Chronia I place my faith… To escape the pain of society’s blight… It is in this dream I find my light… And though I cannot see my star… Inside my dream’s it’s never far… I hope that I return to her… And prove that I’m not just a Dreamer… But here I stand, alone and cold… With dreams not shared, and thoughts untold… But I swear! All is not in vain… Although my life is endless rain… I have a few who stand by me… Who opened their hearts and set me free… These are the few who gave me wings… And show me the happiness your world brings… Even they do not understand… It is I alone who comprehend My Dreams, my Fate, my Destiny… And all the things inside of me… So I remain the only one… To know the truth to what I’ve begun… Human, or Chronian… no difference to me… For I believe in both you see… I am on Earth each passing day…  But on Wings of Time I fly away… As Casartello of the Human race… And Dynedockia of Chu’Bwa Ku’ Space… Two entities exist inside… They are my passion, they are my pride… My heart will heal, my mind has grown… As I slowly drift into the unknown… It does not matter wherever I go… For in my soul I shall always know… There’s always tomorrow… that’s when it may come… And the race against Fate has finally begun…   This is Our World  War is among us… and slowly losing cause… This is our World… We sit back and watch as our children are sent off to die… This is our World… Our society reeks of Corruption… This is our World… The mainstream floats to the top,  as the idealists, the visionaries, the dreamers,  and the different people of this world  slowly drown in their wake… This is our World… Our minds are filled with greed,  And we constantly search for glory, for power, for more… This is our World… We discriminate towards so many,  “They are inferior to us, and don’t deserve the same rights we have” This is our World… Where people stand up and fight the system,  But are battered down by the sheer mass of the opposition… This is our World… We cannot change society… for it is far to big for it to change in whole… This is our World… Through Fire… Justice is Served… This is our World… Even when the odds turn us away, one will still step forward and face society… This is our World… One will let go of his feelings as an outcast,  and open his eyes to the ways of the Dreamer… This is our World… It is I that shall be the one… With clear mind, open heart, and dreams that shall change this world… This is our World… A mainstream has learned to free their minds  and slowly accept the thoughts and ideas of a Radical Dreamer… This is your World… You have all slowly grown… in your own ways… and in your own aspirations…. This is your World… As we slowly travel into tomorrow…  You will all move into the future with strong foundations, And Minds ready for whatever it may bring… This is your World… And as we head towards that day, we stand strong,  Ready to fight whatever the world puts in our way… That is our World… While you spent your days growing up… One was left behind… That was my World… A poor soul who never really got the chance to fit in… That was my World… A boy who’s good nature was forgotten, or worse… never known… That was my World… Until now… Beyond the pain I have felt… lies a place beyond all sorrow… That is my World… A place that has shaped my destiny…  and forged the dreams that lie deep inside my soul… That is my World… In the Galaxy of Chu’Bwa Ku’… on the distant world called Chronia… That is my World… Of Hawk Dynedockia… the Master of time…  And Fate… which cast him away… with the words…  “You are nothing but a dreamer… Fool.” That is my World… And So I wait… and I dream… and I believe in tomorrow… This is my World… With Companions who I hope shall help through the journey that is our lives…  That is my World… We march towards the future… with eyes looking to destiny… Let it be a fulfilling one for all of us… That is our World!  There we are...  Enjoy... and please feel free to add a comment, I enjoy the feedback!  Through Fire, Justice is Served!  No matter how shattered... or how broken... or how impossible they may be... Dreams never die... as long as you beleive.... and I do... - Hawk Dynedockia 
     
    
</post>
<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm in the dreaming/emotional mood I get into sometimes... hehe... I saw some stars tonight too... I've been waiting so long to see them... I've also been thinking of what I might use for a sig... wrote this a little while ago... hehe -  Whether I spend a lifetime with you in my arms... of If I die a lonely death... Know this... I'd give it all up... I'd die If I had too... just to see you smile... One more time... I Love you... and I always will... No Matter What...  Given the right music I might end up crying... lol... well Back to dreaming... and stargazing... = D
     
    
</post>
<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have finished a new piece.... hehe... enjoy:   A New Age: Not Yet...   A new age has come… and the world around me has changed once again… my life is taking an unexpected turn… Towards the society I once feared, I march… yet I am welcomed with open arms… an idea never thought possible in my mind… New friendships are born… and dying love is once again full of life… I have reached the first of my dreams… Life… I stand before people who once despised me… and hold hands with those who once feared me… Laughter echoes in the night… and I continue to dream into the mornings… every night, dreaming of Finding my faith… binding with destiny… and my love for Kid… as I always have… but not something comes to my mind… something new… something unexpected… something… wrong… I dream of the end… of the final moments of the war I will face when I return to Chronia… I see the final battle… I see… the final blow… as thrust Shi Te’ku forward into the belly of Fate… and as his corrupted form falls to the ground… as the battle around us ends… and the forces of Chronia stand tall in triumphant victory… it is the end…but I cannot see that… not now… not yet… How can I Dream of the end of my Path… when I have not even begun my journey…? I shake my head… yet it still drifts there… haunting me… I cannot look to the end… when I have not yet even begun… as I continue to wait for the day that my paths begin to combine… As I wait… I am faced with my curiosity… No one has told me of the Fate I dream… of the Path I have given myself… there are no signs… no visions… just a dream in my soul… What do I wait for? What is the cause of my journey….? What will the sign be… That tells me that Destiny has begun… and that I should begin my quest to find KwaL na’z Theli… Where do I go…? El’ Bah’Nok does not exist in this world… and I cannot hear the cries of the forgotten soul… but still I will go and search when the time is right… I will go to the ends of the earth and find it… but another obstacle now lies in front of me… My friends… my companions… the people I love… What do they say to my journey… to my destiny? What will they choose to believe… And the hardest thing to think about… will they come with me? For so many years… beyond the blindness of my pain… and my loneliness… this trial would be faced by me alone… but they were not here with me then… does the journey change now? Maybe this was not meant to be only my path… maybe it is the ever growing arms of destiny that have led these people to my side… Maybe it is for them to face too… in their own ways… It is too late for them to turn away… for their souls have intertwined with mine… at least I hope they have… My faith is in their hands now… what they choose to do, and to believe… will affect the story… especially one… Kid… Much of this rests on her…on her choices… on her beliefs… on her faith… So the fate of a Chronian rests in the hands of Humans… Being one of them… I find it ironic… that those controlled by time are linked to the one who controls time… So I must sit back and wait… and follow the currents of life… until the time is ready… and the true journey begins… I will not give up… no matter what happens… but I know this… If They are with me…. If She is with me…. If You are with me… I cannot fail…
     
    
</post>
<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was bored so I re-did Shi Te'Ku, Now it's a little more like that way I visualize it... although it's still not quite right... oh well... = D urlLink     urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Ok everyone (Jav here) this is a little thing I had to do for my friend Shayla. She did all the artwork for my story Perfect Symphonies (which will be continued soon) So I decided to show some artwork that she does. When I scan my character artwork for my story, I'll post that too. (This is clism. A character from her story Black Ice. See the story at www.shaylart.com If you want the full sized wallpaper, contact me via e-mail) urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Should Have mentioned it Ealier... heh... Javier is going to be posting his work up on here now.... I'm having it so anything that has -Javier after the title is his, and if it doesnt have that it's me (Plus it'll say posted by Javier Guevara, or The Crimson Dreamer) well enjoy his work... And Don't take up too much space Jav... = P  Anyone else who has anything that they might wanna put up, just email me or im me... Well I've always wanted to say this... - TCD out = P
     
    
</post>
<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well... Here is a Bigger Picture of the Blade of Dreams (Or the best I can do with MS Paint... = P) to the right. Is what it looks like in the beginning as the soul stealing KwaL na'z Theli, and on the left, it's latter version, ShiTe'ku  urlLink     urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
                                          Choose to take the journey of self-discovery…  In a parallel world, but in similar times, the world of M’iel (me el) has a more laid back way of life (More forests, less cities, and relative peace.) Classic tales of groups of young kids who set out to journey and change the world are still told to the young. Enter our main character Toboe (toe bow A), who has always been enthralled by these stories. He decides to make a similar pilgrimage, but on his own accord. Of course it was easy for him to do it because he was orphaned since his parents died when he was seven. His brother Taita (tie sha) however, has lived with his aunt and uncle since that faithful day, when he was taken out of his mother when she was dying. (Toboe never lived with his aunt and uncle because they despise him, even though he doesn’t know why) Toboe is all about making choices, whenever someone would ask for advice from him; he believes that you should never be bound to the words of a man who doesn’t know your true aura inside. He made the decision to go on his own so that his journey was his own passage (he hasn’t trust many people since that summer day.) His plans changed forever when he went to say goodbye to his brother, and he saw what awful things his relatives were doing to him. Toboe rescued him and let him choose whether or not he wanted to escape his life and go with him. After long thought, Taita decides to travel with Toboe and see the world for what it is.  Now as for me, I’m Vigo, (Veego) the narrator of the story (Don’t think that I don’t play an active role in this story though, I know your dying to see me in action.) Enjoy the story for what it is and enjoy Toboe’s many adventures of the wondrous world of M’iel filled with magic, charm, and romance. Also remember what Vigo says, “No matter where your travels take you, you’ll always end up on top.”                               Perfect Symphonies                                Chapter 1   "Wake up Toboe!" A voice from far off called. It had to be his annoying friend lance, who always brought him away from his daydreaming. "What do you want Lance?" Toboe said in a dejected way. "Well, what I want is for you to get up off the ground and come to the forest with me so we can get our job done before the head mistress gets restless." Toboe slowly rose from his once vegetate state, and then gently stroked his hair. He sighed knowing that today was going be another boring day in his meaningless life. Lance and Toboe made there way into the forest to cut some firewood for the fireplace so that all the kids in the orphanage could enjoy some extra heat as spring quickly was dawning on the peaceful town of Almott. You see, Toboe and Lance are the oldest people in the orphanage, (with the exception of the head-mistress) so they took it upon themselves to be the big brothers of all the children.  Toboe and Lance chopped some wood and decided to go to the waterfall before taking the wood back. "I don't understand you sometimes." Lance said jokingly. "I'm not sure I follow you." Toboe said. "Well for starters, it's the middle of winter and you decide to go to the waterfalls. Also, it's dead of night and all you're wearing is a long-sleeved shirt." "Nowadays, I don't feel things much. Inside me mentally and physically, so there's no need for me to use much needed clothes from the kids. Besides, I'm not going to go swimming; I'm going here to think about things. "What could you possibly have to think about? There's not much to do in our life besides helping others, and running around annoying people."(How true)  Lance was confused beyond all belief. He thought that Toboe has been acting rather strangely lately. He's been a lot quieter, not as social, and he seemed to be depressed or that he had something important on his mind. Now you have to be a little dense to not see what's wrong with Lance. (I will explain) Lance is a very plain person; he believes that all he sees is what is real. Sometimes, his "tunnel vision" constricts him from seeing the real problem within like in Toboe's situation right now. "That's exactly it Lance! We don't have anything; our possessions are also the possessions of the orphanage." Toboe started getting exited in his reasoning "So that supposed to make us happy?" Lance still didn't get it. (idiot) "Well no, actually yes, it means that we aren't being manipulated by greed for more like most other people. There is only one thing that we possess, that no one else can possess." "And that would be..." (His ignorance amazes me.) "The freedom of our imagination, the freedom of life, the freedom of life. No matter what, no one can deprive us of that." "That's some deep stuff Toboe." Lance finally got his thought. "I don't know though, sometimes it's not enough. I just wish that there were something more to life than this." Toboe suddenly lost all of his excitement and started to fall into a depression. "Come on now Toboe." Lance went over and grabbed Toboe's arm. He dragged him to the special spot under the water-fall. It was the special place that all the orphans would go to in the summer. They sat on a rock and thought hard about their life. "You're lucky Lance." 'No you are the lucky one Toboe. You had your parents until you were seven. I never knew mine at all. They must have really hated me to just up and leave me like that." He began to cry. 6/21 to be continued 
     
    
</post>
<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I finally figured out how to put pics on my site ^_^   urlLink    Let There be Freedom  Be Peace in This Land... And I swear by my Dreams that This Darkness shall end! Fate is A Demon... He'll pay for his crime! And I'm not just a Dreamer... I'm the Master of Time!!!!  urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      haha... I'll laugh if someone reads this before I change it... but what the hell... I've got a new poem on the way... Ill keep the name disclosed for the time being... I dont want to spoil my own fun... *cocks the gun* lol... well anyway... This is probably my favorite piece so far... I hope you all like it when it's ready!  *UPDATE* Ok it's ready!   Kid...   The clock ticks forward day by day… And my mind is still so far away… In the world at which I want to be… To continue to forge my destiny… But something crossed my path in a way…  That brought sunlight to a cloudy day… In my aching heart deep down inside… In the old void where my dreams collide… There were no more clouds and no more rain… No more sadness and no more pain… So now I am free of that terrible place… And who do I thank? Who’s the one I embrace? The girl who showed me the stars tonight… And helped me escape my lonely blight… Who is the girl that I’m talking about? Take a wild guess… you’ll figure it out… Called an Angel by them for the things that she did… But to me, she is rascally known as “Kid”… Kid I’ve admired for so many years… As I recovered my soul, and overcame fears… She has changed my world, the girl that I love… My only true link to the stars up above… The world is a desolate place without her… But she is the answer, she is the cure… To the worst of pains; a broken heart… Cracked open wide… and torn apart… With her laugh and her smile the pain is gone… And with that the darkness withers to dawn… I dream of a day when you’re by my side… Hand in hand on our wings we will stride… It is only a dream… as much as that sucks… The idea causes my emotions to flux… But again Kid is there, and she has the brass… To give what I needed… a good kick in the ass… She woke me up from that evil nightmare… And awoke me into a place where… That dream doesn’t matter if comes or not… Because our friendship exists and that matters a lot… I drift through the ages dreaming of you… With soul so pure… and heart so true… And of the day that finally she… Will find her wings and fly with me… From a lonely world that writhes in pain… Away from the clouds… away from the rain… To an Azure sky… and a Golden sun… This dream to me has more than begun… It is real to me… as the life that I live… The air that I breathe… and the feelings I give… So what do I see as I turn to the sky…? I see us… up there… flying high… With the wind in our faces… and the stars up above… The clouds at our feet… and our hearts filled with love… We’d race across oceans… We’d drift in the breeze… We’d soar up the mountains… with our souls at ease… Nothing else matters when I’m at her side… Just the song in my heart… and my eyes opened wide…. To the dreams in my soul that one day we may share… In this whole new world that I’ve started to dare… To dream of a future… where Fate is dead… What a beautiful thing I’ve got in my head… You’ve taught me so much in the last 4 years… But there’s one thing you taught me that brings me to tears… No matter what happens… I believe in you… Because the way that I see it… Dreams really come true…  
     
    
</post>
<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      After getting a wakeup call, I wanted to finish The End in a more... positive way... Im sorry to everyone who thought I was feeling really bad... I just got caught up in some stuff... hehe... Well thank Initial D, and Telling off that old bitch (Haha, ask me about it, it was nice) for getting my mind off it, and then gettin yelled at to finally break the chain... Thanks kid...  Heres Part One to prevent confusion  The End...  I stand atop the highest plateau… waiting for the clouds to open… I think I can see them… the stars…I… I have spent my lifetime waiting for this day… And now its finally here… the void inside me is going to close… close forever… My thoughts… my dreams have brought me to this day… and now it is time to say goodbye to an empty… lonely world… As I look up… I can see it… the break in the clouds… a crack to the outside world… a doorway to freedom… The time is right… and I sprout my wings… and take off…  The clouds still roar with thunder…and lightning still dances across the sky… The time will soon come when I enter the clouds… and the maelstrom above… It is then that I must concentrate…  The black ground below slowly disappears… and the grey mist of the clouds surrounds me… as I continue to fly upward… I can feel the winds getting stronger… but I must press onward… The darkest part of my world is here… it is the core… the center of my confusion… my chaos… it is what keeps me from escaping… until now… I can see the opening… and as I race for it… I am chasing by lightning… a demon refusing to let go of its vessel… Closer and closer I get to reaching my goal… the strength of endless dreams and desires fuels my raging fury… it is so close to me… suddenly for the first time in a lifetime… I see the light of the sun… I am almost there… I am almost free… but the gap slowly begins to close… I must reach it in time… before I am too late… Energy surges through me… and my wings press through the gale winds… I am going to make it! I feel warmth inside… The light passes onto my skin… And I can feel the warmth of its light… as I pass through the barrier… and before I can look up... Time stops… My hand reaching out… to you… you the one who has made it possible… I can see you there… it is too bright to see your face… but I can see your eyes… staring back at me… I am free I know I am… I see your hand motion towards me…but then my eyes shut… I cringe in pain… confused… I remain there frozen… unable to move… only my eyes… and as I look down to the horror… A spear impales my chest… a spear with the emblem of… an angel… it is… yours… unable to breathe… I can see myself beginning to fall… my body falls backward… towards the barrier that is the void… the last of you I see… is your face… no longer shrouded in darkness… smiling… laughing… as you walk away… this world disappears.. and the only things I can feel inside are the surge of pain from my heart… and the tears falling from my eyes...  I see the sun… the oh so beautiful sun… rising into the sky… just as the opening to what would set me free… closes in front of me… I continue to fall… I leave behind a trail of dead feathers… and tears… my wings slowly begin to wither and die… and the winds of the maelstrom… throw me across the plains… soon the clouds stretch across my view… as I break through their grasp… feathers chaotically drifting in the winds… my hand still reaching out… as I hit the ground… with a skull shattering blow… The plains roar with thunder… and it begins to rain… my body is broken… my soul is shattered… my wings are lifeless bones on the ground under me… but I feel nothing… not the cracks in my skull… not the raindrops falling on my face… mixing with the tears of blood falling from my eyes… just the pain of a spear impaled through my dying heart… and Fate… watching me from above… laughing… but I am not to die this day… my malediction is much worse… I am doomed to exist for eternity… with broken bone and shattered will… glaring up at the sky… as it rains down upon me...  my hand still stretch out… out to you…   and Part II - The Beginning...  It’s time to open my eyes. There’s more to this... there’s got to be... There’s more emotion elsewhere... and I’ve seen it... and I’ve brought it back with me... There is so much pain... but I can’t let go... not of the world I created… even if I never see it... it’s still mine to command! And with that I make another choice.. with a little yelling of course.. It’s time to let go of this spear... and forget the past... its time to start living in the future... the way I did back then... and so I place my hands on this spear that I have driven into my soul... and I grasp it firm... and with all my strength... well lets just say it FUCKING hurt! Anyway... with that... I could feel my body changing... and the void around me... the rain stops... and the cracks in the rocks begin to slowly repair themselves... so this is truly my heart... As I feel my body once again I slowly make my way to my feet... and with a snap of my hands... the pain is gone... there is no more hole in my body… and the cracks in my skull are gone... Everything makes sense again… and now I realize... I must go. If Fate won’t give me a way out... and with a mere thought, the feathers on my wings again flutter in the wind... I’ll just have to make my own! And with that I give myself a running start... with the speed of Hawk Dynedockia I burst into the horizon... It’s time... I know now that the time is right to leave this place... my wings spread and my eyes focused on the sky above, I speed up the largest plateau... the same one I began my journey on... and with my last look of the plain below me, I took off into the maelstrom.  The winds do not falter my speed… as I race through the clouds above... I can see the end... the barrier... Fate’s hands are stretched out before me...  With the thought, the spear that had pierced my body comes to my hand. The sorrow and pain this whole void, in essence lies in that spear... and with all my strength,  of the powers of every moment in time... past... present... future... combine into one, I thrust it forward into the clouds in front of me… and the hands of Fate Shattered today... I fly through the barrier out of this void... victorious... As I take the first breath in a brand new world, the spear still flying forward in front of my transforms... out of the shadows, and out of the sorrow... comes the greatest blade ever forged... the reborn blade of KwaL Na'z Theli... Sword of Dreams... Shi-Teku... and as I grasp my forgotten blade... I feel my soul deep down inside... I am Chronian once again... I have won my first battle... in the war against Fate... but I do not stop in the world above… I press onward… into the sunny sky… into the stars… Into space… I dream once more!  Towards Chronia! Towards Destiny! And I have you… the one who threw that spear… no… you who have given me the start I needed so many times… when my mind is caught in the snare of pestilence… you are there to let it loose… time and time again... thanks kid...  
     
    
</post>
<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      New work... and if your worried, Im not depressed or anything, though my writing would say otherwise right now...   My World...   There is place far away from here… a place beyond any horizon… beyond your sight... beyond your comprehension… It is a dark place… an endless plain of black rock… cracked and jagged… and above, only clouds… dark grey clouds with lightning coursing through them.  It is always raining… There is nothing… nothing at the end of this horizon… nothing… but one… a dark figure… soaked in water… in tears… in blood… Frozen to his soul… as he stands against the rain pouring down on him… This darkness… this pain… this… is the void… this… is my world… and that figure… with tears in his eyes… and a fist full of blood… is none other than the Crimson Dreamer himself… I am that man… that shell… with nothing inside me but this world that I see around me… Many times have I tried to escape this place…  but as I break the boundaries of it, Fate intervenes… and I tumble back down to this dark earth… There is nothing here… and no one… so I much walk these plains for eternity… with nothing to set me free from this burden… but wait… in a flash of light this world is gone… and I am in another place… your world… where I am with all of you… my friends… and we talk… and we laugh… and we exist… together… l stand here too… facing the sunset… with wings drifting in the breeze… hand in hand… with the one I love… but then another flash of light… and I am in a world I have never seen… standing before Fate… My Crimson Blade in hand, ready to fight the battle that is my destiny… but my eyes open… and I am once again in the never ending rain… they are all just echoes…  in my mind… These are dreams… dreams that are never going to come… love that will never blossom… destiny that will never come to pass… This is the world that I must live in every day… with the tears of loneliness in my heart… and the blood that bleeds from my soul as I am battered down by society… It is so cold here… and there is nothing to keep me safe… to keep me warm… to keep me happy… I have lost it all to Fate… but it does not stop me from dreaming for another day… To stand up tall in the pouring rain… cold… sad… and lonely… and Dream of a place where this world does not exist… Where I hold my beloved in my arms… and where I truly fly on my wings of time… but then I wake up from the dream… and the day begins again… There is nothing left and nowhere to go… there is no more song in my heart… there is no more skip in my step… just the aimless path that I walk in this place…. Hoping to find something… or someone… so each day passes me by... another lonely day is over with… and a new one is here in its place… Think not of this place… but that shouldn’t be too hard for the oblivious children of earth…
     
    
</post>
<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just finished another piece... I don't think a lot of people are going to like this one... but here it is... A good song to go along with it is No More Words... by Ayumi Hamasaki The first minute or so of it specifically    The End  I stand atop the highest plateau… waiting for the clouds to open… I think I can see them… the stars…I… I have spent my lifetime waiting for this day… And now its finally here… the void inside me is going to close… close forever… My thoughts… my dreams have brought me to this day… and now it is time to say goodbye to an empty… lonely world… As I look up… I can see it… the break in the clouds… a crack to the outside world… a doorway to freedom… The time is right… and I sprout my wings… and take off…  The clouds still roar with thunder…and lightning still dances across the sky… The time will soon come when I enter the clouds… and the maelstrom above… It is then that I must concentrate…  The black ground below slowly disappears… and the grey mist of the clouds surrounds me… as I continue to fly upward… I can feel the winds getting stronger… but I must press onward… The darkest part of my world is here… it is the core… the center of my confusion… my chaos… it is what keeps me from escaping… until now… I can see the opening… and as I race for it… I am chasing by lightning… a demon refusing to let go of its vessel… Closer and closer I get to reaching my goal… the strength of endless dreams and desires fuels my raging fury… it is so close to me… suddenly for the first time in a lifetime… I see the light of the sun… I am almost there… I am almost free… but the gap slowly begins to close… I must reach it in time… before I am too late… Energy surges through me… and my wings press through the gale winds… I am going to make it! I feel warmth inside… The light passes onto my skin… And I can feel the warmth of its light… as I pass through the barrier… and before I can look up... Time stops… My hand reaching out… to you… you the one who has made it possible… I can see you there… it is too bright to see your face… but I can see your eyes… staring back at me… I am free I know I am… I see your hand motion towards me…but then my eyes shut… I cringe in pain… confused… I remain there frozen… unable to move… only my eyes… and as I look down to the horror… A spear impales my chest… a spear with the emblem of… an angel… it is… yours… unable to breathe… I can see myself beginning to fall… my body falls backward… towards the barrier that is the void… the last of you I see… is your face… no longer shrouded in darkness… smiling… laughing… as you walk away… this world disappears.. and the only things I can feel inside are the surge of pain from my heart… and the tears falling from my eyes... I see the sun… the oh so beautiful sun… rising into the sky… just as the opening to what would set me free… closes in front of me… I continue to fall… I leave behind a trail of dead feathers… and tears… my wings slowly begin to wither and die… and the winds of the maelstrom… throw me across the plains… soon the clouds stretch across my view… as I break through their grasp… feathers chaotically drifting in the winds… my hand still reaching out… as I hit the ground… with a skull shattering blow… The plains roar with thunder… and it begins to rain… my body is broken… my soul is shattered… my wings are lifeless bones on the ground under me… but I feel nothing… not the cracks in my skull… not the raindrops falling on my face… mixing with the tears of blood falling from my eyes… just the pain of a spear impaled through my dying heart… and Fate… watching me from above… laughing… but I am not to die this day… my malediction is much worse… I am doomed to exist for eternity… with broken bone and shattered will… glaring up at the sky… as it rains down upon me...  my hand still stretched out… out to you… 
     
    
</post>
<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well... a little break from the ANA (A new age)  This is something I started writing a few months ago... and finally finished All I need is a name for the piece...  Here's to you Matt... It's been an honor to learn from the best... ^_^   My Mentor  (Named by anddedicated toMatt Sprotte)  My life’s journey continues it’s race…  But Now Arises a familiar face…  A man from days of forgotten glory…  Back when I began my story…  Back to an age when my dreams were just dreams...  When my heart was a hole... a void so it seems...  Before I saw the power I had...  Or the poet inside me... My writing was bad...  I was merely a Kid... lost in my tears…  With pain in my soul… haunted by fears…  But before I found love… I had an escape…  That was shown to me by a man with a cape…  He saw my potential… but I needed work…  And he stayed by my side when the others were jerks…  He taught me the ways of the people up high…  Who created new worlds in the blink of an eye…  An Adventurer’s fate could lie in his hands…  He’d decide their future… and give them commands…  To succeed or to fail in this game we play…  It’s life in this world… or so we would say…  But this game that we play’s not as hard as it seems…  As I focused the power that channeled my dreams…  I saw this world for what it really was…  Now I stand by his side… and it’s only because…  Of a man with the name that I call my own…  With the lesson’s he’d taught and the ideas he’d sewn…  Into my mind… and then they would sprout…  And I’d know what this creativity’s about…  I opened my eyes… and I set free my soul…  With the help of my mentor… I got out of that whole…  You set me down the path I take…  You gave me a chance to atone my mistakes…  You gave me the skills to continue along…  The Notes to sing the dreamers song…  So here’s to you my venerable friend…  Funny… and loyal to the end…  You’ll always be a mentor to me…  For you helped shape my destiny…  No one out there rp’s like you can…  King of the GM’s… my master… Matt-san!!!    
     
    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well...I've been a little slow with writin lately... but I did manage to pull of something... It's a bit small, and Once I get a clearer idea with it, I'll probably add more.  *Update* Added More ^_^   A New Age: Part Three   Each sees the world with their own eyes...  A point of view it seems... To which we all shall live our lives... and gaze into our dreams...  An uncommon sight exists in this world...  A vision owned by few...  A side of life with truth unfurled...  a Side you never knew...  Some say the world is a beautiful place...  Others say it's hell... Except for those who've seen this face... There is no way to tell... What is the truth about our ways?  Are we Savage and cruel?  Or is peace closer day by day and everybody's cool? To knowhow to solve the riddleyou  must seek these people out...  To findfolks out there like me too see what this is about... Find the "losers" of society who won't give up the fight... With open hearts they'll let you see Just whats inside this light... To see this world another way...  To look through troubled eyes...  And see this world is not so dark... Beyond Cerulean Skies...  Even when we reach our prime...  There are courses we won't understand...  but few of us will take the time...  to stop and try to comprehend...  What happens when we go and decide?  Take the path and see it through...  What future have we cast aside...?  Few if any will ever construe...  The other choice they might have made...  Be it good, or be it bad...  In most people's minds the thought will fade...  And forget the influence that they had...  To change this world with what they've done...  Really big or very small...  The difference between the whole and the one...  Who will open his heart... and in darkness... stand tall...    
     
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My newest piece... Take This assholes!(Before someone gets offended... That comment isn't referring to everyone...heheh... ^_^;;)   A New Age: Seeds of Corruption   Life continues… as time rolls by… With a soul to share… and wings to fly…. Always searching for something new…. Worlds to create… and things to do… This world to me is a beautiful place… But evil lingers beneath it’s face… Corruption’s hands stretch so high… From lowest lake… to starry sky… In the hearts of man this darkness hides… When man goes fourth and shows these sides… The kindest soul can turn on you…  And take your heart and pierce it through… This world is caught in violent debate... They think they rattle the chains of Fate… A society ravaged by hate and lust...  By abuse and drugs... by actions unjust... Look down below society’s line...  The people on the bottom of the grapevine... What happens to them if they wish to fly? Their wings are broken... and some of them die... From the cruelty and hate from the world up above...  While the rest down there have hearts filled with love... But still we are ravaged... and still we are mocked...  Our worlds must be cloudy... and our paths are still blocked… But still we will try to climb up those stairs…  Ignoring the insults… and returning the glares… But I don’t see corruption when I look to their faces… For we are the same in many many cases… I look away from the anger, away from the hate… For I am no longer bound by Fate… No longer drowning in tears of despair...  I can see the people that existed there... As I drifted through anger and cried to sleep... Falling and falling into the deep...  Of the void that was making a pit in my soul... And I would exist in that terrible hole... I am a victim of corruptions child… It took sanity… and made me run wild… But now they see me another way… Most of them are different today… They see me as equal… they see me as me...  They see me as I want to be...  A lover... a Dreamer... a kid just like them... Not a fool or a loser that they can condemn But still some refuse to open their eyes… And it is a shame that they won’t realize… What I have become… and what I will be… And the ideas and dreams they’d learn from me… So go ahead and put me down… Laugh in my face… push me to the ground… You think you are winning… but you’re very wrong… For I will still sing my Dreamer’s song… I will rise up above you… and make you pay… For the terrible things that you’ve done here today… To you I may not be where I am… Just the fool with the big mouth you continue to damn… But I will assure you… your going to fail… For I will still walk…and speak of my tale… I could be on step one for all that you care… But when I’m done everyone will want to be there… 
     
    
</post>
</Blog>