<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
            Wow! School is almost over. THANK GOD! Today was so boring... we aren't learning anything anymore (wait... we never did). In French for an hour and 45 minutes we cut out pictures from French Magazines and wrote parapgraphs on what we thought about there clothes, in French. How educational. Algebra... I must say it was interesting... Mrs. BJ talked about how she almost cut her ex-husbands girlfriend's hair off. However, I now have decided Mrs. BJ is a psycho path! Then creative writing... we played "Ask Mr. Useltoon Any Question You Want" the whole class. It was... different. Then Health... well that is that. I'm super excited about Who's Line tonight... me and Charisse are going to see it! Yay! Ugh... but yeah... speaking of which I better go get ready! 
      
</post>
<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Another Wednesday that I missed church because of Cheerleading. This is getting to be ridicilous! I've missed the last several Sunday and Wednesday nights because of it. But, well I knew it was going to happen when I started cheering. I just wish I could do both. I go to church every Sunday morning though. Darn, I wish I could go on a missions trip and help some little kids out. That would be so awsome. I was just reading in my devotions the other day about this guy that went on one and he gave these kids a rubberband and they were so excited. They thought it was the coolest things on earth! That's so awsome. But it's also sad that a lot of kids here would just be like "Oh a rubberband, woo hoo." We are just so lucky and we take it for granted, and i'm guilty of it also! :;sighs:;. But anyways. I slept late today, until 11:30. Then I got up and like brushed my teeth etc... and went out to the pool. I layed out a long time today and just swam a little bit, cuz the water was freezing. But i'm getting pretty tanned up, so that's good. I'll be ready for the beach. But who will I take with me? ::strokes chin in a profound way::. Then I came in and like took a nap, cuz I was tired for some reason. Then me and my mom went out to eat (My Dad and Sister are out of town until Sunday, that's so friggan awsome... I can't stand them.) Then, my mom took me to tumbling. I was so dissapointed to see my French Teacher pulling out of the parking lot w/ her daughter (a gymnast) just as we pulled in. I want to talk to her, she was awsome, like the over all best teacher I ever had. Yeah, i'm a loser, I miss school. Then I came home and just hung out. I haven't had my devotions yet though, but that's where i'm headin so... peace out! 
      
</post>
<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      (Okay, so I think that tittle was super cheesy, but oh well) So today, I got up at 9:30 my aunt calls at 10ish for me to baby-sit from from 12-5. Okay, sounds good. I need the cash. She gets here early, for once, like by and hour and then so like I feed her kids and we go swimming (I lay in the sun). Then, we came in and ate again around 2:30ish and watched an old James Bond movie (Diamonds Are Forever). Then there mom came at like 4, kind of early. But then she stayed at my house until like 5:30. It was kind of silly. Then I went to my mom's softball game. It was way boring so I walked over to the hospital (They have an awsome coffe shop). And got me a Frozen White Chocolate Mocha Latte and a huge, delicious Chocolate Chip Cookie (it was like a half inch thick and like super round, and goey!)... gosh no wonder i'm so fat! But it was way good. Then I went to tumbling. Not to toot my own horn but ::beep:: ::beep::, j/k. But, I did pretty good tonight. I was like grabbing my knees and all. It was fun. Then I came home took a bath, devoted myself, and then I got online, where I am now. LoL. And i'm way missing that awsome kid whom I like so much. Ahh, they will be back Saturday. Can't wait!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! Well, i'm outta here, au revoir!
      
</post>
<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, yeah... i'm totally missing them. Saturday is to far away. But, oh well. I shall be patient. I'm just going crazy! Ugh, yeah. But anyways. I got up pretty early today, but then I went back to sleep on the couch. Then I woke up and gave Kent (my dog [he's so cute]) a bath. That was grose. I hate giving him a bath, it's nasty. But he needed it. Then... I had to clean the bathroom in which I gave him a bath in. Which is really the only bath tub we have, so I didn't have a choice in the matter of which bath tub. Because were dead broke and our house is a peice of crap with a capitol C. Then... I went swimming and layed out in the sun, or attepted to. STUPID CLOUDS. How am I going to get a tan, with all these stupid Cirro Nimbus clouds?!?!?! J/K I doubt they were that kind of cloud. But, maybe... if so that sure would impress Mrs. Johnston (the #1 Earth Science teacher in the world, you rocked!). It's sad to say but I miss school. So then anyways, I got a shower and went to cheerleading practice (officially open gym, but well, same ole same ole). We really didn't do anything there. I don't see how were gonna win state with the lazy squad we have this year. Afterwards our camp clothes came in so we had to pick those up. I was mad cuz 1 of my t-shirts was back ordered and my new Uniform top didn't come in. I got the shorts to match the t-shirt and the pants to match the uniform top, but t-shirt/top. However, I had to leave my stuff at school cuz no one was there to pick me up so I ran home and I couldn't carry that crap and run at the same time. I could had walked and carried it... but then I would look stupid. So I ran, which was good for me. I'll just pick my camp crap up next week. But seeing how no one was there to pick me, the reson was cuz my rents thought it ended at 8. But if I had a cell phone I could had called them and been like no, it ends at 7:30. But I don't have a cell phone so I couldn't. Maybe now, they will see how important it is for me to have one. I could had gotten ran over running down that busy rode. But I didn't and now i'm here, lol. But i'm gonna bounce. TTYL!
      
</post>
<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I didn't "blab" (lol, Matt) in this thing yesterday. I was to tired last night. I don't know why, though. Well I didn't sleep very much over the weekend, that's probably it. So I went to church yesterday morning. That was fun. Then I came home and was just sort of lazy. Then I had cheerleading practice. That was... pretty good. It'd be better if everyone decided to show up. Well they just better when we learn our competition routine. Then I came home and ate dinner and watched the US Olympic trials for women's gymnastics. Those chicks are amazing! There, like 1,000x better tumblers than i'll ever be. Yeah then I went to bed, I was beat. Well so that was my day! L8er!
      
</post>
<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I miss them! But i'm gonna have to deal with it until Saturday. Anyways, so today I wake up at quarter to 7 (just whack for a Saturday morning). We left for tumbling and stopped and has buscuits then I was tumbling by 9. I did very, very, very suprisingly good today. I was so excited. My standing tumbling was all like, awsome (not to be aragont). I got to start twisiting/fulling again. I started once before but Lisa (my istructor) said I was unsafe before, but now I have things worked out. So that was fun. It's gonna be really hard to catch on to though! Oh and I was so excited! Courtney showed up and brought a friend Pamela. Meghan, Alisha, and Amber still didn't show. But oh well. After tumbling me and my mom went over to Moyer Complex to watch my sister's softball tournament (I HATE THOSE THINGS!). We watched two games back to back it was so hot. I have weird tan lines now because of what I was wearing and the sun was all hot. Then they had a big break inbetween games. So me and my mom went to the mall and I got a cool like button up shirt with these awsome, almost pearly-ish buttons (but not like feminin pearls). And I got some orange and blue swim trunks. There awsome, they match these cute orange flip-flops I bought especilly to wear with the shirt I wore to "Little Shop of Horrors". And it was the only shirt that matched them, so now I have a shirt and swimtrunks to match. But I can't wear the shirt with the swim trunks, they don't match. So then... we ate lunch at this chicken place and went back to the tournament. And going back I found out that theres like 4 lesbos on my sisters softball team. My sister was freaking out because they all had there girlfriends there and they were all over each other. But well, oh well. It doesn't bother me. Then we ate at like Ragazzi's or something. I can't spell. It was good. I saw my tumbling coach for school there with her family. It was fun. Except her neice Morgan whom is in my grade was with her and she's like really mean. I can't stand her! But oh well... i'm nice to her face. Then I came home and took a bath and had my devotions and wrote this post. I'm heading to bed now though, cuz i'm super beat. Salut!
      
</post>
<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      They left, for there Mission Trip today! That's so cool that they got to go on one! And well me I was super lazy today. I didn't do anything. Until tonight, I went to the Mall with this awsome chick, Tiffany. She rocks! She was visiting from out of town... it was so much fun. Or well I had fun, I hope she did. I didn't buy anything though. That was a first for me going to the mall not buying anything. I saw this awsome hot pink shirt at Hot Topic but it said Finch and Finch is a band and I didn't know if they were bad so I didn't buy it. But then I came home and talked to Charisse about it and she said they were good. So I might buy it. Well I bought my dinner. I had a Mocha Late and A Rasberry (or maybe it was Cranberry) scone with a white chocolate filling. Oh, and I bought me some Jelly Beans and her some Runts, it was fun. Well and now i'm home. So talk to me online, or something. L8er! Oh and I miss them already, ::sighs::.
      
</post>
<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      (tittle continued) BOYRFRIEND!!!!!!!! (sorry that wouldn't fit in the tittle box)   That's right! My sister she's so... gosh... i'd fill up to whole page if I used all the adjectives there are to describe her lazy/self-centered/even more self-centered/disgusting/etc... self! I can't stand her. And if she thinks for one minute she's gonna bring a kid home. NO! HECK NO! And she better not go to the beach with us this year, your 18 honey, get a life... you've sure ruined mine enough! Anyways. I baby-sat today. It wasn't fun, but hey I got paid $50... so that was nice. Well that was for two days of baby-sitting, but it's still good. And like all day pretty much the kids just swam while I layed out in the sun, so nothing was really abnormal other than them yelling incesintly. So then one of the kids left then like a couple hours later the other one left, even though there brother and sister. Then... I went running with my mom. I did pretty good, for me, I think. I ran a little over 3.5 miles. Then I walked like 3ish miles. Then she wanted go to the tanning bed so I went with her even though I layed out all day. I still tanned 20 minutes there. But just a little advice to well, men I guess, but if you use the like tanning lotion that like makes you tingle keep it off your, your, umm... your... ::whispers:: balls. It's not a fun experience. But anyways I got tan. Then I came home and ate a late dinner, took a bath, had my devotions, and here I am. So that was my day, i'm pretty tired, it was kind of a big day. AND I dind't get to talk to WDD... there leaving tomorrow for a missions trip from tomorrow (Friday) until NEXT Saturday... i'm gonna miss them. I wish I could talk to them right now but I can't. But oh well.. 1 Corinthians 13 (the patience part... even though I should seriously be thinking about the jealousy etc... parts also). OMG... (Oh My Gosh)... Tomorrow night i'm going to meet Tiffany at the mall. I can't wait, it's been ages since i've seen her. It's gonna be so much fun. But I need to save my money for the beach and the weekend after August 17th... so I probably won't buy much, but just seeing her will way rock! Well I better go, l8er!
      
</post>
<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well... los huevos is Spanish... i'm in French, but well don't ask. Anyways... today, for the morning I was super lazy. I just cleaned house a little bit and watched tv. Then at like 2ish Danielle came over! That was super fun. We watched Kill Bill Vol. 1. We'd both already seen it but it's okay. It's a great movie. Haha, and during the movie the phone rang so I paused it and answered the phone. (I paused it at the seen like where Lucy [I think her code name was ?Cottonmouth?] anyways she was at that table and about to cut the dudes head off and I knew she was getting ready to yell in Japanese) It was a sales person for MCI on the phone and they said "May I speak to Dallas Nolen, please?" So I said, "hold on one second please?" and un paused the movie and held the phone up to it while Lucy yelled in Japanese then I hung up. It was hilarious, but I guess you would have to be there. DUDE, I WANNA SEE KILL BILL VOL. 2!!! So then... ummm i'm not supposed to say, lol. But Danielle taught me how to dance, so we can hit it up in the clubs at the beach! Umm... then we ate dinner and watched Clueless. We didn't get to finish though because I had to leave for tumbling. She went with me. Hehe I felt like a dork, tumbling in front of her. But she's way super cool. Although, I tumbled like crap tonight! I sucked! Last night was good though, I don't know what happened tonight. I might had just been tired. So then... we dropped her off and I came home and here I am. Yeah, lol. So I guess... i'm gonna go chat with some people, lol. L8er! Au Revoir!
      
</post>
<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      HaHa... that was what someone's buddy sound was at like 2 o-clock this morning, So at 2 I was like cracking up over it. I don't know why it's not that funny, I think it was just the way the guy said it. And hey 2 in the morning, anything funny. Yeah then I got up at 8:30... pretty impressive or well early for me on summer break! Then I was like totally lazy, didn't do a darn thing! I talked to some awsome kid in Lynchburg on the phone! It was great. And I'm talking to that same kid now, it's awsome. I like them so much! Yeah so after I talked on the phone... I went swimming for just a few minutes. I felt like I needed to do a few laps to make me not feel so... fat/stationary. Then I ate some grub and got way over dressed to go to my mom's softball game. But oh well, I needed a good dress up, cuz I haven't since school's been out. Then I went tumbling. I did awsome there! I was so suprised with myself. Lisa said now that I have my layout all fixed i'm Definitly gonna start twisting! I can't wait! I hope I do okay and don't like blow my knee out. Yeah... so now that awsome Kid is gone so i'm gonna bounce also! TTYL!
      
</post>
<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Sunday morning, I went to church. It was great! Pastor Mark (the Youth Pastor) did the message cuz Pastor Andy (the really real Pastor) was out of town for Father's Day. Ensuite (then), I came home and cleaned, went swimming, came in the house and got ready for practice. CHEELEADING PRACTICE... AHHH! So I get there... and 9 of the kids are gone. Like, what the crap? Ugh so the REMAINDER of us practiced. It was pretty rough. We learned this new stunt it was like a pyramid called "The Roach". It was pretty easy to do, but I thought it looked sloppy. But the coaches loved it, so oh well. Then we danced, then we tumbled, THEN they decided the guys needed to partner stunt! So Lewis got Ashley Creasy (1 of the three flyers actually there) they were a good match. Then theres me and Connor left and 2 flyers. Flyer 1 is short and super chunky (NO OFFENSE LEAH!) and Flyer 2 is tall and hippy (NO OFFENSE RONI!!!) so I get stuck with Flyer 2 and Connor gets Flyer 1. So she's like taller than me... and heavy. I got her up... oh yeah she got up there (with an assist) but getting her back down. That's different. Coach Jessica was like just flick her so I do and she just like falls and crashes down on my head/chest and were both on the ground. It sucked! And then on the Sore Monday... my back hurts! Like it's hurt all day. I woke up early like 8 and felt like crap so just rolled over and went back to sleep. I finally got up at 11. I did like nothing though. I got around to calling Danielle that was fun. Then... I had cheerleading "open gym" for the school but like 10 people showed up. So we did nothing! Absolutely nothing! Came home, ate, went to sleep, and here I am. LoL. But yeah, so well... yeah. I'm gonna go now, go and talk to some peeps, haha. L8er!
      
</post>
<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Wait, that's right the three of you didn't show up. Ya'll just kind of left me hanging! But oh well... atleast I got some one on one time with Lisa. It's okay really though... we just paid the whole cost... "all our money right down the crappa woooooosh just gone!" Nah but don't sweat it just be there next week, please. I did pretty well today, though. Yeah... so then like after tumbling me and ma mère went over to the mall (au centra commercial)... but it was Tanglewood Mall so it way sucked! It does have TJ Max though... they have awsome housewares (if there not scratched)... I got this 4x6 picture frame which is just way cool. It's like a dull metalic ruby red with a silver outlined border, it's cool. I almost got this way awsome soccer jersey like Nike shirt... but I tried it on and I needed a little bit more (well actually a lot more muscle) to make it fit right. Then I had lunch at Applebee's (not my favorite but it was okay). Then... ummm oh yeah! The number one highlight of my day... I GOT TO WORK FOR THE FIRST TIME! Yes, at Kroger! It was my first day. I got there at one and watched like 3 hours of videos on personal safety, customer safety, co-worker safety, and how to properly bag groceries (it's really quite an art if you do it right... keyword "if"). Yeah then the rest of the time until 6 I got to actually bag groceies. It wasn't that bad... I was kind of slow but, I think I will get better. I don't have to work for a long time cuz i'm just a "bag boy" right now, but once I can be a cashier (I have to take a class which isn't available right now) I will have a lot more hours. But I think I'm gonna like working there it's a start anyways. It's MONEY! YAY! MONEY! LoL. Ummm there was this old woman bagging next to me and it was so funny she yelled out, "I need a bag!" then she ran,literally, (even though we were only like at the max 6 feet apart) to my counter and was like "BAGGY BAGGY BAGGY BAGGGY..." then she mumbled something really loud but it was such a mumble you couldn't understand her... but she was really pissed. I hope not at me. Poor thing, I think she had a problem. Then... so it was like "beep" "beep" "beep" "beep" "beep" "beep"... every two seconds, that got way annoying! But oh well. All in all it was a good experience, lol. Yeah... so before this thing turns into an epic I should go... it's a little long. WAIT! As great as working was I would had rathered been at Peaks View Park with well... them (as in the person)... that would has been awsome. But oh well i'll just wait until August 17th to see them, I hope it works out. I like them soooooo much! Yeah, so i'm outta here, holla!
      
</post>
<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yeah, so here I am... it's like 8:15 on a Saturday morning, well actually I got up at 7. How the crap is that for spending your saturday morning? Yeah... I have like a tumbling class at 9 so i'll be leaving in like 10 minutes. But oh... 9 is not even early i've had tumbling classes at 7 in the morning before. But it's okay... I have fun. These strange times are just the only ones my instructor has available for private lessons cuz she has so many cuz she's the best and everyone wants her! Yeah! And I have her! LoL. Just got to get up a little early... but oh well... i'll sleep in tomorrow. No wait! Tomorrow is Sunday, I have church. Well it's okay I like church! Ahhh guess what?!?! I get to work today! I can't wait! It's gonna be awsome! Or the money will ($$$$$...). Yeah... and like yesterday I went over to a friends house it was... interesting but fun! We watched some episodes of this sitcom "Strangers With Candy" not the most wholesome show, but oh well. It's pretty funny! I didn't understand the towel part... but okay... thats just me. And we watched "50 First Dates" great movie gotta see it, bye!
      
</post>
<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      ha, yeah... So like Wednesday I baby sat mes cousins from like 9-6... not very fun. But hey it's money! Then like that night I had tumbling that was super fun, except I was the oldest kid there and this little girl out tumbled me. But it's okay... I sucked it up. Then I went to Kroger with my mom to get some things and I ran into the manager there whom I had previously conversated with about getting a job. And he said he would call me Thursday night that he wanted to get me working as soon as possible. Then I came home. So here we are Thursday night... he called. I work Saturday at one! I can't wait. Although I almost had a sort of date (if you read this can I call it that... or no?)... well a get together. LoL. Which I was really looking foward to... but job money... okay. So yeah I start Saturday! Other than that today... ummm, I ran... I layed out in the sun, I swam, I bathed my dog... and yeah... that was all. LoL... well yeah. Tomorrow i'm going over to a friend's house, that will be way fun. Were gonna watch some more "Stranger's With Candy" hehe. Yeah so see ya l8er!
      
</post>
<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ugh... no sometimes school would be better than this boring-ness nothing to do around here. I cleaned my grandma's house or part of it today... (eww it was disgusting). Then I came home and layed out in the sun, what little bit of sun we had that is. I'M SICK OF RAIN! GRRR! Then... well I was out there a long time. I fell asleep, lol. I took a quick dip in the pool... then I had lunch. Umm... then I had dinner then I went tumbling. It was great! I did pretty good tonight. I can't wait until I start working on my full, I did once but my instructor gave up, lol. Then I had a ummm caramel milkshake thing... then I came home had my devotions and here I am. But not for long, i've got to bounce, ttyl!
      
</post>
<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well... it's fun being out of school... but i'm kind of bored. This morning I had to go over to my grandpas and clean the grass (which was like three feet tall) out of this ditch so the drain wouldn't get clogged up. Woah... it was hot and I got all sweaty and... dirty, ugh! And BLISTERS! Then tomorrow I have to go clean my grandma's house for her. But I get paid for all this! LoL... so that's a plus. But even better! I got a job at Kroger! Like... umm I start next week! Yay! I can't wait ($$$)! Well minimum wage... but hey it's better than nothing. I need a new computer and clothes! Yeah... lol... umm and I went swimming today and tried to layout in the sun... but after I worked in the hot sun it went away just when I wanted to layout. Then like, umm... yeah I just kind of lazed around the house and chillaxed. I haven't got to talk to my huge "crush" (well it's way more than a crush.. way more!!!!) but I havent got to talk to them (them being singular... just I have my reson for the use of them and not whatever else you may use)... lol, but yeah... and not talking to "them" makes me sad... I hope they like me as much as I like them! I like you!!!! So much! You know who you are... WDD! (</post></Blog>