<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      When I went to the bank with Shawn today, something funny happened at BSN (Bank Simpanan Nasional). My queue number was (I think) 315, when a Malay guy asked me if I could deposit a certain amount of money (LOTS of RM50 notes btw, which would made up to..RM400+?) for him as he has someone waiting in the car etc. I find it even stranger when he told me his number was 320, and heck, it's only  five  numbers away!  His impatience was funny, because if I'm an evil thieving person I would have dashed out fo the bank with  his  money and he wouldn't be able to catch me as I would've caught him unawares. Or was it a random check on how honest society in Malaysia is? &gt;_&gt;  So I was trying to deposit this gift voucher worth RM350 (:D), given by Motorola (my dad's working there) for my string of 7As for last year's PMR =P I thought I could withdraw every single ringgit from my bank account and dump them into Public Bank, when I was told by BSN's clerk that I'll have to wait for 4 days for them to process it. WTH? Having being told this by them, I'm getting put off by BSN and sure as heck will not ever dump in my savings into it, thanks to their incompetency.  Took several pics of the sky 'round evening, it was a creamy yellow and 'twas marvellous. Too bad it was marred by the tall buildings or what not &gt;.           Pretty neat, no? =) Again, camera angle's bad due to these annoying tall buildings and trees&gt;. 
     

    
</post>
<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I had this sort of inspiration on viewing the pictures on  urlLink Neave.com ; trust me, this guy's a genius with Flash and photography. With the inspiration in mind, I went out at about 2am today, gingerly opening the locks of my house door and went out with my trusty ol' gettin-rusty bike. I brought out the StarRewards postcard to mail it at the USJ8 mailbox as well.  You don't know how careful I was not to make any sound, but the automatic gates of my house banged together rather loudly - at least it was to me, in the middle of a dead midnight (or very early morning). Heck, I can imagine my mum's sheer horror to find me missing from the comforts of my bedsheets and rush to the police station teary-eyed while explaining to a bewildered police officer that I'm missing (hmm, but there's that 24-hour requirement, no?). I was also tempted to put up a post-it note on my door or something, saying "Am out for midnight photography." But then I wouldn't be able to answer my mum's questions as to why I would do such a crazy thing. Do y'all think I'm out of my mind?  Well, I did lotsa crazy things as well, like taking a pic of myself lying down in the middle of the road with the help of self-timer, but the pic didn't turn out that well (darn lighting, and I didn't turn on the flash for fear of um, people noticing my inane act). I guess I did felt adventurous, and that's adventurous ol' me for ya :P  When I finished cycling to USJ 8 and wandering around aimlessly at my USJ14 neighbourhood, I heard footsteps behind me and cycled ahead, as I did felt a lil afraid. When I returned to my house gate, to my horror, I saw the same guy, shadowed by the darkness of the night, sitting opposite my house gate! Well, what did I do? I went around cycling to the back of my house - to the restaurants and all to allow him some time to get out of the vicinity of the row of my house.   And near 7-Eleven's Indian 'mamak', I saw a Form 5 guy with another guy and a girl (presumably my schoolmates, I think, though I can't quite recognize them at the moment). Mr Form-5-Guy ( which I now recalled he's Ayub )(waved at me asking " Eh, dah malam tak nak balik rumah ke? " (It's already late at night and you don't want to get home yet?). I merely smiled and waved back and cycled back home, as I barely know that guy and socially-inept me prevented me from having a good conversation with him. &gt;.  On a side note, I guess it's a good beginning for a blog. More (un)interesting ones to come; I'm off to bank with Shawn soon.  Below are some of the pictures I've taken; they don't turn out that good 'cause I didn't bring a tripod with me at that time, and..the lighting's real bad at times.       The supposedly firemen's squatters?     GETS bicycle shop at USJ 8 XD     I've no idea how the picture turned green o_O Must be that green light thingy from my digicam, which I've no idea what it's for   
     

    
</post>
<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Shawn said, it's like waiting till SPM's over. Geok Leng agreed with me that we hardly notice that these exams stretch out to almost three weeks (technically). I remember during my PMR days, I shudder seeing my seniors "suffering" from 2-3 weeks of exams, where else we used to have only 1 week of exams (or even 3-4 days). Times change. :P  After finishing a badminton game, at about 7pm, I saw the sky beautiful with the sun's setting rays. Managed to take several (rather nice, in my opinion :P) still life pics, as well. The still life pics are inspired by Neave's site. ;)     Weird colour o_O The sky's not supposed to be this colour, but I like how the houses and their antennas have become silhouettes.           Here it is...=P      I suddenly thought of this while sitting down opposite this vision school. =P  
     

    
</post>
<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I think I did pretty well in my Add Maths paper II today; not because I am 100% sure that I did correctly for all 12 questions, but because I actually  finished  the paper with 5 mins remaining (with um, the exception of some sub-questions that I skipped :P). And I actually managed to solve a question that most people, including Eugene, did not manage to get. =P (except for [grr], Suet :P). When I passed up my paper, Miss Then exclaimed, "Clement! You're submitting a thesis or what!?" I used waaaaaay too many papers. *sweats*  I have to thank Eugene for all his private tutoring :P Guess it really pays off now ^.^ I cant seem to er, redo the questions that I did during exams. &gt;_&gt; I forgot my working, somehow. It always happens with Add Maths.
     

    
</post>
<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It was, in a way, a very weird but pleasant dream. I dreamt me and my mates - Shawn, Andy and Ryui Bynn - heading to Genting Highlands with Ryui Bynn driving a car (I can't remember the exact make of the car...). Then when we reached there, I saw my "pet sister", Whitney, who was walking through the snow. (Yeah, for some reason it was snowing &gt;_&gt;)  I remembered we were approached by a group of weird Japanese people, and Whitney talked to the Japanese lady in Japanese, and me saying something as well. I remembered what I spoke to the lady, "Kanojo wa watashi no tomodachi desu yo." ( She's my friend. )  Then, everything else was half-videogame. We climbed this weird escalator that moves upwards towards the shopping mall at about 45 degrees. Whitney and I fell down at one point, but we headed upwards. I remembered avoiding a stab when we entered this capsule-like elevator; the lady in a weird costume had tried to slash me with a scimitar-like weapon.  Can't remember much about this dream, apart from me envying Ryui Bynn driving the car. The rest of us were asking if we could test-drive it as well &gt;_&gt;  Maybe this dream happened because of um...several things in real life. A plan to go to Genting this coming Friday (50/50 it'll work out), and RB jokingly said that he'll drive Andy home yesterday night. Nevertheless, weird, but nice =P  
     

    
</post>
<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Got back from Ryui Bynn's house. The whole afternoon and night was spent at Eugene's house studying Add Maths...his dad also spent us KFC! :D And um, some of my friends were doing the farting competition thingy &gt;_  At about 10.30pm, went to RB's hse (and  tapau-ed  some  limau ais ). We played some street soccer, Andy and I against RB and Shawn. Lost miserably, and when Andy kicked it hard somewhere, the ball was missing o_O We searched for quite some time among the bushes with two torchlights, but we still couldn't find it.  RB's house was situated opposite a deep monsoon drain. We went down, with me trotting behind feeling a little scared. It's about 12am, and us going down the monsoon drain is a little bit un-nerving, as I was behind the rest of 'em. We saw some black plastic bag in a box which resembles a dead baby or something, with a toad on top of it. We can't find the ball, but found another deflated ball which isn't ours.  Weird. It's a little scary searching underneath the big, strong trees and its long branches. Especially in the dead of the night, despite the lamp-posts. We were joking, saying that RB would find the ball on top of him at night, or perhaps at the porch of his house. &gt;_&gt;
     

    
</post>
<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ironic, that I had a certain fixed schedule daily during my exam period. Got back from school at about 2-3pm, played around with the PC and I will usually be taking my nap from 5-7.30pm. Next, it's PC again or I will be doing my spot of studying.  Take yesterday for instance. At 12am I tried to read my econs but my eyes were droopy. I ended up using the PC for some time, felt more refreshed and studied a little =P Lost and won my bet on some matches from Euro 2004. Damn Beckham and his freaking missed penalties! That costed me RM5 &gt;_&gt;
     

    
</post>
<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      On 19th July 2004, Saturday (two days back), went out with Shawn to collect our ICs from the respective department. It took about 30 minutes but because my parents wanted to make new ICs as well, we ended up walking towards a Taipan-like area searching for a cyber cafe in vain. I bought the latest Galaxie mag with The Corrs' Summer Sunshine lyrics in it :D It's full-page too! Perfectly luscious.  I had a bout of unfortunate diarrhoea, might be due to the iced coffee I took at this coffee shop for breakfast. It was...annoying and painful, to say the least.  After our IC-collecting feat and lunch at home, the both of us went to Eugene's house for some intensive Add Maths under his wing. Wai Hong didn't study much, and Andy came for a short while before he left for tuition. After studying the dreaded subject from 2pm-6pm, we had a break and played Capcom vs SNK 2 and a Harry Potter's Quidditch on his PS2 till 7pm. Then we walked to the nearby Maju-Maju restaurant for dinner, with Ryui Bynn and Andy.  Resuming our studying with the exception of RB, went back to Eugene's house and studied diligently up to 10.30pm. I think I'm good in my  Sukatan Membulat  now :D Went to RB's house nearby and  lepak  till 12am, where we played 'Monkey' with a ball or simply chit-chatted with two candles. Went back to our houses with Andy's sister's car.  Fast forward next day (20th July), I woke up at 2pm O_O At 4pm I slept again till 6.30pm. Studied Bio (as I did not study it that much yet) from 8pm to 12.30am. Went online to seal a bet with Gopi (which I lost - RM2.50, Spain vs Portagal; I took Spain). at 2am, I studied Physics till 3am and only slept at 3.30am. Then woke up 3 hours later, blurry eyed and tired.  Throughout the entire day I felt sleepy and heavy-headed - with some slight headache as well. Guess my Bio's okay as I spent that crazy amount of time yesterday (but I did forgot some of the terminology, names of parts...). Physics was horrendously hard. I felt English Paper I was the best :D I didn't have much time left as I had written 4 pages of essay and had to end it abruptly (something about my school on fire, while injecting some humour into it :D). Ms Then, who was in the class, pointed out to me subtlely while I was writing, that I had my tenses wrong. On triple-checking it, I found nothing wrong whatsoever o_O  It goes "...then all hell breaks loose." I see nothing wrong in it; and I don't think I'm supposed to change "breaks" into "broke" either. Curiously, I can't imagine Ms Then tipping me off XD She's a disclipline teacher in charge of the prefects! She was laughing out loud when she read certain parts of my essay as well XD 
     

    
</post>
<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      While pondering over my English paper II over the question "what's the meaning of 'just as fair' in the poem The Road Between?", the torrent of wind that had already blown soo hard that it threatened to tear the school to bits, managed to snatch my paper away and sent it over the edge of first floor. o__O Pn Lijah was a little funny XD She was downstairs at the assembly grounds, exclaiming, "Clement!  Kertas kamu jatuhlah! " in that squeaky voice of hers =P When I went downstairs to retrieve it, En Azlan passed the paper to me. Earlier on Jun Man from 4B suffered the same as well. :P  It's the second time that had happened this year, the first being my Moral paper from first term thrown over to the assembly grounds as well. &gt;__&gt;  England won 3-0. Bah! I sorta knew England would won terribly over Switz, but somehow... I should said NO firmly to Gopi in the first place, to bet over that match. &gt;_  While the wind/thunder/rainstorm occured this morning, I sorta had bits and pieces of what to write for a poem and pieced it together when I got back from school. Not very good, mind, just a try at poetry-writing :P   The Rain   The blowing air, Like an angry child, seized and tugged at my waft of hair, In its fury, Unleashed its breath upon me, Chilling my body to skin and bone.  White ghosts floating above Across a body of grey, unanimously, of various apparitions Flow with the flow At an impossible speed, And the body ceased to smile.  They can hold no longer, Weeping and wailing at unsightly sights that offend, A yelling crescendo, All ceased at the conductor’s hand, Abruptly.  
     

    
</post>
<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      In my whole life, I find myself happy to be able to help people in any way, and I find myself being bombarded with people asking me to help out with their PC-related problems, which I happily obliged. Not that I'm an expert in this field, I just have lots of experience and read InTech a lot as well, plus sometimes through the GameFAQs message board which I frequent.  It just so happen that recently many, many people have been asking me for help; and I can't help but wonder if I'm being taken advantage of? *looks blankly for several seconds*  Nah :P Maybe I'm just naïve, but I'm happy enough to be able to help. Even if you can't solve their problems all the time, I feel contented. At least I tried, at least I helped. I don't consciously think of the word "help" all the time, I just thought of it today =P   Went to Joe's house to uh, try and solve his modem driver problem thingy. His parents and his sisters are at home, but not him himself. His dad's really really friendly, and in a way he reminds me of my dad (although I have my fair share of disagreements &gt;_&gt;).  Betted with Gopi today:  England vs Switzerland (this midnight) - he insisted I took Switz which I did, and gave me 1 ball. RM5 :P France vs Croatia (next early morning) - we betted on scores instead. I guessed it might be 2-1, while he betted 2-0. RM2. Italy vs Sweden - I took Italy, gave him 3/4 ball. RM5  In short, RM12 in total XD I'm not sure about you guys, but betting on footie matches brings some kind of excitement and I kinda fancy it =P And yeah, I guess I've never betted that much before, and this is my first time betting over RM3 &gt;_&gt; Gopi even betted with Mr Victor (discipline/ Penolong Kanan HEM  teacher), Matthew's dad. XD RM10, apparently; Mr Victor took Croatia, fair game. It's unbelievable, but Mr Victor's full of surprises =P 
     

    
</post>
<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      *sighs*  So the Germany vs Netherlands (Holland) match turns out to be a draw (1-1), so I didn't lose nor win my bet of RM3 with an older friend. :P And Ms New Girl's not in our class yet, either.  Tomorrow marks the start of technically 3 weeks of exams. I'm looking forward to do Additional Maths to get over it, quickly. Which would be next Tuesday, I think. Currently I'm sick of having being told when to sleep/study by my parents, especially my mum. The incessant nagging made me unleashed curses after curses (to myself, of course), and frankly, it would be better if they trust me that I know my own life and schedule better and would they please stfu. Thank you. &gt;_  *runs off now to watch Charmed on Star World*
     

    
</post>
<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday, after Miss Then, our Bio teacher, reported that there will be  yet another  new student in our class - a girl - everyone started obsessing about meeting her (including yours truly). There's the fun and excitement on meeting a new member to our class; she didn't turn up today, though.  Was reading my History yesterday midnight when I heard this song by Vitamin C,  Graduation (Friends Forever) . There's like a year and a half to go, and I wonder where all of us - my friends - would be once we grew up? Would genius all-rounder Suet Li be the greatest doctor/scientist on earth? Would Ryui Bynn be a geologist? Would someone from my class discover the ultimate cure to HIV/AIDS?  Part of the lyrics ring true to me, and made me think:   So if we get the big jobs And we make the big money When we look back now Will our jokes still be funny? Will we still remember everything we learned in school? Still be trying to break every single rule Will little brainy Bobby be the stockbroker man? Will Heather find a job that won't interfere with her tan? I keep, I keep thinking that it's not goodbye Keep on thinking it's a time to fly And this is how it feels   To all my friends and those who knew me in some way, the chorus portrayed by this brilliant song, I'm saying this to all of you from the bottom of my heart:   As we go on, we remember All the times we had together, And as our lives change, come whatever, We will still be, Friends forever...   
     

    
</post>
<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Phone Booth, starring Colin Farrell is an intriguing movie. If you think that there can be no interesting storyline revolving a phone booth, think again, as the script-writer of this movie has managed to stretch the story beyond an hour in a most interesting manner, touching on subjects such as infidelity.  It's an emotional show too, somewhat, and has an interesting message at the end of the show - that you hear a public phone ringing, you know it's a wrong number but you pick it up anyway - and find that your life (as well as your love ones') is endangered by a serial killer sniper.   Oh, and camera angles revolved around buildings, the street and the phone booth for the most part of the show, so it's definitely interesting. Expletive are used freely in this show as well - you've been warned. :P  Kill Bill Vol 1 - it's nice as well, but too much unrealistic violence - blood spilling forth like fountain etc. Japanese accent by main character (Uma Thurman) is horrid, while Lucy Liu's slightly better (playing an underground Yakuza queen in Japan as a Chinese-Japanese American).  Did I also mention that the subtitles for both DVDs are...terrible? Horrid grammatical mistakes, and they don't follow the characters' speech as well - I just had to turn the subtitles off, for once. Bah! But that's what you get for pirated stuffs done locally &gt;_&gt;
     

    
</post>
<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just watched Black Hawk Down yesterday, a movie about war in Somalia. It just goes to show that war, no matter for whichever and whatever ideals, always end in greater loss of lives; how men needlessly throw their lives away, dying in the most horrifyingly grotesque manners, wounded at all sorts of odd places. War is ugly.  “This is civil war,” said a Somalian, “and this is our war.”  Why do people have to interfere in other people’s war? Why does former US President Clinton have to send his men out to do his dirty job? It’s easy to command soldiers to fight, it’s easy to place his ass onto some chair, and counting casualties “19 died, 56 wounded” like they’re simple maths, when the soldiers who fought bravely out there yelled “Man down! Man down!” signifying the importance of lives. They’re more than just numbers, they’re lives.   Seeing a man’s torso got completely destroyed; your driving comrade blasted in the face by pieces of mirror and got blinded, with you yelling, “Step on the gas pedal! Keep stepping on it!” while you semi-calmly take control of the wheel; your teammate got deafened by sudden firing of the weapon you’re using; and a man whose pelvis got wounded badly by shots, and your mates and yourself had to perform a primitive operation using whatever knowledge they have and equipments at hand, watching your men trying to restrain a screaming friend in utter extreme pain of the highest degree as he fainted, your hand digging through the pelvis trying to clamp the arteries together, trying to do everything you and your men could do but in the end, all fails.  As he slowly wakes up, he asked weakly, “Fixed it?” and you had to give him hope, and you smiled encouragingly saying “Yeah we did.” In the end, he died. Died saying, “Tell my parents that I fought really well today, that I fought really, really well…”  In war, whatever you speak might be your last words, ranging from “RPG!” to “Fuck!”. In war, your very mind is split into several decaying matters trying to survive the onslaught of upcoming attacks. Men, women, children of Somalia are all against you. War… why must there be a fucking war upheld by bastards of politicians who had the worst and most unreliable intel that results in unnecessary deaths?  Seeing them encouraging each other, patting each other on their backs, giving them hope when there's minimal chance of surviving... I could've broke down.  In SFC “Hoot” Gibson’s words, war is about looking after men next to you. SSgt. Matt Eversmann: In war, there are no heroes. 
     

    
</post>
<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      After finish using the PC and studying History till roughly 2:40am, I felt myself still fully awake. Deciding that tossing and turning around in my bed would be a complete waste of time, I watched The Hot Chick with lights out and used the ever-useful wireless headphone :D It has subtle sex-related jokes as well XD (not the actual act of sex, but um, basically anything to do with sex; the male genitalia, homosexuality...et al).  So um, watched till 5am. It's a really funnnyyyy show but I had to stiffle my laughters (which turned into mere smirks &gt;.  I still couldn't sleep. So I proceeded with my tossing and turning around my bed till I slept at 7am. And awoke again at 10.30am, my mind slightly stale but nevertheless still alert but the strangest thing is, I didn't felt at all tired physically. And proceeded to do my Add Maths homework with Kai Shen, Andy and Chee Hee at the Hipermedia library for 3 hours and a half. o_O  Oh, and while walking to the restaurant where they were lunching earlier, I scraped my right heel and it was scratched semi-badly and bled. Ouch. And just few hours earlier I scratched the same spot again at the base of the very chair I'm sitting. Double triple ouch.
     

    
</post>
<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      That's what I've been doing of late. I slept at 4am for the past few days...and I still felt awake at that time! (and woke up like, at 12.30pm or 1.30pm later on &gt;_ _     Now isn't this nice? =) It looks better in bigger resolution, and I focused on these two main ideas/objects; one's a decoration thingy gave to me by Julia (I think) for my birthday and another's a now-useless poem theme for my English Literature (turns out that the sylabbus changed &gt;_   I totally hate History. That's relatively speaking, because I  do  like certain parts in History such as religions and certain cultures but putting 5 topics devoted to Islam? Hellooo? No offense to Muslims, but can't they shorten the whole thing or something? Yep, I'm pretty interested to learn more about Islam, but non-Muslims would get bored with 5 consecutive topics while Muslims would've already learnt those 5 topics somewhere in their Islamic Studies.  Oh, and eating a slice of cheese-cappucino cake and drinking Dutch Lady Chocolate Milk forthwith is a bad idea. *stomach rumbles*
     

    
</post>
<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hehe, it's great when I see lots of my friends had took up blogging because I introduced it to them =P All thanks to TheStar for featuring blogging in their previous StarEducation, which inspired me, and in turn, inspired other people around me. =)
     

    
</post>
<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just finished watching School of Rock. It's the type of movie that gets you all inspired and all you want to do right after watching the show is get your fingers into some kind of instrument and start rocking! Ah, but there's that one thing. I can't play. And you can say I'm tone-deaf. Oh, and I can't sing. So does this make me the next William Hung?  Ah well, I can only dream :P It's absolutely lovely when you're in a band, and you hear your bandmates play and you do your stuff. It's the best thing ever in cooperation even if it's just musically. Being an ex-vocalist, um, it's a huge embarassment when I hear myself on record, but I guess I had lots of fun. :D And that, I think, is most important when you're doing something. Go have some fun!  Quote from School of Rock: "I wasn't like this! I was fun! I was funny!" "But they, their parents! They turn me into this! They'll come to me with a nuclear bomb if something's wrong!" - Principal Miss Muller to Dewey Finn.
     

    
</post>
<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well...watched both shows yesterday night (or this early morning). Um, that show and its sequel are highly sexual and vulgar, but they do offer lost of laugh at the expense of the embarassment of the actors (and actresses). The former has a simple storyline of 4 hormone-charged guys wanting to "get laid" before high school is over; and their last chance to get it would be the night of their prom; the latter simply depicts their college life, and them renting a summer house beside a beach.  A quote from American Pie which I thought is funny: "There's this one time at band camp..." - Michelle starting off a conversation with this phrase almost every time. (well, you gotta watch it to get what I mean).  And another quote from American Pie 2: "I got peed on." - Stifler having an unfortunate incident. Again, you gotta watch it to get the joke. :P
     

    
</post>
<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ...for about an hour before it finally subsides with a loud burp (and some obnoxious gaseous remains that were expelled forthwith).  Also just came back from Jon's house; borrowed 14 DVDs of various genre (and 1 School of Rock DVD which I borrowed from Shawn, who borrowed from Andy, who borrowed from Ryui Bynn). Comedies include American Pie (and its sequel) and The Hot Chick, war-themed includes Black Hawk Down, action-related includes Phone Booth and Kill Bill Vol 1 (yay!)...and, that's all I can think of for now. All in all, 15 DVDs. :D *thumps boredom out of the window*  Oh, and my new maid just arrived today. o_O Let's just hope she won't start to run away. I pity maids actually. My previous maid (who ran away) was only 17 (just a year older than me, imagine that!) and she studies Chemistry, Bio...and whatnot, before she came to M'sia. She actually studies! o_O (Okay...maybe because I have a stereotyped image of how maids lived previously in Indonesia...) I'm guessing that my previous maid ran away because my mum nagged a lot (she's a... clean-freak! &gt;_&gt;). Maybe maids should be named as housekeepers; the term 'maid' sounds so...um, slave-like &gt;. 

    
</post>
<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just realized that our mind has so much power untapped. I was roused by my dad's voice when I took a nap, and I could sort of visualize his image and his voice clearly in my mind for that 2 seconds, asking me to wake up (he was in the kitchen, in my mind). Okay, I don't know how to describe it but it's weird - it's like um, a mini-premonition of sorts that's just a milisecond faster. Okay, that may not make sense &gt;.  Couple of years back, when we were having assembly in school, I had a deja vú - at least, that's what I'm inclined to believe. The teacher who was conducting the assembly dropped some papers onto the floor, and a few seconds later, I saw the same thing happening except that, in between the action of the papers that are falling onto the ground, several frames of time are missing. (Um, did I make sense?) You know how a video goes, so assuming that the action of paper-falling is the video, several frames of the video are missing - that it made the action...sorta interrupted.  Okay, I think I'm not making total sense at all to you guys &gt;_&gt; Oh, can I mention something Corrs-related? XD The Corrs are made Artist of the Month by MIX FM! Mwahaha! :D  
     

    
</post>
<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yep, that's about one of the weirdest things I've eaten for lunch in a while (yesterday's). Been listening to my Borrowed Heaven album. :P Amazingly, Heng Li actually likes Angel too :D (a track from BH, directed to their deceased mum). It's going to be the second new single off the new album =P; the song is so uplifting that it's ironic, plus with the brilliant lyrics as well.  I especially like part of the bridge, when it was sung very quickly:  Confidence and conscience  Decadent extravagance  Never ending providence  For loving when I had the chance   Off BH, I like Angel, Borrowed Heaven and Humdrum. =) 
     

    
</post>
<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, watched Harry Potter: The Prisoner of Azkaban with Soon Guan and my bro yesterday night, at 11:45pm. We went there at almost 10pm, so it's semi-dead in The Summit shopping complex, but we hung around at the arcade (Time Crisis 3: god I died pretty quick &gt;_&gt; Tried twice too, and managed to only finish up to first half of Stage 2), bowling center (totally regretted playing bowling, it's so damn expensive after 5pm, and I didn't know that ;_;) and finally some food court centre near Summit (drank there, and watched some Chinese B-grade horror movie on TV at that moment).  So the verdict: In my opinion, the movie is sooo short (only 2 hours?) that it just didn't do justice for the books. And having switched director, there is less action compared to its predecessors, although the scenes are well-done, even if they don't necessarily follow the book in detail.  That's yesterday. Today we (me, bro and SG) watched THREE movies on my PS2 in my room, from 3-10pm (although SG left at around..9 something =P; *is borrowing his DVDs*). Chronologically, we watched Underworld (interesting, and cool action scenes, plus a neat storyline too), Charlie's Angels 2: Full Throttle (watched it before in the cinema, but what the heck. This one's not censored by the Government anyway), and Cheaper by the Dozen (comedic, loved this one; family-value themed).  Okay, so un-chronologically, right after we got back from watching Prisoner of Azkaban (which is about 2am), we watched Scary Movie 3 in my room (I watched the first disc before, but disc 2 just won't play on my Dreamcast for some reason). God I love this phrase, "Cindy! The TV's leaking!" XD That show is helluva funny! (especially how SG says that quote XD) - despite showing like a B-grade movie :P Raw stupidity and sex-related jokes in abundance. :P  Am changing my blog's name. The reason why I had this link "saigoexp" is because I thought of the experience points from the Final Fantasy games, only that I didn't explore the idea till Iona mentioned this. Experience points.   Life is akin to a game, every choice you make affects the future - the good and the bad choices; if you're not careful you'll end up in mortal danger, or just like the game, anything might happen. The airplane you're in might experience engine problems, but just as you thought you're going to die, the pilot manages it and has everything under control, which adds up *his* experience points - and everyday we experience new things. Won't it be neat if we can see how much "experience points" all of us collect in total? - though how much "experience points" you'll gain for each "experience" currently eludes me (it sounds impossible anyway).  Just a thought.
     

    
</post>
<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Slept at 4.30 am after chatting for quite some time with Soon Guan while both of us were lying down on my bed (that is, after we finally turned off the PS2 at 2 am). Discussed about school, music, videoclips, movies, et al; basically, anything that can be talked about :P).  Then I just  had  to get up  at about 8.20 am as I have my Biology extra class in school. It's in the lab, and it turns out to be rather surprising to me as 4A and 4B were not together in one lab; instead we were to stay in our own labs, and Miss Then (my Bio teacher, in an outfit that's unlike her - some rather tight-fitting clothes) had to go to and fro in both labs to conduct her lessons.  Went to Burger King Taipan to eat; the Chicken Smoked Turkey set was excellent. Jon returned my RM50... said that his parents said I don't need to pay them for the disc, and to treat it as a souvenir o_O Man his parents are damn generous. =P Thanks unc and auntie!  What else? Spent the rest of the afternoon playing Power Stone 2 (on Dreamcast) and Soul Calibur 2 (PlayStation2). After taking a short nap before dinner, felt slightly refreshed now, and more alert. :P Soon Guan told me that he saw Galaxie mag with  The Corrs  on its cover! :D It was at 7-Eleven, gotta buy that later.  Also receive a phone call from my cell group leader, as to why I didn't attend church for some time &gt;_&gt; Ah well :P
     

    
</post>
<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Oh lovely god and holy mother that is Mary, I'VE JUST BOUGHT  BORROWED HEAVEN!!!  Okay maybe I'm a lil emotional to the point that I might drop a tear or two, but hey, I've been anticipating this album for freaking ages!! &gt;. _&gt;).     Earlier this afternoon, I went to Eugene's house to study Add Maths under his wing (more like trying to finish up my homework &gt;_ Persamaan Serentak  (Simultaenous Equation) and am currently doing  Sukatan Membulat ) (Circular Measure). Then when I went home and saw Jon's online, I went to his house immediately, paid him RM50 and grabbed MY copy of The Corrs' Live in Dublin :D Excellenté.     And now, my friend's staying overnight now. At the moment I'm writing this, he's in my room playing PS2 (Silent Hill 3) with my younger bro. I'm in a state of heaven borrowed - ecstatic, happy!  Oh, and done solving Suet's problem :P (more like the thing worked now). She can't login into her blog for some reason (season expired problem).  Adios for now!
     

    
</post>
<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I had a weird dream; I dreamt I was buying Borrowed Heaven in one of the CD shops in Taipan. At first I couldn't find it and I remembered feeling disappointed until I spotted it; it has a WESTLIFE back cover, which is a no wonder why I can't find it &gt;_&gt; Um...okay, I know it's completely un-interesting but I thought I'd like to mention that &gt;_&gt;  Well, here's a virtual graffiti I made using...um, one of the links provided by  urlLink Neave.com .     Not bad eh? :P There's some sorta hidden meaning to it, that humanity's becoming more corrupted. 
     

    
</post>
<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Seeing that I'm rather bored now, and it's already past 12 midnight and I  really  should be studying, I think I'll write what I'm anticipating for today when I get up later in the morning.   For one, The Corrs' new album  Borrowed Heaven  is slated for release today in M'sia! :D But unfortunately, I think I don't have enough money to buy one thanks to BSN's horrid processing of my gift voucher, and I don't think I'd want to withdraw from my Public Bank account either; it's there as a fund for my planned Australia trip end of next year, with Joe :D  Secondly, Jon's supposed to return today from his trip from LA (a damned 2-week trip at that, man was I freaking jealous and full of envy &gt;_&gt;), where I have to pay him RM50 for buying me The Corrs' US-only album  Live in Dublin  (which is why I'm as broke as ever &gt;.  Heck, that's  why  I'm joining these StarRewards contests (especially Week 1's, where the first prize is two return trip tickets to anywhere in   Australia  , which fits my condition perfectly). Winning some money from the contest would be excellent as well &gt;.  And thirdly, my best buddy Soon Guan's staying overnight as well; he got his green light from his mum already :P So I guess I'll have some kinda fun these holidays.. he'll be accompanying my oh-so-bored hols for several days I guess, which I'm gonna make sure I'll maximize the days he's staying to their full fun potential ^.^  And crap, my download of Hunter X Hunter episodes 26-62 (in a single torrent file) is simply taking ages (helloo, it's SEVEN GIGABYTES!! &gt;_  And double crap, I just remembered that I have EXTRA CLASSES on Wednesday and Thursday for Biology. Damn. And Friday's Chemistry which I'm certainly not going, 'cause the teacher's rather...boring, and she's a text-book reader for heaven's sake. Her dull monotonous voice simply lulls us to sleep (I'm sure SMK USJ8ers would be glad to fill you guys in). I'm catching up pretty well by reading my reference book by myself, without having to resort to her help.  Oh, just phoned Joe an hour earlier, and apparently his dad took out his modem and he had to study, and that's why he didn't go online for the past few days &gt;. _  I guess that's all for tonight. Procrastinator ol' me would have to catch up on my other subjects, if I feel like it tonight :P And no, I won't be wandering around later past midnight outside my house, unless something drives me to do so =)  C'est la vie.
     

    
</post>
<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Walking around in school today, I had to use the power of estimation to roughly guess who the person that was standing few metres away really was. XD I kinda got used to it, and got used to all the teasings and the stupid "guess how many fingers" game. &gt;_&gt;  Got back my spectacles today at about 8pm. It's fixed, and I'm not used to it. The moment I stepped out from that shop, I realized that I missed the beauty of everything for the past 48 hours - the vibrant colours of the word "Secret Recipe" written in cursive font, the big electric banner of  Restoran Nam Heong  in brilliant yellow and red, the flashing headlights from passing cars...it's like an utterly different world. Now I know what it is like to be blind (although I was far from that); after years of enduring total darkness, you went for an operation to have your eyes restored and you take in the beauty of everything the world has to offer. Which is particularly why I love photography =)  Geok Leng came to my house earlier at about 7.45pm, to transfer pictures from her digicam to my PC andburn them for her. 
     

    
</post>
<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Without my specs, my line of vision is sooo blurred it's as if someone used a Photoshop and used the Blur effect on my world, visually. I brought my cam to school, and played around with it =P I think I looked better without spectacles actually, with Geok Leng agreeing to it as well although Xin Hui said otherwise, saying that she's not used to my spectacle-less outlook. :P          I think I looked sooo innocent. XD What dya think? :P       Took some photos with Geok Leng as my model for the photography contest...I had a few ideas in mind, and I think they're nice, except that the blackboard and the mirror pic was slightly blur-ish. I'm submitting the birdie pic and the last pic of Geok Leng.       Those Chinese words represent her Chinese name =P      This pic was snapped at the girl's toilet, ground floor, shower area XD      At the stairs, overlooking the field,  bengkel pertanian , and canteen.      Was in a rush trying to snap this pic. The bird was flying too fast, and Miss Then wants a scenery pic (only knew that during the last minute).   
     

    
</post>
<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Bah. Went for football with the rest of the team (which we called ourselves, as eXodus). Azim, Matthew, Joe, Shawn, Heng Li, Jon, Wai Hong, another ex-USJ 8er and I were there. We were training ourselves basically (...it was tough trying to kick a  straight  ball =.="), and played a game among ourselves, with Heng Li as the goalie.   After some of them Malay guys (not trying to be racist here, but they're sorta like..delinquents &gt;_&gt;) - namely Fareez, Helmi etc - came, we sorta lost the mood. So Shawn and I were kicking a ball between us, when Shawn unsuspectingly delivered his wonderful back-kick 'skill' and rammed the ball straight to the side of my face. No sound of anything being broken - but I felt my specs slipping off my nose.   So this is like the [insert 5 digits here]th time I've broken my specs, or have been involved in any football mishap. *rolls eyes* Shawn apologized "Sorry, Clem" about 50 times that I've nothing to say really. I'm semi-angry, frustrated, annoyed, kinda pissed...   Then I said out loud to myself (and to Shawn's face), "Think rationally, think rationally," and I noticed that it's the lens that got broken. Which means easily repaired, but there goes the moolah. Unlike some people who might yell at the offender with profanities, I simply kept my cool outwardly - since he can't do anything about it (and most likely unable to pay for the repair), neither could I.   Shawn felt most guilty and was kinda sombre throughout the journey home. Heh &gt;_&gt; Lesson learnt (which I never did) - don't ever wear your fragile rimless spectacles when playing football. This incident costed me (well, my parents &gt;_&gt;) RM70 - discounted from RM85 thanks to my mum, the super bargainer.   
     

    
</post>
<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Went to Jon's house at 4 something after doing a little of Moral  folio  at Wai Hong's house. Jon kindly taught me guitar - the basics, how to press them strings, etc. It hurts.  A lot.  I watched him play Gunbound while I continue pressing down the strings to get used to it. It helps in a way, as I paid less attention to the pain and to the game instead.   Next, I need to practise strumming. If only I have a guitar, I'd be able to practise =/   
     

    
</post>
<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Earlier today, went out to Midvalley with my parents to hunt for a pair of running shoes. I thought their budget was low (they didn't want to tell me), so I found an All-Conditions Gear at about RM170, and my mum thought it looked like the one I'm wearing (which is not); it wasn't exactly that comfy aroun the ankle area. I also phoned up Joe, the shoes expert to get some advice, and he said that he would recommend me running shoes.  Well, I couldn't find one that fits below RM200. &gt;_&gt; So after letting her see my other choice, surprisingly she agreed o_O(after asking me repeatedly whether it's worth buying such a pricey shoe &gt;_&gt;; and told me to choose between a guitar and this footwear. She assured me that she would get the guitar end of next month instead, so I happily agreed). So I got myself a Nike Air Max Turbulence 8.5 (US size 9); it's navy. :D Original price: RM379. Slashed to RM227.10 thanks to 40% discount from the Megasales starting today :D  Take note that this is my first pair of "pricey" shoes, I've never had the luxury of owning branded shoes, be it Adidas, Reebok etc. So...yay ^.^  Also found the book that I sought for, "most of us are here against our will" by David Levinson at MPH. Costs at an expensive tag of RM60+. Second yay for finding this book finally. ^.^ 
     

    
</post>
<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Saturday - 24th July 2004   After spending enough aching and tiring stationing at the school entrance in a complete scout uniform - while repeatedly greeting parents with pre-programmed statements - I went hanging about in my class. It was a report card day, splendidly boring. Helped around with scout-related stuffs till about 1pm before I went back home.   At 2:45pm, I went out again to Gopi's house who took his sweet time trying on his socks and various articles of apparel. Jeremy was already at his house. After we took a wrong bus (number 10) and realized that 5 minutes later, we had to wait for bus number 4 to move. Apparently, only bus number 4 goes to Bangsar now, despite what was stated at bus number 10 that it goes to the Kotaraya.   Anyhow, the whole misadventure of this stupid bus took us a long time to reach our desired destination. We stopped at Asia Jaya to get on the LRT there (instead of Bangsar, it's further - I researched on the Net before I went to Gopi's house). After we missed the train by mere seconds, we waited a while and went on board. I misheard Suet talking over the phone, so the whole lot of us took the feeder bus to SS2, only to be told on the way that she was already at the Taman Bahagia LRT station waiting for us.   We were one hour late from the appointed time - 4pm. She had to go as well, so we chatted for roughly 5 mins before she dropped us off at the aforementioned LRT station. Hope she didn't get pissed &gt;_&gt; (though she didn't look like she was...) We took roughly 2 hours just to get to SS2 - horrid public transportation.   Then to get home, Jeremy and I took the train to KL Sentral (Gopi dropped off at Bangsar to be picked up by his dad). All in all, whenwe reach Court 3 (where Jerm stays), it was 7pm. It wasn't worth it &gt;_  As I managed to convince Joe over the phone to go to an online friend's church concert (Dinghy's), I waited for him at the guard house, and talked for several long minutes to Jon who happened to be there as well (he just came back from church). Joe and I set off via bus (again &gt;_&gt;) to reach SJMC, and headed off to Holiday Villa. Joe phoned Geok Leng to go, while I received an SMS from Iona (yet another online buddy, whom I never met before) that she's coming as well =)   Iona greeted me with a bow and said, "Hajimemashite!" =P She's a funny, giggling lot; an interesting personality =D Geok Leng was pestering me (which she did in school before as well &gt;_&gt;) to  belanja  her  makan , on the basis that I didn't treat her after "9 years of friendship" XD   The church concert was nice, but the preaching was...dull. I barely understood what he's talking about, and we weren't interested at all (maybe except Ding :P). We even keyed our messages to each other via handphones, and showed the person sitting next to us what we were keying (an elderly man hushed us after we chatted among each other). Iona keyed in on her handphone, "Evolution of instant messaging". rofl XD   Joe and Geok Leng escaped to Holiday Villa's swimming pool, which I found out later and joined them for a short moment. Iona went back first (she  tumpang  us in her dad's car, to go to the nearby 7-Eleven). From there, we walked to SS15's infamous Salmon Steak with Shearn (which was Ding's real name), and ate our dinner there. I had to  belanja  Geok Leng, of course. XD Shearn was fasting for spiritual purposes, and he eats only breakfast. /swt   Went back at roughly 11.30pm with Geok Leng's car, which was extremely comfy (no idea what car that is). Reached home at near 12am. Watta busy day &gt;_   
     

    
</post>
<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       It’s the perfect whether of sorts when it comes to a day where we do a lot of walking. Yeah, it rained. Gloomy, droopy rain.   It all started when Gopi, Jeremy, Heng Li and I set off with high spirits to various educational institutes to request them to advertise in our school magazines. Gopi lugged his bag around that weighs thrice of my own school bag, while Heng Li decidedly brought along his lightweight bag which his connecting straps tore during the beginning of our trip.Mr Victor (our discipline teacher) gave us a letter, stating said students are given permission to go out of school to find sponsors for school magazine. Whee.   Gopi’s mum brought us first to Taylor’s College at SS15, braving the traffic jam along the way. “We are determined people,” Gopi reminded us several times, as we looked like some fools in a school uniform playing truant. Our first visit went okay, and the lady in charge said that he would contact us soon. So far so good.   Walking underneath the cold pelts of the rain, we proceeded to Inti with similar results. After finishing our McDonald’s breakfast, the rain seemed to be lesser than before, and we went for the Metropolitan College, again, with similar results. “We’re idiots wearing school ties,  dei ,” said Gopi.   We boarded a number 10 Metrobus to Sunway Pyramid. From there we went to The One Academy, under the pouring rain, with me shielding my precious gelled hair with Gopi’s nifty file-holder. We were made to sit down by the receptionist and waited for roughly 10-15 minutes, who told us that the person-in-charge’s line was engaged. After watching some highly unenlightening advertisements made by the academy itself on the nearby TV, the receptionist told us that that particular person is not in. Oh joy.   We went inside Sunway Pyramid and used the walkway to Sunway Hotel. I’m sure we looked like school kids playing truant, and we reaffirmed it by saying, “The difference is, we’re wearing school ties.” I mean, how many students playing truant did you see wear their school ties?We trotted a long distance to our next destination, Sunway College. Walking under the rain, Jeremy started singing “I’m a big, big boy, in a big, big world…” when the rain pelted down heavier (I’m sure it’s those overhanging trees with their big, big leaves &gt;_&gt;).   Gopi, the great one, actually managed to jump across an Olympic-sized pool (albeit with some effort)! Take that and put it at a scale of 1/1,000,000, and you’ll see that it resembles that of an Olympic-sized pool to an ant. “It’s a miracle!” exclaimed Heng Li, somewhat sarcastically. “Now I believe in miracles!”   “I feel pathetic,” I mumbled. The rain was dying away, though the drops were still pouring onto us with cold winds chilling our skin (perhaps Gopi wouldn’t feel a thing, thanks to his  tisu adipos  &gt;_&gt;). We arrived at Sunway College, our legs aching, but our spirits were still high, until –   “Please wait,” said the guard, which contacted the head guard we presumed. We waited for quite a long time – about 20 minutes perhaps – and we overheard the guard mentioning that we’re in our school uniform. Okay…   After the head guard showed up, he asked us for our driving license. Yay, WTF? And he didn’t accept ICs either. Thankfully, Jerm brought his student card and that moron accepted it. The other kindly guard wanted to tell us where the “Students Services” were but that illegitimate son of a female dog gestured unpleasantly at us while making a “GOGOGO!” noise that resembles a dying bulldog.   Jeremy wore a tag we all presumed was the visitor’s pass, but on closer look, it says in big bold words  CONTRACTOR . Rofl. We wandered ourselves and found Monash University’s reception centre; the receptionist was most kind, and was very friendly, which is what we needed after that encounter with that bastard. She even exclaimed on seeing Jeremy’s unusual pass. XD   We handed in the letter which quotes the various ridiculously cheap prices that our school offered to her, and next we went for Sunway College’s reception. We got our deal of RM200 from Sunway College on the spot! o_O (full page, black and white, RIDICULOUSLY CHEAP). That was like a light shining through this dark, dreary day, and our efforts before seemed worth it.   After deciding underneath the drizzle where to head next, we cancelled off plans to go to KDU (as we had no idea how to go there), and went for Taipan USJ10 after dropping off Jeremy at Prime College, Summit from a cab. We walked around to various shops and educational centres which we think would accept us (before I can open my mouth when I entered Big Bookshop, the old lady at the counter said immediately, “Boss not in!”).   One computer-related learning centre accepted our offer (she said she’s considering full page, back page, black and white, RM500. Again, RIDICULOUSLY CHEAP). April, the lady, was kind as well =P   After finishing our lunch at McD’s (yet again), we went to Erica’s mum’s house (Gopi called her teacher Anne). She’s willing to advertise in our school magazine, although she said she’d rather it be “Best Compliments from …”, as she said she get her students from word-of-mouth, and not advertisements. Very kind of her.  All in all, it was fun, and I've certainly gained a certain experience and knowledge from this. =)   
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Got my haircut two days back from the salon I usually frequent to, which is opposite my house. " Zhing pok, slope! " was what Andy recommended, so uh, I tried it as well. We wanted to go to Geok Leng's auntie's salon, but it's RM16 o_O So we decided against it XD (we being me, WH, and Jon).   So the next day after school, WH and Jon stood in front of my house with their new haircut XD It's like staring at the same hairstyle, but maybe a little different individually. Jon's hair is already damn short, yet he cuts again =.=" But all of us looked better though :D   Tomorrow I'll be heading to some of those colleges near Sunway (Taylor's, etc etc) with Heng Li, Gopi and Jerm, to  beg  them to advertise in our school mag &gt;_&gt; Gopi called ourselves the  ambassadors  of U8; rofl XD   On a side note, I want a guitar. /swt Joe's been raving about playing it and all &gt;_</post></Blog>