<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      'time, the devourer of all things' .....or something like that...i forgot the exact translation....so dont kill me...  people do that ya'know....kill me that is.....for any minor boo boo on my part....sigh!!...but i guess thats what life is about..killing people for no serious reason at all...that is what is goin on nowadays! ...isnt it?.....  well anyways...im here...its my turn to 'express' myself...all this time...thoughts just bulding up inside me ...accumulating...they shall be set free....bwahahahhahahah!!! ......ahem!!....*cough  i hate u......
     
    
</post>
<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      “welcome to the darkside”. This is what a dear friend said when I told him that I wanted to play an online mmorpg. Him and some others have totally been engrossed in that fictional world for more than 2 years….the latest victim being another dear friend who has been doing nothing but ‘xp’ing’ for the last couple of months. And now…..uberness prevails…..  What is it all about, I mean WHAT IS ALL THIS ABOUT?!!...u suddenly find urself as  part of another world. A world with ‘other’ friends, where you go about roaming the landscape killing whatever stands in your way, moving from one ‘zone’ to another, searching for items which wud make your ‘character’ more powerful, grouping up with other players to kill more stronger enemies to gain more l337 l00t, giving you more abilities, more experience ….interesting aint it?  ...ahem!...   ’sorry bro…cant cya tnight…gotta attend a xegony raid…yea….k….bye….’ WTF!? ‘nah man….cant go to the gym…im in the middle of getting my epic’ WTF!?x2 ‘not in the mood to go out…have to spend time with the family, …plus gotta kill this mob …uber drops’ ….. o_O….k…nevermind then….  and then there was one late night call…’oye yaar…guess what item I picked up..check this out – 18/20 double hander, +50 to all stats, sv- 40, 100 mana, 100 hp, right click heal instant cast, quad proc’ ….I don’t know what I wrote here…but it sounded something like it!.....  never ending discussions of what one did at a particular moment in the game, how one used the abilities to overcome a really difficult situation….gives one a sense of satisfaction …definitely…but that is all u get…….constant bickering abt mistakes made in the game, ….’u cant kill a mob if it were snared, slowed, dd’ed, rooted, poisoned and down to 10% hps, …u suck at this game’ …or maybe even ‘bro…I died…my corpse is in a weird place…no one willing to gimme rez….do something la!!!’....blah blah blah blah…..  …..sigh….the bastards at verant (game developer) and soe (sony online entertainment) ….destroying innocent lives…ermm….well not innocent….kindly ignore that!....  hard to understand in the beginning, but it all makes sense when u hear about all this for more than 2 years…I guess its my turn now…to see what really makes em tick!...i bid thee farewell ……for now…  I have to go xp….plus need to buy this really uber bp….damn ….im running short of cash….  /shouts …..wtf bro?….i need some pps…. 
     
    
</post>
</Blog>