<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   juz heard the ling zhi ying yue ri ji again.. suddenly i realise wad she said veri true. hahax.. 我们 is so diff hor? hahax. 

						
</post>
<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   你看过了许多美景 你看过了许多美女 你迷失在地图上 每一道短暂的光阴 你品尝了夜的的巴黎 你踏过下雪的北京 你熟记书本里 每一句你最爱的真理  却说不出你爱我的原因 却说不出你欣赏我哪一种表情 却说不出在什么场合我曾让你动心 说不出离开的原因  你累计了许多飞行 你用心挑选纪念品 你搜集了地图上 每一次的风和日丽 你拥抱热情的岛屿 你埋葬记忆的土耳其 你流连电影里美丽的不真实的场景  却说不出你爱我的原因 却说不出你欣赏我哪一种表情 却说不出什么场合我曾让分心 说不出旅行的意义  勉强说出你为我寄出的每封信 都是你离开的原因 你离开我 就是旅行的意义  

						
</post>
<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   i tink i saw kyoko today. tsk.. so disappointed wif myself. how come i still cannot overcome it huh? this famous quote from a OD author made me believe in it ever more..'maybe it's really something magical abt being the 1st crush...  she's ideal, almost perfect, untouchable... cos i'm just this nobody attracted to her... when so many other better looking, fitter, richer, wittier guys are after her. who am i? i am no musician, no entertainer, no model, no perfect gentleman... who am i to seek someone so ideal?' she has this uncanny ability dat make me distracted. first it was prelim, den came 'o' level. i could not and did not study for the a maths paper 2 and physics. she gave me probably the most distraught xmas i have ever past. i was determine to forget abt her on the birthday when she did not reply abt the gift. or maybe she din noe? or maybe she din receive?   haix.. i have alot habits dat cannot change.. i will always to choose to walk the long way around the coffeeshop.. round the shops.. den back home. i will always to at her window whenever i pass .. but the optimism never came close to helping me.    i should end off any lingering hope now.. no point being distracted to her.   

						
</post>
<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   如果说了后悔 是不是一切就能倒退回忆多么美 活着多么狼狈为什么这个世界 总要叫人常伤悲我不能了解 也不想了解我好想好想飞 逃离这个疯狂世界那么多苦 那么多累 那么多莫名的泪水我好想好想飞 逃离这个疯狂的世界如果是你 发现了我 也别将我挽回想了你一整夜 再也想不起你的脸你是一种感觉 写在夏夜晚风里面青春是挽不回的水 转眼消失在指尖用力的浪费 再用力的后悔   this was the song dat caught my attention. from den on, i became a keen admirer of the rock band from taiwan. their music and lyrics have alot of feel n meaning to me i muz say. the lastest 时光机 possess one of the greastest lyric of all time~   it goes like this... 那阳光 碎裂在熟悉场景 好安静  一个人 能背多少往事 真不轻 谁的笑 谁的温暖的手心 我着迷 伤痕好像都变成了 曾经  全剧终 看见满场空座椅 灯亮起 这故事 好像真实又像虚幻 的情境 只是那 好不容易被说服 的自己 借口又顶不住懊恼的侵袭  好后悔 好伤心 想重来 行不行 再一次 我就不会走向这样的结局 好后悔 好伤心 谁把我 放回去 我愿意 付出所有来换一个时光机  对不起 独自回荡在空气 没人听 最后又是孤单 到天明  真的痛 总是来的很轻盈 没声音 从背后 慢慢缓缓抱着我 就像你 你和我 还有很多的地方 还没去 为何留我荒唐的坐在这里   steady~ confirm!    this is my fav line.. '这世界全部的漂亮，不过妳的可爱模样' 

						
</post>
<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   the template i chosen looks like those ancient times where pirates roam. the yellowish background and cursive writings make it look real lor.. but blog like not veri good lehx.. cannot delete entries. 

						
</post>
<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    i juz saw the frenster of kyoko.. she is in a relationship.    actually i saw it coming.. is juz a matter of time.    

						
</post>
<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   自从那天开始我认识了你 整个世界就变的 有点不一样  你散发出来的那种自然的魅力 让我深深的对你着 了迷 被吸引  爱 不可以伪装 我 变的默默的紧张 心 怎么小鹿在乱撞  为何手机还没有响 因为 有你在我的身旁 靠近 弥漫着你的想象  发现 只要我想着你 忽然之间失去方向 爱一起慢慢慢慢的向我靠近  怎能够预见了你我是如此幸运 如果说爱就是要让我们在一起  感谢上帝 我会带着你去找寻甜蜜 爱一起慢慢慢慢的向我靠近  怎能够遇见了你我是如此幸运 如果说爱就是要让我们在一起  感谢上帝 我会带着你去找寻甜蜜    

						
</post>
<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   我会想念你 我不会忘记 永远想念你 直到在相遇说  在前好难忍住泪水好难 离别这一刻我不甘心放手 我会好好过勇敢又坚强 那就像钱包丢掉所有的烦恼 不要在回头走你要走的路 总会有一天我们会在相聚 我会想念你 我不会忘记 永远想念你 直到在相遇 我会想念你 你不必担心 永远想念你 直到在相遇 因为你的善良 因为你天真 让我感觉到拥有你好幸福 你因该知道好舍不得滴 留下的泪水一颗颗的是爱  最后得言语句句都是感伤 那先说在前我永远爱你 我会想念你 我不会忘记 永远想念你 直到在相遇 我会想念你 你不必担心 永远想念你 直到在相遇  

						
</post>
<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Don't Wanna Think About You  by Simple Plan   Album :   Submitted by : SAGE  Corrected by :     Can you leave me here alone now  I don't want to hear you say that you know me  that I should be always doing what you say  'cause I'm trying to get through today  and there's one thing I know   I don't wanna think about you  or think about me  don't wanna figure this out  don't wanna think about you  or think about nothing  don't wanna talk this one out  won't let you bring me down   'cause i know  don't wanna think about you  don't wanna think about you   When I wake up here tomorrow  things will never be the same  'cause I won't wait  'cause you won't change  and you'll always be this way  now I'm gunna get through today  and there's one thing I know   Don't wanna think about you  or think about me  don't wanna figure this out  don't wanna think about you  or think about nothing  don't wanna talk this one out   this time  won't let you bring me down  won't let you shut me out  this time I know  don't wanna think about you   run away, run away  im running as fast as i can  run away, run away  i'll never come back again  run away, run away   don't wanna think about you  or think about me  don't wanna figure this out  think about me  don't wanna talk this one out   Don't wanna think about you  or think about me  don't wanna figure this out  don't wanna think about you  or think about nothing  don't wanna talk this one out   this time  won't let you bring me down  won't let you shut me out  this time I know  don't wanna think about you   run away, run away  don't wanna think about you  run away, run away  don't wanna think about you  run away, run away  don't wanna think about you  run away, run away     

						
</post>
<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   我受够了等待 你所谓的安排 说的未来到底多久才来 总是要来不及 才知道我可爱 我想依赖而你却都不在 应该开心的地带 你给的全是空白 一个人假日发呆 找不到人陪我看海  我在幸福的门外 却一直都进不来 你累积给的伤害我是真的很难释怀  终于看开爱回不来 而你总是太晚明白 最后才把话说开 哭着求我留下来 终于看开爱回不来 我们面前太多阻碍 你的手却放不开 宁愿没出息求我别离开  你总是要我乖 慢慢计划将来 我的眼泪却一直掉下来 过去怎么交代 你该给的信赖 被你亲手缓缓推入悬崖 从我脸上的苍白 看到记忆慢下来 过去甜蜜在倒带 只是感觉已经不在  而我对你的期待 被你一次次摔坏 已经碎成太多块要怎么拼凑跟重来  终于看开爱回不来 而你总是太晚明白 最后才把话说开哭着求我留下来 终于看开爱回不来 我们面前太多阻碍 你的手却放不开 宁愿没出息求我别离开 终于看开爱回不来 而你总是太晚明白 最后才把话说开哭着求我留下来 终于看开爱回不来 我们面前太多阻碍 你的手却放不开 宁愿没出息求我别离开  

						
</post>
<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   from far, everything looks good. almost fantasy, almost dream-like. Perfect, because most of what we make of it was made up by us, by our own mind, by our own ideals. we added the touches of perfection shaped by our ideals to the otherwise blurred image.  

						
</post>
</Blog>