<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      This Blog doesn't exist. You will be redirected to my site.  If it doesn't work,click  urlLink here     
     

    
</post>
<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Neone doing nething on friday??? My last resort is SRC sports day...which seems da option at da moment. Leave ne comments to wat u mite do n where u mite go. Cheers
      
</post>
<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hiya ... i'll post my 'likely' subject choices 4 next yr.... ahhhhhh lil johnny's growin up soooooooooo fast.  yr 11:  3 Maths  2 Economics  2 Physics  2 Chemistry or Business (chem prolly)  2 English + 1 ext english (or Jap) ..... english sux... boring as but jap used 2 b worse. i wasn't gonna do it but den im  a lot  better at eng den jap (my rank in eng(grade) was same as jap(class) =8. no fob 4 me ^-^) but i h8 it how teachers go on about all dis meaningful crap dats supposedly tryin 2 b told by the author. n then while harry was torkin 2 teacher bout 3 Unit next yr she's like "you're gonna do ext eng next yr rite..... Jonathan" n them im like damnnnnn. "yeah errr... welllll ummmm.... most prolly". Dang those piercing eyes cut me deep, sweat poured down my back, i felt my face slowly changin hue I just couldn't say no.... ahhh the pressure. so i guess now im stuck wif 3 U, if i'd said no... english marks = DOWN. O wellz i can drop it in yr 12 n pik up 4 U maths (no im not a nerd, im simply azn). and js rndmly "friends...NOT boy/girl-friend" oooooo andy's got a bf..... keke *cough*  andy unsure of his sexual preference  *cough*.. ahhh we knew it all along. and yes andy i kno wat u mean but it still sounds funny. :P
      
</post>
<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      WARNING: author is pissed and will ramble and rant. ok. im pissed. mum chucked a psycho when she found out about me organising fundraising for our formal -.-;; that just sux. she demanded that i withdraw from organising it altogether, and im only allowed to sell 2 boxes now. far out. but that was sortta ok. and then she went on about how i go online too much and how i don't tell her when I go online ie. sneaking on without telling her. she said that she had had enough and the punishment would be that i won't allowed to go to the formal! aRgH! i'm sorry shues &gt;. RANT #1 ||| wtf cant parents (esp mine) lay off a bit? they have to follow you around and keep track of what you do, when where and why. what they don't understand is the fact that maybe if they lay off a bit, it would work out fine, maybe even better! take for example, reports. if they would let you do anything, ie. go online whenever, sleep whenever, watch TV whenever, go out whenever, etc. whose to say that one's report won't remain at a high standard. ok, maybe i exaggerated it a bit - obviously parents have to impose SOME restrictions. but can't they loosen up a bit and stop being so uptight? they aren't even willing to try and let us go wild. cant they try it once and see just how effective it is to let us have more freedom? and it's not like my results were that crap *ignores all the techs at school*. far out. its not like i have to top the class in every subject!! so why cnt parents just loosen up a bit and let us be? RANT #2 ||| why do parents, azn ones in particular have such a big problem with us mingling with the opposite sex? don't they understand, as shues pointed out, that we cannot get outta uni and find a wife/husband settle down and have kids in a flash? we need time to gradually get to that goal -- and that time is usually high school. we need to have the opportunity to communicate and understand the opposite sex. understand them as FRIENDS will be sufficient. but even talking to them as FRIENDS cannot happen because one's parents don't trust you, they don't want to risk the 0.000001% (as zbaras said, 98% of statistics are false ^__^) chance of you: a) for a guy to impregnate a girlfriend or b) for a girl to get impregnated by a guy far out! and they say WE watch too much TV...obviously they watch too much of those stupid today tonight reporters interviewing that small percentage (in comparison to the rest of em) of pregnant teens and their bfs. and also the fact that due to our absolutely obsessive love for our partners that we will fail academically. because of these factor, they believe that we should avoid the opposite sex until we get into uni -___-'' ok. let's just say (sounds like an 'even if' debate) that there is a remote chance of this happening. but even so, is it bad enough that they have to stop us from being FRIENDS with the opposite sex? KEY WORD: friends...NOT boy/girl-friend. if anyone can answer this question, please do. i'm eager to find out the answer. RANT #3 ||| this really isn't that big of a rant but i think it concerns a large majority of us. in regards to the formal, DO NOT stress. it is FOUR WHOLE months away! well i suppose for the girls...they're dresses will take forever to find so you should have started. besides that, you can all wait for a while longer to find bloody dates. calm down pplz! don’t fight over ppl either. LMAO -.-" so anyway, if you skimmed through that and didn't get the most important thing about this blog, then here it is again: I AM NOT ALLOWED TO GO TO THE FORMAL NOW *damn* SO LADIES, NO NEED TO RUSH TO ASK ME AS YOUR DATE ^__^ keke. ok, maybe the last bit wasn't necessary. hehe  anyone else not going to the formal? i would like to know, maybe we can organise something ^__^  until next time --- bye! 
      
</post>
<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I personally think that 12 for Prelim n 10 for HSC is not enuf.. cos it's just too narrow n risky...  ... IF Software Design goes well THEN     do 12 units for prelim     do 10 units for HSC ELSE     do 14 units for prelim     do 12 units for HSC ENDIF ...  ... get it?  Anyways... i'll probably do:  2 english (Fobbish me) 4 maths (though i'm not dat gud... = 45th) 2 commerce subject 2 musik 2 physics (2 not decided yet...)  = 14...  
      
</post>
<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      In this point in time i think i'll do:  3 maths 3 english 2 chem 2 phys or bio 2 engineering or one of the commerce subjects  That's it!!  
      
</post>
<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      lolz...wayne, notice that adro said, if you're a member...BLOG it up? haha. anyhow. adro you should already know mine but i'll post ---  3 Maths, 4 English or 4 Maths, 3 English -- ionno yet, depends on how i go. 2 Chem, 2 or 3 Jap, 2 Legal Studies.  i may not do jap if i do legal and vice versa. but for now...these are my choices. cheers adro.  so anyone else care to share their sub selections at this point in time?
      
</post>
<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well me and my dad had a talk yesterday about subject selections for next year, and I was just interested in what everyone else was planning to do as well. So yeah, if you could post it up if you're a member, or leave it in the comments section that would be great. (Something serious on this blog for once... haha). Well anyway, at the moment I'm hoping to do:                    3 English                       2 Economics                   3 Maths                         2 Legal Studies                   2 Ancient History  Hmm... that's providing that I get a better rank for Maths in second semester. Now that doesn't sound too promising does it?
      
</post>
<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
          I'm so seriously bored it's not funny         As you can tell from the absolute boredom it took to create this         So yeah....         leave a comment if you feel inclined to...    
      
</post>
<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
         HOPEFULLY getting chocolates on MONDAY *grins at emymui  co.* keke     organised formal fundraising stuff today ^___^ currently in last period jap....so bored... took vball and debating photos today...skipped 5th period. yay! chem next....*bored* wayne says its boring too...so anyway. nothin to talk about. but i vow that our blog will not die out before the fruitsalad blogs. *grins at gill and co. keke*  baibai.
      
</post>
<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
         FUNDRAISING 4 FORMAL meeting --- Lunchtime B11 until further notice     doing science h/w. prolly won't finish it &gt;.  went to see work xp guy today...man...downing centre district court has tight security. they took my scissors before i was allowed in with jeff -____-''  so anway. sorry guyz about the cancellation of the supposed meeting today...stupid roll office lady didn't put it up for friday. so whoever reads this...the meeting is tomoz at lunchtime --- tell everyone! you are fundraising for your OWN ticket. however, if you do have excess money *grins* i'm sure your friend wouldn't mind the money. i'm sure a lot of ppl will struggle to rake in the money for the formal by themselves...hopefully fundraising will help. even if you aren't going...you can still help ^___^ like ian. thnx mate. see you guyz tomorrow!
      
</post>
<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Stupid school reports, my parent's are so pissed! cos i got ranked over 130/150 for both history n geography... (mai bad!)  Oh well... Betta luck next term...  But i guess i did alrite overall...   Oh yea.. an another thing...  Anyone interested in beta testing my snake game? It's pretty dodgy, but it serves it's purpose...  n Beta testing's a component of my major project.. so  Please help me!  You can download a copy of my game from  urlLink Here    Oh well... leave you guys to it...    Hehe... i'm the first one to start this marquee thingy...  But then  Andy  and   wayne   starts copying it...  
      
</post>
<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Once again, it is only I who on this group blog that actually uses proper English, and spelling. I can safely say that all those below and above me will most probably be using horrible truncations and acronyms that should safely stay within the boundaries of a chat program window, and never more. I do not care how absolutely cool it may be in writing in inane and mindless gibbers, as that would really show how education is being wasted. Also the only way I could become cool would be by living inside a fridge for three months.  If one observed the frequencies of my posts on this blog, then one would be able to find out that this is only the second post so far. It is mainly because of my general style of blogging that I believe would make it stand out too much from the average blogger crowd. That is why I mainly post in my own blog, which is untainted by grammatical mutilations and second-rate spelling.  So, if anybody wants to see some real fevered ranting using correct English and suchlike, then www.wellerzheng.blogspot.com is where most of it can be found.    This post was not shameless self-promotion disguised in any form. Nor does it contain any blatant subliminal messages, although you may get an urge to join the Navy. Only sick twisted conspiracy artists, such as those claiming that table tennis is not a sport and NSB is lesser than James Ruse, would spread such profane rumours. golb ym daer golb ym daer golb ym daer golb ym daer golb ym daer golb ym daer golb ym daer golb ym daer golb ym daer. 
      
</post>
<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Tuesday debate against Chats..... stupid koziol paranoid bout gettin bashed... but then again if i was him i prolly wud be 2. i bludged 4th speka ^-^, read tomorrow series (sooo gud) during prep.. and randomly poked andy and .... errrr inspected adro's bag. hehe gw adro no... ummmmmmm *coughcough* vocal chord problems this tiiiimmmmmmmme. neway afta i killed time in chats.. n den went 2 my ortho.. stupid trian was 17 mins l8 so i had 2 run to ortho wen i shuda just strolled in grrrrrrrr. Gud test 4 my hip neway 4 socca. well went to hornsby 2 shop a lil afta where i  GOT MAH PHONE  it wuz sold out n like 5 shops so i wasn't gonna get it den js saw it on da way out n got it ^-^. its sum dodgy phone, was gonna get Sony Ericsson T230 (sooooo cute n tiny), isn't as gud but i'd get it js 4 da lookz :P. won't post numba here 4 same reason as adro didn't post his email "*darts eyes*". socca 2day, first real game played for 3rds afta 3 forfeits, injury 2 me :(, strike and bye. n guess wat we lost, well actually if u read jacks blog u wouldnt hv 2 guess, neway, report 2moz, i can c dere'll b a major posting of ranks, marks etc. Andy i fink we need a ladder :P. I won't post mine unless i'm da best in da group (jack u ruin everything.....).
      
</post>
<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Sport is da shining light in an othawise crappy week of skool. But dat light often gets dimmed by constant losing...  3rd Grade Soccer - Lost 2-1 to Epping 3rds Solo goal to Alex. Fairly decent performance  2nd Table Tennis - Lost to Epping 2nds Supposedly murdered. (Thnx Benlee)  15s Hockey - Lost 7-1 to Epping 15's THRASHED, OBLITERATED, etc.  So as one can see, our skool is quite crap at sport. I think da word "victory" got ripped out wen dey were handing free, yes dats da only ones we can afford, dictionaries to da skool.  N yes, we get our reports 2moro...WATCH THIS SPACE!!!
      
</post>
<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      yes...we won debating against chatswood high!!! not by much unfortunately...but all the same we won. technically...the debate was pathetic --- both teams defined the topic as totally different things --- they defined it too truistically though ^___^ the topic was about 'that jobs are more important than future trees". we thought it was a metaphorical debate...stupidly ignoring the environment factor in our case altogether...i spoke for like less than 3 minutes. we defined it as jobs in today's society having higher priority over family, social life and social issues (lack of environment?!?!?). they defined it truistically as developing for the future -___-'' you got to admit...it was a realli crappy debate. but now we're in the next round! yay! HAPPY BDAY JAMES! yes...a bit random. almerick...stop being a retard --- damn spamming our tagboard using alias...this applies to wannabe spammers and also james in and benlee yap *glares* and mabel...i shall 'DUH' you for the rest of eternity ^__^ keke. i modified my layout for those critical morons...ie JACK. i changed the navigation panel and also added a 'home' link as suggested by jono and jack.
      
</post>
<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      As da title states...Happy B'Day James!!!   
      
</post>
<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well sure enough, I'm back, and what a bludgy week it's been. First there was the public holiday on Monday, where the Queen played no part in anybody's day off and I decided to dog Andy and buy wood (???). Then that assembly on Tuesday, where I ranted about RICE... come to think of which... COME TO RICE!!  Weekend, weekend. It's been a good one. Challenged to take God's word more seriously and spent more time reading the Bible and AWAY from the computer!!   And Andy, look seriously, your new layout's good. I mean you should see me trying to design a web page.. even Junwoo could laugh at me!! Trying to learn Photoshop myself at the moment. Oh, and check out the footer at the bottom of the page. (me!)  Hmm.. and yes. Ask me for my new email address. Don't want to put it up here just in case evil spammers are lurking on introspective...*darts eyes*  Anyway, I am sleeping too late and it's time I got some rest. So yeah maybe I'll blog during our science lesson tomorrow in class. Until then, later. 
      
</post>
<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      1)go away bloody yap and james...the nerve! the go and copy almo's annoying style of spamming OUR tagboard? !#$%^ off....and the nrequest permission to JOIN our blog?!? far... 2)ok...so y is my new layout so bad? is it cos it relates to like none of those who have actually seen it? ie. wayne, jack, fatdoggie. stupid *lets barr all azn films+music* pfft. and considering they dont even have their own websites with the exception of doug. you pplz are in no position to critisise...annie, lora, yi, feng ying, hum, etc DO!  on a happier note, i am totally surprised at the lack of heavy critism which i am used to from grandmaster chow ^___^ haha... these couple of days have been hectic. haven't done any homework watsoever...attended my lil cusins bday gathering...slept over, woke up in the middle of the night and watched 1 hour of some random movie...saw the mando version of KOMA (thnx mabs)....it was GREAT! im gettin the canto one on dvd too! yay! karena has the *im playing with your mind* look about her in the movie ^___^ chinese skool --- boring as usual, played honey cave two on daz's fone for most of the lesson...no more cskool for another 5 wks! good ol' debating training day at UTS  next wk. speaking of debating...we better not lose to chatswood high on tuesday *panics* but if nsg lost to st ives high....*snickers* no offense kiz...you weren't there anyway. sounds like nsg had a bloody cold time at DOE...and wat the random tags from iliah on the fruitsalad site?! and then a weird blog...how can you be bothered to write that iliah?!?! so anyway....keke...more vcd's to pore over this wk...a horror one with karena *AGAIN!! ^__^* and leslie *da one that passed away &gt;.  ~~baibai...oh, happy bday to vivian (thursday last wk), emily (friday last wk), lil cusin (tomoz) and james (tuesday) !!!! *so many!?!?!?*
      
</post>
<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      ..... Got caned in bball AND socca, dats 2 canages in like 12 hrs.. well mbe 15 hrs. 54-11 and 7-0. Im so used 2 losin dat i now hv immunity to da pissed offness of losin. Yeah well afta bball on Friday there was dis ABA game (didn't kno wat it was until Arun was like yeah soz guys doggin u to go watch..... thankfully he played :P). It wuz afta game neway and i was like :| wth omg ........... massive huge giant 7ft+ dudes ez dunkin.... We were like ok lets watch, dis rep team's prolly gud and den dey said "would u plz now stand for da national anthem" and I was like :| wth omg all ova again, dese guyz must b pro. Hornsby Spiders got caned nearly as badly as us :P by Norths team hu hit every 3 and it wuz 39-13 at quarter time. ^-^ new inspiration to practice. n we were like I losing would make no difference if we could verse dese guyz just to watch em cane us and dunk n do all these mad cool trix.   P.S gw Wayne uv officially got da title of most commented blog on ur .. controversial money whining blog
      
</post>
<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      We had da most hilarious day in chinese skool. Firstly, while we sat in our class, pretending to learn, a head teacher came along n said we were going to get kicked out by little yr 1s. And wen we moved into da hallways, where a makeshift table was used...Den i got pissed. It was fuckn cold n dim, making it a great classroom :) Afta 30 mins of pain, we eventually got to move....to a room where there was only 3 ppl. (Rove: DUUUUUHHHHHH!!!!) It took dem a goddam half n hour to find a room....where dere was only 3 ppl...Dats wen i really got pissed.   But dat was da end of da shit I had to take. During break, we dogged da teacher, went to CFN, played CS, with my team getting canned cos none of dem could get at least a 1:1 ratio (of course i could :P) n went bak with 20 mins of class to go.   Da teacher didnt even care....which was da sweet part. Den agen, were pretty "trustworthy". HAHAHAHAHAHAHAHA...  Did neone see Zlatan Imbrahimozvic's goal agenst Italy??? ABSOLUTE PURE MAGIC b CHEEKINESS TO DA MAX...  GO DA EAGLES...KILL DA BUNNIES 2day.
      
</post>
<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      thx to adrian for inviting me into this elite group of random ppl ill admit once again it was I who spammed that tagboard for a bit...got called lamer than almo and receive mulitple death threats from a person under the alias 'tran' n lastly if u happen to play mafia...always kill mak first, then the su's, the wu
      
</post>
<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Awww... wat you meen go to the gym, n ban B-ball?  I thought the PE teachers were pretty slack...  Just because we didn't want to watch a movie with the school, doesn't allow them to treat us like that...  ... but we still had fun Hehe.. had like 3 hrs of   Summer   rehearsal... that killed time!  Hope you guys who have watched the movie think it's good....   Oh yea... n another thing...   Happy Birthday, Emily!   ... hehe  awww.. script's not allowed on blogger...
      
</post>
<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      GOD DANG...Not too gud.   Sheehan...plz stop telling ppl to do dat.  OLE!!! Allez Francais!!! J'aime l'equipe de francais. Henry est tres superbe. Trezeguet, Saha, Silvestre est aussi. Cependant, Zizou est le numero un. Le free kick est magnificente, car il marquent toujours les buts.  OLE!!! Go Ronaldo...Figo and Van Nistelrooy. As well as others.  OLE!!!
      
</post>
<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      man! it was so cold today! argh! i kinda feel sorry for nsg DOE'ers. lolz. have fun in the cold! but our one was actually worse....it was snowing AND it was longer too. so yeh. in the spirit of cheerfulness...there have been many good happenings. both my mum AND dad have gotten jobs...outta the blue for my mum ^___^. my friendship with yi seems to be resuming. bludge day tomorrow. just feeling in a happy mood now. besides the fact that my mum is sick &gt;. thank you wayne for your most truthful essay bout our school's financial status. just in time for those yr 6 selective people eh? lolz.  storm the castle sounded realli crap....and shrek 2 sounds good...but expensive ^__^ which means im not going with the school. ill go in the hols or something. debating nxt wk against chatswood high. man, the pressure's on to win eh?! cRAP! more debating events coming up: one day event at macquarie uni and another one elsewhere in some currently unknown location. and ANOTHER three day one in the hols --- but that one's just to watch. saw sam gerber today when me and almo were in chatswood...wow, he has changed...looks more evil with his lack of transition glasses. lolz. anyway...time to go watch a chrstian chinese movie?....hehe *looks at ben, adro, doug, etc*
      
</post>
<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yeh...friday is supposedly a skool day! WTF??? I thought it was a bludge day...O wait, it still is!!!  First 3 periods...den ppl go to Shrek  N DATS WEN DA FUN STARTS!!!  Bball in gym...n den watching a certain movie??? Possibly.... OR IF HEIN IS GEY...No gym (replaced by soccer) wit a possible watching of a *certain* movie...  HAHAHAHAHA...We won soccer agen cos dey forfeited...othawise its been a pretty stable n reasonably average week  O yeh by da way...My cousins a fuckn freak...got 100 UAI......................
      
</post>
<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       	Our school needs money and a lot of it. Sure, you may be casually strolling past NSB one day and notice all the construction work going on in the front and think “wow this school can afford to build a new carpark, turfed area and new tennis courts” but think about this, it took our school something like 5 years to get the permit and federal funding for that. Most of that funding came from our parents anyway leading me to think that maybe the school has just been saving all the building fund donations from parents for the past 20 years in the eventuality that despite all the governments promises, there is no way in hell that they are going to give our school money.  	In the newspapers are few months ago, we all read that NSG had a million dollars in their trust fund, which made us NSB’s realize how much better our education could possibly be if we were taught at NSG. This notion was stopped when we got to the third letter of NSG, which we understood to mean girls. Obviously this created a problem. Fortunately for us boys (and NSG’s who read this), the mind of an adolescent male supposedly thinks about sex every eight seconds, so eight seconds later we promptly forgot about that topic and found something else to think about for the next eight seconds before we got distracted again.  Recently a friend from NSG asked a group of us whether our school actually followed a curriculum. Do people think that our school’s poverty is really that bad? The answer to that would be yes (the curriculum question, not the poverty one), but one can never be too sure. This question was asked following a brief exchange of what we have learnt in school so far and a comparison of textbooks. I have noted that in the subject of Latin we have the same textbooks, but they are ahead of us in learning and their textbook pages a white and shiny while ours a stained, tattered and yellow. They have one textbook for all the math classes while we have like five different textbooks for each of the five math classes. “Can’t afford a 150 book set” is what I thought I heard. I put that in, in the vain hope that a highly recognized public school education official with connections to the government will read this and increase our school funding or drastically cut funding to the girl’s school.  In the same session I also learnt that the level of information the girl’s are learning is much higher than what we are learning. This matter was put to rest when a friend said “Their teachers get paid”, which is a fair enough comment when you think about it.  I’m pretty sure that’s why NSG always beats our school in HSC rankings (the fact that boys are lazy bludgers, who wouldn’t do work if our lives depended on it had absolutely nothing to do with the rankings). It makes sense, paid teachers are happy teachers and it’s quite obvious that our teachers aren’t happy. For instance, today one of the geography classes had a substitute teacher. As I was leaving the school for sport, I saw the real teacher drive into the school and park his car. This prompted me to wonder whether our school is really bad enough to cause the teachers to jig. Of course the teacher in question could have been in an important meeting outside of school, but for the sake of the argument I’m going to assume that he wasn’t. So in the hope that someone important will read this I offer this ultimatum. Give us money or give us some of NSG’s money. It’s quite obvious that they don’t need it, girls are supposed to be resilient and I’m sure they’ll find a way to get more somehow. Failure to do so could result in hostile action. I mean we’ve already turned the school into a terrorist training camp with “Storm the Castle” and pretty soon you’ll have a bunch of semi-intelligent terrorists running around. Now you wouldn’t want that would you? 
      
</post>
<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well i kno wayne n jack'll prolly talk bout storm da castle but I'm gonna get in first n brainwash u all. Don't kno  how dey thought our skool was a castle, mbe illusions from getting thrashed by melbourne hi in crawford shield, mbe we gotta storm dere castle n steal the shield bak next yr hey guys (sry Mr. I don't play sport and don't use sport in debatin). Wasn't even gonna go until hai chen stuffed his ankle at socca trainin, 1 hr b4 da thing, he alrdy paid so i took his spot :P (I paid him of course). Yeah it was funnish but no offence prefects but organisation sucked. ppl cheated (i was innocent of course, until i stumbled onto a stash of weapons^-^). Dere were all dese rndm cadets in our skool, quite funny really just walking past wen they're all srs n stuff, wif dere funny hats (no offence wayne, ben and co). I got wasted so i gave up and just got absolutely soaked, n it was freezin, shuda thought b4 goin wif singlet n shorts from socca trainin, but i couldn't go home :( neway our group sucked and bloody curry group wif nearly double as many ppl won. Socca 2day guess wat? they forfeit again, u kno in da 6 wks dat i've joined 3rds socca we're undefeated,not to mention the um 3 forfeits, strike, bye etc dat we had hehe. and b4 dat dey lost every game. And i won't post my h/yrly marks ,not to "show some ppl up, namely Andy, wayne" and Jack. 
      
</post>
<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      short, bludge day today: p1-arrange jnr assembly, p2-jnr assembly, p3-science~sorta bludge, p4-jap in comp room...BLUDGE!, p5-eng-test results, p6-maths revision. really bludgy day ^__^ english results were ok. language came second in class i think. essay wasn't so good --- as usual. funny assembly with athletics carnival video and yr 10 kayak camp photos ^_-...nothin else happened today. really bludgy. SHREK on friday...doubt that i will go *sigh* $15!!!!!?!??! oh well...maybe before RICE events in holidays.
      
</post>
<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      ok well ill talk again :P First blog.... cos of sum1's stupid dead link (u can guess hu). On Friday no bball cos of sum stupid long wkend thingy even tho friday isn't part of the wkend. n den on Saturday we WON SOCCA. w00t first win all season 5-2. stanton scored lmao from a free kick, dats like first time in ..... ever. den rushed to chats to c HP3 n stupid train wasn't runnin to gordon so i had to w8 4 20 mins for bus n den had to w8 another 10 mins at gordon for train. ended up 20 mins l8 n 3 o'clock session was sold out so had to c it at 4&gt;.</post></Blog>