<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Since my last entry, I've gained a few highlights and heartaches... Bad first! Leaving FFXI is much harder then I originally thought it would be. All my friends I use to hang with in game, and chat with every minute will soon be near-gone.  "Near-gone" I left them my contact site ( http://www.geocities.com/jegsii/ranjik.html ) so we can still chat it up! But they are all still in game a lot too :P so they are... around, but not near.  HIGHLIGHTS!! :D Who can't be happy about highlights?  My job is selling video games for Gamestop in the mall :P The other day I signed a Commendation that not only did I get a copy for doing very good that week, but a copy got sent to corporate too. Same day I was asked how far I wanted to get in this company from my Manager.  Might not be the best job ever, but if I make it my career, I'm gonna go as far as I can. Telling this to my Assistant Manager, he started teaching me things :D Job is looking (in Strongbad’s voice ( http://www.homestarrunner.com )) very, very good!  Daily news. I've been praying most every morning and night. Tip: Even if you don't believe, I suggest you prey like today is your last. For you never truly know for sure when it will be. And what IF God is real? And if you start believing, what will you lose? Now think about what you'll gain if God IS real! I recommend that if you pray, pray like you mean it. Repent for your sins, yes, we all have 'em. And start believing :) I hope to see YOU in Heaven too.  New/old activity~! :) I'm thinking seriously about my story and my art. Of course I want to be the main creator and designer :P But my current skills suck in both writing and drawing. Reading mangas ( http://www.snoopycool.com ) got me thinking about a lot of things... my story is now far better then it would've been. I can't wait till I start practicing my skills! Which I start today when I go to the mall :P Beware passer-bys, for you may be one of my models for today ;P
      
</post>
<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Since last Sunday I've been doing things a little diffrent. The mornings I wake up (~10am!) get a good breakfast, pray, then eat.  Then I reed a few chapters in my Bible. Only about 2-3 pages each time. Then work out :D Do whatever till lunch time, usually errands in town. Get a healthy lunch :) Do whatever till dinner. Usually just chill. If I snack, I find fruits :D ~12am, I'm off to bed. But before I lay down, I pray again. Since Sunday, I've been a little happier :D Everything just feels better then before. I went for a walk in the woods in front of my house. Nice, peaceful, relaxing (till I jump down a cliff and quickly restep a few times while I slide down to the bottom). They cut down soo many trees &gt;</post></Blog>