<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The Y Factor  After my playtime with the kids on Saturday morning, I thought I would send you a weekend “rant”!  I thought a lot about what I would write about, world events, like the Middle East, nah, or jobless statistics in the US, nah, a nonevent.  So I guess I will discuss in my own dogmatic way “Love in a Relationship”.  It’s funny how many teenage girls hear the words “I love you” in the back seat of a Chevy just as the bra strap is cautiously being removed.  And then the girl feels the stick shift that the girl thinks is poking her in the side of the hip until she remembers she is in the “back seat” … dah!  Of course this teenage boy will forget he ever said these words 2 milliseconds after the words “no, stop” hit his ears.  This kind of “event” is happening every weekend in every small town and metropolitan city in America, and has been going on for years.    Of course even earlier in Egyptian days, if the guys got too frisky Cleopatra just had the guy’s hands, and / or other parts, chopped off .  These poor fellows were known as “eunuchs”  and the king had them working the queens quarters (for obvious “security” reasons) for the rest of their lives … what a boring life!  Think about it, you watch and help the queen bath everyday, and you can’t do anything about it, to yourself or others.  These eunuchs would have paid $1,000 for one pill of Viagra!   Well, back to the 21st century.  So what do these three little words mean, “I love you.” They are easily the most inappropriately overused words in the English language, and the most manipulative and misused (see above teenage example) words.  But what do they mean?  Are they the same for everybody, like the color “red” is always “red” to everybody?  But love is different in its interpretation by each individual … I think anyway!  I am not sure even the most prominent psychologists have discovered the precise meaning of the words, correct me if I am wrong here!  I have often felt the “in love” part of love was dramatically different from the just “loving” someone, like your sister or brother, or even husbands and wives in some situations (these couples keep therapist in business!).  I believe the “in love” part of the term refers to “the romantic intimacy combined with a pinch of lust”.  In other words the “strong desire for the physical sensuality with a heavy dose of respect” part of the relationship enduring in the couple to some degree due to the let’s call it “the Y Factor” still being present in the relationship.  The “Y Factor” is very elusive and a strangely mind-boggling item and the subject of about 500 million books.  And due to the fact these “Y Factor” (my term and I get the royalties to the term if it becomes famous!) books with the varied subject of love are still being written, and becoming best sellers, it is obvious that the answer to the question of definition and how to get the “Y Factor” remains a vague (what do I call it, thing, item, feeling, event … what?) term!  Well, not being a genius, accomplished clinical psychologist, or “unusually enlightened by heaven” I will not be able to truly answer this question … today, but maybe next week!  So I will not bore you any longer … till next week!          
     

    
</post>
<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well, yesterday afternoon, I thought to myself it’s my Friday night of true “personal unstressed freedom”, therefore I should venture out into the mysterious world of the “Urban Kansas City”, and explore the world. Hey, I have been watching “Sex and the City” for months, now it is my turn to see for myself the realities.  Of course I was taking one of my employees and his wife to dinner first, but that just an innocent looking “dodge”, my true adventure was a quest to witness the bar scene antics of “Sex and the City - "Kansas City style"!!  After my employee and his wife said their thank yous and good-byes, I sat down at the stressfully populated (the crowd looked like a 250lb woman in a size 6 polyester pants suit from the 1960s) main bar of the Capital Grille on the KC Plaza to start my “visual exploration”!  The following are the items I found “interesting  laughable”:  1) Why does a 65+ year old “lady” dye her hair bleach blonde, cruise the bar with a totally fake Julia Roberts grin, with plastered Tammy Baker eye liner, looking like the Saturday night “blue light” special from Billy Bob’s Retirement Village  Escort Service. This was not appetizing for the rest of the patrons who were waiting for a table to dine in the restaurant!  2) Why do bald, or almost bald men, in the 55 to 65 year old category insist on combing over the three hairs left on their head so it appears like they have more and better hair than Brad Pitt. You know, those 3 hairs with all that lacquered hair spray are more nervously starched on the top of these men’s heads than George W. Bush as the guest speaker at a Sierra Club dinner.  I say please guys, take a hint from Bruce Willis and Andre Agassi, just cut it short and BE YOURSELF. You are bald…. Get over it!  3) Of course I still can’t figure out these wealthy 55 year old male divorcees with their bold Tommy Bahama shirts (of course I love the less bold Tommy Bahama clothing) unbuttoned to their beer bellies with more gold chains than Mr. T from “Rocky II”.  I thought this went out in the 70s, or maybe they are just now catching up to the 70s.  Guys it is 2002 already…. Grow up your not 25 any more!   It is always interesting to witness the mating dance of the high end restaurant martini bar, all the men are so bold flashing themselves to the audience like Jesse Jackson looking for a TV camera, actually any camera within 100 miles will do for Jesse.  And, of course the women with their cool, collected demeanors like they have no interest in anything, except maybe something attached to a Mercedes SE series or better preferred, an Armani suit (not off the rack), and a Rolex will do!  And these women think that with their bodies by Dow Corning that they deserve this attachment to the Mercedes…. Of course if they spent $10,000 on boob size and cleavage the guy should “appreciate her”!  This was too much for me, I chuckled as I walked out the door and to the valet to retrieve my company provided Chevy Malibu. Dressed in my subtle but smart Tommy Bahama shirt (buttoned all the way up) and off the rack jacket and slacks. Then go home to watch the New York version of this situation on HBO, because I can be anything I want to be in my own home, in front of my own TV …. Thank you very much!  
     

    
</post>
</Blog>