<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Get your hands off my hot dog that is something . . . . . . can't touch.
     
    
</post>
<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hiya. I'm back. Didn't expect me didya? Excellent. . . . . . . :p  Anywho, school is almost over and summer vacation is here for me in 1 more day! :D I can't wait! But the biggest reason I'm so excited about summer is that I will get loads more time to spend with my girlfriend! :D Stephanie ^_^   Maybe I'll go to driving school and learn to drive, and maybe even get my provisional license, and then maybe even get a better (higher paying) job too. But until then, I'm quite content with walking(and running) to see my Stephy ^^ and to go everywhere else.  Incase you haven't noticed. Stephanie is everything to me! :D I love her so much! She makes me feel like the happiest person in the world! Even if I could only see her smile it would brighten up my day! :D There's a piece of her I carry with me! :D it's everywhere I go, everything I see ^_____^ When I sleep, I dream of her and it gets me by :D I can make believe she's here with me ^^ (does it explain why I like to fall asleep alot? lol)  Sure we have our problems, but we work it out and solve them ^^ and I couldn't be happier! :D She's the world to me! My only one ^^ I couldn't picture life without her ^^  "Here I go, scream my lungs out trying to get to you You are my only one I let go, there's just no one, no one like you You are my only, my only one" --Only One-- Yellowcard  Songs like that remind me of her! :D They make me appreciate how fortunate I am to have her ^_^ how lucky I am to be with her :]  I love you Stephy!
     
    
</post>
<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I knight ye post: SIR UPDATE THE FIRST!  &gt;Pick up ye flask.    Ye can't pick up ye flask. &gt;Dam ye.    Dam ye too.
     
    
</post>
<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A blog! @,@ so simple yet so very, very effective.   I think I might like this. I was first introduced to this by my girlfriend! Who also happens to have a blog! :D (lol, whaddaya know? hehe, she actually made it first, so I'm giving her due credit)  I might update this blog sooner or later. I think it has a lot of potential.
     
    
</post>
<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ... I was awakened by an awful stench. To my greatest horror, the giant branch that fell on me, was actually the cow itself. And the incredibly terrifying stench was its crap, on my face. This is turning out to be the worst day of my life, I should run home and clean up now but...
     

    
</post>
<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      and then it happened a giant branch came down on me.  I was knocked out.  I then dreamed of a beautiful world where everyone was biped versions of animals.  It was totally amazing there were many people there some wonderous with wings while others were dragons.  In this great dream world there were other dream worlds and each one was just as unique as the last i couldn't believe the site.  This world was totally amazing and i wish i could never leave....................
     

    
</post>
<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I nearly crapped my pants when all that happened. Not only was I beaten to within an inch of my life, but she threatened to castrate me too. I ran for my life, and my genitals.  I tried to run as fast as I could, as far as I could. But apparently I couldn't, seeing as how I ran into the tree, very fast, although not very far.  It happened to be that same tree that had the cow in it . . .
     

    
</post>
<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ...Until some odd woman came up and started beating the crap out of me.  I felt very amused and ashamed at the same time, laughing because she was rather short, but she was managing to hurt me.  "Ever mention those cows again and I'll castrate you!" She shrieked.   Geez, what does she have against cows?  
     

    
</post>
<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ... there was a UFO in the sky. It swung around and curved, apparently searching for an open space to land, but it didn't find one, so instead, it exploded.  ::&gt;</post></Blog>