<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm depressed and bored for no reason.  Maybe it's because I'm still single.  As they say("they" being people), "...Youth is wasted on the young."  I was supposed to browse for a job with like eight of my friends, but now it's down to just me..so I'm like, fuck it.  I'll just do it tomorrow after(or before) I see dodgeball.  So many stores, so little time.  Speaking of stores, I hope they open a Hot Topic or Department Store, kinda like Neiman Marcus.  I saw this kick-ass Armani spike jacket that I must get, for about sixty bucks at Franklin Mall.  Why the hell did we name a mall after Franklin anyway?  A mall isn't an institution.  Tribute to this great nation my ass.             So anyway...       Still single and to paranoid to do anything about it.  If I can't open up to one girl, I don't know how I'm ever going to find anybody.  Everyone I know is like "...You look fine, you'll find someone... Someday... Somehow."  Sympathy for the Devil, the devil being me,  *Harmonica drones on in the distance.*        A couple CD's from a couple great bands I must get: Linkin Park: Hybrid Theory(Can't keep burning things forever), recent Korn CD, HIM- Razorblade Romance, SlipKnot- The Subliminal Verses, Evanescence- All of the CD's I guess, System Of A Down- Steal this Album, Toxicity, Self Titled      Clothes I must Buy: A couple Calvin Klein t-shirts in black, white, or red in cool ass street lettering or simple label near breast( (O_O)~).  Some black jeans or cargo pants containing an endless amount of pockets(that's why I want a hot topic), spike brace things on both arms, spike choker(like Tisha), and black or red Nike running shoes. Maybe some express, polo, or Italian dress shirts.  And a pair of black, silver buckle Cole Haan dress shoes.  They'll be calling me Yakuza a lot more these days.   Stuff To BUY: anime wall scrolls(Hellsing, Trigun, cowboy bebop, samurai X, Ragnarok) posters for games and music(Metal Gear Solid, Final Fantasy, Ragnarok Online, Halo, Warcraft, Ninja Gaiden, Starcraft, Linkin Park, Evanescence, System of a down) a katana, a Lord Of The Rings official Glamdring sword, DVD player, Return of the king DVD, surround sound speakers, CD player, new headphones.  Skate shoes..bah.  This is going to be an everyday rant/complain/comment journal, so don't take me too seriously.  Like Paul Brown.  HAHAHA fucking loser.       If anyone is reading this, could you IM me on "Jinn Wraith(AOL instant Messager, Yahoo Messenger, MSN)" to help me edit the font, back ground colors, and pasting images? Sorry for all the capitals randomly assorted, my keyboard does that...Space becoming a delete button.  "Dream with me, and drown these fears and worries of mine." -Me  Current Mood: Lonely(going to go listen to J-Pop to soothe my soul..Make some tea.) Current Music: Seether  Amy Lee-Broken( so into it right now)
    
</post>
<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          Right now I'm lost and confused.  Mainly because the Granite Run Mall isn't showing Dodgeball this Saturday and that is really stupid.  What, is that stupid theater too cheap to purchase the damn film?  And what exactly is with the skyrocketing prices?  Movies aren't exactly oil, ya know.  We're not fighting to control that.  Ten bucks to watch the damn thing, I have enough money(half, i guess) to watch the DVD as many times as I want.      Besides that, my summer has gone pretty well.  WE had mini parties where we trash things(my fan), people(White-ass "Black" Carl), and places(my house).  I can't complain, seeing how most of my lame excuses for friends sit there alone all day(You know who you are..if not, just IM me and I'll say it to your FACE).  That's the summer I don't want.  One of my other friends is enjoyable to be around with, but with that guy, life revolved around games and talking in my  cold, lonely, yet nice basement.  That really gets boring and lame.  Now that I'm in high school and meeting new peeps, so I plan to go outside, and fuck up other peoples' lives.        I pity those who take buses to go places, so I guess I pity myself more than ever.  A damn bus just to get to Granite Run Mall is too much money, and I don't even have a job..      My first comments on the journal: Critique #1:Well written.  Not the best, but what you would expect a journal to look like. Critique #2:More like a wishlist than a journal.   Critique #3:I liked it.      Author Comments: It's an introduction, so things are going to get rough, lighthearted, and completely not-serious.  And to critic #3 I say, yeah right, like you read it.  I'm coming over there, you bastard.          Well, I guess I'm done for the day.  If I want my damn sister out of the house, I have to sign off this 56k compu-crap, then call my dad.  Maybe, just maybe I'll write more tonight.   And, oh yes.  A special shout-out to the lady of my dreams, so close yet so far away in my mind, and this mortal plane.  If only I could proclaim my love...   Current Mood: Depressed Current Music: Auf Der Maur- Followed The Waves
    
</post>
<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Me, lying on my left tricep while holding the camera.  How exciting.  At least you assholes know what I look like now. urlLink     urlLink   
    
</post>
<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          I stayed up till six a.m, playing Phantasy Star Online.  I just couldn't fall asleep.  I was entirely compelled, killing animals, and listening to my mix the whole time.  For the record, this is the longest I've stayed up doing anything. I've got free copies of the closed server version of PSO(Still a lot of people there, though, like 10-110 each server), so IM on my multiple screen names if you feel like getting a copy.  Preferably on AIM, since MSN allows worms to get through.  Now my stomach hurts, I'm dizzy, and lightheaded.  Not a good thing.      Hee.  When Kat said she wanted to be one of close friends, she enlightened my morning.  I'd love to, but the thing is, right now I just don't feel like I can have one.  "People come and go," I usually quote, applying that to relationships, friendships, and partnerships.  I'm just more wary around the people I know now.  I think they've noticed it, too.  I want a friend that I can turn to, die for, and generally have fun with.  A friend whose life I would sacrifice my own for(I don't know how lame or gay that sounds, but hey, if you think like that, maybe you should just die, too).  Not many people like that come around, I've noticed.  Friends you can hold value in, secrets, confidence, and to back you up in a fight.  I recently ran off during my first official fight with my best friend doing the fighting, but the fear was so immense at the time.  My legs trembled the whole time, and I probably couldn't even hold a knife correctly.  But I don't like that friend of mine as much as I used to, so right now I don't know what to think.      Chris is really nice, and Kat is too.  They both seem to believe in me, that I'm intelligient but I just don't apply myself.  After giving other people pep-talks, I'm glad to see the favor returned.  However, I just lost all my confidence in mankind somehow, and that rekindled flame scorches brightly whenever I seem to be around someone.        The other day I hung out with Antonio, Kevin,  Shanna, Anthony, Lucy, and Jew Boy Phil.  I guess I had some fun, but once again that fear arose.  That fear of judgement most of us try to hide, but cannot conceal.  Even around Antonio, almost like some wacky brother, I felt distant and just couldn't comment on anything, or even talk.  When I did, it was in short bursts.  Maybe I'm just too kind and quiet.      Afterwards, they came into my house.  I felt like a jackass, letting them fuck up the house, and bother me the whole time.  I know it was a joke, but...      Maybe I am slightly neurally imbalanced, and need to take depression medication.  I'm not going to let the man tether me down though.  If I suffer, let it last.  It's  helping me write this journal.  Well, even if I don't get any sleep, I'll probably be working.  I'll just stop by Wawa's.  A hazelnut coffee(or two) with irish cream, half-and-half milk, with 6 packets of sugar is sounding really good right now.             Current Mood: Sad  Tired Current Music: Zombie Nation(original, and vocal version)                     
    
</post>
<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          A toast, to the beginnings of a good friendship, via Kevin, and Kat. ===============================================================================================    Kat, you're really nice, and you're the one friend I think I could die for.  I hope we can hang out more often, be it alone or in a group.  I don't want my summer to suck, and I don't want yours to, either.  One of these days, we can stroll down the poetic area of Philly(the one with the classy cafes, and area where Sixth Sense was shot.  Good movie), visit Zipperheads, and get a coffee afterwards.  You know how it feels to be loved and I don't.  Don't sweat the small shit.  You're luckier than me.  Call more often, and I'll fill that emptiness.  You know what I mean.  ^_^           Kevin, you're an ass, but a good person.  Besides that first time we hung out at one of my parties(and you nearly broke my door), I've gotten to know you a little better.  I can tell you're a good guy, no matter times old caucasian mall police scold you.      Anthony, I don't know you too well, but you seem like a good guy.  Sure, we do usually have short word exchanges, but you're a lot cooler than most people I know.  Maybe this summer we can hang out more, and watch Dodgeball with Kev' and Toby if my mom doesn't tell me otherwise.        If you think you could possibly be one of my good friends and I left you out of this journal, talk to me. =====================================================================================     Friendships, burdens, and secret hatreds I am glad to relieve myself of.      Steve Wilson.  Boy, am I ever glad.  I know that CD player is mine, and maybe one of these days we can hang out.  In a federal court of law, that is.  I'll give you back your Dynasty Warriors for my Vice City when I find it.  I still have your Roller Coaster Tycoon, but you'll get that piece of god condemned crap back when I receive Age Of Empires  II.      Tom Wegan.  You're really nice, sometimes, sometimes an ass.  But then again, so am I.  You apologized to me, I apologized back, and wounds are mending themselves.  Steve was what helped me talk to you, but now that I resent him, I feel distant.  You're one of the people that seem to care, and I appreciate that.  Maybe we can still be friends, and I'd like to hold that belief.      Dennis Young... You damn asshole.  You're an okay guy.  But things change, and so do people.  I'm guessing you already know this, we never talk anymore, besides the occasional hallway shout-out.  If you ever do want to hang out again, just call me, and we'll beat up Toby.      Old Tony.  You acted like Dan Costa, and tried to put on a tough guy persona, through an endless stream of swears. You were dorky and quiet, and noone liked you except Carl.  He respected you more, then(apparently), and was a good friend.  I'm sorry to disappoint you with my failing grades, and lust for all things troublesome.  Alcohol, class cutting, and friendships with some mistakes for friends.  I really am sorry to leave you behind.        James Lafferty.  Your nickname was BJ, for god's sake.  Where's the respect in that?  James, you really are something else.  Just when I think I've figured you out, one tiny little problem is added to the mix.  You said you like rap, then later deny it.  You sad, pathetic little boy.  Grow up, man.  It doesn't matter what people think, stop conforming, and find your crowd.  =============================================================================================== Shout Outs to really nice people:          Chris, you already are one of my best friends and I plan to keep it that way.  When you do become un-punished, I plan to have you plan a big game night shindig!  Sure it might not be all about games, but afterwards we head outside and bother people.  Thanks for being there, talking to me, and giving me advice on life.  Also, you're kind of arrogant now that you've got a grilfriend, but knowing you, I was expecting that.  I plan to return the favor one day with something big.          Dan Friggin' Suen...  Talk to me man!  All you do is play Diablo.  Go outside!  It's better for your damn health.  You never hang out with us anymore.  Seeing how Chris just cuddles with Ashley for hours on end, I guess I understand.           Ian, you beat me up way too much.  Sure, it's all fun and games but one of my arms is hurting.  LOL.  Anyway, you're like a brother to me, there to talk to, scold, and give advice.  Stop staying inside so much.      Tisha, Ashley, Candice, Joe, Donna  Brandon     Tisha, you're one of the funniest, most enjoyable to be around with-type jackasses I know.  Ashley, you're talkative, your life sucks, and my best friend is your boyfriend.  Good luck with that, LOL.  Candice, good luck in the future.  You're one of the seniors I hoped will succeed, if I ever do get that loft, you can move in.  Joe!  Good luck with the band.  I plan to join DeMolay and uphold chivalry just like you, man.  Thanks for being there.  Donna and Brandon, I still don't know your last names, but you haven't said anything rude to me.  Cool people.          Yuri.... I loved you at one point, but I guess distance, tastes, and differences separated us.  I know online conversations don't count, but I want you to know that I loved you, and would pay to fly to Korea.  If you ever come back to America, talk to me, please.      Antonio.  You're my lil' bro man, when we get older, we'll all head to the strip club!  This kid is fucking awesome.  Great humor, great personality, and a true friend.  Harold and the Purple Crayon indeed.      Left you Out?  IM or call me. ===============================================================================================    Whew!  Done with the shout-outs.  I said I'd go into religion, but then people probably wouldn't read all of this.  Maybe next post.  Well...  I hope all the people I shouted out to like me and respect me like I would them.  Paranoia comes into play, and everything's down to oblivion.  May it never wound these pacts I've established with these special people.  Just know I'm here for you, I'm a friend, and everything will be okay.  Let me just say right now, if you don't like someone, just say so.  I need to start being more honest to others.  God knows I am to myself, always running from the past.  I need to focus on my future, to leave my print in Earth's dire history.  I want to be known, yet carried in the breeze like a whisper.  Thinking about all my friends makes me think maybe I don't want to die early, I just want to belong.  I want to stand by my friends and fight until the end.  Life has its champagnes, and it has its whiskey.  Stand by me, and I'll stand by you.             Kat and Chris, thank you.  Current Mood: Satisfied Current Music: Dream- My Will       =================================================================================== Poll: Should I get 2-3 lip rings, 4 earrings, and red hair dye?  IM me with your answer.
    
</post>
<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          I just typed three paragraphs on the cold memories of my past.  Well, they weren't that good, seeing as how I'm morbidly tired.  I'm on the verge of death as we speak.  I'll write more later today, if my lazy dad doesn't take me home before then.      Crept out at like two-ten A.M. and hung out with Mcknight for at least thirty minutes.  Thoughts of night-patrol cop cars, dead janitors, deceased teachers, organ-playing apparitions, and angry dads taint my sanity.  If I ever do leave the house that late again, I leave through the window.  Thinking back on that, how suspicious do two black clothing-clad teenagers look walking around at two A.M.?  Stupid society. =============================================================================       I'll go into the details of my cold, nearly-forgotten memories later today.  Its late(four-thirty in the damn morning), and I want to head to sleep.  Maybe later I'll delve deep into my my own psyche on thoughts of religion, and why I strongly detest the holy bible.  Rocking back and forth unintentionally due to fatigue is a bad thing.  Heh heh, I'm half-dreaming of the perfect bed to doze in.  Silk blanket and super soft pillows, firm, yet soft, the bed lying atop grey rain clouds in an ethereal heaven.         Goodbye.  Current Mood: Sleepy, and exhausted(I worked today)      Current Music: Jimmy Eat World- My Sweetness =============================================================================  Damn life to hell.          
    
</post>
<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          -Two-forty seven A.M.  When I got back from lurking the streets of Collingdale with Kevin. ====================================================================================================      I made a personal entry to publish one entry in my journal every day, and here it is.  God, I'm all shakey right now.  I felt so miserable today.  Everyone just seems so cold whenever I delve into my past, remembering everything said, done, and felt.  All these emotions just emerged when I listened to  Thrice's "All That's Left".  My chest burned, and I felt a burning hatred.  Self-pity just seemed to consume me wherever I turn.  Trying to remember all those enjoyable moments just brought up pessimistic memories.  Maybe I need to loosen up.  Today I feel sick to the stomach.  Father's day is later today, and we're just going to see a movie.      It's shocking how much you think you know someone, and then something just clicks.  People change, a fact a lot of us need to acknowledge.  Words slip, confrontations arise, and chaos ensues.  People you thought you knew turn out to be assholes, and those you dislike become acquaintances somehow.  Over the duration of my freshman school days, I've gained friends, and lost some.  The people I lost, become nothing more than bitter memories.        Right now, I'm really uninspired.  Those of you who analyze my writing may have been able to tell.  I'm just bored right now, and typing every thought that comes to mind.  I still feel slightly depressed, but I'm just really tired right now from last night's gaming session(twelve to six A.M.).  Even after that coffee McKnight theoretically bought me, I'm getting dizzy and losing focus on my computer screen.  I'm going to go play Phantasy Star Online, then head off to bed.  Current Mood: Tired as all hell, mentally not phsically. Current Music: Franz Ferdinand- Take Me Out                     
    
</post>
<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          Another boring day.  My sister couldn't be picked up, and I can't go outside.  I hate you, Mother.  She gave me life, and is currently taking it away. I don't plan on withering away in this cheap neighborhood, irrevocably placed in front of a computer or tv screen.  I'm going to live life the way I want, and how.  I don't want to be like my other friends.  It's so miserable lying in this damn chair, staring at an ancient CRT monitor.  This is just depressing.  My mom is the communist everyone one of my cruel friends makes her out to be.  Every aspect of may life, love, appearance, friendships, interests, entertainment, living, she controls  it all.      I can't go outside, I can't get money to get decent food.  I'm stuck dining on instant noodles, leftovers, and condiments.  I no longer receive clothing, and those that I want, I must purchase myself.  I can't talk on the phone too long, instead I sit here by myself.  I want to cry tears of blood and slowly bleed myself to death.  I want to kill someone, and have that person take my life as well.  I want to end my suffering, without a goodbye.  Perhaps my own family is driving me to insanity.  Demons disguised as angels with holy golden wings, and silk robes that commandeer your life.  When will I be free of these tethers take anchor me to this icy hell?      Of course friendship helps and cures wounds.  But when you're chained to a place like mine, social interaction must be attained illegally.  Through lying, cheating fate, and luck.  I don't know how many risks I've taken to be with people, and I don't care.  If I must continue my life like this, then so be it.  What a sad existence.  If you think your life has more anguish, you're probably right, but my worries are my own.  No one can help me, because it seems like no one can or will.  Maybe I'm stuck here alone, without true friends.  Those I do have, separated by distance.  Current Mood: Depressed Current Music: Utada Hiraku- Sakura Drops        ============================================================================================= What is a true friend?        
    
</post>
<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Join the community.  For about $9.99+tax, that is. urlLink     urlLink   
    
</post>
<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          I played around with the template the whole time I was on the internet, and went to Taco Bell today.  This will probably be my shortest entry in awhile.  Let me tell you people right now...  Never order the Grilled "Stuft(Yeah, that's how you spell it)" Burrito from Taco Bell!  That damn chihuahua doesn't know what he's talking about.  It's empty calories!  About the only thing I could taste was burnt bread, bad service, and that droll bean taste.  Get something a little zesty, like their Border Bowls, or real food.      Anyway, today had to be the most boring day of summer to date.  I didn't feel like talking, and drove off most of the people who did try to talk to me(Sorry, Kat v_v*).  I just want to bask in the moonlight.  A drink, grassy plain, and the sky is enough to put me at ease.  It's so serene, and comforting.  These are the kinds of moments I'd love to share with somebody that understands these things.  Just staring into the sky...  Even at night, when cars never drone by, and people rest.  I could simply fall asleep in the grass or on my roof talking to someone.  The best things in life are free, greater than any material possession in  the world.  One of these days, I plan to bike or walk somewhere really far with a friend or alone, and appreciate nature in its prime.  The night air will soothe my worry, and the day's sunlight will put me at ease.        Talking to my friend at two-thirty in the morning made me appreciate the simple things in life.  Even though, almost everything I want costs money, life requires people to show you the finer aspects.  It's surprising how relaxing and stress-free writing in a simple journal can be.  Expressing your thoughts and feelings is one of the best stress relief methods I know.  That, punching something, cutting myself, and/or stabbing things.      I'm still waiting for that special gal, and I feel it's going to be a long wait.  People that feel the same way as me about life are rare, and with the same tastes, even more difficult fo find.  Even when I do find people like that, something goes wrong.  I dunno.  Maybe god wants me to be a swingin' bachelor for the rest of my life.  The night life is a good one, especially near historic Philadelphia.  That place rocks so hard.  People there seem so friendly and active, and the energy is like some pulsating nirvana that never releases you. My outlook on the future sounds so good right now, night life, bars, and dance clubs.  Anyone who's reading this, take a stroll down South Street with a couple of friends.    Current Mood: Hopeful Current Music: Von Bondies- C'mon C'Mon      
    
</post>
<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      When all is said and done...  urlLink     urlLink   
    
</post>
<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          I just awoke from a nightmare.       Anthony, Kevin, and I sat in my living room asking ourselves what there was left to do to pass the time.  We had just gotten back from the Springfield Mall.  Just as I was about to escort them out of the room, the door handle started to turn.  I slowly turned the lock to confuse her, because a quick lock would only alarm her to their presence more.  As Kevin and Anthony quietly started to the basement door(unlike most of my other friends, BOOM, BANG, SHEBOYGAN), the front door flew open.  It was at that point that my mom yelled.  I explained they were here to use the phone, and I actually wasn't lying this time.  When they left, my mom YELLED for me to wash my hair.  The sexy-blueness looked too punk for her, apparently having my hair blue does not qualify me to look for a job in the Springfield mall.        I simply told her I was leaving.  She must have assumed I was leaving for the night, due to a later comment she made*****.  That day I hung out in Boyer's basement, fooling around with a guitar making myself look like a jackass, incapable of playing a musical instrument.  I was the only one there who didn't play anythng.  Oddly enough, that made me feel even more out-cast.  On top of that, I got my bite-plate today.  A.K.A. retainer.  For all you ladies, I won't be wearing it at dates and social gatherings(big sigh).  I don't know what to think.  A retainer....      Right after the awesome guitar  drum session with Anthony, we went up to the Sev' Eleven and Mckinght brought a Star Wars laser gun.  I felt like a jackass the whole time.  A jackass having fun, might I add.  After some more chatting, I walked home with Kevin(Nine P.M.), who had to use my phone to attain a ride.  When I stepped inside the house, my sister warned me to be careful of glass in my room.  It was at that moment that I said "What the fuck?" very loudly, but my Mom seemed not to care.      I stepped into my room with a sense of foreboding.  I saw my chinese laterns torn down from the ceiling, and my beloved black-and-white japanese(chinese?) mountain hill photo frame on the ground, the glass shattered.  With a searing sensation in my chest, I took the sharpest piece of glass I could find, not knowing why or the purpose.  I was probably going to cut myself, or something, but I then took another large shard of glass and stored it behind my wicker chair for future use.         With no one left to turn to, i walked to my dad's after Kevin's mom dropped me off.  Such humor, those two.  Anyway, I must have walked back and forth for ten or fifteen minutes.  I then summoned all of my courage to walk to my dad's.  My dad is disappointed by these things.  A disappointed dad, is an upset one.  An upset one lectures and bothers you.  My dad said to stay cool, and that my mom signed papers to keep me until I was eighteen anyway.  Out the door when he sat on the doorstep and talked to me, I told him I'd walk, in the darkness. I then flipped him off, but he didn't see me.       While I walked, a slutty blonde thirteen to fourteen girl in glasses, standing in her doorway told me I looked cute.  Oddly, it made me feel a little better, although I wanted to impale her with the piece of plastic I attained from shattering one of my CD's.  I went home, washed some clothes and slept in my basement watching Adult Swim.  Highlight shows of the night, Futurama: Dr.Zoidberg's home country takes over earth when his freedom of speech is threatened.  Family Guy: Death visits Peter after faking his death to avoid paying an HMO bill.  Cowboy Bebop: Beautiful morale, beautiful art, beautiful story.  Jet visits his past lover on Ganymede to discover why she suddenly left him.  Any episode starring Jet or Spike, awesome.  Even Ed's.  Trigun: The wandering orphanage priest dies.      Will I wake from this nightmare?  Who will be there to grasp my hand when that cold breath of air seems to numb your lungs?  Who will I turn to when my mom finally gives up on me for some inane reason?  Who will I temporarily take residence with?  So many questions, so many answers, and so little time.  I guess my Mom feels she is losing control.  When she walked upstairs, she said, "*****Don't walk in here and pretend everything damn thing is normal.  Next time you do something like that, you better find somewhere to live."  Will I be living in a home, military base, or orphanage?  I don't know.  I'll probably walk to CA or FL if I get exiled.  That, or suicide...  She probably got pissed at me for having blue hair, also the fact Anthony was wearing that kick-ass Korn shirt.  Maybe my Mom feels as if she is losing control.  Maybe she is crazy.  Maybe I am, too. When all this is done, I'll fall with a bang and a resounding crash.  My whisper will be spread through the wind, all will hear, and all will think.  What is worth fighting for, and is human greed the cause of suffering?  Current Mood: Bloodthirsty, and agitated.   Current Music:  My coarsing veins, and Thrice's All That's Left =========================================================== Those of you that think you have it worse, go to hell.  I'll deal with my own damnations.  Me couper, me tuer, et me casser le coeur! Vous serez la mort de moi... Me réveiller de cette éternité de damnation!                                                   
    
</post>
<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          HeHeh.  I crept out at like twelve A.M. last night to hang out with Toby and Boyer.  I am so damn tired right now.  Antonio came in later that morning and the thought just kept me up.  OOh boy..      This might be my vaguest, most incoherent journal entry yet.  i'm tired, it's not my fault.  If i could, I'd stay up until I died.  Some jackass posted Kim Ercolani's phone number in my journal.  I have a feeling it was Charlie Fucking Walls.  I hope he gets hit by a car, or something.  I'm pretty sure he knows I hate him,  but he IM'ed me yesterday.  Popularity is so overrated.  With people like him, I'm surprised most of my friends haven't become posers, conformers, followers, and trend followers.  Almost anything Charlie says he likes becomes cool.  Justice League?  You fucking stupid?      Enough about jackasses.  I want to sleep peacefully tonight.  I'm just astounded I haven't fallen into a near dead faint on the keyboard.  Damn, I feel like I just took repeated bottles of beer.  If this is the teen night life, I'm loving it so much.  Settling down is highly-overrated, and are children.  Who wants to raise a kid?  Err, I think my keyboard keys are crooked.  That, or I need some sleep.        I aplogize, this journal entry was highly irreleveant.  Anyone reading this, please post.  Hey Kat!o_- ==================================================================================================== "Jesus Tap-dancing Christ, Kyle!"-Cartman  Current Mood: Happy, cheery, sleepy, and dead. current Music: Steriogram- Walkie-Talkie Man One-hit wonders.^up there^  Geeze, my keyboards starting to look like an old school keyboard/guitar thing.  The right side's all crooked...      
    
</post>
<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The real folk blues... urlLink     urlLink   
    
</post>
<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          Another one bites the dust.  Another, another, and another.  Just be glad someone is reaving this plague of locusts called humanity.  Honestly, we're just empty space consuming minerals and elements.      This weekend is a SLOW one.  I watched the MTV2 Spider Man marathon leading to Indy's coma.  Awesome show, makes all other American shows(cough,justice league) look like crap.  As most of you know, my mother is not aware of the fact I have illegally obtained the internet.  SO basically, when she is present, Internet access is slim to none.        Inspiration is at a loss, and I miss my buddy Chris.  I might have to move soon, too.   My mom's renovating and scraping some stuff off the wall.  I'm going to miss so many people that I didn't even get to know. I guess I'll just leave going-away presents to some people.  Money for chris, a game for Ian, and I can't think of anything else.  Maybe I'll buy a manga for Candice, and a poster or CD for Kat.  For Antonio, I'll have to think.  I'll need a lot of money to buy all this for everybody.        I don't really know If I'm moving or not, which makes me sad.  My mom looks serious.  When I move, I guess I'll just be a social outcast, once again, lurking in shadows silently and unnoticed.  SO many things I haven't said, so many people I should have forgiven or apologized to...  Maybe the people there won't all be stuck-up caucasians, or jocks.  Hopefully, I'll meet people like Chris, Kat, Antonio, and Yuri there.        Since things seem so imminent, I should live life to its fullest for the duration of time I am here.  Parties, girls, and alcohol.  Sounds good.  Drown my fears with alcohol.  Sure I never got drunk, but it seems to work.  People that I probably won't get to know too well because I have to move: Kat, Candice, Ashley, Tisha, Kevin, Anthony, Donna  Brandon(nice people).  People I REALLY regret to leave behind: Chris, Ian, Antonio... Not much anyone else.  See ya later Chris.  Come back from Europe soon. ====================================================================================== Current Mood: Depressed and sad Current Music: Utada Hiraku- Simple and Clean 
    
</post>
<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So far I haven't been able to go anywhere.  Partly because I have to watch my sister, and I have noone to hang out with.  Also, life demands Lysol according to the blonde lady on my television.  Kat invited me to see Two Brothers(Disney...Shiver), Kevin wanted me to call a couple people so we could go outside, and Antonio went to the zoo.  ZOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO.  Anyway, my mom wants us to move to Oxford, and it appears we are going to.  If I meet some whigger-tastic kracker folk, I'm going to go insane.   I can't believe my mom wants to move.  Sure, I can start a new life, but with who?  My sister?  This is going to suck so much.  Hopefully I can find a job there, or something.  Maybe they'll also have a better school that serves real food that wasn't scraped from the wall of an insane asylum , or the bottom of a toilet.  Sorry for that disgusting description.  Most of you reading this would be appalled, associating prison wall scum as cafeteria food.  Just imagine every disgusting drip of "gravy," dropped, not poured, onto your "turkey and bread."    My Positive Outlook: Maybe life can't possibly suck anymore.  Sure, I'll have less friends, and less area to party and then evacuate people, but it might be fun.  Maybe there's a Hot Topic there, too.  Of course, driving to zipperheads is going to take a lot longer, but the employees won't be assholes like everyone else.  Also, the chicks there are a lot sexier, too.  I know, I've been there.  Plus, buying manga will be less difficult, being near a mall.  My Pessimistic Outlook: I can't see my dad as much, internet access will probably be non-existent, and I won't be able to talk to my dad or be with him as much.  I'm going to miss Chris a lot, and the people I never had the chance to know well.  I'll be leaving a lot of people behind, my slightly-nice house, my best buds, and my own bedroom.  Maybe there, I'll get to decorate it according to my on tastes.  I'm going to miss everybody.  I don't know how many people know that or read this, but I'm going to miss you all.  I talk like I'm going to die there.  Who knows?  So far I can't say anything about my house/apartment, I have no idea what it's going to look like.  Two-bedroom, or one-bedroom? I'll just sleep in the living room and watch TV until I pass out from fatigue.  I love someone here, I don't think they know it, I want to go out with them, and it's too late for me to tell her.  Either way, it might have ended in anguish for both of us for multiple reasons.  She liked me, I liked her, I had my doubts, and she gave up.  So kill me.  Current Mood: Paranoid Current Music: Music from Diablo II: Lord of Destruction         
    
</post>
<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I wish I had a gun and hair like that.  Only, not blonde. ^_^  urlLink     urlLink   
    
</post>
<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ..In my faith I must confide.  Go Elligible Bachelors(My friend's band)! Uh huh.  I lugged my computer down into my basement at midnight, to go online and chat.  So far, only a few people talked to me.  Some, too busy.  What effort.  I switched the Tv's position, and moved everything downstairs, aside from the desk.  It appears we are moving.  My mother said I misbehave, and I don't give a shit.  I said this already, but she said it like she really means it now.  So now, I must start saving money. Kevin, maybe I will get you something.  Antonio says I don't need to get him anything, but I'll find something.  In my faith I really must confide.  I'll try not to be a shy bastard, like I was the first time around some of my friends.  Most of my friends, I had to make by being myself.  I realized being quiet, noone will turn to you with a greeting or smile.  Just this vague look that says, "Uhm... Hi?"  I do value my friends, and I plan to purchase a car(Mitsubishi Eclipse '90-'01), so I can still hang out.  When I get my license, I don't know.  All I know is, Boyer is getting his first, and he can drive us places.  In a VAN.  More room!    When I get to Oxford, I'll probably see who my true friends are, by correspondence, or instinct.   By the way, doing something like this was only partly worth it, if you know you can avoid trouble.  My 56k modem screamed when I signed on.  Also, Kat, if you tell Bay anymore things about Kevin, I'm telling a certain someone your secret.  Or something.  I'm kinda hyper, I had an asian coffee laced and created from caffeine.  Xanga.com...can I transfer my journal there?  IM me with answers and you will receive some complimentary gift of little, or no value.  There's also an ASIAN AVENUE website for asian thoughts.  Awesome.  Current Mood: Even more Paranoid Current Music: System Fan's droning.   ======================================================================================== Sorry.               
    
</post>
<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Jay-Z.  I hope he dies slowly and painfully.  His last music video was a gay one, and I'm appalled at the fact I sat through it.  He tried to make his death like Denzel Washington's in Training Day in his video.  I hope he suffers slowly, and dies a grisly death.  Why?  he fucking sucks, that is why.  He has no talent.  I've got an idea.  A bunch of crazy BDSM ladies strap him to a boat in the middle of a pacific ocean in one-hundred  degree weather, tied down by barbed-wire, and dip his fingers in toes in napalm.  He'll die slowly and painfully.  By the time someone finds him, his flesh will be charred and decayed, maggots and flies dead on his body from the intense heat and napalm.  Sorry for those of you that think I am sick.  This isn't a death threat, only my personal wishes.  So if the secret service comes to my house, I'm going to be sarcastic the whole time.  If I get some kind of notice for this, then I might delete it.  But why?  Why do rappers suck so much?  They always seem so self-centered.  Intent on geting more ladies, booze/drugs, cash, and street rep.  I doubt they're are any rappers these days with any true meaning.  Sorry, this journal is nothing more than a rant.  BUT I HATE RAP SO MUCH!  However, without them, we'd have too many posers walking around, and goth-wannabe's, like Mary Panasewicz.  If you're reading this, go cut yourself with a fucking knife or shard of glass you damn fag.  Combs don' work.  You'll never get a boyfriend except wife-beaters like your last one.  Charlie Walls, I hope you die.  No, seriously.  Curent Mood: More agitated then last time. Current Music: Linkin Park- Breaking The Habit   ================================================================================== KILL.
    
</post>
<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What happened in my past?  In Fifth grade, I was one of the intellectual cocks-of-the-walk.  I could stand there and mock others for their inferiority, and know it was true.  Now, I could barely hold a flame to most of my friends in intellectual superiority.  Maybe I still can surpass some, but not as many as I once could.  Perhaps I still am intelligient, but what happened?  K-6th grade I washighly intelligient, top-rank in my class.  Seventh to Ninth?  What happened?  Everyday I ask myself why I can't try harder, or succeed in the smallest of efforts.  I conceal that through putting the blame on something, like my parent's divorce.  All I ever hear are complaints, insults, envy, and malice.  Especially from my mother.  If anything, she is the main problem.  Like me, she is too stubborn to admit the truth every once-in-awhile, and rarely forgives.  Maybe it's just me.  On occasion, a random thought of suicidal action seemed to plague my thoguhts.  That, and homicide.    Maybe it is me.  Maybe I should give up, forget trying, and lay here and die.  I could join a crime syndicate and unleash my vehement rage against innocent bystanders, and rival mobs.  Just a thought.  My shortest journal entry by far.  ALthough that above paragraph was more like two or three.  Also, Catwoman the movie looks to suck, with a huge suckiness.  Halle Berry, taking any paycheck with seven zeroes.  Catwoman? Really.  Current mood: Bored Cuurent Music: Incubus- Talk show on mute   
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just confessed to someone I know a lot of things, the result a little awrkward.  Perhaps I should have just kept my mouth shut, but I wanted to know how she felt.  Now that I know it can't work out(although I knew it from the beginning), I feel a little depressed, yet content.  Actually, I feel a weight lifted from my shoulders.  Letting go is always best in the end, whether  it comes by choice or conflict.  I don't think I'll actually ever hang out with her, things always seem to go wrong.  Maybe she just doesn't like me at all.     I met Ashley today.  Cool chick, another one of Kat's friends.  She has a lot of connections, and is very cool.  She draws good, too.  If you're reading this, Hi.  I feel empty today.  I dunno.  I think I just want a good friend I know I can turn to.  I walked around Sharon Hill alone today, thinking of nothing in particular.  I went to Ian's, played Ninja Gaiden, Guilty Gear x2, and Soul Calibur.  Okay time.  Not too talkative.  Problem is, now Carl wants to come to the movies with me.  I don't like him as much as I used to.  Now I feel guilty talking about him and not saying it his face.  Why?  Because I'm really not sure what I desire.  What am I thinking?  Why can't I tell him the truth?  I think he's starting to realize it, but why bother?  Because people change.  I think the only person I can turn to right now is Chris.  He was a little rude, not as much as Carl.  Still, I feel unconfident.  I don't know why anymore.  I've repeated it so many times.  Deprived of that which guides.  I've lost faith.  Who can restore that faith?  Why can't I just die?  Before I move(IF I DO), I want to say my goodbyes.  I know something just won't work like this.  Something's bound to happen.  I'm not sure what, when, or why.  One of these days, I'm just going to walk around someplace peaceful and fall asleep under a tree, and forget my worries.  Everything will just go away.  When I wake up, I'll just figure everything out, and when I'm in Oxford, things won't be so bad.  I'll get a car, and still hang out with everyone back in Sharon Hill.    Current Music: Yellowcard- Ocean Avenue            Current Mood: Depressed ================================================================================================ Without a thought.  
    
</post>
<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My cat, Gabby, and me sleeping on her head.   urlLink     urlLink   
    
</post>
<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I feel so lost right now.  Lost and scared.  Mainly because I went to Ebaum's and read this thing about ghosts and murders in the flash section.  If you're highly superstitious and thoughts of mysterious ghosts from someone's past visiting you in the dead of sleep is horrifying, don't open the urban legend or ghost flash app.  ==========Irrelevant_Notice============================================================ Now, I think my mom doesn't want to move.  Not sure, because I asked her, and she said "I don't know," half awake on the basement couch.  She was peeling the grape and wine pictures from the wall, and she wouldn't do that unless she really wanted to move.  She could possibly be warning me with signs.   ========What does it mean?=============================================================  Shivers are running through my spine right now.  Imagine what I'm thinking.  Walking around your home in the dead of night, when yellow eyes peer out in the darkness.  Slipping over a power tool, your hands glide over a light switch, and this ghastly half-devoured vision of death lies before your eyes bent over you.  It's face the vision of horror that seems mos compelling.  Fragments of bone, tattered flesh, and blood matted hair decorate the mutilated head.  IT's eyes have a cold blackness, sunken into a pale, wrinkly skull.  Their sockets stained with a red hue.  A decaying hand reaches down your back, resulting in the coldest, spine-numbing touch in existence.   Sitting there in the weak light, every inch of your body is frozen with fear.  His eyes peer into yours, even deeper into your soul.  The only part of you functioning seems to be your hand.  A gun lies next to you.  Let him kill you, only to bask in the darkness of his mind, kill him and possibly be unsuccessful leading to choice number one, or put yourself out of your own misery?    On occasion, I long for the simple life.  I think way too much.  This icy paranoia that seems to plague every facet of thought and psyche.  A cold hatred for everyone that just seems to grow, and doesn't seem to let go.  At the end of the day, lying there in sadness, reflecting on the past, present, and future is the result.  Thinking isn't going to do you any good.  Those who cannot help themselves, cannot help others.  Withering away in the darkness, knowing everything accomlished could be rendered obsolete, one mistake bringing life to a crashing end.    When you realize eveything you've done is completely irrelevant to anything, you wonder who you can turn to.  Time passes you by, and you see no one in the passing storm.  Tears turn into blood, bones into dust, mind into oblivion.  Current Mood: Lost Current Music: Breaking Benjamin- So Cold, and the sounds of morning fauna. ======================================================================================= WHY? 
    
</post>
<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was awake from Friday at 12 P.m. until sunday 6 p.m.  I decided not to take Tesha's 96 hour challenge, I might faint in the middle of something.  As of right now, I'm teetering back and forth on a chair, eyes randomly darting back-and-forth without focus.  I played Phantasy Star Online from like 1 am to 5 10 am.  Online crack.  Also, I watched this really funny video.  Turn all the lights off, turn the volume up, and make sure no parents are watching.  LMAO hilarious.    urlLink      Heh, sorry, this is my worst, most nonsensical journal post I've probably ever entered.  Thoughts are passing through my head, in one ear and out the other.  My fingers are elgantally dancing over the keyboard, and my eyes feel so heavy.  Even after a Dunkin Donut's Koolata at 2 pm, and some really strong chinese tea at 4, I'm dead.  I probably won't wake up, Don't call me, I'll call you.  The tea costs 180.00 in chinese currency.  Not American.     I watched "The Patriot" at 10:30 pm for the last thirty minutes.  It wasn't the same.  Without the incessant bloodshed, it felt like some government brainwashing scheme.  Mel Gibson is his name.  Ahh foo, I'm losing focus on the keyboard keys now.  This is why people must learn to chat and/or type over the internet without staring at the Keyboard,  Crap!  I'm half-dreaming, hallucinating, on the near-enge of fainting.  But yet, I write this journal for those who care what I think, and wonder how life passes me by each day.  My god, I keep getting hallucinations of my cat entering the room!  This is awesome.  Stay up for 35 hours straight and list the effects.  Each yawn is feeling like a rush of blood loss.  Crap I'm going crazy.  Gabby didn't actually crawl/jump/run by.  I hallucinated that image 12 times already.  Current Mood: Morbidly Tired.  Tesha, you win the bet. Good thing, I didn't bet anything in on this nefariously idiotic plan. Current Music: Incubus- I wish you were here =========Die=================================================================== Good morning America, I'm heading off to bed.   
    
</post>
<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today's Panda Chinese Restaurant Fortunes: -=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-= An empty stomach is not a good political advisor. Daily Numbers: 8 6 1 Lotto Six: 35 20 30 21 33 40 Comment:  These ancient chinese sure do know more than us.  Typing fortune cookie messages from their graves, and all.  Apparently, even those of us who do not work in political offices have the potential, if only we applied it, and utilize it to it's fullest extent.  Today's Panda Chinese Restaurant Fortunes: -=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=-= You may attend a party where strange custoims prevail. Daily Numbers: 0 2 9 Lotto Six: 43 35 12 40 6 25 Comment:  Perhaps asians aren't as ingenius and as accredited as you gwei-lo's give us credit for.  Either way, they're telling me I can attend a massive HIV end-of-the-world orgy party, and will walk out unscathed.  Also, I can drink twenty shots of Bacardi vodka, and I won't feel the slightest buzz.  Rock on, Mao Zedong.  Second time this week I stayed up until 6 A.M.  Ooh yeah.  I played Phantasy Star Online, and ended up playing it with three other asians until six.  Last time I ever dupe anything for anyone...    I'm somewhat bored, and typing the people's fortunes is hard and strenous work.  Often involving back-breaking keyboard typing.  Ha.  Either way, that's all you jerks get for today.   Current Mood: Happy and Tired Current Music: Blink 182- Adam's Song. ============================================================================== I just realized BLink 182 is kind of good.  Soothing beats, and nice music.
    
</post>
<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I owe my journal another entry snce I couldn't type one yesterday, being outside, and offline.  I really am at a loss of inspiration, but I'm still thinking about that court order.  That is going to haunt me all summer.  Eventaully it's going to rise up like some great creature from a sea of blood.  It's going toswallow me, and I'm going to drift in my own insanity.  In court I'll plead insane, and I will be.  Kick-ass idea, escept for the nuthouse part.  Insane Asylum's are depressing, and quite scary if you ever think of the possiblities of a patient  going on a killing spree, with a fork and napkin, somehow managing to kill twenty in less than an hour.  Of course, the tissue could be laced with chlorofoam, rendering the victims unconscious and an easy target.     I'be suffered so much over the years, of my own cause, and of others.  My mother is driving me there, as she is herself.  She cracked when she saw my hair blue, and she might soon do the same when she sees the court order.  I don't know what to do, but I might just show it to my dad.  It's so much easier to run...  Next entry, I'll probably just take  a quiz and post my results.  At least everyone with a journal I know has posted something like it, as well as stupid, irrelevant quiz results.  What powerpuff girl are YOU?  I'mm  going toake some sort of lame ass quiz and post the result for all of you to see.  What will be in the next journal entry, I haven't decided.  I'll check past entries to post things I said I would have, but never did.  Current Mood: Annoyed Current Music: Linkin Park- Easier To Run   ================================================================ Movie?  
    
</post>
<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      September 22nd I am to be summoned in Delaware County Court on convictions of school truancy, and false information alledgedly disclosed.  Fuck.  I skip one class, lir about my name, name, address, age, and present should-be-whereaabouts and I'm fined $400.97.  I hate the man more than ever.  I get this, for skipping ONE class??  I don't care what anyone says, the man is highly overrated, our Government overlooking obvious flaws in the sysytem to deal out their so called justice, that all of us fear.  Terror sown in and out through the media, stories of racism, lies, and justice dealt with an un-american manner.  So many cover-ups, deaths, and black-op's that we don't even know about.  (IN?)Justice comes at a price, but what might that be?    I think I know why Tesha despises the man so much.  Now, I don't even blame her. Anyway, I have no idea what to tell my parents.  My mom already knew about this, but the court summon will probably just enrage her further.  If i do move, then I'm not sure when or how I'm going to get back.  i don't want to serve any community service, those orange jumpsuits look horrid.  Hopefully, Ican take my dad, and He will pay my fine, with a lecture afterwards about school and law conduct.  I have decided I am going to plead guilty, instead of sow any other lies that would later catch up to me in the future, and make my life suck even more.  The problem is, the money, or....  The Community Service.  Besides, like Kevin said, everyone skips school(in my case, class), or does something unlawful at one point in their life, and I've served mine.      Now, I actually think I might want to move.  I dont' want to see any more of the same assholes who live in the same area as me, or attend the same school.   Hell, I don't even want to see their faces.  I want to see them dead, strewn across a charred, war-torn landscape.  I want to be that tool of destruction, to lay waste to mankind and put the rest of you out of your misery.  Am I sick?  Like, a homocidal serial killer?  Possibly.  I enjoy suffering, and I don't think i've everfelt true compassion for the dead, even my deceased relatives.  I've often wondered, why I don't feel emotion, why I feel so empty.   As much as I like my friends, I can't help feeling, that maybe I'd be better off alone.  Right now, I think I do want to go to Oxford.  Just to start over, and forget.  The Borders book store would be a lot closer, and the mall would be a short drive/walk.  Buying clothes would be much easier, and getting reserved stuff would be really easy.  Like Halo 2.  Maybe I just need help.      Current Mood: Hysteric Current Music: System  Of a Down- Deer Dance =====================================================================  (*_*)&gt;
    
</post>
<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ooh!  Today was mucho lame. and I feel hyper.  I cleaned and shit, and was checking out this hype-grillin' cook book, yo.  Ah ha ha.  Where do this afro-gangsta culture get their bangin' slang?  I don't fucking know, but If i hear another lame joke about some white kid saying, "Right Thurr," I am going to pass out and vomit on his shoes while simultaneously beating the crap out of him in my sensory-deprived state.  GO AQUA TEEN HUNGER FORCE GO!  WASABI!  SEALAB OWNS YOU!  This show is so awkward but it owns so much.  Also, my mom is at a wedding of some sort and I don't know where or what she is doing/at.  Kevin thinks it is weird that I think Amy Lee rocks, and I told him to shut up.  Bizarro!  i need to type one more paragraphs to fill fulfuilled, since I had to type three entries and it was really annoying.  I got two honor classes, and two college prep classes.  The classes of honor were: English, and some how Biology.  I'm not sure how I got Honors for Biology, but if it was some awkward error, let is stay.  I at least deserve the honors for English.  Biology?  I didn't do anything worthy of Honors, but this Bizarro thing on Adult Swim is annoying me.    My College Prep classes, IMP II, and something else.  World Cultures II.  Yeah.  I wonder what kind of school system they have in Oxford.  I bet I'll see wangsta cracka-ho's walking around, a dime a dozen.  Either way, they'll be rich asshole whores.  Meep.  My other classes are Phys . Ed., Art I, Introduction to Computer Technology, and Spanish, which I plan to cancel.  I didn't turn in my book, "Flowers For Algernon," so I owe a fee if i want my Report Card.  I'll turn it in August.  That way, I'll hand my mother the report card, and the court-summon at the same time.  I'm screwed either way, I think.  Current Mood: Somewhat Happy Current Music: Evanescence- My Immortal =================================================== Me couper, me tuer, et me casser le coeur...   
    
</post>
<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      One hell of a yesterday.  My sis was picked up to go to Helen's(My Chinese Almost-aunt).  THing is, I wake up, and she's not there, no note, no shit.  What the hell is wrong with my family?  I woke up, started my computer, played a little Star Wars: Jedi Knight, and got dressed.   Fly Clothes I chose(It rhymes!)? -Express Jeans -Calvin Klein Emo T-Shirt -Florenzini Dress Shirt  After a bus n' trolley trip, we headed to the Springfield Mall.  Our first stop was.... selective memory kicking in!  Samsung, to look for Emo Kids. *Author Comments: I need new gel, my hair refuses to spike anymore. Aside from that irrelevant comment, my day went awkward yet fine.  i saw the ice cream dude at Susan's who didn't want to hire me, 'cause I'm underage.  After stopping at a table with pretzels we made up nicknames for wangs.  Among them, Wangzilla, Tweezer Teaser, and something else Kevin said.  Anthony purchased a DVD for his father, there's something "MORE" about Mary.  I hate those titles.  The media makes slight innuendo seem like full-on pornos.  Around the time we walked in, Boyer and McKnight started singing this ridiculous tune from one of McKnight's mixes.  I didn't buy anything, and when Antonio bought Full Metal Panic, i summed up the cliched plot with a guess.  A so-so day, but the laughs kept me going.  Antonio is awkward and spontaneous, Kevin is loud and obnoxious, and Anthony the equivalent of both, and a little more.  We missed the trolley after lying pennies on the track, and the guy skipped right over us.  The pennies falttened into the track, and two became one.  Like some awkward deja-vu-ness.  I shouldn't be online now, I owe my journal three entries, and that's two down.  I'll probably do the spelling and grammar correction next time I'm at my dad's, and have a faster Internet connection to analyze and correct things at optimal speed.  Current Mood: Nerve-wracked Current Music: Evanescence- Tourniquet      
    
</post>
<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Evanescence.  Fallen.  Excellent Cd, but a word of advice.  Before you buy a CD, don't kill it by killing all the songs within.  Basically, I listened to all the songs on the CD before, and bought it a year after everyone else.  I just suddenly found the time to buy it, and here I am, listening to all the songs I didn't download.  Eeg.    i owe this journal about three entries, one for THurs., Fri., and today.  So here's Thursday's. ========================================================= What did I do on Thursday?  Nothing, I think.  Watch my sis, other shit.  I think I went  outside, but my selective memory refuses to let me remember.   BRB? Current Mood: Annoyed Current Music: Evanescence- Everybody's Fool    
    
</post>
<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Five a.m, sun's rise should be in full effect shortly.  I've been awake for the whole night,   and Tesha's been bombarding me with stupid comments since FOur, until I just stopped talking to her.  I had the oddest dream the day before yesterday.  I  dreamt I awoke on a beach, with an ominous high-rise wooden mansion stood ominously before my family's eyes.  Without warning, a second passes and I find myself chatting in a small opening surrounded by trees, somewhere on that same island.  It is then we realized that we must find ways to utilize Modern technology.  Oddly enough, the mansion has Nickelodeon on in the room I would later claim as my own.  Cable, on an island?   Minutes later, I find myself locked in combat with my uncle, using shishkabobs, the clang of metal echoing in my mind.  My sister then recommends we explore the island, and we both dropped our weapons without a word or action.  Almost as if I was summoned, or being controlled in the dream by some godly force.  Peering over a ridge, we see a sequence of islands with a smaller mansion adjacent to ours, lying atop a seventy-foot cliff, looking over the sea.  Once more, I appear without warning, in the basement of the first mansion.  My father, uncle, and I are searching for radio equipment to broadcast our whereabouts.  Oddly enough, it looks like Boyer's basement, with a sea instead of a neighborhood.  It was at that point I slowly awoke(reality), to the sight of my locked bedroom door handle twisting in vain.  I hate dreams like that one.  I always have them.  I wake up somewhere I don't recognize, and  everything feels empty and desolate.  I never clearly see other people's faces in my dreams.  I was always focused on my own struggle.  Perhaps dreams portray life.  I am lost, and confused.  For some reason though, I do keep dreaming of bloodthirsty raptors in pursuit of me, and Dr. Hammond for some reason, telling me to deliver a healing herb to some stranded child.  My dreams, the gateway to an awkward reality where nothing is as it seems.  Maybe I should live in a sleepless state for the rest of my life.  Insomniac.    Current Mood:  Wary Current Music: Audioslave- Like A Stone ================================================== Now, if you will excuse me, I must break into my bedroom window from my basement.  
    
</post>
<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My gods, Tsubaki's voice acting is atrocious, as is her dialogue!  "Demonic Power flos through me!"  Give it a rest, lady.  Here's another entry, my record of four entries in a day.  Or is it five?   No matter!  I am bored.  My last entry was typed about 10 minutes ago, and I have to go.  I wil continue this tomorrow.  
    
</post>
<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's six thirty in the morning.  I left at five thirty, to get a coffee.  Here's how my super stealthy action escapade went down:  After signing off, I left my basement to climb my roof, and enter my bedroom window.  Immediately afterwards, I found sleep was eluding me.  Once more, I climbed out my window, to get my rollerblades and shoes.  After nearly falling from my roof, I put on my rollerblades.  The ride was smooth the whole way going up to Caron Lee's Street, but after crossing the track, the sleek friction against the wet road was suppressed by gravel in my wheel bearings.  Stopping at the WaWa, I saw five people awake.  I bought a sixteen ounce coffee, Irish cream, with milk, 6 Splenda sugar packets, and some Irish coffee creamer.  Once again, the skating was rough, add to that, the fact I had to carry my sneakers in one hand, and a coffee in the other(Run-On sentence, I know).  I stopped in the park parallel to god's condemned shopping center, Acme.  There, I finished my coffee in gulps.    There is nothing like heading down a street in the morning at five A.M., going down a hill at nearly forty miles per hour.  A quick turn, and the momentum(for more on this, analyze Newton's Laws Of Motion) allowed me to cruise at a moderate speed, slowing down gradually.  After that, I headed inside my bedroom, with my blades on the lawn chairs.  Here I am again, restless, and without a moment to spare.   Some of you may ask, "Why the hell did you put your trip to the WaWa in your journal?" Answer: 'Cause I want to, and I want you people to know the risks I take to enjoy life by my utmost desires.  As I type, I am watching the Style Network(WTF), gawking at the atrocious American fashions.  Only on special occasions should you let a gay man choose your repertoire of clothing.  I shiver at the thought.    Current Mood: Caffeinated, Robotic almost. Current Music: Evanescence- Haunted(It's playing in my head) ======================================================= Another coffee sounds good right about now.          
    
</post>
<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I made up a new name for New Jersey.  Hick City/State.  I rarely saw any african-americans or asians walking around.  There was an abundance of espanol speaking people though.  My mom took us to the zoo today, surprise, surprise.  My mother is actually more lively than I give her credit for.  She seemed much kinder, livelier, and happier than I've seen her recently.  I still stress over my own financial situation, however.  I lost my three-digit cost retainer, and owe Collingdale Court four hundred bucks.  I was in a happy-mood five minutes ago, thinking about animals and such.  Foxes are so cute.  Now I feel worried, paranoid, and shaky.  Other than that, I'll tell of my recurring premonition.  One Hundred Percent Non-Fiction.  Days before I visited this particular house, I was browsing my kitchen.  I then remembered tamarind flavored candy, and how odd it was that I found them delectable.  I thought of the times I'd wonder upstairs, playing Sega, and on the Computer, trying to play 8-bit Chess.  Simple times, where I didn't stress over things like school, money, and life.  July Eleventh, two-thousand four, one fifty-five A.M. I ascended the stair way lifelessly, staring at another hopelessly unattainable, asian femme fatale.  She greeted us warmly with a, "Hello! How are you?."  I simply nodded, while my other family members said hi.  I stepped into the house, the scenery vaguely familiar.  The same run-down neighborhood, and yellow paint job.  Cold blackness swept over me, and I remembered our night visits.  The image of two girls flashed before me, one red-hot, the other, slightly geeky.  Apparently, the geek had evolved into a femme-fatale.  I then remembered browsing my house for food, and candy.  I walked through, slowly remembering bits and pieces.  A wall appeared to be installed, and the two old fat-cats were deceased, replaced by a male, identical to my own feline, his fur a different tinge.  I remembered a closet connecting to an adjacent room, where I use to play hide-and-seek with the girls as a child.  They were at least five years older than me.    Eerie coincidence, or destiny for some awkward reason?  I don't know, but it kicks ass, and I want more of it.  I have to sneak back in my bedroom, and this is getting annoying.  My AOL membership should expire soon, and I'll have to get some deep-voiced friend to cancel it for me.  I think I sound too much like a teenager.  Aside from that, this was a pretty generic journal entry, I apologize.  I'll try to make the next one more engaging by being depressed.  Good night/morning, I'm going to bed.  It's Five in the morning.    Current Mood: Ditzy?  I dunno. Current Music: Three Days Grace- Just Like You Additional Notables:  Offspring- Can't Get My Head Around You    The Killers- Told Me Linkin Park- Breaking The Habit  Suckables: Beastie Boys: Check It Out 311- Any song, really.  Particularly, But this song really sucks.  Down, I think.      ================================================= Redemption is free, distasteful jimmies on vanilla ice-cream a quarter. You decide which you need more.   
    
</post>
<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Antonio has completed the 96-hour stay awake challenge!  I plan to surpass him, as soon as I get the chance at my dad's.  Boo Koo energy drink.   Accurate Nutrient Count for 1/3 of the can. Vitamin B6  250% Vitamin B12 100%  Niacin 100% Taurine 1000 Mg ...  Shouldn't I be deceased, or something?  Recent- Chinese- Cookie -Fortune -From -A -While -Ago. enthusiastic leadership gets you a promotion when you least expect it. Lucky Numbers: 1 2 3 17 27 37 Learn Chinese: Egg, Ji-Dan "So basically, ancient Chinese entrepreneurs and genius philosophers are telling me by saving a drowning nest of ants and directing them to higher ground, could net me a job as CEO of Sony America/Japan Corporation."  I love the Chinese.  They teach me so many things, like what to do with chopsticks, and how making Americanized Chinese food even if you're combating, Laos, Japanese, Philippine, Thai, Vietnamese will make you success full.  I would know, I'm Asian.  Anthony says I'm white, the hell he knows.  For the record, I have bashed on almost every race, primarily on Caucasians.  Happiness in a Oreo cookie.  I'm bored, and my friends online are boring as hell to talk to.  On phone, a little better.  In person, enjoyable.  Aside from that, this day has been lackluster, but I've stayed awake  for forty hours straight again, yesterday.  I got four hours of sleep, and I'm wondering if my normal complexion has restored or not.    -------Recent Moving Report------- My mom says she wants to move, but it could be as far as next year.  She says it's because of my grades, and the neighborhood I live in.  I agree on the neighborhood notion, for the most part.  Next Journal Entry: The Pros and Cons of Trends  Current Mood: Bored Current Music: The Killers- Somebody Told Me    
    
</post>
<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Trends.  You hate 'em, you love 'em, and you let 'em go in a heart beat.    Yo-yo's.  Scooters.  Pokemon.   This is a list of highly questionable trends many people look back on, and try to forget, or just pass off.  People these days, crowd-worship, ideal-followers, and idiots.  How popular was Limp Bizkit a while ago?  Celebs and businesses make money from trends, be it business or entertainment.  I know I'm not going too deep into the subject, but I just had an hour long chat with this girl I have a lot in common with.  I hope I find someone like her, my age.  I think trends are the by-product of greed, envy, and pride.  These things are the basis for so much bloodshed.  It all eventually leads up to  hate, suffering, and death.  It's the people that find something and stick by it, I like.  They're often them most unique, and not afraid to exhibit their differences.  I'm just glad there aren't a lot of white kids walking around acting Goth, because their life "sucks," from things like their parents not having a decent car, not enough money for music, and not having a girlfriend.  Shut up.    I said I'd write about trends and this is a promise I did keep.  I've never fulfilled any objective I've promised myself, and I find that pathetic.  Ian wants me to work out for the movie we're doing, and I haven't been doing it.  Also, I don't know how to do a cartwheel, or play Dance Dance Revolution.    I talked to a girl I met in a "Philly" chat room who lives around Lancaster.  She's intelligent, book-smart, street-wise, and just know things.  I realized simply talking is enough for stress relief, as well as talking about problems and emotions.  Kevin tried to help me, and I rarely noticed because I just wanted to forget everything and hold my hatred inside of me.  Sorry.  It's almost this sweltering pressure that seems to drive a person to homicide.  The girl.  She and her have enough things alike for me to like her as a friend.  Not the kind that says hi to you for something she needs, or for cheap thrills, or to flirt and tease you without meaning anything, but the kind you know does care.  I don't think I have enough of those friends, and it's probably my fault.  Cuurent Mood: Empty Current Music: Linkin Park- Meteora CD(Chris, I'm keeping it.) ======================================== Life sucks, embrace it with open arms and tears of scarlet.
    
</post>
<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Occasionally out of boredom I read other people's journals just to know what they think.  I see such misguided anger, and pointless rage.  I can't help but wonder if I'm like all these other generic people.  It pains me to see friends suffer, sometimes I just wish I could take their suffering and make it my own.  Maybe I care too much, but I treasure the friends I know will stick by me no matter what the distance and difference.  Things like these make me depressed, to see these unlived pockets of time where I could be doing something to help someone, a friend, a stranger, just anyone.  I know I do  enjoy  human suffering, but even I have compassion for mankind.  Maybe I really am just sick.       We all talk, but does it mean anything?  When we talk about people behind their backs, you just feel dishonorable and unclean.  I know I do it a lot, but now Ileast I tell it to people's faces now.  When the dust clears, you'll see who's there for you and who's not.  People like Chris, and even Kevin.  I used to think KEv' was such a jackass, because of that time he almost broke my gals screen door, and torched my house.  But if you take the time to look beneath the surface, you'll notice an immense density of life and emotion in people, unnotciable upon first glance.    I said I was going to be depressed this journal entry, and here it is.  Music.  It just stirs up so many moments, you begin to feel sorry about the things you've said and done, and regret ever person you've left behind.  From my mom's side, friends and family can tell I'm just as stubborn as her.  I'll hold a grudge longer than most people, where they just forgive you the next day like nothing happened.  Maybe I need to be more forgiving.  Quarrels that arise from small things, I personally tend to, until they become behemoth problems I should don't deal with.    It's the fact I hold everything in, evey bitter comment that haunts me that I think about in my sleep, to the point I want to kill.  It's my fault, I never deal with anything.  One of thses days I'm going to break down again, and end up hurting somebody or myself.  I just can't deal with it.  My father told me to " bite my lip " in situations such as these, and this is the result.  A broken soul, lying in the shadows.  People judge upon sight, and that is probably why I do so.   People take one look at me, and either frown in pity, hatred, or misunderstanding.  I hate it so much, which is why I look down upon every person I see with a look of utter hatred.  It's just this look, I can't help it.  The look that says, "I'm not happy, I hope you die soon."    The staring most frequently came from old white people.   *  -_-     I was always alone during middle school.  I just kind of sat in secluded areas where noone can see me, and wallowed in my own self-pity.  It wasn't that I was lonely, just that I couldn't understand.  I still can't.  The understanding of my misery, that is.  It's not complex, it's just that I can't find a compromise to help my dilemma.  I would have taken depression medication like Chris, but I'd feel worse because I'd have the insult of knowing I am incapable of solving my own problems.  It's a chemical imbalance, but I am human.  I can overcome it, if I had the effort.   The thing is, I don't, and I am an utter failure in my own right.  Why?    Current Mood: Moody  Current Music: Blink182- Adam's Song  ==================================  Spare me sympathy.  Just understand.                     
    
</post>
<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Blogger just got an awesome update.   I can now customise my text,  style,  font, timestamp-edit, upload pictures, and insert URL links.  Kick.  Ass.      Number of Sad Things Today: Two.    What happened?        I bladed to Chris's house(twenty to twenty five minutes), only to have his mother take a trip to pick Donna up, when I could have stayed home and haave her pick me up.  Folcroft has the worst ascending hills.     </post></Blog>