<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      =) To Jac (= Haha... ok...i will break up my words into portions k...so to safe ur eyes..hehez.. well...tml u kao shi le...gOoD LucK!  =) Homework (= Wo Finally Finish Le~~! YeaY~~! *cLaPs* hahah... yes! i tot i cannot finish...but i did! woOoW! *drumrolls* haha! sooo happie!  =) Project )= Finish F le! Maths haven... ): but aniwae is end of july pass up ma...slowly lar...haiyo...   =) OuT (= Went swimming todae... sOoO Little PpL~~ lol...y? my philosophy: LAST DAY OF HOLIDAE = PIA HMWK! but i left a little ma...so i go lor..hahah...then become chao dar =X heheh..who cares~ lol...i happie jiu hao le...hehehehx  =( Pack Bag )=  I hate to pack bag! ee yer... pack until so sad de...lol.. tomolo muz carry alot of books...later i go pack at 8 plus pack maths file...muz pass up tml! yUp =(  =) Radio (= Keeps mi company..hahah...ThaNk U RaDio .... i noe...its lame... hahahahax  =( My TagBoard Is Gone, sO aS MusIc )= haiyo...my blog got problem mux solve.... :'( ********************************************** oOkiE...i stop here liao...tml muz go sch... now muz go eat dinner...haiyo.... ookie...to  those still pia-ing...GoOd LucK!! fOr ThOse  FiNiSh LiAO~~ yay~~ hahah...ookie...bubye  ppl...cya tml~~!~~! *cLe* ***********************************************
    
</post>
<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yay~~! I fInIsH My HmWk Le...ExCePt FoR F LeFt A LiTtLe BaH~~ hehehe...tomolo SURE FINISH DE~ ofCuz ThE oNlY DaE leFt To FiNiSH~~ heheheheh....soooo happie and relieve.... todae...i go a friend de house downstairs pei ta tok tok....oso do hmwk lar... yar...bu zhi bu jue de....6.30pm le~~ ye zhuo wan le.. haha...had an enjoyable time ... yUp... hehe...then oso got go tammie house borrow maths...dunno how to do lar....and oso cant finish ma.. =X heheh.. so last resort lor...u noe lor.. hahaz... hmm..then i continue f at home then...OH! no reinforcement ring le... so i go hougang mall buy lor... there dunno y...sOooooOO crowded..i walk until so pek cek.. but managed to get lar.. Oo...my file gonna explode le.. so packed de... then haven put in contents pg and bibliography... haiz... ying sai ba~~ todae oso very gan dong~~ my dad bought mi a KeYcHaIn WITh ClOcK De~~ is a shape of a ladybird~~ the buggy thingy...yar...i sOoOo surprised! i tot i cannot find le...guo shi le... yet my dad found dao~~ wow~~ ai shi ni le~~ hahahZ... hmm... then todae got rain wor....but still hot lar.. hahaha... nvm...got rain jiu hao... juz recieved my dear friend shi wen de testimonial~~ im oso ShOcKeD! i tot i will nvr get de testi de... hahaz...finally le... so gan xie ni ;) yar...but abit sad to hear tt... becuz mi, [mel and shi wen]</post></Blog>