<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       time: 3pm location: office ================= wah! terribly sleepy now and no mood to work. start to understand why resigned staff have no mood to work in the last month.! also, i am so eager for the new laptop assign by new company. miss chu said i am so chu wo... ng! but, i really eager for it ah!     
    
    
</post>
<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
          珠珠!  
    
    
</post>
<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       in yesterday course, it showed how to boot from CF and busybox. it is a very brief intro. only. let me explore more later! actually, i started feeling the course is too easy to me.   references:  urlLink busybox    urlLink course content  
    
    
</post>
<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i have resigned from my current company. a bit "dont know how" feeling.  anyway, quote a passage from my frd. i think he also copy from elsewhere. it should reflect my reason of resignation.   I would rather be ashes than dust!  I would rather that my spark should burn out in a brilliant blaze  than it should be stifled by dry-rot.  I would rather be a superb meteor, every atom  of me in magnificent glow, than a sleepy and permanent planet.  The function of man is to live, not to exist.  I shall not waste my days trying to prolong them.  I shall use my time.    
    
    
</post>
<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       是嗎？真的完了嗎？ 
    
    
</post>
<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        I found my japanese name is  松尾 Matsuo (tail of a pine tree) 雄大 Masahiro (big hero) .  i got this translation by my chinese name in english from a webpage but i dont know how it do the translation.  urlLink You may check out yours from  this link!      
    
    
</post>
<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I think, I really broke up with her...   DON'T BREAK MY HEART ==================== 也許是我不懂的事太多 也許是我的錯 也許一切已是慢慢的錯過 也許不必再說 從未想過你我會這樣結束 心中沒有把握 (心中如此難過) 只是記得你我彼此的承諾 一次次的衝動 Don't Break My Heart 再次溫柔 不願 看到你那保持的沉默 獨自等待 默默承受 喜悅總是出現在我夢中 你所擁有的是你的身體 誘人的美麗 我所擁有的是我的記憶 美妙的感覺  
    
    
</post>
</Blog>