<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Did nothing today.  Actually, i walked to the kitchen around 1, and to the backdoor once.  Awsome stuff.  Hours upon hours of CS, time flew.  I'm still liking this summer stuff now, it'll wear off.  After mutti's arrival home i ate some din and headed off for bowling.  Bowled a 612, which is uber good for me at playmor.  I seem to suck there with my low avg or 186.  Might be good to some of you readers, but not really for me, thats what i had last year :(:(.  Anywho i think willis seta and joe are coming 2mEEr to save me from bordum.  Should be fun.  2mEEr = the last time i bowl for about 5 days.  For any1 that really knows me, you would know that is an INCREDIBLY long time for me.  Hopefully the carpets will let me bet with them again (so i can take their mula).  Uhh...poker friday i think, let me know peeps.  Sunseri is the only hardcore cat i know is in fo SHO, so holla.  TY, your "pal" nub-it.  
    
</post>
<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Changed my mind, i'll continue blogging.  I just wont really speak the WHOLE truth, just speak what i know wont offend.  I'll walk away from the experience with just a little more knowledge and wisdom.  And remember kidz, Truth Hurts, and is better left untold. 
    
</post>
<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This will be my last post.  Its caused me more trouble than i bargain for.  The truth is not meant to be told, for all those who dont know that already.  If u have a problem, hide it, and dont ever make it obvious.  Thanks for reading all of the few things i have been able to post, its been fun.  Sometimes i think that things are unfair, but thats only the way that things are meant to be.  O well is all i can say.  I'm gonna go now, lay down and rethink.  Thanks again for reding my life adventures and opinions for the while that you did.  Your Friend, Wiseass Spoiled little boy, Alan Davis.  O yes, if any of you decide to make one of these blogs, make sure that everyone u think might react badly to your postings is blocked/ cant have access to it.  Its deadly.  Ta Ta for now.
    
</post>
<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Poker tonight, yes, the second week in a row.  I'm glad, its addicting and i have a lot of fun doing it.  But anyway,  i lost miserably in the main game.  100 bucks going to the winner, most people we had yet.  Lots of fun tho.  So i walk over to the side game that dave got started.  And wouldnt ya know it, my luck changed. Flipped 180 degrees and i won.  50 bucks or something.  Overall profit for the night is 30.  Atleast my confidence in my poker playing hasnt completely vanished.  No fireworks 2nite, i know whats better between fireworks and poker, i'm no fool.  Not much besides that today, just an average day.  And thats a good thing i suppose.  I'm probably not gonna do much 2mEEr either, again, a good thing.  I'm sick of being alone :-\.  </post></Blog>