<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   &gt; &gt; seorang ibu mertua (berumur lingkungan 50an)datang &gt; &gt; menziarahi rumah anak menantu perempuannya yang baru &gt; &gt; berkahwin. setelah membunyikan loceng, si mertua &gt; &gt; terkejut kerana mendapati menantu perempunnya yang &gt; &gt; membuka pintu tanpa seurat benangpun di badannya. &gt; &gt; &gt; &gt; tanpa di tanya, si menantu berkata "saya sedang &gt; &gt; menunggu suami saya pulang dari berkerja!". &gt; &gt; "tapi kau telanjang !!!???" marah si ibu mertua. &gt; &gt; &gt; &gt; "ini BAJU CINTA saya" balas si menantu &gt; &gt; "BAJU CINTA ??" si mertua kehairanan &gt; &gt; "ya, suami saya menyukainya, saya juga begitu senang &gt; &gt; MEMAKAInya" &gt; &gt; "saya harap mak dapat balik dulu sebelum suami saya &gt; &gt; pulang keran tentu suami saya nanti akan berasa malu &gt; &gt; melihat saya memakai BAJU CINTA ini di hadapan mak" &gt; &gt; pinta si menantu. &gt; &gt; &gt; &gt; Si mertua faham kehendak anak menantunya. dalam &gt; &gt; fikirannya mungkin itu cara terbaru si isteri melayan &gt; &gt; sang suami. di dalam perjalanan pulang si mertua &gt; &gt; mendapat idea ... fikirnya dengan mengikut cara anak &gt; &gt; menantunya, sudah tentu dia dapat mengeratkan &gt; &gt; hubungannya dengan suaminya yang sudah berumur. &gt; &gt; &gt; &gt; sesampai di rumah, si mertua tadi menanggalkan semua &gt; &gt; pakaiannya, mandi, berbedak dan memakai minyak wangi &gt; &gt; sewangi wanginya. kemudian si mertua tadi pun menunggu &gt; &gt; suaminya pulang dari bekerja. &gt; &gt; &gt; &gt; lat berberapa ketika suami si mertua tadi pulang, &gt; &gt; dengan bangganya simertua tadi menayangkan tubuh badan &gt; &gt; yang tanpa seurat benang kepada suaminya. (dengan gaya &gt; &gt; ala marilyn monroe) &gt; &gt; &gt; &gt; "kenapa dengan kau nie ... buang tebiat???" marah &gt; &gt; sisuami tadi. &gt; &gt; "ini lah BAJU CINTA bang" kata si mertua tadi &gt; &gt; "hah? BAJU CINTA???" soal sisuami sambil memandang &gt; &gt; dari atas kebawah. &gt; &gt; seketika si suami tadi menambah &gt; &gt; "KENAPA TAK SETERIKA DULU ??? NAMPAK SANGAT KEDUTNYA" 

						
</post>
<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Malam semalam aku tak boleh tidur.. puas aku pusing sana sini. tak leh gak tido, penangan kopi la ni. Maka semalam aku pun tengok Euro2004. Dua perlawanan, yang pertama France vs Swiss(3-1). Yang kedua Italy vs Bulgaria(2-1). Kedua-dua perlawanan ni, sangat menarik sekali. France memang dah dapat masuk ke separuh akhir dan Italy pulak di kedudukan genting. Akhirnya, tahniah kepada pasukan France kerana berjaya, manakala pasukan Italy walaupun menang game semalam, diorang kalah pada kiraan mata. Walaubagaimanapun cara permainan diorang semalam boleh dikatakan terbaik... Sehinggalah pukul 5.00pagi baru aku terlelap kat lantai. Bangun tidur pun lambat he he...Tapi aku tak menyesal mengenangkan perlawanan hebat semalam.   

						
</post>
<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    ITALLY urlLink    

						
</post>
<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    EURO 2004 urlLink    

						
</post>
<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   bg yg bersekolah d zaman 70-80an :)  hi guys!! read this.. teringat kat zaman dolu2...our sweet old times..hehehe &gt; Those OLD days!! &gt; &gt; You grew up watching He-man, Transformers, &gt; Thundercats, Silver Hawk, Space Cop Gaban, &gt; Ultraman, and Mighty Mouse. Not to forget, Ninja &gt; Turtles, Mask and Smurfs too. You grew up brushing &gt; your teeth with a mug in primary school after &gt;recess time. You squatted by a drain with all your &gt; classmates beside you, and brushed your teeth with &gt; a colourful mug. Remember the days when the school &gt; nurse comes with a list for the dentist &gt; appointments, the sound of the drilling when your &gt; friend has a fill in his tooth. &gt; &gt; You remember the packets of milk (Projeck Susu &gt; Segar) and milo we get in primary school to &gt; encourage us to drink more milk. And when we had &gt; to line up just to get one cup, and some of us &gt; would line up again for another cup of cold milo. &gt; And remember we use to buy susu sekolah and get &gt; stomach-ache the next day. During primary (some &gt; KBSR  3M) school days, the teacher will punish &gt; you using a long ruler to hit your palm. A bowl of &gt; noodle soup cost only 40c in primary school days. &gt; When you were in primary school, girls like to go &gt; to the bookshop to buy cute stuff such as animal &gt; erasers, sharpeners, notebook etc. Play with these &gt; paper doll... with all the paper clothes.. etc etc &gt; &gt; In secondary (some KBSM) school, girls go to the &gt; library to borrow their favourite romance &gt; storybook. In secondary school, girls altered &gt; their school skirt to shorten it and guys will go &gt; to the school appointed school uniform tailor shop &gt; to tailor make their school trousers to the then &gt; fashionable "baggy pants" , or the GQ one with all &gt; the 'batik' or buckle at the edge of the pocket! &gt; the straight cut jeans.. or codroy... In secondary &gt; school days, you buy the Bata BM Turbo school &gt; shoes. Some guys like to wear those china made &gt; ankle high shoes. Some even like to wear those &gt; very thick socks with their school shoes. remember &gt; the panda, carefree or warrior shoes.. :) &gt; Internet? E-mail? What the hell is that? So you &gt; thought a decade or more ago. Your friends don't &gt; have pagers or handphones in school. CDs? What's &gt; that? Cassette tapes were the norm. Movie tickets &gt; used to cost less than $5 last time. there is no &gt; KLCC.. Pertama or Bukit Bintang the only place we &gt; have.. &gt; &gt; The goodies from Mamak shop used to be Mamee, Ka &gt; ka, Kum Kum, Ding Dang choco balls (with toys in &gt; the box) + the mat sentul voices as a jingle, &gt; colourful hard "egg", "cigerette" chocolate, pink &gt; bottle of bubbles, and small tubes with yellow &gt; sticks to blow "more lasting" bubbles that you can &gt; pop more air in or slam it on. You never forget &gt; 'Ti Kam'. When exams are over, the board games &gt; (eg: UNO, Monopoly, CLUEDO)  hand held video &gt; games will be all over the class room. Girls will &gt; start playing 'batu seremban'. guys with 'tudung &gt; botol oren' Your favourite sound is the bell! For &gt; it's the homemade ice cream man. The cream that &gt; tops Haagan Dazs! The pink colour ice-cream with &gt; eyes plus a wide smile. Another bell is the recess &gt; bell, a time to get away from school work and to &gt; eat. Another time when there is no bell but all &gt; guys will anxiously wait for it...The PJ, PE &gt; time (time for football!!) &gt; &gt; Your favourite childhood games were playing &gt; "guli"(marbles), five stones, zero-point, &gt; catching, and/or "Pepsi-Cola one two three"! The &gt; best thirst quencher of all times is the yummy &gt; colourful ice tubes you can buy from provision &gt; shops. To eat them, break the tab and suck while &gt; holding the freezing tube! All gals had barbie &gt; dolls, My Little Pony, pound puppy, Polly Pocket &gt; and etc, while all boys had star wars figurines or &gt; a rubber band catapult that shoots folded paper or &gt; eraser bits. Once was the era whereby ice-cream &gt; sticks were valueable items, than came the paper &gt; aircrafts, chalk fights. &gt; &gt; Everyone envied the class monitor and his &gt; assitant, cos they were the ones who came up with &gt; the daily duty roster, giving names to teacher on &gt; who makes the most noise and who's running around &gt; the class. The elite group are the prefects, the &gt; one with license to move around, they consider &gt; themselves above the law when not many students &gt; actually listened to them, and that's when the PK Hem comes in. &gt; &gt; Some boys made their own guns from wood,and used &gt; 'Bacali' as the bullets. Some even used matches to &gt; shoot and burn kids'lanterns during Latern &gt; Festival.. and you also rather to 'ponteng sekolah' &gt; juz to watch final episod of Moero Attack .. miss that much.. &gt; summersault berkembar... hehehe.. still remember this one.. &gt; &gt; Cheers to the 70's..80's babies... WE RULE THIS WORLD!  

						
</post>
<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Lama juga aku tak updated site nie... maklumlah tengah pening kepala nak cari rumah nak pindah pastu sibuk dengan kelas, kerja dan sebagainya. Macam-macam nak difikirkan tapi yang jadi pokoknya duitlah, apa lagi. Hmm.. aku risau juga dengan isu duit nie ...makin lama hidup makin tak cukup duit . Hai pening-pening...dulu masa kerja McD gaji RM600/- rasa tak cukup, tapi sekarang nie gaji dah RM 900/- ingatkan dah cukup dah tapi rupanya tak lagi.      Bulan depan aku pindah rumah baru di Kampung Keramat, rumah flat sewa RM500/-. Pengalaman hidup yang baru aku. Nampaknya lepas nie aku kena kerja kuat lagi. Begitulah hidup orang yang mula dari bawah, kena kerja kuat sepanjang masa, kalau tak tak hidup. Dalam masa yang sama aku kena jumpa penyelaras aku untuk selesaikan masalah Latihan Industri aku, cover kerja, cover subjek aku semester nie.Kelam-kabut juga dibuatnya. Hai mana satu yang nak di buat dulu.        

						
</post>
</Blog>