<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink mono  1.0 is supposed to be released today. got into  urlLink python  some more. i made a program that prints out my  urlLink amule  stats and then made an  urlLink xchat  plugin to do the same thing except msg it to the active channel. also made a stupid thing that makes use of uname. oh well, whatever, i'm tired and low on cigarettes, so i'm going to bed.
    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      last night i had, as the title of this post suggests, a really weird dream. i was leading this group of like 10 people into a huge castle/fortress. we all stayed together with our backs to eachother and took out the entire entrance court thing. i remember someone was going to behead a guy and i was like "no no.. give him an honorable death!" and pushed him onto his knees and thrust the sword through the back of his neck and into his body, and of course it went right through because it was a dream. and i guess i got that from the movie Gladiator. then we all spread out all over the castle to kill anything we found alive. some time later, and i have no idea how much time that would be since it was a dream, i found that every member of my group was dead except for me, and everyone on the enemy's side was dead too except for the leader. i climbed up a shitload of stairs to the very top of the castle where i found these two huge wooden doors. then this big satan-like demon creature thing bursts through them at me and i woke up. guess i'm not the man for that kind of job. i gotta render a movie based on this dream some time though.
    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      everyone who cares about the title of this post should read  urlLink this  interesting editorial  about filesharing's effect on the music industry (which is actually fractional).
    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i slept like a baby all night and woke up at 7am. took a shower, made something to drink and gave the cats some food. sat at the computer, lit a cigarette, turned on some  urlLink Stevie Ray Vaughn . checked some of my favorite sites for updates, caught up on emails, and checked my  urlLink aMule  downloads.  awesome morning so far? yes
    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ever since i got on linux i've been exploring what all is possible with it. from  urlLink XMMS  to  urlLink aMule ,  urlLink RealPlayer  to  urlLink Gaim ,  urlLink X-Chat  to  urlLink The GIMP , i've definitely done a lot of exploring. and now that i'm comfortable with linux, i've decided it's time to get back to hacking. i've been very interested in  urlLink mono , even before i switched to linux. even though i already know some C# from developing with the .NET framework on windows, and even though it is a very well designed, and very powerful language, i've become interested in  urlLink Python . and since i know you can use any language with mono, i've decided i'm going to try to use python with it, and go down that path.  today i discovered  urlLink wxPython , and it's awesome.
    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so google accepted my application for AdSense, and i logged in and it asked me for all this info, which i gave, without needing to look anything up. then when i started reading the terms and conditions it says: .. you must be at least 18 years of age .. (or something like that). *alt+left,left,left*. bummer. i can see how they might require you to be at a legal working age for your state.. but they strictly forbid porn and things like that, so i'm not sure where the 18 comes from. i'm employable. i'm taxable. believe me, i'm very taxable.  but in other good news, i passed out on my bed around 6pm last night and woke up about 30 minutes ago. feeling pretty good right now. a little sore, but still, it feels good to be up this early, and not because i stayed up all night.  but anyway, i just lost like 20% of the respect i had for google (so i'm now at 80%), so fuck that anyway. i have something else lined up for advertising. something that will pay me by time, not by clicks. so take that google! jk ilu </post></Blog>