<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Here is where I post my random info on my book The Grimoir of Azrael Blacksun. It has a lot of cool stuff and will have at least two posts a week so keep looking back. As I say, it shall be so!
     

    
</post>
<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						     3480 C.E.    	 	If you hadn’t seen the battle you would have thought that an army of dragons had waged war over Hundred-Mile Oasis. This once glorious and spacious hide away for the desert dwellers was no reduced to a smoldering pile of charred brush. The ash of the recent battle stretched the width and breath of the oasis, leaving no tree whole, no pool or stream moist.  Most hadn’t fled at the beginning of the battle and were incinerated, and those were the luck ones. Those who had would die a slow and painful death of dehydration and starvation out in the harsh sun of the Southern Desert.  	From under the remains of a once glorious temple to a god whose name was now illegible crawled the victor. Covered in ash and gore he tried to stand but the ground would not let him. Every time he tried to steady himself the ground rushed back up to meet him. 	“I got to use less power on that next time,” He panted. “If there is a next time.” 	He scanned the freshly cauterized landscape for some thing he could use but to no avail. ‘It seems I will die here’ He thought.  	The world around him finally stopped spinning and he was able to stand. Slowly, and with much pain, he crossed the battlefield looking for his salvation. Kicking ash and soot into the air with every step all he uncovered was more ash and what was left of the village’s dead. 	Behind him a faint pant called to him. “You beast. You killed them all, the entire village, man, woman and child. You killed my friends… my family… my son.”  	Spinning around to see the voice a heaving feeling caught a hold of his gut and emptied the contents of his stomach onto the ground in front of him. He beheld the body of a woman, or what used to be a woman, in a glowing suit of armor. All that remained of her was a tattered and burnt mask of a face and what part of her torso that was still beneath the armor.  	“I did what I had to noble paladin. That beast killed my parents. It killed the monks who raised me from childhood. It desolated every home I have ever had. It has caused too much pain to let it live. You must accept that.” 	“May your body rot in the abyss,” The female paladin on the ground coughed between harsh wheezing. “No. I will not accept it.” 	The paladin reached out with what was left of her arm and coughed some gruff words. Out of her stub of an arm shot a bolt of white light. The bolt cracked its target square in the chest but he just shrugged it off. It seemed to energize him. A ring on his finger that was moments ago completely covered in soot started to glow a faint blue. 	“I thank you noble one.” He whispered. “But you are a bout to die and I must live to ensure that my mission is a success.” 	He reached down and touched the suit of armor that encased the destroyed woman gently with his fingertips. Instantly a blue flame engulfed his body and the armor started to fade, along with the little life that was still in the woman’s face. Power flooded his body and it left the armor and he could feel his strength return.  	The blue flame slowly faded out. A gentle wind blew on the field of death blowing away the paladin, and her armor’s, ashes; never to be seen again. 	“Now,” He said resolutely. “To make sure this is truly over.” 	The ground beneath his feet heaved up suddenly nearly throwing him to the ground as a bright silvery flash broke the surface of the ashen barren. It rose quickly towards the white sun growing brighter the closer it got. It finally stopped and seemed to be consumed by light. 	“You will die defiler!” The light called. “I will destroy you Yai for your sins towards this land.” 	A blue flame engulfed Yai’s body. “Come get me dragon,” Yai shouted as he rose up into the air. “Or are you too cowardly to loose another arm?”  	The light faded a little to reveal a tall draconic humanoid with scales like mirrors, clad in the same type of armor as the paladin. Out of its left socket where it’s arm should have been dripped a shiny, metallic white liquid. 	“I fear no human, monk!” the dragon roared as it’s right claw lunged at the young monk’s throat.    -*-  	The keep was cold and dark. Onyx walls and floors dominated the nearly bare room. 	The hum of the chaos beyond the walls of his keep ground on Xaros’ sanity. The most powerful mage, no being, in the multiverse and he couldn’t relent the constant noise of sound that flashed between the planes. It was a perpetual storm of song, cries and screams mashed together in a spiraling mass. 	Not that Xaros needed his sanity; he was beyond such restrictions and labels. He existed beyond the bounds of mortals and god. His word was his will and his will was law. With but a thought he could create or destroy. 	It was an orgasmic experience, to be.  

						
</post>
<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    3461 C.E.   	“What is this?” a small man wrapped in tattered old cloths shouted to his companion.  	“It look’s like a child to me,” The other man said quizzically. “But who would leave a child out here?” 	The first man reached down at the child. The child, only a few days old already had a full head of long silver hair, something birth the travelers lacked. They both chuckled. ‘Some people have all the luck.’  	“I guess there is only one thing to do,” the older man said. “We must take him back to the monastery.”    -*- Eighteen years later… -*-     Liona rode her steed up to the top of the crest overlooking the oasis. She loved it up here. From here she could see the entire oasis, all one hundred miles of it. It was where she went to regain her peace. 	Sliding of her majestic Pegasus she patted it on its flanks and it took of the edge of the crest back to the village. She needs to be alone. Or at least as alone she could be. Looking down she rubbed her stomach through her specially made silver chain mail.  	“I am really starting to show it now,” She thought. “It won’t be long my son. Soon you will be born and your all the world will know your power.” 	The thought brought a grin to her face. She had been planning to take on a husband for years to produce and heir to rule the village after her death but always feared the weakness of being tied down. Then, nine months ago she was blessed with this child. The midwives in the village were all astounded by it. They had never seen a child born with out a father. Yet they knew to Liona. She was their Matron, their ruler, and none lived to tell of contesting her. 	With a sharp whistle he winged companion returned to her side and knelt down to allow her to get on easier.  	“I may be pregnant you old mule, but am I still able to get on to a steed with out being treated like an old relic.” 	“I am sorry madam,” The Pegasus said in an airy voice. “But it makes it easier on my back if you don’t jump on like before you put on all the weight.” 	Liona grunted as she strained to climb onto the Ariel horse. “I have half of mind to turn you into a pillow Zephyr,” Liona growled. 	“You would never do that madam,” Zephyr laughed. “Who would help you guard he skies.” 	Zephyr kicked into the air and soared far up into the sky.  	“Damn mule,” Liona growled as Zephyr let out an airy laugh.  	  -*-     The streets were filled with people of every race scurrying and bumping to get to their diverse location. Yai went completely unnoticed in the vast crowd, but that was how he liked it. The less attention he got the better. All he wanted to do was get in, get out, and get on his way. These streets were far to crowded for a boy who was raised in a monastery.  	‘The people I passed on the road said that it would be deep within the magic district of Silver Coast,’ Yai thought. ‘ Now if I could only find that.’ 	Pushing his way past a small group of female dark elves he thought he felt a dagger graze his coin purse but decided to not try it. It was far too public a place to challenge anyone. ‘I got to get of this street. I wish I could find someone to help me.’ 	“Maybe I could be of service young monk,” A gentle voice called from behind him. 	Spinning on his heels Yai couldn’t see anything through the river of bodies and then looked down towards a kick to his shins. Right at his feet was a dwarven woman with long hair clad in tight fitting studded leather armor. ‘I have never seen a dwarf before, but I have heard stories,’ Yai thought. ‘Maybe she can help.’ 	Before Yai could even sputter a greeting the dwarven woman chimmed in. “I can help you young one, but only if you don’t let the tales you’ve heard get in the way.” 	“How did you know that?” Yai started. “I never said anything!” 	“I see you don’t get out much honey.” The dwarf laughed. “I am a telepath, I can read minds. I know you’ve never seen one of those before?” 	“I guess you would.” Yai tried to laugh, still caught off guard by the fact that his thoughts weren’t safe any more. “So… can you help?” 	“If it be the Crone you seek then I recommend you wait till tonight. She won’t even think of letting you in till the black sun reaches it’s peak.” 	“This is a problem.” Yai said sheepishly. “I have no where to stay and not a coin to my name.”  ‘Not anymore anyways,’ he thought. 	“Yah I saw it earlier.” She chuckled producing a small leather bag with a silver feather on it. “I thought you would like it back. Oh… before I go. My band and me have a small headquarters near by. If you be looking for a place to stay I am sure my band won’t mind helping you out for a night. Provided you can give us some payment… a thrilling story of your travels.” 	“I’m not much of a story teller but… I guess I have no choice,” Yai grimaced at the thought of the gruff crowd the dwarf worked with. 	“ I guess you don’t,” she chuckled as she walked off. “Oh, by the way I and Yroc Retep, leader of the Guild of the Golden Ram.   

						
</post>
<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   This is my new posting site for my book called  The Grimoir of Azrael Blacksun . It is a fantsy story set on the plane of Tyre, a world not dissimmilar to Torile from  D  or Dominira from  Magic: The Gathering . Each post will be a diffrent chapter in the stroy of a young warrior named Yai where he discovers his true inner power and in the end meets an interesting fate. From time to time I will post small tidbits of info about the characters or the general world of Tyr on a seperate blog:                                 http://legendsoftyr.blogspot.com  Hope you check in often and early, I will post the first chapter tommorow. As I say, it shall be so! 

						
</post>
</Blog>