<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       節奏, 對於一個人的生活是非常重要的. 當你捉不到他, 你便要花上很長的時間才能找回她的踪影. 抓不緊他, 那段時間大多也只是白過, 全因你對事物已失去興趣. 這, 全因為她. 有時, 你甚至會放棄找回她他,  在你的內心深處, 這可能並非你所想的. 人總會累, 你也不自覺的停下來, 小休一會. 但只要你堅持信念, 有一個明確的目標. 最終, 你也能找回她的.  Get with the beat!  
    
    
</post>
<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       諗左幾日,終於搵到一個term去形容自己今次考試. 都唔想咁講, 係放"pea". 可能真係自己讀咁多年書, 都未話有一次認真咁去讀過, 到左form 4, 過左三次test  exam既洗禮, 累了.  依家考試, 就好似做quiz咁, 都唔知係好定係壞事. Anyway, the exam is almost over. Prepare for the worst, hope for the best. 
    
    
</post>
<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       今日收到個份野, 好surprise. 始終, 當初咁做並唔係為左d乜, 只想盡一分微力, 幫下手.  最初, 真係唔知乜事架, 見到份野, 個一刻真係唔識講野, 只懂笑. Physics I 既唔開心都走哂. 開心既程度, 非筆墨所能形容.  下次講下呢一年所發生過既野. 
    
    
</post>
<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Anyone Of Us (Stupid Mistakes)  by Gareth Gates   I've been letting you down, down Girl I know I've been such a fool Giving in to temptation I should've played it cool The situation got out of hand I hope you understand  (Chorus) It can happen to Anyone of us, anyone you think of Anyone can fall Anyone can hurt someone they love Hearts will break 'Cause I made a stupid mistake It can happen to Anyone of us, say you will forgive me Anyone can fail Say you will believe me I can't take my heart will break 'Cause I made a stupid mistake A stupid mistake  She was kind of exciting A little crazy I should've known She must have altered my senses 'Cause I offered to walk her home The situation got out of hand I hope you understand  (Chorus) It can happen to Anyone of us, anyone you think of Anyone can fall Anyone can hurt someone they love Hearts will break 'Cause I made a stupid mistake It can happen to Anyone of us, say you will forgive me Anyone can fail Say you will believe me I can't take my heart will break 'Cause I made a stupid mistake A stupid mistake  A stupid mistake she means nothing to me (nothing to me) I swear every word is true don愒 wanna lose you  The situation got out of hand I hope you understand  (Chorus)  It can happen to Anyone of us, anyone you think of Anyone can fall Anyone can hurt someone they love Hearts will break 'Cause I made a stupid mistake It can happen to Anyone of us, say you will forgive me Anyone can fail Say you will believe me I can't take my heart will break 'Cause I made a stupid mistake  Anyone can fall Anyone can hurt someone they love Hearts will break 'Cause I made a stupid mistake A stupid mistake    =================================== Anyone of us would make a mistake, just make sure that you won't make the same mstake again, so you did earn something from it. 
    
    
</post>
<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       呢幾日本應溫好physics  chemisrty, 奈何捉不到節奏, 咁就浪費左三整日. 幸好, 今日下午, 有如"連同昨天所失的 都找到了",  搵番應有既節奏, 都總算睇過下chemistry. 只希望明天再找回狀態, 好好的溫習physics吧!  時間, 好似一向都係我最大既競爭對手, 時間, 你何時才能跟我交好, 成為我的摯友呢?  我努力地尋找, 熱切地期待這天的到來!!! 
    
    
</post>
<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       今日個兩份paper既表現, 的確有d令自己失望. Paper3做完唔夠時間check, paper1 仲搞笑, 直頭無proofread到, 仲要塗完個字, 唔記得寫番. 又勁錯GRAMMAR. 我諗max都係64到... Anyway, it's over. And i'm glad that i laughed, saying that i didn't do well on this two papers. 盡左力, 對得住自己!  又要爆氣, (Plan to)搞掂埋chemistry lu~~  
    
    
</post>
<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Feeling exhausted, I've no idea about what to write. And here is one of my favourite song, Emotion.   Emotion by Destiny Childs -------------------------- It's over and done but the heartache lives on inside And who's the one you're clinging to instead of me tonight? And where are you now, now that I need you? Tears on my pillow wherever you go I'll cry me a river that leads to your ocean You never see me fall apart  In the words of a broken heart It's just emotion that's taken me over Tied up in sorrow, lost in my soul But if you don't come back Come home to me, darling You know that there'll be nobody left in this world to hold me tight Nobody left in this world to kiss goodnight Goodnight Goodnight  I'm there at your side, I'm part of all the things you are But you've got a part of someone else You've got to find your shining star And where are you now, now that I need you? Tears on my pillow wherever you go I'll cry me a river that leads to your ocean You never see me fall apart  In the words of a broken heart It's just emotion that's taken me over Tied up in sorrow, lost in my soul But if you don't come back Come home to me, darling You know that there'll be nobody left in this world to hold me tight Nobody left in this world to kiss goodnight Goodnight  And where are you now, now that I need you? Tears on my pillow wherever you go I'll cry me a river that leads to your ocean You never see me fall apart  In the words of a broken heart It's just emotion that's taken me over Tied up in sorrow, lost in my soul But if you don't come back Come home to me, darling You know that there'll be nobody left in this world to hold me tight Nobody left in this world to kiss goodnight Goodnight  In the words of a broken heart It's just emotion that's taken me over Tied up in sorrow, lost in my soul But if you don't come back Come home to me, darling You know that there'll be nobody left in this world to hold me tight Nobody left in this world to kiss goodnight Goodnight (Goodnight)  --------------------- It's time for me to have a good sleep. And tomorrow's exams, just try your best and make it! Believe in yourself!  
    
    
</post>
<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       今日食完飯之後, 個人有d亂, 漫無目的咁走左落街. 一路行, 都唔知想走去邊. 過左一陣, 去左個平時唔會點去既地方. 咁啱又俾我撞到個咸蛋黃.  今日個蛋黃唔算好靚, 不過都攞起部holga執左幾張. (遲d沖完post番)  影完相, 坐低左. 以前既我, 基本上係唔會坐低感受一下個atmosphere. 今日唔同, 可能因為個卷係120菲林, 有12張啦.  坐係個度, 見到好多老人家, 明白到時光一去不返. 慶幸個一刻有部相機, 留住快門釋放, 曝光一刻的景物.  ======================================  幾日, 無論係讀書, 抑或gears方面, 都有d "覺今是而昨非既感覺"  而個一刻, 係夕陽下驀然回首既我, 頓感 "實迷途其未遠, 知來者知可追"  I got the feeling back now!!!    (The sunset by Holga: http://img78.photobucket.com/albums/v290/issactsang/P6300003.jpg) 
    
    
</post>
<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       每個人都有目標. 我亦不是一個例外. F.4 開學既時候, 諗過話要係年尾上台攞獎,  管他是英文或econ. As time goes by, Oh My Goodness! 發覺自己既競爭力越來越低. econ就咪講啦,  英文, 勁人多的是,  Miracle, Jason, Ricky, In, Anthony..... 嘩... 自己, 都係算啦.  But I always believe in myself. Even it's a slight chance, if i can, I will seize it. 凡事最緊要盡力, 對得住自己. 就算真係博唔到, 都無藉口俾自己, 只可以講一句, "咁人地係勁過你嘛!"  I remember an ad's slogan, "Impossible is nothing." 
    
    
</post>
<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       今日去左打保齡, 都唔錯, 88~128 ^^ 最開心係有一round諗住落梗pin,  點知炒番起,  打橫掃番哂, 過癮! ^^  阿ball又勁, 好好玩!  睇日又同sis打lu~ ^3^  
    
    
</post>
<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       今日心血來潮, 睇番以前既野:  - G2G 既舊post  - 3A party 既相  突然, 累透了的我臉上露出一絲微笑.  看著那些舊post, 心中不禁對自己說,  "原來我也這樣的幼稚過."  那時, 也許是在一個陌生地的緣故,  大家的說話可以是毫無保留,  每天回家, 當然是到G2G呢!  一下子, 那兒熱起來了.  那時跟網友的關係也是最好的.  也許沒有CE的牽掛,  大家很盡情地談心.  那時,  ItMan, Losy, LOG, 乂‧藍‧忍‧者‧乂, plk.1.7, lonely person,....   ^^    
    
    
</post>
<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       咁多部相機, 真係用唔哂. 放番部, 最主要係套現啦,  居然賺左10%, surprise! 其次, 防潮箱多番位放野.  今日jason睇slide個樣, 好得意呀! 佢講得無錯, 個種感覺係唔同既...  #$%^*, 功課都無乜點做過... =.=  
    
    
</post>
<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       網上拍賣的確方便, 我也曾經買入幾部相機. 足不出戶, 的確不錯. 偶然也會遇上物超所值的. 但那裡亦有不少人混水摸魚 http://hk.page.auctions.yahoo.com/hk/auction/1106640838?aucview=0x13  那相機, 一部全新的也不過是千多元. $2000即賣, 引人發笑! " 800萬像素輸出(最高) ", 不過是插值罷了. 像素非一齊, 影像質素呢? "產品特點" 也不過是一般功能來的.  奉勸大家, 網上拍賣, 先看清詳情, 再作資料搜集才出價呢. 
    
    
</post>
<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Being totally exhausted, I have stopped postingblogs in these days.   Sorry for disappointing you guys.   I'll be back tomorrow.   I experienced a lot these days, and of course, learnt a lot.   Preview -Shopping spree in Shenzhen @ Jul 24, 2004 ^^   
    
    
</post>
<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       近期, 迷上古玩相機. 的確, 有點對那數碼相機所出來的照片, 要求愈來愈高. 看過不少網友所發表的文章, 也購入了一部不錯的.  真棒! 一卷不到二十元的膠卷, 一百二十元的鏡頭, 加上五百元的機身, 成像的質素足以媲美五千元的數碼相機. 而那轉動光圈環, 對焦環的手感, 遠較數碼相機為佳. 縱使有人可能說,  那已是三十年前的技術, 落伍了. 但我, 就是這樣的落伍, 不入流.  老東西, 總是有老脾氣, 這也不例外. 已經不止一次,  它的測光系統出了毛病. 試過很多方法, 也無法醫治, 我也只好作出最後的嘗試 - 動武.  真的, 只有這才成功. 它, 又能正常地拍照了.  老東西, 老相機, 就是這般可愛.  
    
    
</post>
<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       今日買左本Practical Photography, 英國出既. 都好貴, 成$80, 不過個度本本都好貴, 有邊於內地出版既平靚正, 即使兩者既內容其實都好掂.  翻開雜誌, 掀到廣告頁, 眼前的盡是各式各樣的鏡頭, 菲林. 而價格當然是不可少呢!  細看下, 經過換算,  發現即使所售的是一樣的貨品,  所標的都較本地的售價為高. 比方說, 同一枝鏡頭, 你能以$700於本港購得, 於英國卻需近$1100.  香港, 果真是購物天堂.  
    
    
</post>
<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       今日天氣超正, 最適合游水. 本來同ball ball  Jason 十點去科學館,  點知原來開一點 &gt;. 跟住做左自遊行, 去左一陣藝術館, 再行埋星光大道, 不過天氣太熱了, 但風景確是一絕.  去左游水, 超好玩. Ricky, Bosco, Jason, Tostao, Lok, Alan, Issac  Eric 一行八個人, 好開心, 曬黑左少少. 跳水好玩, 雖然唔識, 仲拉親條頸... 下次都係唔好lu~ Anyway, today is COOL~ 
    
    
</post>
<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       愛上攝影差不多一周年,  在技術進步的同時, 不知不覺也中毒了.  埋單現有既gear: i) Olympus C5050Zoom ii) Holga 120S iii) Yashica Electro 35 GTN iv) Agfa Optima I v) Praktica MTL5 (wasted) vi) Fujica St801 vii) Asahi Pentax Super-takumar 55/2 viii) Helios 44M 58/2 (SC)  嘩! 嚇死自己, 乜完來都咁多啦. 但其實部Yashica同Agfa, even 未試過機.  But 我個wish list(within 3 months): i) Olympus mjuII ii) Zenitar 16/2.8 iii) Lomo Lubitel 166U  算啦, 我得認同我已經中左毒, 但正如今日slayer講,  你再玩slide, 遲d分分鐘上埋大底... 都係影negative啦.  咁又係, 我轉行用film, 都係想提升技術je, 好啦, 等我又用下negative la~ 的確, 感覺又真係唔同喎.  Anyway, 搞點埋個wishlist, 儲錢啦, 其他既, 考完CE先買啦. ^^  
    
    
</post>
<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       我從沒想過事情會發展得這麼快.  阿東, 你好勁!  今日另一件我好高興既事, 係我終於遇到一個, 識得自己學校既人啦. 可能係我自己一向住得遠,  唔知原來自己讀緊個間係區內名校. 今日打電話俾一個網友買鏡頭,  原來佢住係黃大仙, 讀緊IVE. 咁講講下, 我話自己係TWS讀書啦,  跟住話讀保一, 佢就話, "讀書人喎!"  唔好意思, 真係今日先知^^" And, that's it! 
    
    
</post>
<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       It's not the first time that i have such feeling. But it's the first time, you give me. It's comfortabe to chat with you, though sometimes I don't even know what to talk about. Pets, music, I don't know either of them well. And it's always good for us to learn more.  I wanna tell you many things, anything that you wanna know. I staying with you, the feeling is unique.  It feels so good. 
    
    
</post>
<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       從朋友的blog上得到靈感, 就說Wants吧.  我想, 搞番好CIT, 至少睇番個兩本書. 我想, 睇一d關於Game Theory既書. 我想, 讀好Bio  Chemistry. 我想, 做好多好多數. 我想, 學沖黑白菲林. 我想, 充實自己. 我想, 成績好d. 我想, 有fluent既spoken English + written English. 我想, 去旅行, 去Maldives, 去西歐, 去Australia, 去Miami. 我想, fit D. 我想, 攝影技術上一層樓. 我想, 我想...  我想既, 其實可以做到, 可以係呢一個暑假做到, except go travelling. 想, 就要去做. 唔做, 想, 始終都係想罷了.    
    
    
</post>
<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Tonight, there's some problem with the tap in the house. The whole family has no idea about why would this happen, 'coz the taps were replaced last weekend only.  First, mom became nervous, she called the management office,  and of course, a tecnician. From her eyes, and her behaviours, i knew that she panic.  Sis gotta leave home early in the morning the next day, so she wondered whether she could bath or not. My father was calm at the very beginning, but then, as time goes by, he became unpatient as well.  All these did annoy me. I said loudly, "Just calm down," yeah, and it came under control.  In our life,  sometimes, we will panic. But bear in mind that you should calm thyself down. After that, everything's gonna be fine.  Now, the problem is solved, temporarily.   
    
    
</post>
<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       The overcast weather made today a good day for photography. I went to the Hong Kong Park with ERIC LI to pay a visit to the Lotus Exhibition.  When we arrived at there, the professional gears frightened us. THough it's we, who take the photos, not the gear.  The flowers are beautiful. No one can resist their them. I took some shots of them, however, none looks cool.  The one which impressed me the most is the one i took leaving the greenhouse. It was a photo of a waterfall. I can't even imagine how could it be their, the CBD of Hong Kong.  Next time, before I take some shots of Lotus, I should improve my skills. 'coz Lotus is just like a mystery, it's difficult to present its beauty in a photo, but once you can did it, there's nothing that you can't express through the camera.  
    
    
</post>
<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       同你一班都三年啦, 好奇怪, 無乜同你認真的communicate過. 直至尋日... 可惜, 天意弄人乎? 將快要打開話題時, 那可愛的機器給我關了機. 再登入時, 你已不在線上了.  今天, 錯手的進入了standby mode, 又錯失了一個機會, 留下的只是一個offline message.  妳, 原來跟我從前所想的不同哩! 真想跟你盡情的chat一回! 
    
    
</post>
<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       哈! 我一開始會認為自己未必有恆心, 每天寫一段文字. And now I found that i may not have that stamina to do so.  Today after school, after changing my clothes,  I went to 志蓮淨苑 to have some photo shots.  The weather was fine when I left home, but then it started to rain cats and dogs when I got on the MTR. Eventually, it became fine when i arrived at 志蓮淨苑.  I was shocked by what i saw, there were no flowers,  not even one! Perhaps I didn't go there at the right time. Taking a short walk, I decided to leave. Luckily, I found one hiding at the corner.  I taking a few shots of it, the sky started to shout at me. Soon, I returned home.  As I view the picures' enlargments on the computer screen, I realized that I satisfied with one shot only. Anyway, that's enough. I still very happy now as i look at the photo. What i concern is the quality but not the quantity.  Sometimes, satisfy with what you have, you will feel happier.  
    
    
</post>
<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I knew little about him before today. I thought he wouldn't be that nice, but he was.  Sitting for about 7 hours on the chair today, I attended two tutorial classes. Physics  CIT. Both were interesting, and I love the pace. In fact, I'd like to go to school every morning during the holiday, rather than wasting the whole morning, sometimes even afternoon, sitting in front of the TV or the Laptop.  'coz I'm me, and I love to go to school.  
    
    
</post>
<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       累‧Relax‧睇波  一邊做功課, 一邊睇波, 一邊relax, 一邊緊張, 一邊睇書, 一邊聽歌, 一邊食野, 一邊飲野, 一邊睏, 一邊醒.  就是這樣, 一個典型的星期六晚上.  在夜深人靜之時, 獨自在桌上工作, 享受那一霎間的寧靜. 時間彷彿停了下來, 一齊都凝結了, 只餘下我獨個兒在工作.  那一刻, 心, 靜如止水, 那一刻, 心, 得到了釋放.  不知何時開始, 變了夜鷹. 也不知何時開始, 愛上這個角色, 愛上那種寧靜的感覺.  心, 終找到釋放的空間.   
    
    
</post>
<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       今日去太空館睇左兩套全天域電影. "澳洲"  "深海火山" "澳洲"~講述澳洲這一片陸地上的生物如何適應天氣去生存. "深海火山"~於4公里的海底, 海洋生物的傳奇.  兩部全天域的電影, 同一個感覺. 在澳洲內陸的生物, 為求存, 作出層出不窮的應變, 也許不停地轉換環境, 已是牠們生存的一部分. 生活於4公里的海底下的海洋生物, 不斷培植細菌, 以從礦物中得取養份.  人則有各式各樣的藥物, 衣服, 電器.  活著才是最好的!  
    
    
</post>
<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       "Every action has an equal and opposite reaction."  呢一條經常應用於Physics, 但除了Physics外, 其實這也能用於待人接物中. 我們所作出的每一個決定, 譬如對人的態度好了, 我待人好, 別人亦會對我好, 反之亦然. Equal: 態度 Opposite: 方向  ~生活中的物理~  
    
    
</post>
<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       今日燒番3A Party既相俾Miracle, 既然燒開, 就睇番下d相. 發覺原來自己係未試過一張張去睇. 雖然個mon唔係大, 但係呢十二寸既空間內, 看著一張張快樂回憶, 即使自己只在兩, 三張相中出現過, 但那時的情境就像錄像般在腦海中重播. 臉上不自覺地掛著一絲微笑.  就是這樣, 又一年了. 甜的, 酸的, 一下子湧上心頭, 又回想起這一年所發生的. 將來的, 又會是如何的呢?  
    
    
</post>
<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       今日學到一個好重要, 亦應該早知的道理. 一個人online, 唔代表係佢online. Even佢availiable, 亦唔代表係佢.  我就係好搞笑咁, 不斷send massage俾同一個人, 以為佢online緊(當時佢係availiable), 但一個response都無.  結果, 用緊電腦個位user就笑到傻左, 我, 都唔知應該喊定笑好, 因為個user係...  
    
    
</post>
<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        十二點先起身, 
</post>
<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       A month has passed, but i haven't done the homework, nor read any books yet. I regret.  That's the way life goes on: One should be responsible for his own choice, and i paid a price for what i have done.  I will never allow this happen again. I promise.  
    
    
</post>
</Blog>