<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      truly I am a person that does not learn from their mistakes...same problem as the night before, and the night before that, why do I ever care you ask? call it a personal goal...Ill write more tomorrow, w00t, bye
    
</post>
<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Once again Im afraid Ive made the severe mistake of posting too late once Im already tired! and I have to get up early for one of those appointment things, for a college Im probably not even going to go to *sigh* oh well itll be a time killer, tomorrows college day I guess...or somethin, yea sure, why not, makes it sounds like less of a drag, eyes heaaavy, and I just ate food, so now Im wanting to just lay down and drift off, which brings another point, I need to fit God somewhere into this mess as well, which is odd because I should be working other stuff around him technically, not the other way around, hehe oh well, Im workin on it man!!! I tells ya the truth!! woooo Rebekah just asked me if my blogs going to be short tonight, Im gettin kinda freaked now, maybe she really CAN read my mind, what a frightening place, yeesh, I dont even want to read my mind =P buut anyway speaking of which I must be off now, sleep calls, curses curses, just imagine what could be accomplished if people didnt have to sleep, wouldnt that be nice? goodnight everyone!
    
</post>
<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      WOow I think Im dying, so tired, all the time, but especially now, Im only typing this because Im trying to do it once a day...God knows why, heh, not much to say, well alot to say in reality but too tired to say it, oh well I need a short post once in a while to even out my hideously long rambles so my poor friend's eyeballs dont melt out of her skull, Im offffff -- food and sleep, food and sleep, food and sleep, gooodbye!
    
</post>
<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      EDO here, hehe. Actually, the person known as EDO is about to fall asleep right before my eyes! Let's see, today, I sat on the computer for the majority and played Parasite Eve 2. Talked to the most obnoxious girl in the world for, I don't know 10 hours. Made a bet, if it's comes down to a half split, I'll get a trip to Ireland, and she'll get my playstation! I just hope it doesn't become a collectors item later on! Let's see, I don't want to sound arrogant or anything, so I'll just state what my friend thinks of me. "Eric is the most wonderful awesome person I've ever met" I could list more, but I really don't want to make my readers ill, you know.. I have enough stomach problems as it is, with being so hungry all the time. I think, I need to add a photo on my profile.. I have the perfect one too.. bwah, ha haha. I think I'm going to put something in here to decode for everyone who reads it WCREWHITVB? I need to figure out the whole HTML thing so I can add some photos in here, maybe I can use Netscape composer or Jasc? Hmm... Will try later, definitely. Let's see.. Summer SummerSummer, can't wait until College starts. That should be fun- making new friends, learning stuff, out of the house.. away from the killer online.. You know, things to look forward to and such. Had an awesome storm today, heard some of the loudest shots of thunder I've ever encountered, I believe. Stormy weather is really quite wonderful, much better than happy grass and floating fluff. You know, I should try and send sublimable messages to people... ..^^^</post></Blog>