<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    A nice surprise when I got home this past weekend from lake Tahoe. urlLink   
    
</post>
<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This one was the nicest out of five hatchlings. They all were smokin, but this little guy was the prettiest.  
    
</post>
<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Mitch Kupchak.It's obvious that he is in over his head at this point in time. Dr Buss,feel free to call Jerry West up and apoligize to him for running him out of town to Memphis. We need a real GM right now who has the experience. Every passing day brings more and more bad news. D Fish has opted out of his deal now. Let's see, I guess that leaves "the glove" Gary Payton and Deaven George on the team now(even though Shaq is under contract,I'm not counting on him being around anymore because it's obvious he doesn't want to be Laker anymore). Great, that's just a fine nucleus of players,NOT. 
      
</post>
<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This makes all the sense in the world for the Clintons. urlLink Drudge  is quoting an unnamed top Kerry source saying that "all the signs are pointing in that direction". This is a scary development, but one that if true in my opinion will only help solidify support for Bush. Sure Hillary will energize the female vote, etc, but she will energize the GOP base like nothing else could.This is a fascinating development in the campaign. 
      
</post>
<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      As i was going through the news today,I am always struck when I hear democrats,specifically Hillary at a San Francisco fundraiser for Barbara Boxer,say that we need to recind the recent tax cuts for the "common good". Huh???? Excuse me  urlLink Hillary , but the money I earn is my money and not the federal governments money. We are not under taxed in the US. What an amazing story.                      Also we handed sovereignty back to the Iraqis yesterday. That was a great symbolic day for them if nothing else. We all know that security is still going to be a problem for them over there,but it was nice to see that we are keeping our word to them that we are not occupiers,but liberators. Their destiny is in their hands now.                     I have mixed emotions about the Supreme Court's ruling that enemy combatants can now have access to the US Judical system. On one hand everyone deserves to get their due process and day in court if accused of a crime, but the people we have down at GITMO are not US citizens. They are enemy combatants. Are our soldiers now supposed to start reading the Miranda warning to all prisoners of war that we capture? Hard questions. I think the court has just muddied the waters
      
</post>
<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I posted a comment a few days ago about the political futures market being a great predictor of future events and low and behold I found an article by none other than  urlLink Larry Kudlow  of "Kudlow  Kramer" fame and also star economist and member of the Board of directors of the Club for Growth that articulates this alot better than I did. Please take a look at the article from National Review.
      
</post>
<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Oh my how the double standard/hypocracy wheel turns.Get ready everyone for fireworks this week in the John Kerry Campaign. It seems that what's good for the goose is good for the gander.  urlLink Drudge  is reporting that the same media that demanded sealed divorce records from now former Republican Senate candidate Jack Ryan of Illinois,are set to demand full release of John Kerry's very messy 1988 divorce. For those that aren't familiar with the Jack Ryan details,his divorce records say that his wife alledged that he wanted some form of sex in public at certain strip clubs(Bill Clinton eat your heart out!). Your about to see a media feeding frenzy that doesn't happen all that often,but when it does it is a sight to behold. The only question I have is if the media will have the guts to actually follow through with this.What a great start to the week!
      
</post>
<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well,I'm back from an awesome three day weekend in Lake Tahoe.Everything was perfect,except I lost about $100 playing blackjack. I want to give props to the Nelson,Barnett,and Hagemeyer families for putting on a wonderful event.The scenery was beautiful,friends  family great and much more. It looks like we will do this all again in three months when Katie  Jonas say their "I do's" in Napa. I'm looking forward to that one too. For anyone reading this wanting a great wedding reception place,you couldn't do much better than Edgewood Country Club in Tahoe.What a place. I'm out
      
</post>
<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      that show more of a Bush trend.First we had  urlLink Rasmussen  with a 2 point Bush lead,then  urlLink Fox News  with a six point Bush lead,and last we had  urlLink Gallup  showing Bush with a big improvement over their last numbers. If anyone out there has John Kerry's ear,please tell him that his campaign is on life support.
      
</post>
<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        I have a question for all you liberals out there.I'm putting a fund together to help  urlLink Al Gore's  family pay for the insane asylum.How much can you guys pitch in? It's obvious he has lost all touch with reality.They might even just send him to some sort of anger management program to deal with his issues.Between his and Howard Dean's speeches,it's a wonder Kerry is even close right now.John "f..ing" Kerry has got to be cursing at himself right now and trying to figure out how to muzzle these idiots.I say,keep it up Al and Howard.The more America sees these speeches,the faster you'll slip into political oblivion.  
      
</post>
<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      As i'm sitting here at my desk thinking of how we all can best honor Ronald Reagan,I got it.What if everyone took one Saturday a month out their busy schedule and volunteered for the local/county Bush Cheney 2004 team from now until election time to help Bush across the finish line a winner.It is going to take a huge effort to turn out our voters.The RNC has put together what they call the "72 hour task force" to mobilize voters during the last weekend before the Tuesday election.We plan to put together the biggest get out the vote drive that has ever been undertaken by a campaign.Everyone knows that the stakes couldn't be higher in November.Everything from security,taxes,judgeships,etc is on the table.A few votes in a few swing states is going to make all the difference.An added benefit is that working for the campaign is fun.You get to meet all kinds of new people and make new friends with people of like mind.
      
</post>
<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Bad news for democrats, urlLink new U.S. home sales leap to record high . John Kerry et al can't be very happy about all these positive economic indicators lately.I mean according to him we're in the worst economy since the Great Depression.All this good news is just not good for them.They were hoping to campaign on gloom and doom as always.  
      
</post>
<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      As the election gets closer and closer,I am becoming even more optimistic about our chances to pick up some badly needed Senate seats so President Bush can get his judges confirmed.I figure there will be at least two Supreme Court vacancies during the next Presidential term if not three.It is very important to have a Republican Senate to break the democratic filibusters that they have been using. urlLink John Thune  is a great candidate.He barely lost to Tim Johnson in an off year election in 2002.Tom Dascle has seen his best days already.It's time to send him back to home to his real home in Washington D.C,not in South Dakota where he pretends to be conservative the closer the election gets.Any donations for him would be greatly appreciated.   
      
</post>
<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      is a place called  urlLink Refdesk .Take a look at all the links on the page.You literally can "let your fingers do the walking" as they say for any piece of info you need.
      
</post>
<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      As if this guy's head wasn't any bigger.Now word has come out that Benifer has won a World Poker Tour event here in Los Angeles at the Commerce Casino.I don't need to hear about these stories.I really don't care.Dude is an egomaniac.Nice to see that J Lo was really so heartbroken over him that she waited a whole four months to get remarried.
      
</post>
<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yesterday at the polls.This is exactly what the  urlLink Club for Growth  was formed to do.It bundles financial support to pro growth,free market conservatives over RINO candidates.In the case of David Beasley of South Carolina though,it was because of his protectionist views.In the Utah 2nd district race,John Swallow won the right for a rematch against Jim Matheson.John lost a squeaker in 2002 and seems in good position to win this seat back.He should get good coattails from Bush's upcoming winning margin in Utah.
      
</post>
<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well I guess it's time to go on record about my illustrious   urlLink UCLA Bruins  for the upcoming season.After all,I did name my blog after them.I'm afraid this is the season we are going to hit rock bottom.I really would like to believe that the glass is half full,but after reviewing this years recruiting class,player losses,coaching quotient,and a few other factors,one can only come to the conclusion that this season is going to be an absolute train wreck.They probably will be unwatchable.If the gutty little bruins can scrape a victory over USC then I would classify that as a good season for them this year.I'm not getting my hopes up though.  
      
</post>
<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It looks like based on today's latest poll that Jim Demint will defeat former governor David Beasley(R-SC) in today's South Carolina Senate primary.This is indeed good news.Chalk up a win for the good guys.Demint is a strong free market conservative.He will have a great shot at capturing this open seat for the republicans in the fall.
      
</post>
<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Being the commodities/futures broker that I am,I believe that psychology is what drives the markets.When people feel strongly about a market,they wager money or trade on that information.There are now exchanges to take action on political races.One such place is called  urlLink Intrade . Right now based on current betting and trades, urlLink George W Bush  has a 58% of pulling out a victory in November.This of course can change,but right now the so called "smart money" is on Bush.   
      
</post>
<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Once Al Qaeda followed through on their promise to murder their hostage.My thoughts and prayers go out to the victims family of the South Korean gentleman.Kudos to South Korea for not giving in to the terrorists.This is another great reason to keep  urlLink George W Bush  as our commander in chief.We need steady leadership during these hard times.  </post></Blog>