<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          A lot of people believe that an employer’s decision on  hiring a candidate depends on just skills and experience.  Well they couldn’t be farther from the truth because that is  false.    Here is the truth…      Skills and experience within your profession aren’t what  gets candidates the job. The truth is that there are too  many candidates with the proper skills and experience to get  the job, and ONLY one usually gets the job.       Companies are looking for more than skills and  experience these days. So it’s extremely important that you  all your individual characteristics mirror your passion.    So what are the other factors that are usually invisible to  candidates?   **Self-Awareness** – who are you and where are you going?  What are your plans for the present and the future? How do  you know what you want? How do you know that you’re right  for this job? Employers want to make sure that you’re not  lost.   **Learning Skills** – Are you willing to learn? Are you  current on trends and technology? Are you a person who loves  to “grow” within their profession? You want to show an  employer that you’re a candidate that learns in order to  progress your career.    **Adaptability** - With everything changing so rapidly  today, it’s possible that tomorrow your skills may no longer  be relevant. Are you a person who adapts well to change?   **Character** - Do you show passion in your industry,  because when you do, it projects through your résumé, cover  letter, and especially during the interview. An employer  wants a dependable trustworthy employee. The more you  project your positive character, the better!        You can have a huge advantage over your competition by  going one step. Create a career portfolio and within it make  sure that you showcase all the categories above in the  proper manner. I guarantee that this will give you a major  edge over your competition.        So you see that it’s not all about skills and  experience. It’s really important that you consider the  factors above, because them alone can get you the job.     =========================================================== David Green is an author and hiring manager of Distinguish  Marketing, LLC. Want more information on how to receive a  job in 30 days or less? Including free lessons for more  resume, cover letter, and career portfolio tips!   Click Here – http://www.forcareersuccess.com  ===========================================================
    
</post>
<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Emailing may seem simple, but there are some complications that you need to be aware of, otherwise, your email may never be read by an employer.   1.) Your subject line is crucial…   How would you like the employer to be drooling to read your résumé? Of course you would, right? Because that will increase the likelihood that the employer will read you whole cover letter and résumé.   Note: An employer usually takes 10 – 15 seconds to overview a cover letter and read it.   It is to your advantage that they completely absorb your cover letter and résumé. The subject line of to your email can create this urgency, this excitement, and this greed within the emotions of an employer.   To give you proof of what I just said, what motivates you to read most of the articles that you like to read? I bet it’s the headline. Nine times out of ten, if the headline doesn’t interest you, then you won’t read it.   It’s no different with an employer…they are human just like you. We read what we want to read and what we read usually strikes our interest.   Tips on writing a magnetic headline:   ** Write a subject line addressing the company needs, NOT yours.  Ex. I have ___accomplishments to provide value toward ____ position   ** Put the employer’s name in the subject line (notice the cliff hanger as well…)  Ex. Hi Dave, I love your product and I would like to work for…   ** Stir the employer’s emotions by teasing them with value.  Ex. Here is how can increase your sales by 8%  Ex. How would you like a lawyer who has won 98% of the time!  Ex. I am used to communicating with dozens of people who recommend me to other friends.   3.) Houston we have a problem with spam filters   According to Time Magazine, between 40-70% of all email is getting killed (Spam Filtered) BEFORE anyone has a chance to read it? It’s true!   You may think an employer is getting an email but nope it never reaches the email inbox because the spam filters stole it like a thief in the night.   What can you do to make sure your email arrives to an employer?   You have a choice. You can ask if the company uses a spam filter or you can assume that they do. I don’t know the exact statistic for the exact number of companies that use spam filters, but I would make an educated guess that it’s 50% at least.   I would say that your best bet would be to prepare for the spam filter. The spam filters have a point system. Now usually when a email has more than 5 points then your email will ether not make it to the inbox or it will be place in the spam filter folder.   To give you an example on how the point system words: If you have “Free” anywhere in your message and especially in the subject line, you will receive 2 points automatically. There are many words that trigger points, and its way too long and boring to go through all of them. So here is…   A free resource which detects your point system of an email:   lyris.com/contentchecker   3.) How should I send my résumé?   Before I begin writing about how to send your résumé it is critical that you ALWAYS include a cover letter with your résumé. That’s right, even when you send it through email.   You actually have a choice. You can send your résumé and cover letter in the body of the email, or as an attachment.   Beware! Sending your résumé as an attachment could cause it to be scrambled or lose it format structure during its journey. This means that an employer wouldn’t be able to read or have trouble reading your résumé. So how can prevent this from happening?   Send an email to yourself. Go to msn.com and yahoo.com to get a free email account from each. Then send your résumé and cover letter from one to another and see whether your résumé and cover letter are formatted correctly.   Should I send my résumé and cover letter in the body of the email or as an attachment? I recommend that you do both. That way you know the employer will be able to read it, no matter what.   Check with the email content checker above and see whether your email with the attachment has under 5 points. If not, then I recommend that you send two emails to the employer’s inbox. The first has the attachment and cover letter and resume in the body of the email as well. Then send another email with just the cover letter and resume in the body of the email.   ========================================================  David Green is an author and hiring manager of Distinguish  Marketing, LLC. Want more information on how to receive a  job in 30 days or less? Including free lessons for more   urlLink resume writing , cover letter writing, and career portfolio tips!  Click Here – http://www.forcareersuccess.com  ======================================================== 
    
</post>
<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
           There are over 6 Billion people on earth, and to no surprise there aren’t 6 billion jobs to equal the score. As a matter of fact, there aren’t even 1 billion jobs in the world today.   What does this mean for you?       You have plenty of competition in your industry and the numbers aren’t getting any smaller. There is a new person born in your industry every minute. So for you to stay in the elite crowd or join the elite crowd in your industry you have to create what I call a “Distinguished Identity.”   What makes you special in your industry?  What have you done that very few have done in your industry?  What can and what will you provide on a guaranteed basics?        These are all questions that employers want to see within you. The job of the employer is often tough because they have to search to find out what’s within an individual. The employer or recruiter has to search if nothing stands out to be beneficial to the job. Most employers are to mature to go hide and go seek, so don’t hide behind the tree.          The key is to make yourself into a shining bright light like the sun if you will. Make it easy for employers to see your benefits, and they will find it much easier to hire you. What is one way you can separate yourself from the crowd and become the first star to shine bright at night?  Let me tell you a secret…       Did you know that fewer than 15% of people who have a career DON”T have a career portfolio. I willing to bet that in your industry it’s way smaller than 10%. What is a career portfolio?       A well-prepared portfolio that provides "evidence" to an employer of your accomplishments, skills, abilities--it documents the scope and quality of your experience and training in the proper manner.       A career portfolio reveals everything an employer wants to know about you. Remember an employer usually doesn’t hire an individual if there are unanswered questions. So you want to make sure tat every question is answered promptly, vividly and clearly.  ======================================================== David Green is an author and hiring manager of Distinguish  Marketing, LLC. Want more information on how to receive a  job in 30 days or less? Including free lessons for more   urlLink resume , cover letter, and career portfolio tips!   Click Here – http://www.forcareersuccess.com  ======================================================== 
    
</post>
<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      1.) “Proof” shall set you free!      Put yourself in the shoes of an employer or recruiter for a minute. Looking over hundreds of applicants, they always have a problem. Which is a major problem…they have no idea which individual has the best package to deliver.        That’s why there is an interview to choose that one person. Who is the person that gets the job? The individual who show the most “Proof” that they can get the job done.  What shows “Proof” to the highest degree during a job search? Without hesitation it’s a well organized career portfolio.        Employer Moto: You can have the skill and have plenty of experience, but you still have to prove that you’re worthy of the job.    2.) Are you waiting for a Promotion?       A popular question in the job industry is how can I get a promotion or how can I get promoted faster? Here is the simple reply to that question…      Create a Career Portfolio that exemplifies your skills, experience, and most important accomplishments. Let me ask you a question: Why should you get promoted if you can’t at least “show” what you have accomplished?      Your reply to this question may be “they should already know since I’ve been working there for so long.” This is not the case. The bottom line is this… companies don’t record what you have accomplished. They just evaluate whether you’re doing the job or not.       Your accomplishments probably go way beyond what you have done for the company. And guess what…your company or association definitely doesn’t know about that. So always keep a record of everything that can be tied to your profession.   3.) Are you in need of a raise in salary?      Who wouldn’t love to receive a raise? The real question that you need to answer is “Why should you receive a raise in salary? One of the hardest aspects of a career is getting that raise.       The more value you bring to a company or association, the more you get paid. You can have the skills and experience, but that still doesn’t answer the question: Why should I give you a raise?      Here is the solution to getting a raise. You have to prove to the company that you can provide more revenue or value then a normal individual. Just to give you one quick tip on how to distinguish your value from others… create a career portfolio and within that portfolio compare your skills to other people who work in your industry.       That way you eliminate the work for the employer. Now they don’t have to figure out whether you’re worth a raise because you have already showed them proof of why you’re worth more than the average person. Remember, it all starts with providing the company with more revenue or value…that is the key.   ======================================================== David Green is an author and hiring manager of Distinguish  Marketing, LLC. Want more information on how to receive a  job in 30 days or less? Including free lessons for more   urlLink resume help , cover letter help, and career portfolio tips!   Click Here – http://www.forcareersuccess.com  ========================================================
    
</post>
<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
           The person who always gets a good job is relentless and persistent in getting the job. The person who goes an extra mile by doing the unnecessary. It’s the person who goes above and beyond by doing something different or unique.        We have been playing by the same job search methods for years. But I found out a startling pattern with the people who bend these traditional methods.       The traditional methods are creating a resume, cover letter, or filling out a job application. Is there a law that states that you must not go beyond these methods? Of course not, I recommend that you do more by striving for what you want.        I guarantee that you will get noticed just from being unique. Now I’m not saying just do anything to get the employer or company attention. You want to think of create of ways that you can show that value that you will provide or the accomplishments and results that you have accomplished in your track record.   Let me give you a few examples that are rarely used:   ** Spice up your resume or cover letter by including a testimonial.        Have a current or past employer give you a testimonial based on your skills and accomplishments. I’m telling you that this will strike the interest of any one who reads your resume or cover letter.  ** Come in with a plan.       Nothing rocks a company’s or employer’s boat like a person who comes in with a plan that will increase the company or association’s revenue or productivity.        Take a moment and brainstorm some ideas that could improve the value of the company you are applying for. It will be well worth your time and effort.      ** Be included within the top 5% by the follow-up.        Yes, about 95% of job seekers usually don’t follow up. Remember that companies hardly ever hire a person in just a few days. It takes weeks to fill a position.        So guess who the employer will remember the most when the time comes to hire that one individual. It’s that person who has multiple exposures. Always remember that our human mind stores much easier from repetition…so don’t be afraid to follow up.  ** You can really crush the competition with a career portfolio.        Yes, it doesn’t matter what industry you’re part of, you can create a career portfolio even if you haven’t been working for long.        Your portfolio doesn’t have to be about how you perceive yourself. You can use the leverage of others to create the ultimate career portfolio so your career can continue to grow and prosper financially over years to come.   The “proof and evidence” shall set you free!!  ================================================= David Green is an author and hiring manager of Distinguish  Marketing, LLC. Want more information on how to receive a  job in 30 days or less? Including free lessons for more to   urlLink write a resume , cover letter, and career portfolio tips!   Click Here – http://www.forcareersuccess.com  =================================================
    
</post>
<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Making A Resume 
    
</post>
<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Professional Resume 
    
</post>
<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Write A Resume 
    
</post>
<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Resume Service 
    
</post>
<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Resume Form 
    
</post>
<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Resume Writing 
    
</post>
<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink resume help  
    
</post>
<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The person who always gets a good job is relentless and persistent in getting the job. The person who goes an extra mile by doing the unnecessary. It’s the person who goes above and beyond by doing something different or unique.   We have been playing by the same job search methods for years. But I found out a startling pattern with the people who bend these traditional methods.   The traditional methods are creating a resume, cover letter, or filling out a job application. Is there a law that states that you must not go beyond these methods? Of course not, I recommend that you do more by striving for what you want.   I guarantee that you will get noticed just from being unique. Now I’m not saying just do anything to get the employer or company attention. You want to think of create of ways that you can show that value that you will provide or the accomplishments and results that you have accomplished in your track record.   Let me give you a few examples that are rarely used:   ** Spice up your resume or cover letter by including a testimonial.   Have a current or past employer give you a testimonial based on your skills and accomplishments. I’m telling you that this will strike the interest of any one who reads your resume or cover letter.   ** Come in with a plan.   Nothing rocks a company’s or employer’s boat like a person who comes in with a plan that will increase the company or association’s revenue or productivity.   Take a moment and brainstorm some ideas that could improve the value of the company you are applying for. It will be well worth your time and effort.   ** Be included within the top 5% by the follow-up.   Yes, about 95% of job seekers usually don’t follow up. Remember that companies hardly ever hire a person in just a few days. It takes weeks to fill a position.   So guess who the employer will remember the most when the time comes to hire that one individual. It’s that person who has multiple exposures. Always remember that our human mind stores much easier from repetition…so don’t be afraid to follow up.   ** You can really crush the competition with a career portfolio.   Yes, it doesn’t matter what industry you’re part of, you can create a career portfolio even if you haven’t been working for long.   Your portfolio doesn’t have to be about how you perceive yourself. You can use the leverage of others to create the ultimate career portfolio so your career can continue to grow and prosper financially over years to come.   The “proof and evidence” shall set you free!!   ================================================= David Green is an author and hiring manager of Distinguish  Marketing, LLC. Want more information on how to receive a  job in 30 days or less? Including free lessons for more to  write a resume, cover letter, and career portfolio tips!   urlLink * resume writing, resume cover letter, write resume, resume help  Click Here – http://www.forcareersuccess.com  ================================================= 
    
</post>
<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink cover letter 
    
</post>
<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink resume cover letter 
    
</post>
<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink resume 
    
</post>
<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink resume 
    
</post>
<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I think it’s about time that you tap into the mind of employer to explore their needs and wants. After all they are the individuals who hire you. If you give an employer exactly what they need and want, then you will get the job.   Can I share a secret with you that very few people realize?   You can help control a person’s decision by creating emotion. The kinds of emotions that you want to create in an employer are excitement and curiosity.   Primary Emotions (feelings during finding an employee)   • Boredom: Let’s be honest. Reading hundreds of documents about people you don’t know or care about can get very boring, especially when over 90% of résumés are terrible by providing very few benefits if any at all.   • Confusion: Reading hundreds of résumés that aren’t equivalent to the position needing to be filled causes confusion.   • Urgency: Employers need help, and that is why they are hiring. They realize that they have a position to fill as soon as possible, and the longer it takes, the more money or productivity will be lost to the company.   Your objective is to cure these emotions for time that the employer takes to overview you as a candidate. You want to provide an “antidote” with your words. How can you do that…   Now that you know an employer’s habits, emotions, and desires, so now you play the right cards. The best way to change someone’s habits is to interrupt their pattern. How can we interrupt an employer’s pattern?   “Interrupt their present limiting pattern of association to create new results.”  Tony Robbins   You can interrupt an employer’s pattern by giving them what they want. Instead of boring an employer, make them curious. Instead of allowing employer confusion, provide them with clarity. Recognize their urgency and provide them with excitement by providing a solution.   When doing this correctly the reader will love you and reward you!   =================================================David Green is an author and hiring manager of Distinguish  Marketing, LLC. Want more information on how to receive a  job in 30 days or less? Including free lessons for more   urlLink Resume Help - For Career Success , cover letter help, and career portfolio help!  Click Here – http://www.forcareersuccess.com  ================================================= 
    
</post>
<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink resume help  
    
</post>
<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      How Reading Employers’ Chromosomes Will Get You Riches I think it’s about time that you tap into the mind of employer to explore their needs and wants. After all they are the individuals who hire you. If you give an employer exactly what they need and want, then you will get the job.  Can I share a secret with you that very few people realize?  You can help control a person’s decision by creating emotion. The kinds of emotions that you want to create in an employer are excitement and curiosity.  Primary Emotions (feelings during finding an employee)  • Boredom: Let’s be honest. Reading hundreds of documents about people you don’t know or care about can get very boring, especially when over 90% of résumés are terrible by providing very few benefits if any at all.  • Confusion: Reading hundreds of résumés that aren’t equivalent to the position needing to be filled causes confusion.  • Urgency: Employers need help, and that is why they are hiring. They realize that they have a position to fill as soon as possible, and the longer it takes, the more money or productivity will be lost to the company.  Your objective is to cure these emotions for time that the employer takes to overview you as a candidate. You want to provide an “antidote” with your words. How can you do that…  Now that you know an employer’s habits, emotions, and desires, so now you play the right cards. The best way to change someone’s habits is to interrupt their pattern. How can we interrupt an employer’s pattern?  “Interrupt their present limiting pattern of association to create new results.” Tony Robbins  You can interrupt an employer’s pattern by giving them what they want. Instead of boring an employer, make them curious. Instead of allowing employer confusion, provide them with clarity. Recognize their urgency and provide them with excitement by providing a solution.  When doing this correctly the reader will love you and reward you!  ================================================= David Green is an author and hiring manager of Distinguish Marketing, LLC. Want more information on how to receive a job in 30 days or less? Including free lessons for more  urlLink resume tips , cover letter tips, and career portfolio tips! Click Here – http://www.forcareersuccess.com =================================================
    
</post>
<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink  real estate course   
    
</post>
</Blog>