<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink     Metal detectors; they are freakin' everywhere. Metal detectors have to be, quite possibly, the stupidest security measure in existence today. Do you know when metal detectors were useful? The day they came out. Do you know when metal detectors became useless? The day after that.    Do the security folks seriously think that the only materials that can be used to make weapons are metals? What is even stupider is that not even all metals set the thing off….I’ll be damned if I know which ones do and which ones don’t, but if I was a bad guy, I would probably find out.   The point of all this is not to expose the metal detector as a useless piece of junk (which it pretty much is), but rather to expose a fundamental principle of the “War on Terror” or more generally the “War on preventing someone from doing something really mean if they really want to do it bad enough.” Just as viruses, other infectious agents, and other illnesses manage to keep finding a way to make us sick despite our best medical attempts to stop them, terrorists, assholes, and crazies will always find a way to do mean things. They will dodge the metal detector as HIV dodges Retrovir(R); they will hide in the shadows of our country as a tumor hides in the shadow of an MRI.    All of this may sound a bit defeatist. I am not saying that we cannot stop terror attacks any more than I would ever say that we could not find a cure for HIV. They will build up our country’s immune system by repeatedly testing our defenses. If we are lucky, 9/11 was the vaccine that will cure the disease; hopefully, we will not need a booster shot. urlLink    
     

    
</post>
<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Standing outside their trailor at Paradise Acres, the members of Whitesnake think, "Maybe we shouldn't have gone again on our own...damn." urlLink   
     

    
</post>
<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink     This week's  Weekly Brock  will focus ona good friend and ex-roommate of mine, Tim M.--known betterto the world as Timmy Romance. As I did with Brock,I did a modicum of research to dig up fun things from Timmy's history...I found some stuff...but I will first do the comparison that has becomethe hallmark of the  Weekly Brock ; the comparison in which I point outthe subject's strong points and my comparitiveweaknesses.   Let me first say that I have an outstanding credit rating; there is one simple reason for this fact, Timmy; were it not for Mr. Romance who handled finances (and not begrudgingly)for the entire apartment throughout my undergraduate career, I wouldcertainly behiding from creditors and cable men inMexico. I can also say that I have been pressing my luck with creditors ever since Tim and I graduated and I had to 'learn to write checks' and 'havebank accounts' and 'pay bills.' I have learnedabout such entertaining things as 'bouncing checks' and rememberingPIN numbers' and 'making deposits'. So the first tally is:  Timmy: Good with money. Ted: Sucks with money.   I also learned a lot about women fromTim. He has an exceptional ability to 'not give a crap' or 'not put up with whiny chicks'. (It is important to note that Tim's ability to do this is nowhere near Brock's ability to do so, which borders on pathological--Brock once dated a girl for like nine months and then just stopped calling her. Why? Quote: 'I dunno, she wasn't that cool.') So consequently, Timmy is better at sustaining relationships that I. For example, our next tally:  Number of failed engagements:  Timmy: 0 Ted:1   The final comparison I will make is in overall coolness. This topic was subject for debate when Tim, Christian, and I lived at Ghettoridge 3C. The easiest way to identify who was cooler was to look at our music collections. Tim's collection included: Monsters of Rock Vols. 1-10, Monster Ballads Vols. 1-10, Ozzie Osbourne Live and Loud, GNR, Whitesnake (pictured above), and various other hardcore bands. Timmy could oft be cajoled into performing an intoxicated and shirtless version of 'Here I go Again'...a 3C favorite. My collection, however, included Sarah McLachlan, Jewel, Hanson, and various other non-hardcore artists...and as everyone knows thanks to Jack Black,'you're not hardcore (no you're not hardcore), unless you live hardcore (unless you live hardcore)'. So our final tally:  Do you livehardcore?  Timmy: Yes Ted: No  Do you need more proof of Tim's hardcore status? That is where my research comes in. The underlying links prove two things: 1) Timmy was on the Honor Roll in College; and 2) Timmy got busted for public intox. Work hard, Play Hard...the Mantraof Timmy Romance!  1)  urlLink http://news.siu.edu/news/June00/060800p0093.html  2)  urlLink http://www.dailyegyptian.com/Summer00/07-14-00/blotter.html   urlLink    
     

    
</post>
<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
          So I just bought an IPod...Why? Not Sure. For about a year's salary in many regions of the world,I purchased a digital music player capable of playing songs from 1) my CD collection, 2) songs purchased from download sites, and 3) songs "borrowed" from the fine users of internet file-sharing sites. Also, lest I be caught at some point in my life without immediate access to the 1994Live-at-Soldier Field version of 'Black Muddy River' by the Grateful Dead, I opted for the 40Gb(10,000 song version) as opposed to the measely 20Gb(5,000) song version. Thus I have joined the elite ranks of the 3 million other IPod users.    Why am I such a slave to the consumer culture? Is this IPod really something I need? Apparently so. Is it that I need 10,000 songs at my fingertips, or do I need theIPod status symbol that says, 'Hey, look at me, I have enough flexible income to buy something clearly excessive both in price and functionality?'Maybe I am just doing my part to 'keep the economy rolling.' No, thats not it. To put it in perspective, lets see what else I could have done with my $389.94 (aftergovernment discount and tax):   1) Purchased approximately 30 cases of beer and provided an excellent party for my friends who mean more to me than anything (even music).   2) Supported102 starvingchildren for 1 month each ($0.23 per day) throughthe Feed the Children Foundation.   3) Purchased 1/3000th of a$1.2 million 'smart-bomb' used to 'defeat the evil-doers' and'destroy haters of freedom'...and everyone knows, ILOVE freedom.   4) Donated the money to the presidential campaign of my choice...or similarly, just thrown it in the trash...this election is particularlydifficult for me--I have problems with Bush (for obvious reasons),but I also have problemswith the Kerry/Edwards ticket (as Edwards is a former malpractice lawyer).     As it stands, I amambivalent about the purchase. Perhaps, I can make myself feel better by saying, 'Although I chose to spend my money on the IPod, everyone else should take the money they would have spent on the IPod and use it instead for one of the above four options.'Ah, hippocracy, always a friend of guilt. But, I really, really love music. Ah, rationalization, another of guilt's allies. Damned moral compass. urlLink      
     

    
</post>
<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink      Beer has so many uses. And that is fine because beer is not a life-force--you may use it and abuse it without any regard for its well being. Save excessive and blatant spilling, there is no alcohol abuse. Sweet little puppies, on the otherhand, arealive and have a moral worth; therefore, if we apply Kantian ethics, sweet little puppies should not  be used simply as a means to an end. Unfortunately, even today, in our 'civilized' society, people are everyday trampling the moral rights of sweet little puppies. A travesty.     So who are these wretched soulswhotake advantage of sweet little puppies?  I will tell you--people who use sweet little puppies to pick upwomen. An Abomination. Lets run through the typical day in the life of a sweet littlepuppy abuser (we'll call him D'Artagnan):   D'Artagnan wakes upandrolls out of the bed of anunknown woman hepicked up at the park on the previous day. He tosses his sleeveless shirt on, grabs the woman's spare change, and proceeds out the door... Oh Crap!... he forgot that  damn puppy. He walks back into the woman's apartment and grabs his puppy (which is cleverly named after a mixed drink) out of the closet he tossed him in last night (without food and toilet)when he got to the apartment.  Come on you stupid mutt. Afterzipping Martini up in his backback, D'Artagnanbriskly jogs home.    D'Artagnan decides that it is time for Martini's daily flogging so he ties Martini up and beats him up a little. Now that the sweet little puppy is tooexhausted from the beating to lash out against hiswicked owner, it is time for D'Artagnan to take Martini to the park. So, after D'Artagnan shaves hischest, trims his sideburns into perfect Z's, and dons his sleeveless t-shirt with a clever phrase on it, man and man's best friend proceed to the park.    'You ready to pick me up some chicks little fella?' Obviously Martini was ready because he neverreceived food unless D'Artagnan scored. So man and sweet little puppy strolled around the park trying the various poses in front of girls:  1) The 'Down on the knees playing in the grass' is a favorite because it conveys a sense of vulnerability on the part of the puppy owner.  2) The 'Teaching the little guy a new trick' is also an effective manuever as it is impossible to not laugh at the failed attempts (doing even more damage to thepuppy's fragile ego).  3) The 'Isn't that funny, the little guys got a red rocket' is second to none because it is not only funny, but it alsoestablishes the penis as an appropriateconversation piece.    Regardless of what move he uses (there are countless others), some girl, not recognizing the scheme, will inevitably fall into the trap; she will end up letting D'Artagnan get away with much more than he deserves because he will use the line, 'you don't want to disappoint the puppy, do you?'   The bottom line is that this has got to stop.Animals are not here simply to allow us to pick up women; everyoneknows that animals are here to entertain us by learning stupid tricks such as roll-over and crap in the toilet clearly not designed for you, as well as serving as the 'guest of honor' at every BBQ...mmm, beef!   Here is the link to PETA (People for the Ethical Treatment of Animals):  urlLink http://www.peta.org/index.asp   And their rival PETA (People Eating Tasty Animals):  urlLink http://mtd.com/tasty/  urlLink      
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       My good friend Brock pointed something out to me. He queried, 'Why do you spend all this time making a website to glorify yourself?' You know what Brock, you are right. From this point forward, I will make a post each week that highlights the coolness of one of my friends or family members...and when I run out of them, I will start highlighting acquaintances and public or not so public figures. At the same time, I will compare myself to these people, and in doing so, will tear myself down. In honor of Brock's courage for pointing out the error of my ways (knowing full-well I could beat the crap out of him next time I am in Chicago), he will be the first subject and subsequent posts about friends will be called the  Weekly Brock . So lets get to it.    Brock L.: The man, the myth, the legend.     First let me tell you a bit about Brock's physical characteristics. The man is 6'4", 220lbs, and built like a brick sh*thouse. Despite his size, he has the grace of a butterfly in a cool spring breeze. He is quite dashing with his blond hair and blue eyes--he looks like your typical All-American Johnny Football Hero--and that brings us to our next discussion.    Brock is a legendary football player (and that's le football American for you soccer fans). Brock's strong right arm and comfort with having hishand on the center's ass led the Carterville Lions to aIllinois StateFootball Title in 1996. Let us take a look at Brock'sstats, and by comparing them to mine, get a sense for why I am always humbled in his presence. Shall we:   Passing Att. Comp. Int. Yds. TD  Brock L.  150 717 1,357 20   Anything  Ted C. 0000,000 0   It is clear who the better man is.    But football is not all there is to this man...oh no, no, no...Brock is also wise. Let us explore, again comparatively, some statistics.   1) Number of timesone of us kissed a girl,and then welater realized it was a really, reallybad idea:   Ted: 9  Brock: 0   2) Number of years served as a University Mascot:   Ted: 3  Brock: 0   3) Number of dollars earned to date:   Ted:-$100,000  Brock: $657,432.34   4) Number of times singing Spanish karaoke (without speaking Spanish):   Ted: 1  Brock: 0    It is clear from these stats that Brock uses his immense wisdom to make rational, logical choices; whereas, I do not always do so. I would like to note that, if elected, I would hire Brock as a senior advisor to help me make logical, rational decisions. The funny thing about all this is if I do run for office in 2020-something, an aged, decrepit Bill O'Reilly will be reading my Blogs from 2004 and be using words like 'travesty', 'abomination', and (my personal favorite) 'idiot'.  Now for some links:   1) This is a newspaper article from Brock's University, which features the quote, 'Sophomore quarterback Brock L. has been the only quarterback in camp, and [Coach] Quarlessdid not look forward to having that situation.'  urlLink http://www.dailyegyptian.com/Spring98/041598/spt-drills.html   2) More on Brock's high school career:  urlLink http://www.ihsa.org/activity/fb/1996-97/3info3.htm   3)More on Bill O'Reilly:  urlLink http://www.billoreilly.com/     
     

    
</post>
<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    I mean, honestly, which plane is cooler?? urlLink   
     

    
</post>
<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Museums: Boys, Girls, and the Wooly Mammoth     One of the major advantages of DC is the presence of museums and historical sites—most of which are free.One should definitely take advantage of the museums. There are five thingsone will notice in the museums: 1) people would rather look at the diamonds and jewels than the cultural artifacts; 2) people would rather look at planes with guns on them than without; 3) everyone loves space (and anything related to space…even that God awful space ice cream); 4) boys like to take girls to the museum both because it is free and to flex their “knowledge” about thestuff in the museum; 5) there is no reason the Wooly Mammoth should be extinct. I am sure each of these five observations could be expanded into a 200+ page social commentary, but due to laziness, I will only expand on one…for now.     Watching couples in the Museum:    Youwill hear some pretty funny stuff if you walk around and eavesdrop on different people in the museum. Among my favorite people to eavesdrop on are couples. Regardless of whether they are MM, MF, FF, MFF, or MG [1] , one member of the couple or triple (usually the male and never the goat) is trying desperately to impress the other with their knowledge of the museum exhibits. Most of this knowledge is pieced together from scattered educational experiences from decades ago that have been clouded with malted hops and bong resin (thank you Tommy Boy); however, surprisingly, many of the tidbits of information these ill-equipped teachers spit out are almost right…some, however, are just completely made up. Some examples:    Example 1:  M: “See that baby, that is the Bell X-5; that plane, piloted by Tom Yeager, was the first plane to break the sound barrier. [2] ”  F: “Wow! That’s impressive! How do you know that?”    Example 2:  M: “The current leading hypothesis is that the dinosaurs actually became extinct because of a fad diet. [3] ”  F: “Wow! You know, that actually makes sense!”    Example 3:  M: “You know, I do not think it would be bad for us to mate because we both evolved from the same species. [4] ”  G: “Bahhhhh”     So what is the result for the recipients of the false information? The recipients either: 1) integrate the information, and become stupider; or 2) ignore the information, and remain neutral. What would the result be if the teacher had not taught at all and just grabbed the recipient’s ass throughout the museum? The recipient would remain neutral. The message is clear: Um…oh yeah…Don’t tell people things that are not true; they will either be worse of or no better than if you had simply grabbed their ass…I declare July 25, 2004 National Shut Your Mouth and Grab a Butt Day…somewhere this train derailed…my apologies. Oh yeah, if you would like to order space ice-cream or other similar atrocities,click thelink:  urlLink http://nasastore.jsc.nasa.gov/bigpicts/icecream.html        [1]  M=male; F=female; G=goat    [2]  Real Fact: The Bell X-1 was piloted by Chuck Yeager and was the first plane to break the sound barrier.    [3]  Real Fact: That statement is actually complete bullsh*t; however, it does make sense.    [4]  Real Fact: I have no idea.     
     

    
</post>
<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink     So I think I found the last can of TAB on earth; I found the old boyin a back alley convenience store in New York. The can was dated 1993--probably the year thefinal saccharin report came out. The dangers of saccharin have yet to be proven. It tasted like crap--the fact that it may cause cancer just adds insult to injury. To purchase vintage TAB or other sodas that were virtually discontinued(for good reason) contact:  urlLink http://www.sodaking.com  urlLink       
     

    
</post>
<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink     The SIU Salukis Are Always an Exciting Team to Watch!! SouthernIllinois University at Carbondale provides some of the most entertaining sports teams in the country. SIU is Division I in basketball and Division IAA in football. In this day of all the exciting athletes leaving the'Major'athletic schools before their sophmore year, Mid-majors such as SIU have had theopportunity to thrive.   In basketball,SIU is on its third straight NCAA tourney birth, as well as a sweet-sixteen run three years ago. The team is dynamic, hard-working, and an absolute joy to watch.   In football, the team is ranked #1 in the preseason Division IAA poles. The team has picked up some big-time running backs and returns a solid core from last years 10-2 team.    Why is it so fun to watch the Dawgs? 1) They are always given a somewhat underdawg status; and 2) theyjust play with so much passion. The coaching and team mentalities lead the players to give everything on every play...it is truly exciting to watch.   Check it out:  urlLink http://siusalukis.collegesports.com/     urlLink      
     

    
</post>
<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink     If anyone has a spare one of these guitars (Paul Reed Smith Brazilian Custom 22 Limited), may I have it please. Or if anyone is feeling generous/stupid, you can purchase it for me at  urlLink http://www.wildwoodguitars.com/electrics/prs/brazilian_ltd_home.html . urlLink      
     

    
</post>
<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My current favorite band is the Counting Crows. I am going to see them tonight at the Merriweather Pavillion in Maryland. So the question becomes then, why are they my favorite band?  The lyrics.  Something about the liberal use of metaphors (and sometimes just plain nonsense, it seems...at least to me) allowsone to hear their music in many different ways. One person's heartbreaker is another person's love song; one person's get-fired-up song is another person's chill out song.One example:   When I here the song  Round Here , and Adam strains the words, '...round here, she's always on my mind,' I have an instant flash of every girl I've ever lost to stupid pride, fear, or just geographical and timing differences. It is always a pleasant reflection. For some, it is not pleasent; for others, it elicits no response at all.   Ok, hopefully, my minor emotional jog did not bore my massive readership. I will try to keep the blogs more fun.  I would encourage anyone to read Counting Crows Lyrics:  urlLink http://www.countingcrows.com/      
     

    
</post>
<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    So, apparently, we rocked so hard that we melted the lens of the camera because all the photos came out like this. Dave is sittin' in the corner there, and there are about 20,000 screaming fans (rough estimate) in front of us.This concert rocked; for the first time in over a year, I was reminded of my days back in the band 'Flinging Foreskin' featuring master guitarist KetanAmin. Speaking of master guitarists, we are trying to get a gig opening for Esteban on his 3:30 am infomercial. And yes, the guitar has a'Solid Spruce Top'. urlLink    
     

    
</post>
<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Figure 1: The Food Guide Pyramid. Who is right? Scientific Reasearch or a dead doctor? urlLink    
     

    
</post>
<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       I currently work in the Department of Health and Human Services; therefore, I am conflicted everyday when I have to decide between the stairs and the elevator. Lets see, do I take the stairs and attempt to improve my cardiovascular health to the potential detriment of my knee and hip joint health, or do I opt for the elevator and decrease my chances of developing osteoarthritis. Of course, none of this would be a problem if I could swim up to my office on the fourth floor, or maybe even take a mobile version of that Gazelle(R) thing that guy with the pony-tail hawks at three a.m. on virtually every station. Honestly, if I am watching television at three a.m. (which I do), I have larger (pun) problems than a small penis (not sure), the need to exercise (pretty good at that), or really tough stains (like blood—okay maybe that is a problem) (Plead the fizith).   The most difficult time I have, however, is with the cafeteria. I did mention that I am with the Department of Health and Human Services, right? A quick review, this is the department (the largest in the Federal government) that produced the wonderful thing we know as the food pyramid (figure one), as well as serving as the home to the USDA and the FDA.   [Side note: confidential sources say that the other two major contenders for the symbol that would be used to help millions of Americans to remember the very difficult concept of six food groups (ah hah, and the number of servings) were (1) the food pie; and (2) the food lion. There were obvious difficulties associated with both. First, the food pie, although visually pleasing, led to some confusion among test groups who began eating nothing but pie (Side note of a side note: the pie diet turned out to be a front-runner when Dr. Atkins was trying to decide which asinine diet plan he would use to make our morbidly obese nation even more unhealthy). The food lion was an early favorite, but PETPA (People for the Ethical Treatment of Pictures of Animals) quickly stepped in and shot that idea down much like the black rhino hunter shoots down the beautiful black rhino.]   Let us turn back to the cafeteria. It is clear that the cafeteria is NOT based on the food pyramid; unless, of course, you turn the pyramid upside down, replace the fruits and vegetable group with an overripe fruit and creamed vegetable group, insert a deep-fried whatever-the-hell group, and finally, add the vending machine group. Sure, I suppose I could get the salad everyday; but daily wilted lettuce with a sliced up egg and low-fat ranch will eventually weigh on souls of even the most health conscious. Being that it is this difficult to get a healthy meal in the Department of Health and Human Services, it is certainly no mystery why we had the first American Yokozuna[1] a couple of years ago.  With regard to obesity, I will not bore you with the statistics; suffice to say that they are alarming at the least. There are two thought processes in the American mind that need to be addressed, lest we end up disappearing like the dinosaurs.   [Side note: Most scientists believe that the dinosaurs became extinct due to starvation, an ice-age, or some asteroid strike; however, no one (to my limited knowledge) has proposed the perfectly reasonable hypothesis that the dinosaurs ate themselves to death. For example, perhaps T-rex made a habit of eating the high-fat brachiosaurus, as opposed to the high-fiber pterydactyl. Next thing you know, T-Rex is turning 23 and on his third heart attack. Hell, maybe all the dinosaurs went crazy on some Atkins-esque diet and just dropped dead (although considerably slimmer at the time).]   The first concept that we must break away from is the concept of “getting your money’s worth.” I was raised this way, as were most other (99%) of Americans to which money was an object. Let’s do an example: Joe P. Average is faced with a decision. He can either: 1) buy two Cheeseburgers, large fries, and a 188 oz drink for $3.29, or 2) buy a package of all-natural, earthy, whole-grain crackers for $3.29. Joe knows two things about the McD’s(R) meal: 1) it will make him full for several hours, and 2) it tastes pretty good. Joe also knows two thing about the crackers: 1) they will keep him full for 30 minutes, at which point Joe will have to spend more money, and 2) they taste like sh*t (edited so my mother can read it). Joe may also be distantly familiar with the fact that consistently eating McDonald’s(R) will harm his long-term health. With all his knowledge, Joe proceeds to conduct an internal cost-benefit analysis. Those of you that are familiar with the concept of “present value[2]” will understand why Joe chooses to eat at McDonald’s(R).  The long-term costs of unhealthy eating (knocking 10-15 years off his life, thousands of dollars in personal medical expenses, billions in Federal health care expenditures) do not cast a significant weight on Joe’s decision….damnit Joe, wake up. After everything is calculated (even the utility Joe loses from eating the crap-tasting rice crackers), the crackers actually are the best value. Choose the crackers Joe, and “Get your money’s worth.”   Unfortunately, it is very difficult to convert a nation of people who are (for the most part) obsessed with “getting their money’s worth” in the present tense to a nation of people who are dedicated to “getting their money’s worth” in the long-run. Can you imagine someone going to Golden Corral(R) and having a nice salad….sure, maybe, but the salad is usually immediately followed by 3 steaks, a plate of wings, a slice of pizza, mashed taters, and a bowl of ice cream with strawberries, chocolate, and sprinkles. After all, you could not possibly let the owners of the Golden Corrall(R) make a dime off of you;  screw them , you work hard for your money, and you will get your money’s worth. And lets not even get started on Chinese Buffet; many believe it is their patriotic duty to put those  sons-of-bitches  out of business by eating 23 plates of crap. We must change the way we think.   We also need to discard the idea that anything other than eating less calories and burning more calories will lead to healthy, sustained weight loss. As much as I hate that guy with the pony-tail, he is right—get your ass on the Gazelle(R) for a least 30 min a day. As much as I hate Whole Foods(R), eating some of that crap is necessary.    FACT: People hate working out…well, the average American hates working out. Some actually enjoy it and/or obsess about it (obsessing is not healthy in a different way....it makes people hate you).   FACT: People hate eating healthy…well, the average American hates eating healthy. Some actually enjoy it…no, that’s complete crap, no one  really enjoys eating healthy (even if they think they do); it goes against human nature.    Think about it, five to six million years ago the first bipedal hominid (apparently our ancestors… so say the smart folks ) stood up on his back feet and thought… I’m hungry …what did he find? Twigs and berries. Meat, milk, and chocolate were very tough to come by. Finally, in the last 100 years, the US has moved toward providing a ridiculous amount of food to the majority of the population. Do you honestly think that 100 years of food-a-plenty is enough to reverse 5 million years of natural selection toward those bipedal hominids that consume as much food as they can get their hands on. What do you think  homo erectus  would do at Golden Corral(R)? You can be damn sure that crazy SOB would get his money’s worth, and then probably ask for the extra animal skins to wear home.  So what do you think is going to happen when Whole Foods(R) dangles the twig and berries while McDonald’s(R) flops down meaty, juicy beef?  We homo sapiens will be compelled by millions of years of habit to go for the beef or butter or cheese or deep-fried anything or (heaven forbid) an entire loaf of bread.  As if all this is not enough, a fat person walking into Whole Foods(R) has to put up with psychological pressure somewhere on the level of what I (Illinois country boy) would experience walking down the streets of Baghdad, wearing my Toby Keith t-shirt, and singing God Bless the USA. (We’ll talk about Toby Keith later).   This is the point at which we must separate ourselves from the animals. It was not until Orwell’s animals became cognizant of their situation that they chose to break from the power of instinct (not that I think obesity has anything to do with socialism) and improve their lives. A dog (or any other animal), when presented with limitless food, will eat until it is obese and unhealthy; actually, I think I have heard stories of dogs eating themselves to death. It does not do this because it enjoys eating (have you ever tasted dog food?). It does this because of instinct. The dog does not think:  will this make my ass fat?  (consequently there are no eating disorders among animals); or  will this raise my cholesterol?  A dog just eats.   We must exercise our sense of reason…yeah, I said it, personal responsibility. Some people literally sh*t themselves when they are told that a person is responsible for any aspect of their condition; they sh*t themselves and then they blame it on someone else. Of course all this eating would not be a problem if we would get off our butts and move a bit. Please note that I realize certain people have a genetic predisposition to be a particular weight, and that weight may not correspond with the expected “norm” of our skinny-crazy culture. I do not think everyone can or should look like skin-and-bones “super models” that love to take their shirts off and show off their sexy pancreas'; I do, however, think that everyone (save those with metabolic/ psychological disorders) can sustain a healthy weight.   ([1] A Sumo wrestling grand champion. Also, the reference is for comedic purposes; Sumo wrestlers are actually in good health. Please do not kick my ass.)  ([2]The concept of Present Value basically means that Joe does not give a sh*t about the future (or at least, less of a sh*t)).   
     

    
</post>
<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink     This is Secretary Thompson and I after our long, in-depth conversion involving such importantthings as what my name is. The red thing in my hand is my red blanket...I had just finished bull fighting. urlLink      
     

    
</post>
<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So I suppose if I am to get elected in 2020-something, I should start to put together some kind of platform. Let's start with the environment. Has anyone ever driven an ethanol powered car?? I have. I drove it all though college (I lived in the Midwest). 90% EtOH/10% Petro. The car ran quite well. There was one drawback, however--everytime I filled it up right before work they thought I was drunk because I smelled like a damn brewery. Small price to pay to reduce our dependence on both foreign and domestic fuel. I mean, granted, the ideal situation would be cars that run on water and crap like that, but the techonology for EtOH cars exists NOW. Imagine the midwest turning into the mideast (in terms of wealth resources, not in terms of violence and anti-american sentiment....silly). Hell, right now we throw corn away....it could easily be fermented and distilled to produce a fuel that is cleaner, renewable, and a good transition from fossil fuels to newer fuel sources.That is the only environmental statement I want to make right now. I dont want to talk about forests and wetlands....I dont think I know enough about it, yet.   
     

    
</post>
<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    If we dont do something about the environment, this Wooly Mammoth could become un-extinct....not good. urlLink   
     

    
</post>
</Blog>