<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Woah!   Well, I'm back from a long absence. I have been doing alot of things the past week or so. One of those things was working on my new Website!   It isn't much yet, but it will be soon! It's called  Levile's Lair .   You should visit it and check out some of the links I put up. Anyway, I'm gonna go now.     Fare-Thee-Well  
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       This is my first Web Log Post. I guess I should introduce myself. You can all refer to me as Levile. I'm fifteen years old. The rest of my information is in my Profile.       Anyway, today I did a few things. For one I joined the Cowboy Bebop forums:  urlLink http://bebopforums.proboards19.com  Also, I downloaded a new MP3. The song is titled "Green Bird." It's from Ballad of the Fallen Angels (Cowboy Bebop Session Five.) The song is hauntingly beautiful. A young lady by the name of Gabriella Robin sings the lyrics in a language that I'm not sure of. However, even though I can't understand the words, the song is still great. It makes you remember things from your past. Old friends, places, events, etc.       I should tell you all that I've been depressed for quite some time. Three years ago, I moved to Upland, Indiana and met a kid named Skai Haley. Me and him became very good friends. He was my only friend at the time. My family has always been moving around the state of Indiana. Despite this fact, I kept in touch with Skai. But now, I've moved too far away to contact him. I haven't a clue about his e-mail, and I forgot his address and phone number. The county I'm living in doesn't have the right phone book, so I can't look him up. I haven't seen him for two years.       Well, now that I've told all of you that, I guess I should stop whining and wrap up this post. However, to whomever reads this, if you know Skai Haley, tell him his fellow Otaku says hi. He'll remember me, I know it.       Bye for now. I'll be sure to keep posting, though.        Fare-Thee-Well  
     

    
</post>
</Blog>