<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Trapped in the mysterious fire column, Tai Wu sweated profusely, gradually to the state that he was not able to think properly and eventually fainting.  After what seemed to be eternity, Tai Wu woke up…only to see himself on a barren and scorched field with ashes, slightly burning bushes and plantation. In his hands was the heavy sword “Flamer”; it’s heavy, much heavier than any other sword that he had ever held before. The cracked sword which he used previously was now broken.  A lot of doubts and questions are in Tai Wu’s mind now; where is he, what happened to him after the fire, why didn’t the fire kill him, why is the whole placed burned…  Tai Wu tried standing up, but the weight of Flamer made him unable to nudge.  Tai Wu, “What the…How can anyone use such a heavy sword?”  The sword was not emitting the orange glow anymore, its body a beautiful, clear and clean sliver, but it didn’t seem at all sharp, more rather like a sliver stick. Tai Wu summoned all his strength to the arms, with both hands lifted the sword and used his shoulders to support it.  Tai Wu, “Huh…? There’s no sheath for it…”  With that, Tai Wu tore off part of his sleeve and wrapped it around the blade; at least it looked less significant.  He walked around the area and realized that the fire has an enormous range, walking for few miles; signs of burns could still be seen. Tai Wu started to get worried, there was not any life in sight and the whole area is totally unfamiliar to him.  Tai Wu, “Where…where am I? This place doesn’t seem anywhere near to my hometown at all.” He started running frantically, although not much life can be seen…the signs of the fire grew weaker.  “There must be something beyond this place, it would be madness if this keeps going on, am I really in a different place as said by the man?”  He continued moving and finally he heard voices in a distance.  “This has been happening for years! We need to have water if not our crops can’t grow at all!”  “So…this is once a farming land but the fire destroyed part of it.” Tai Wu thought…  He continued walking to the voices and finally caught sight of humans, they were wearing the same ancient Chinese garb as him…seeing someone, Tai Wu felt a sign of relief, that he wasn’t alone. He approached the guys…  Tai Wu, “Err…Hi, I’m lost and can I know where is this place?”  Man A, “ You’re at the south region, controlled by the earth.”  Tai Wu, “ Huh…? What…controlled by the earth?”  Man A, “ You don’t know? The five elemental regions; Gold, Fire, Wood, Water and Earth. This is the south, which is controlled by the Earth…understand?”  Tai Wu, “What the…Isn’t this country Cheng Du?” (Cheng Du, a state of China)  Man B, “What is Cheng Du and China?”  Tai Wu abruptly realized something…it was true…it was true that he’s in a totally different world.  Tai Wu, “No…no way…”  Man A, “Hmm…judging from that sword of yours…you seem to be a fire wielder. The competition for fire wielder’s in the east side, just travel straight from this path here and you’ll reach the capital of yours.”  Tai Wu, “…” He was too much in a shock, all these happened too fast. He stood there for a while, ignoring the curious calls of the two men before proceeding eastward. He had no other clues of how to get out of this world…and after all he did remember the man mention ‘the next wielder of fire’  While moving through the path, everything seemed normal; fields were being plough and life remains the same as his usual scene. However, it did get ‘strange’ for Tai Wu as he began to see ‘strange’ things like a small glass ball covering over a thin metal strip and lighting up when a button was pressed, if not, a thin circular strip wood with a little black substance at the tip of it. What intrigued him more is that the clothing of these people starts to change to button-less shirts and some of the females actually wore sleeveless clothes, revealing much of their arms. (In ancient china, there are no such things as light bulbs, pencils, t-shirt and girls are very proper with their attires, normally girls who reveal parts like upper arm or even up to the knees are considered rude.)  (To be continued) 
     

        
</post>
<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      “Whoose!” A group of burly man with weapons of sorts surrounding a teenage backed off. The teenage is around seventeen, holding a cracked thin sword in his hand.  “Darn! Keep on resisting on you’ll be dead!”  The men rushed forward, only to realize that two of them had their weapons broken in an instant. It was the teenage…  “Wu Jian swordsmanship?! You little brat…prepare yourself!”  The teenage continued to pant, he had been running and defending himself, looking for the right chance to strike back…Now is the time.  Teenage cried out, “Re…return my parents!”  The teenage ran forward and in a split second, he pierced his flimsy sword right into the abdomen of the most prominent figure in the group, blood gushed out all over his face.  The rest of the guys were stunned by this sudden change of events. The boy once again struck, this time killing four other guys with just one stroke. In the end, only one man was left standing.  “Tell me…why?! Why must you kill my whole family?! Where did we offend you?!”  “Argh….Som…someone paid us…, we’re just in…instructed to do it….”  “Who paid you?”   “A masked man, we don’t know his re~~…”  “You don’t deserve to live…”  The teenage now began moving out of the dark alley he was in…  The time and location is in the ancient times of China. The teenager’s name is Jian Tai Wu, the only heir to the Wu Jian swordsmanship. His mother died ever since he was borne, thus he has no image of his mother and received no motherly love. The previous group of people killed his family of thirteen in just one night through a sneak attack. Strangely, although the bodies of them were present, his father’s body was not there, on his father’s bed is just a note,   “Look for me”  After traveling and pondering for a week after the whole horrible incident, Tai Wu had his clothes tattered and torn, feeling hungry and depressed at the lost of his family. His eyes became misty, he was tough…but even man cry at times.  Suddenly, out of nowhere, a voice rang in his mind…  “South…head for south now…”  Amazingly, Tai Wu felt obliged and head towards south…despite feeling weak, Tai Wu just kept on running. After crossing over a last bend…  “You’re finally here…”  A vigilant looking middle-aged man with a huge and long broadsword stood there. The sword radiates a fiery orange glow. Being blinded by the light, Tai Wu cannot exactly focus out this strange man’s looks.  “You will understand all there is to it of this world and get answers when you reach there.” The huge man spoke calmly.  “Who…who are you? Wha…What do you want calling me here?”  “All the doubts which you have will be discovered upon reaching the other world, now hold this sword…I do not have much time.”  Tai Wu stepped forward and did as told, “What is the other world? Why is it that you want me to hold this sword?”  “Good…this sword is called Flamer, take good care of it as it’ll resemble your fate in the other world. Now, I’ll teleport you there.”  Suddenly, a pillar of light appeared on the ground where Tai Wu is standing.  Man,” Fire of the south, may you summon this child to the true world. Help him with all your might as he is the next wielder of Fire!”  The pillar of light explodes into a column of fire, engulfing Tai Wu who is shocked and somewhat petrified.  (To be continued) 
     

        
</post>
<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Alright, I'll state first. True, i've finally got influenced by the big number of people around me writings blogs. But...don't be mistaken, I have done another Journal in another website which i hadn't disclosed ^^, locate it if you can XP  Ok, this blog would mostly be about my reviews on Anime, Manga, Cds and Games which i have. Also, my hand-written novel would be posted up here as well (hey, i need publicity for my novel) ^^  My novel won't be as creative as Harry Porter, not as imaginative and exciting as Star Wars, but after all...it's my own work...show some support yea? ^^  Finally, if possible...can someone teach me how to post pics up here? Thank you ^^  Next post up: TakaHina's novel : Neverlasting Time Fire Section Chapter 1-1
     

        
</post>
<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Karean, “Precisely…”   Sitting in the dimly lighted and quiet room, Tai Wu and Karean continued communicating about the futuristic life and this world.   It seems Karean has got there 2 weeks ago and had been discovered by the people of the Sen Arashi manor; hence she began to get accustomed to the life there. Strangely, the chief of Sen Arashi sect ranked Karean with quite a high rank once she got in, she was even given a secret room and had servants under her.   Tai Wu, “Haha, it seemed that you have a charmed life. Lucky you.”   Karean, “Well…I don’t really know is it luck or so…”   Tai Wu, “Why?”   Karean, “It was as if the chief is using me…she taught me skills and techniques…chose targets who seem totally innocent and commands me to assassinate them.”   Tai Wu, “Hmm…”   Karean, “What do you think? Is this master of mine really reliable?”   Tai Wu, “I can’t be sure…”   Hearing this, Karean purred her mouth a little and knocked lightly on Tai Wu’s head shortly.   Karean, “Hah, well…stop thinking of all this serious topics, you wanna have a bath?”   Tai Wu, “Bath?!”   Karean moved over to Tai Wu and began sniffing at him like a dog, soon complaining, “Smell yourself! After all this is a lady’s room mind you, I won’t like my room to be filled with the stench of a man who hadn’t bathed in days!”   Tai Wu rebutted back with a hitch of reluctance, “But…I don’t have any clothes nor is there a bathroom in this room of yours.”   Karean, “Oh yeah, forgot to tell you…outside this room and in the right side of the tunnel is a spring, water there is clean and portable. Then when you’re done, just knock on my door. Ignore the scarecrow…it’ll fix itself.”   Tai Wu, “A scarecrow can fix itself?”  Karean, “It’s made of a special metal which has the properties to attach itself back to its broken part…just like water. It’s very hard and only Sen Arashi’s fatal kill; Dai Kai Sen has the power to destroy it.”   Tai Wu, “…this world just baffles me…”   Karean, “Ok, don’t just stand there, go bath.” She proceeds over to the door and opened it, eyes staring at Tai Wu hinting him to get out. Reluctantly, Tai Wu went for the shower.   Walking in the dark, Tai Wu’s eyes gradually grown used to it…sighting the spring, Tai Wu undressed and soaked himself in it. Coincidentally or purposely, the spring is just of the right size. The water is cooling and relaxing, soothing of all the tiredness and worries, Tai Wu for once can let his mind off. He glanced over the bulk of his body, raw wounds and scars have increased in number, the few weeks of traveling in his hometown after his parents death had forced him to grow up…no more of the well-lived life and no more of the leisure he had experienced.   Tai Wu, “All this is just too strange…what exactly is this world? Why am I here? What’s the purpose in all these…and why did the man said I would find out the answers to all my questions here? I have more questions now instead of answers!”   Suddenly, footsteps and voice can be heard spreading through the tunnel,” Missy! Is that you?”   Tai Wu was alarmed, someone had found the entrance to this place, “That’s not good, I thought only Karean can enter?”   ???, “Missy? Please reply!”   Tai Wu remained silent, slowly he got out of the bath and dressed himself, creeping towards the giant door.   ???, “If you don’t reply, I’ll proceed forward!”   Tai Wu thought, “Not good…” Frantically, Tai Wu knocked the door…however there were no answers.   Tai Wu thought, “This is seriously not good!”   ???, “Missy?! Is that you? I’m coming forward now.”   Abruptly, a voice emits from the door…Karean’s voice, “If you move just one more step closer! I’ll accuse you of molest! By that time prepare to get the punishment from Master!”   The man stopped…seemingly relieve at hearing Karean’s voice, “Sorry for my intrusion, but I brought your dinner here…I didn’t know you are taking a bath.”   Karean, “Just leave the food there…I’ll get to it when I’m done.”   ???, “Yes…Karean-sama”   A small tap sound is heard…continued by footsteps. Finally, the door exposed its entrance and let Tai Wu in. Karean is just wearing a light pink nightdress, which seems translucent under the light, the figure of her seductive body much apparent now. Tai Wu blushed again…   Noticing the redness of Tai Wu face, Karean turned back, “Don’t look at me now! Turn back!”   Tai Wu, “Ye…Yes!!!” Immediately he turned back.   After some time…Karean spoke, “Alright, you can turn over now.”   Slowly shifting himself, Tai Wu took a glance at Karean…she’s back in her previous dark green ninja suit.   Tai Wu, “Phew…Ok, Why is it that the door can be opened by somebody else?”   Karean, “That guy is one of my servant and bodyguard, he seem to have gotten wary that I snick off last night…”   ???, “So, you did snick off yesterday night…and the night before!”   Shocked, Tai Wu and Karean turned their heads over to the door which is now open…a man is standing there bent down a little, right arm raised perpendicular and the forearm ninety degree as well, left hand is totally stretched straight forward.   Karean, “This stance!!”   Tai Wu, “Isn’t this Sen Arashi’s…”   ???, “Prepare yourself stranger! Sen Arashi! Dai Kai Sen!”   
     

        
</post>
<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
          Playstation 2 game   Genre: RPG   Story:   Many years in the future, the once hometown of human; Earth, has disappeared and rendered unknown. Human have been living in outer space inside various colonies and spaceships. A great war, the Militian Conflict broke out and created monsters known as Gnosis...   14 years since, people have been living in fear and uncertainty of these monsters. Various organizations began to start collecting "Zohars", plate-like objects said to be able to summon or control the Gnosis.   The Woglinde, the ship which Shion Uzuki is in discovers one of it, however no one could expect this discovery to lead Shion on a trip to save the universe. Along with KOSMOS; Shion's creation and other comrades, the saga of a lifetime begins...   Review:   Frankly, I have heard great things about it, quite a number of people I know of totally adored this game. However, it didn't bring that much fun to me.  Being a RPG, the storyplot must be an excellent one, but sad to say, i was not that impressed by the storyline of this game. Maybe it's because i'm too dumb to understand the complexity of the plot, or maybe because that is a second episode to this game, thus the first episode leashes out all the main questions without having any answers to them. The storyplot has a very strong science fiction feel and maybe even a little religious touch, sadly, I have no particular liking to either of these.   Another important factor to RPG has got to be the gameplay system. Xenosaga uses a rather strange way of battle system. Players attack in a somewhat martial art way. Don't get in wrong though, it's not in those Street Fighter way, it's turn based, the player would have to press certain buttons to initiate attacks which follows up with another attack, acting like a combo. Interesting at first, it soon grew stale on me. Also, as tradition to all RPG, magic is surely included. Termed as "Ether" in he game, each character have their own sets of magic which you evolve it to more magic. These magic can be shared among characters as long as you have the points to share it. Beign a futuristic RPG, Xenosaga includes as well "AGWS", a kind of robot whereby certain character can summon and sit in during battle, not a bad inclusion in my opinion.   Next, on to the game character's develop system. No originality at all if i may add, stats and  numbers are all over the place. It is extremely uncolourful and tiring. One interesting thing though, is how characters can develop their attack, points are collected in battle and then used to develop their "Tech Attack", "Skills" and "Ether". "Tech Attack" is the attack which you use in your combo attack, "Skills" is drawing various...skills like "Prevent Poison" or so, "Ether" as said before, is to develop the "Ether" of characters. This may not be original, but it suits rather nicely here, other than that, nothing else interesting.   As the game proceeds ,it may be more of a movie than a game. In about 60% of the storyplot is continued in the form of movie scenes. I appreciate the producers effort, but it gets players bored at times, especially for such a science fiction plot, players may not understand what they are talking at times. The only time where players are actually involved is during the dungeon fights and touring of the place, which in my opinion are too little.   Mini games are somewhat reasonable, but it proved a little useless and totally unrelated to the main flow. It's like the producers added in Side Quest for the sake that it's...Side Quest. In other words, useless...   Graphics wise, the game doesn't score as much as maybe, Final Fantasy X? It's impressive, but not eye catching. I would only deem it as maybe just above average.   Sound and music are usual as well. There aren't any spectacular or exceptional tunes one can relate to. Voices to each character however are really well done and selected. Definitely a plus for this or any game.   Overall, I don't really find this game attractive. Story being too complex, graphics and sound not that spectacular. It is playable...but i won't really recommend it unless you are an obessed fan of science fiction. Some scenes however, are quite funny...like KOSMOS stoic behaviour or a gang leader acting sissy.   Extra: I heard that the game "Xenogears" from PS1 is a continuation of the game, Xenosaga is acting as a prelude...So Xenogears fan may want to try it out. Also Xenosaga 2 has been produced. Make no mistake, i may not like Xenosaga 1, but i would play Xenosaga 2 nonetheless. After all, Xenosaga 1 is just the first episode. Xenosaga 2 may clear all doubts in Xenosaga 1.  Score: 3/5   
     

        
</post>
<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
       Karean takes in one deep breathe… “Sen-Arashi! Dai Kai Sen!”  Tai Wu, “What in the world…?”  In just a flashing moment, Karean has moved and is now standing behind the scarecrow with her right hand bent forward while the left hand is totally stretched to the back this time.  Tai Wu, “What just happened?” he exclaimed.  Suddenly, the scarecrow’s whole body broke into half…falling to the ground with a large ‘crank!’ sound. Examining the scarecrow, Tai Wu realized that it’s not made of grass and straws…instead it’s made of many metal strips stuffed in it, cutting it into half would not be easy…yet Karean just did it with a sudden movement which eludes the eye.  Karean, “Pant…I’ve never like using that skill…it uses up too much energy.”  Tai Wu, “What did you just do?”  Karean, “This is Sen-Arashi, the current most powerful skill in this world.”All of a sudden, a silence click rang through the tunnel.Karean, “Ok, the lock is opened, let’s go in.”  Approaching the giant door, Karean push the door with ease…creaking sound of the joints indicated it.  Karean, “Haha, welcome to my room” She said smilingly. Next, she just walked into the room. “What are you waiting for? Come in.”  Tai Wu, “…Ok”  Moving through the door, a majestic seek soon welcomed Tai Wu. The whole room is made up of raw stonewalls with several sword traces and cuts on it. Sitting in the right corner is a big sized bed with pink covers and a drawer sitting while in the other is a small stool and table. There would just too little furniture to find in the room; overall…the whole room gave a very empty sight. A small window sat at the top corners of the room, giving off just minimum light and air.  Karean, “So how? What do you think of my room?”  Tai Wu, “Uhm…It’s big…hehehe” he spoke…the laugh didn’t seem convincing.  Karean, “Big…it’s too big! In my hometown, my room is just the size of one-fifth of this room. No televisions, radio…it’s pure boredom staying here.”  Tai Wu, “Televisions? Radio?”  Karean, “Oh…haha, well you’ll see it soon enough when we get to the town areas.”  Tai Wu, “Right…”   Karean, “Ok, I’ll start with the question…Are you hungry?”  Tai Wu, “Wha?…I haven’t eaten in days…”  Karean, “Poor guy…” She opened the drawers, took out a strange looking box and threw it towards Tai Wu.  Tai Wu, “What’s this?”  Karean, “In my hometown, we call this compressed food, various nutrients are squeezed into the biscuits inside…one biscuit can survive you for about one day.”  Tai Wu opened the box…inside are just small yellow biscuits and it looked rather plain.  Tai Wu, “ One of this can survive me for a day? You must be kidding.”  Karean, “Hah, don’t look down at the power of science and technology of year 2500. Try eating more than three of this, you’ll feel bloated.” She challenged proudly.  Tai Wu, “Year 2500?! You live in that time period?!” As he said that, he tasted the biscuits, its much more tastier than the biscuits of his time.  Karean, “Yeah, I can be said to be your ‘descendent’. In that time, people has already developed space travel and Mars is our second home planet.”  Tai Wu, “Space travel?? Mars??”  Karean, “…I’ll elaborate on all those, lucky I’ve learned on ancient history…”  With this, Karean began explaining of the whole history from the past to the future…it intrigued Tai Wu a lot…the development of guns, story of space and many others…  Tai Wu, “So…so much has happened…”  Next, Karean began on explaining the origins of her life. In the future, there weren’t much space for development anymore…therefore most landed property were mortgaged and high rise buildings grew in all countries. As for fuel, Scientist had developed a way to harness the burning of Hydrogen and thus fossil fuels were being kept and preserved. Science progressed at an amazing rate, and new inventions and discoveries like ‘compressed food’ and ‘Super Antibody’ was gradually created. However, crime rate grew at an overall high as the standards of life was much higher, also more destructive weapons were created and small scale wars broke out almost every month…the whole place is just chaotic.  Karean, “Sigh…well, stop talking the future. You sure have many questions now don’t you?”  Tai Wu, “…yes. What exactly is this place we are at now?”  Karean, “Well…to say truthfully, this is beyond my knowledge. This place seems to adopt the cultures of three major periods, the past, which is your time, the mid past, or mid future for you, which are around the 1990s, and my period. There seems to be no government, but instead the people around here with their own similar beliefs rule it. Altogether there is five different type of thinking and they’re labeled as; Gold, Fire, Water, Earth and Wood at each different positions of; North South East West and Central.”  Tai Wu, “This is almost identical to the five elements we practice!”  Karean, “Yeah, I’ve noticed as well…but there seem to be no link between this two sets.”  Tai Wu, “…then what’s the deal that some people carries swords and what exactly is ‘Fire Wielder competition’?”  Karean, “This is the part whereby we have to complete.”  Tai Wu, “Huh?”  Karean, “To return back to our original world, we have to win the respective competition we all have, Fire Wielder, Earthly Mortals, Water Hunters, Lightning Strikers and Natural Champions. I win the ‘Earthly Mortals’ competition while you stand victorious for the ‘Fire Wielder’ competition.”  Tai Wu, “What’s the reason behind all these?”  Karean, “There will be three more people from other time and world in this place now, and as you’ve guessed, they are the ‘Water Seekers’, ‘Lightning Strikers’ and ‘Natural Champions’. We have to seek them out and relate to them the whole deal, I’ve spent the whole week looking for them and I’ve only found you.”  Tai Wu, “Hmm…I get the whole picture now…so to return to our world, the five of us have to win our competitions… “  Karean, “Precisely…”  
     

        
</post>
<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
         Anime Review  Story:  Shinohara Miho is a third grade pupil in a primary school. She is a shy introvert with little self confidence. She calls herself "a young firl with a lot of worries."  Results in school is average but she's good at drawing. Her greatest dream is to be a cartoonist. One day, she acquires some magical powers by chance. She can change herself by using magical powers into the fifteen years old her, a.k.a Fancy Lala, a superstar. In the other world with novelty and challenge, she disguises herself as another identity to do great performance on the stage.  However, be sure not to rely on magic too much!   Reviews:  You may be put off by the story, "Ack...you actually watch girly and kiddy anime!", but...Superb! I can't find any other better words ti describe this anime. This anime is not well known and most people won't be attracted by it. But lucky me for having the chance to get it and boy do i love it.  The plot focuses on Miho being 9 years old, turning into 15 and an artist when she's at it. Touching and an eye opener, it brillantly shows of the 'magic' in the world of stardom and the perils that come with it. Also, it depicts of how Miho juggles between her 9 years old student lifestyle and her 15 years old superstar lifestyle. Simply, it's how a girl copes with her dream. This kind of anime is rather new and rare in anime, therefore it brought a totally new experience to me. the ending, i might add is quite touching as well, almost bringing my tears to my eyes.   Graphics is nicely shown as well, nothing too complex or plain, just suits nicely with the theme of this anime. May i add that Lala looks quite cute to me as well. ^^  Being an anime dedicated to the road of stardom, there are many songs sung by the various characters and the overall melody is never too heavy. Seiyuus are well chosen with voices suiting their character and mood. One may find some of the songs featured a little too childish though...  All in all, this is a great anime for young girls and maybe some if the young males. Each character are introduced properly and one may even relate some of the events shown in the show. Action fans however, may be disappointed as this anime has totally no signs of any violence or action. This is a pure light hearted anime aimed for the adolescenes (there are exceptions). I may not be that young, but i definitely loved it.  Score: 5/5  Extra: Spanning 26 episodes, the local television once aired it, this is where i first saw it. The DVD boxset i bought has some cards and drawing of the anime as well.  
     

        
</post>
<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Tai Wu, “…”  Karean, “…??”  Tai Wu, “Uhm…er…don’t you have anything to tell me?”  Karean, “Oh yeah, follow me, this isn’t a good place to talk.”  She went forward and grabbed the embarrassed Tai Wu, dragging him to a nearby dense forest. Tai Wu didn’t opposed at all, he hadn’t truly communicate with a local and to say…a wide-eyed girl with adorable face.  Karean, “All right…we can talk now… What’s your name by the way?”  Tai Wu, “Tai…Tai…Tai Wu…” he murmured slightly.  Karean, “Ok, Tai Wu… I have some questions to ask you. What is the current date in this world?”  Tai Wu thought, “Huh?!… why did she ask me this question? Damn, I have to think of something…”  Although looking rather dumb, Tai Wu is quick in his thinking and he answered, “In actual fact, I’ve just woke up from a deep coma and now searching for the people who left me at the Southern village.”  Karean heard the answer and looked rather skeptical at it, “Is that true?”  Tai Wu, “Why should I bluff you?”  Karean, “Okie…What is the biggest power now in this world?”  Tai Wu was bewildered now, why would a girl of this world ask him such questions, “What do you really want to know from asking me all this?”  Karean, “Just tell me, do you know the answers?”  Tai Wu, “…alright alright…I admit, I don’t know the answers.”  Karean, “Ok, one last question. What time are you from?” she said with a slight smile, as if happy at hearing Tai Wu’s ignorance of this world and the last question is like a joke.  Tai Wu, “…Ancient China, from Cheng Du. Happy?”  Hearing this, Karean jumps up with joy to the complete baffled Tai Wu. He stood there, gleaming on.   Karean, “Haha, I finally found one!! Finally!”  Tai Wu, “Huh?”  Karean stopped her short celebration, lifted her hands for a handshake, but Tai Wu unknowing of this ‘action’ stood there with that confused look on his face. (Tai Wu’s from Ancient China whereby there is no cultures as handshakes.)  Karean, “Oh yeah, I forgot you’re from Ancient China…This is called a handshake, similar to a bow.” Saying that, she went on and did the handshake. “Understand now?”  Tai Wu, “…ok, you believe about the ‘Ancient China’ thing?”  Karean, “Hah, of course…I’m from another world and time frame as well.”  Tai Wu, “What?!”  Karean, “Quiet down, nobody can hear about this…How bout this, we’ll head for my place here…I’ll explain all about it.”  Tai Wu, “You sure it’s alright? How can I enter your room…”  Karean, “Are people in the past so shy? Just listen to me and don’t worry.”   With that, she started leading Tai Wu deeper into the forest until almost no light can past through the canopy above. Reaching a clearing, they stopped.   Karean, “Now remember this route, it’ll be equivalent to your house’s route.”  Tai Wu, “I’ll be staying in your house?”  Karean, “Hah, no dummy…this is all too long to explain. Just keep quiet for now.”  She bends down and swept away several dead leave and grass, eventually revealing a small hook. Sweeping more away, it showed a large hatch with three relatively rusty ring in a line.   Karean, “Now…here’s the hard part.” Then, she draws out the two kodachi hidden in her boots.  Tai Wu, “What are you going to do with those?”  Karean, “Hehehe, Magic.”  Holding the two swords and setting it up high, she sets her left hand over the other, making the Twin Kodachi in her hands set above the other as well. Soon after, Karean began chanting an unknown phrase. Amazingly, the Twin Kodachi began reacting, they began to glow and eventually into blinding light, now the Kodachi is like a light beam…totally harmless. Next, Karean places her right fist over the left, merging both beams of light. After a short period of time, the blinding glow stopped, replacing in its place is an ultra long, twin and sharp sword.  Tai Wu, “Your sword is…Astonishing…”  Karean, “Haha, thank you. I’ve just learn of how to harness the power of my Earth weapon “Creator”. You learned of yours?”  Tai Wu, “Huh? This sword?” He starts flinging his sword onto the ground. “Nope, I still haven’t even started using this sword until previously.”  Karean, “Hmm…alright. But you better learn of how to develop the power of your sword. Ok, lets continue.”  Carrying the newly formed long sword, she slots Creator into the line of rings. With just an easy flick, she easily cuts open the rings, which lead to the open of the hatch. After opening the hatch, Karean once again draws out the slotted sword and in an instant…changed back to the Twin Kodachi.  Tai Wu, “Your sword can change form?”  Karean, “I’m not sure whether it can, but the long sword form is what I’ve discovered. It’s original form is still the Twin Kodachi. To open the hatch, you have to open the rings within it, bashing it from the surface can’t help at all. Alright, lets head in, my room is just at the end of this cave.”  Keeping the Kodachi, Karean jumps into the dark hole below. Tai Wu hesitated a little before following into the hole. They began traveling through a long series of darkness and creepiness before reaching an enormous door with a strange and out of place scarecrow standing beside it..   Karean, “Alright, my room is here.”  Tai Wu, “You need such a big door?”  Karean, “Oh, I’m supposed to be sealed off from the rest of the world and totally focusing on my form of Martial Arts ‘Sen Arashi’. I don’t like this way of life so I found of a way to run. Ok, stop all these questions…I’ll open the door.”  Karean bent down a little, holding one of the Kodachi with the right arm raised perpendicular and the forearm ninety degree as well, left hand however is totally stretched straight.  Tai Wu, “Why this position?”  Karean, “…”  Seeing Karean is actually serious, Tai Wu quiet down…He knows that Karean is going to show her skills now.  Karean takes in one deep breathe… “Sen-Arashi! Dai Kai Sen!” 
     

        
</post>
<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
         NOTE: Contains bloody scenes, not suitable for kids.  Story:  A massive earthquake hit Japan and devasted it, along with a clan named Oboro. A golden castle appeared shortly after the last tremors...Along with this phenomenon came many supernatural creatures named Hellspawns, changing Tokyo into a city of demons.   The last and the leader of the Oboro clan, Hotsuma sworned to eliminate the Hellspawn, deceased Oboro clan possessed to attack Hotsuma and to exact revenge onto the source which downed his clan.  Little did anyone expect, that the story doesn't stop with just that objective...with the inclusion of Hime, his brother Morinaga and the accursed sword which eats it's owner.   ..............................................................  Review:  This is a game which i had wanted for a very very long time, I was a great fan of Shinobi in it's Sega Genesis years and was delighted to hear it coming out for PS2. In fact, this game is one of the reasons i bought PS2. Naturally...i had high expectations with this game.  Story-wise, this game doesn't lose out too much. Despite the plot of a city getting invaded by monsters and an one man hero saving the city, it's used a little too much, but many other plots get involved in it as well, making this game all the better. But still, what this games focus on is the gameplay and graphics, at least it's acceptable for such a plot to be used. No doubt the storyline didn't get to me much, but i'm not turned off by it...which is a good thing.  In terms of graphic, it's shown in 3D form and is quite good. The flow of the visual and effects moved nicely and merged well with the fast pace and moment of the game. You can see blood spilling out, monsters getting cut into half, from the top of high rise buildings to the blooming park of Sakura...Although it can't be compared to the extremely beautiful images of Final Fantasy CGs, it's really a good job done by Sega.   Gameplay and difficulty, i will have to say, unless you have sheer determination and is fast with your fingers, you would be better off not playing this game at all. This is the hardest game i had ever played in my life! It contains 8 stages, full of trecherous terrain and incredible enemy and the bosses are just out of the world. It may sound fast, 8 stages that's all...But I took nearly a week to complete this game. Really, each boss has their best way of fighting and even if you found out the best way...it'll still take the hell outta you and your "Ninja" skills to defeat the boss. All i can tell those playing it: rely of Tate. As i've said, the game flows nicely, there would seldom be hang ups or jolts of the screen. The most smooth flowing game i've ever played.  The sounds are also a good factor in this game, the music and mood fits exactly with the stage and place. It also brings out the fight in one...although it may not exactly be enough to finish that place...Another good point is that there can be 2 voices, English and Japanese, with english subtitles, a very good inclusion in my opinion.  Overall, This game is just the hardest game i have ever played in my life of gameplaying. It can make one go so frustrated that he can almost throw his controller out of the window, yup that's the degree the game can bring you. Unless, you are always in for a good challenge and fight...or you wish to train out that gamer in you...I would advice you to think twice before playing it. Not that it's bad, but it's that hard. Oh...and did i say that i have only completed the game once in normal mode and not hard mode? ^^   Score: 4/5  
     

        
</post>
<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Seeing so many new and strange gadgets around, Tai Wu got aroused…feeling uneasy and intrigued by this future, which he sees now.  Gradually, he was out of the town, but he saw stranger things now, a whole road which is paved in black with strips of white in between.  Tai Wu, “Is this how the future looks like? It looks…scary…”  Now, the whole path is exposed in front of him, mountains scaling the skies in the far right, occasional people carrying swords of different size and shapes walking down various paths, in the far front looks cloudy and gloomy with lightning striking down frequently.   Tai Wu, “That’s the place where I have to go…? Well, it doesn’t seem I have much of a choice.”  Nudging his giant sword a little and starting to pick up his pace, Tai Wu proceeded. Unfortunately, the place appears further than expected; Tai Wu had been traveling to the other area for 2 days but without avail, although hungry and exhausted, that was the only clue he has, thus he pushed on. Strangely, even though 2 days had been past, there were still noticeable lightning strikes on that area.  On the 4th day, Tai Wu finally reached the area; this area is a queer sight. There is a town within the area, but the area itself had been fenced off by constant lightning strikes on the border, the town however didn’t suffer any kind of damages. There was also no thunder sounding.  Tai Wu, “The so-called fire wielder competition is held there? How can I get in the first place?”  Nobody is in the town; the buildings in the town were somewhat new to him, they were tall and comparable to the emperor’s palace in terms of majestic and awe.   Female voice, “ Hey! Don’t just stand there! Come help me a little!”   Tai Wu, “ Huh? Where are you?”  Female voice, “Are you dumb!? Here…Hereeeeee!!”  Tai Wu looked around the place, only seeing a small sized girl holding twin kodachi, she’s masked and wearing a dark green cloak, seemingly of an assassin. She stood at the border, raising her twin blades to counter the lightning strikes, whenever a lightning strike hits her sword, the lightning will get reflected away and even grow bigger.  Tai Wu, “That’s…that’s amazing…”  Female, “ Are you truly dumb?!!! I need help here!!!!”  Tai Wu, “Oh…yes!!”  Tai Wu unbound the cloth of Flamer, raising the sword with both hands and headed off to the Female’s help. The fiery lightning hitting down forced Tai Wu off, added that the sword was almost impossible to use for adequate turns and shifts, Tai Wu can only swing Flamer around in a crude and clumsy manner. Pin-pointing the correct timing to swing Flamer, he pushed the girl out to safety while he swings his giant sword to effectively deflect off a few of the lightning strokes. The lightning got reflected back as well, however the beam did not grow bigger; instead it gradually integrated and became nothing. Seizing the chance, Tai Wu got out of this lightning nightmare as well.  Tai Wu, “Pant…crap…this sword is just tedious to even carry. Hey…are you alright?”  The female just stood there, eyes flashing with joy. She has already kept the kodachi during the intervene of Tai Wu helping her.  Female, “youyouyouyouyouyouyouyou…”  Tai Wu, “Wha..wha..what?”  Female, “Are you a fire wielder?”  Tai Wu thought, “Even though I don’t know what is a fire wielder, but it seems I can save more trouble being one…”  “Yap I am.”  Female, “Haahaha, finally found one! Come with me now!” Grabbing Tai Wu’s hand while she said it.  Tai Wu, “Hey hey!! What are you up to? First you called me a dummy, second you didn’t even thank me for saving you, thirdly now you just pull me around like I’m a toy…At least say what are you up to!” He said sounding annoyed. Brushing off her hands, Tai Wu placed Flamer on his shoulders and began to walk when the girl suddenly leaped in front of him.   Tai Wu, “What the…”  Female, “Alright alright, I apologize for being so rude…Sorieeeeee.” She sounded joking while saying ‘Sorie’.   Tai Wu, “Er…ok ok…What is it?” She started to remove the mask…  Tai Wu, “…?”  Having removed the mask, she revealed a sweet smile, “Ah…this feels much better, a hate the smell of that mask.” Saying that she chunked the mask to the ground, and slowly walked towards the unmoving Tai Wu in a emotional manner. Tai Wu stood there blushing a little, this time looking really like a dummy.  She tip-toed and whispered into his ears, “Don’t you think I’m cute?” Soon after, she kissed him on the cheeks…and jumped aside laughing a little. Tai Wu’s face was totally red now, he hasn’t had much communication with any girl, except maybe the granny who had brought him up.  Female, “Haha, your face is so red, cccuuuttttteee…” she said laughingly. Suddenly reminded that his face is pure heat now, he scrubbed is face with his hands.  Female, “Hahaha, ok ok. I’ll stop teasing you. My name is Karean Miyamoto. That’s K.A.R.E.A.N .M.I.Y.A.M.O.T.O, remember it well, okie?”  (to be continued)
     

        
</post>
<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Escaping from the various guards and fight, Tai Wu is once again out in the light and forest. The light blinded him a while since he did spend some time in the underground. He slowly moves out of the forest he is in; he realized that if not for Karean, he could never find the hatch, getting in and out of the dense forest is much harder than he thought.  Nonetheless, by the time Tai Wu managed to get out, the day was setting with a field of orange over the sky above him. It has been 5 days ever since he got there, but he was more aware of his situation now…to get the champion for Fire Wielder.  He sat along a lone tree, observing Flamer. Recalling of all that happened in the fight, Tai Wu was enlightened and happy at the abilities of the sword.  Tai Wu, “This sword knows of what state it should be at the right time…as if it’s able to read my thoughts. Guess I’ve overlook its usefulness over its inflexibility.”  He raised the sword high with both hands, “Change into flame…” Flamer soon changed into flames…it soon returned to its usual state with a thought from Tai Wu. He repeated this action several times, as if a child playing with his newly found toy.  Soon, nightfall approached. Feeling exhausted…Tai Wu soon felt asleep with a fire burning nearby.  The chirping birds woke Tai Wu up from his deep slumber; looking around the area with drowsy eyes, Tai Wu realized that it was near noon now. The sun has broadened its rays across the land, various strange looking people traveling around as usual. However, something seems short.  Tai Wu, “…The Lightning strikes! They disappeared!” Getting up, Tai Wu rushes towards the town with the Lightning border.  Tai Wu reaches the town eventually, but he was much shocked by the contents of the town itself…  Tai Wu, “This is…this is just horrible.”  The previous lightning strikes were outstanding, but this time is different; buildings with splashes of red on them and unrecognizable matter that resembled minced meat appearing in some part of the area, the floor as well looked quite burned. Another significant piece is a detached arm with shaded white particles and purple blood still flowing out from the supposed joint area. The perimeter is big… it covered a whole patch, giving off a gory and disgusting feeling. Even though the place is a town, nobody was in sight…  Tai Wu, “What has happened…?” Walking around the dilapidated place that emits a rather foul smell, Tai Wu notices the blood were relatively fresh.  Tai Wu, “Fresh…” Glancing around, Tai Wu discovers a trail of blood that leads to a smaller path in the town. Attempting to follow this trail, a loud “Bang!” suddenly shifts Tai Wu’s attention away…the lightning border is closed now, trapping the whole town with it.  Tai Wu, “Damn, I’m trapped!”  Running towards the lightning border cautiously, Tai Wu swings the giant sword towards this magnificent fence. The rays that were in contact with the sword did get reflected and soon dispersed, but new rays of lightning placed it soon enough before Tai Wu was able to seize the split second time to escape.  Tai Wu, “Looks like…I’ll be staying here for some time.” He said with a somewhat dejected tone, although he finally managed to enter his known destination, he hadn’t a chance to escape it now.  Tracing back to the red trail, Tai Wu progresses gradually to a small and quite hidden building with the board sign in a language totally unknown to Tai Wu. Observing from outside, it seemed quiet and has dim lights in.  “Nni Airyahs”  Tai Wu thought, “Huh? What kind of shop is this? Still, I cannot be absent minded…danger may lurk in it.”  Positioning himself with Flamer, Tai Wu slowly approached the tiny and insignificant building. Carefully, Tai Wu opened the shop door and peered inside; only a few tables and a candle lit, it seemed to be an Inn.  Tai Wu, “Strange…” he stepped into the inn when a piercing pain was suddenly applied onto his abdomen.  Tai Wu, “What the hell!” He tried to shift himself, but the sharp object prevented him to do so.  Tai Wu, “Wu Jian swordsmanship: Stork picking its wings!” With a short twist and unexpected precise movement of both hands, the heavy blade was held pointing backwards. Tai Wu then injected a fast stab backwards; this amazing and quick action forced the piercing object behind him to shift out of place.  “Danger!” Strangely, Tai Wu’s sword was met with another tough object and a ‘Kiang’ sounded. Sensing something wrong with his expected result, Tai Wu dashed himself forward and confronted this new opponent.  Standing in front were three people, a short weak looking girl wearing thick glasses and Kimono with fair complexion and a vulnerable expression. A one armed man holding a strange looking weapon that juts out sharply at its tip. He was wearing rather tattered clothes with painful expression and several scars apparent on his face. Another man in long pants and shirt…relatively good looking and holding an exceptionally long Katana with handle and sheath distinctively made from lightwood.  Man in long pants and shirt, “Who are you?! What are you doing here and why?!”  Tai Wu, “I’m a fire wielder, I noticed the trail of blood outside and follow it here.”  The man looked towards the one-armed man, seemingly wanting to get instructions from him, the one-armed man just shook his head.  Man in long pants and shirt, “I have a few questions to ask you.”  Tai Wu thought, “What?! Again…?” he then spoke, “Alright…”  Man in long pants and shirt, “Firstly, where are you from?”  Tai Wu thought for a while before answering, “Jian Tai Wu from Cheng Du of China, I live in the Song Dynasty.”  All three people had surprised faces, guessing from their expressions, Tai Wu continued, “Are you three from a different time and world?”  Girl, “Shinto! We’ve finally found the fire wielder!”  The one-armed man stared at the girl for a moment, slightly anger by her exclamation.  Man in long pants and shirt, “…What is your condition to return to your world?”  Tai Wu now was confident that this trio was from another world and time…in other words comrades in the same situation as him.  Tai Wu, “My condition, to be the official Fire Wielder!”  Once again, the man looked towards the one-armed guy…after a short period, the one-armed guy nodded, but the indifferent look was still hanging on his face. The man asking the questions and the girl by now began to smile. Walking to Tai Wu, the man in long pants and shirt raised his hands for a handshake; “Sorry for the barrage of questions just now…I’m Shinto Kimura, the girl is Ayako Matsura and lastly my master Rinto Gareth.” Ayako then bowed down politely, “Nice to meet you Tai Wu.” She was soft and feeble, seemingly to be defenseless; Tai Wu was quite puzzled at how she could win any fights.  Rinto, “…” he just remained silent ever since the start.  Tai Wu thought, “Looks like what Karean has said is all true…there is indeed someone like us…”  
     

        
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Kaito stood on, watching Flamer changing from steel to fire with stunned expression on his face. Karean however didn’t look that amazed, instead…relieved.  Although Flamer is now pure heat, Tai Wu felt at ease with it even though holding it with his bare hands. Rather, he couldn’t feel any heat radiating from it at all…he is immune to the scorching flame of Flamer. Despite having no body, the fire still burned in the same position of it’s former, tamed.  Tai Wu raised Flamer, pointing straight at Kaito, he seemed confident this time.  Kaito, “Since you requested for it…I won’t hold back.” For the third time, Kaito once again assumed the position of Sen Arashi: Dai Kai Sen. Karean looked on quietly at a safe side.  Tai Wu, “Stop jabbering…” Tai Wu didn’t move his fire blade at all, it was still pointing straight at Kaito.  Kaito began his move with his frightening speed, this speed forming into a huge vacuum. Dust flew and the flame of Flamer flickered despite having quite a distance between Tai Wu and Kaito; unknowing to Kaito, this flicker is a sign for Tai Wu. Tai Wu immediately reacted to it, dashing forward strafing a little to the right, his sword now pointing towards the left side.  Tai Wu, “Wu Jian swordsmanship: Trapping a Tiger!”  Kaito cannot stop nor notice the counter move by Tai Wu, he went straight through the blazing fire “line”, this fire was enough to slow and stun Kaito down. Tai Wu successfully avoided Kaito’s move even though suffering a little cuts due to the fast flowing air current; from there, Tai Wu began his next move. Tai Wu stopped his movement, he somersault into the air, with Flamer pointing right down at Kaito.  Tai Wu, “Wu Jian swordsmanship: Eagle’s prey!”  With that, Tai Wu dived down right at the stunned Kaito and swing Flamer right at the opportune timing. The hit connected and brought further more fire and pain to Kaito. Kaito has totally stopped now, Tai Wu as said has countered Kaito’s Sen Arashi: Dai Kai Sen.  Kaito fell to the ground and began rolling himself about, trying to extinguish the fire still burning on him, Tai Wu on the other hand landed safely from the air attack. Tai Wu surprised Karean at this counterattack, but still she seemed slightly worried for Kaito…Tai Wu noticed it.  Tai Wu, “Karean, get some water and help Kaito out.”  Kaito’s cries and moans grew louder eventually until Karean splashed a pail of water at him. Shortly, Flamer changed back to its metallic form, seemingly realized that the current situation is safe.  Karean, “Now stop! Obviously you have lost, even with your best skills you can’t win over Tai Wu!”  Unexpectedly, the dishevel Kaito did not listen; he rushed towards Tai Wu unleashing a barrage of attacks with his Katana.  Kaito, “Argh!!!!! Sen Arashi: Berserker’s Crave!” Kaito began lashing out random orders of strikes, totally leaving himself open and vulnerable. However, the attack was strong and unpredictable, Tai Wu was unable to seize any chance to deal blows to Kaito. Instead he can only shift and evade the blows done by Kaito, occasionally raising the heavy Flamer up to block the heavy and lethal blows of Kaito.  After around thirty blows, Kaito halt his continuous attack; with a last block knocking Tai Wu off him, then he leaped towards Tai Wu, his Katana raised up and ready to apply a downward slash at Tai Wu.  Kaito, “Sen Arashi: Splitting a Mountain!”  Tai Wu thought, “Damn it! This can’t go on! Wu Jian swordsmanship: Flying Dragon!”   Tai Wu pulled Flamer up with all his might, making a forceful upward blow. The two blows hit, with Tai Wu’s blade weight gaining an advantage and knocking Kaito off balance; Kaito landed badly, breaking several bones in the process. However, the impact caused Tai Wu to release his grasp on Flamer, the heavy sword spinning into the air and landing with a loud thud and a big vibration on the ground.  Tai Wu headed back for Flamer and held it firmly in his hands; he turned his head back only to see Kaito getting up again despite injuries.  Tai Wu, “This guy…impressive.”  Kaito, “I haven’t lost yet! Unless I die you won’t survive!”  Tai Wu, “…if you really say so, I’ll fulfill it.”  Karean, “Wait…Wait a minute! This is going too far! Kaito stop just let this matter rest!”  Kaito, “Sen Arashi: Senpumaru!”  Kaito now holds his Katana in front of his chest, tip pointing out.  Karean, “Kaito!!! Stop it now! Senpumaru is too dangerous for your current situation!”  Tai Wu embraced himself for the next attack by this undying opponent, judging from the strange position of Kaito he knew that it wouldn’t be simple.  Kaito then looked at Tai Wu fiercely, with a light nudge of the Katana, Kaito ran towards Tai Wu and first sliced out with a circular motion; Tai Wu easily blocked it. But then, few more heavy circular slashes crossed out, pushing Tai Wu off. To Tai Wu’s amazement, Kaito was actually turning in circles with his Katana slicing in every revolution; it resembled a spinning top with blades sticking out from its side.  Suddenly, Flamer grew into orange lights and flames again.  Tai Wu, “What the…Great timing! Wu Jian swordsmanship: Random Move!”  Tai Wu then began slashing out without concern; he stood at a fixed spot, moving Flamer with fast paced strikes. It didn’t manage to hurt the literally spinning Kaito but the heat slow him down, the slicing of Kaito however did get to made a few cuts to Tai Wu’s torso. Gradually, Kaito began spinning slower while Tai Wu’s fiery strokes went faster; the fire blade eventually formed an orange semi-sphere figure, looking similar to a large shield protecting him.  Soon, Kaito’s spinning couldn’t last; Kaito ceased the spinning looking dazed. Tai Wu seized this chance and stops his move as well. Tai Wu then placed Flamer above his right shoulder, imitating a baseball bat, in a flash, Flamer changed back to its silvery form.  Feeling the sudden change in pressure, Tai Wu made his move, “Wu Jian swordsmanship: End of Move, Last Stroke!”  Gathering all his strength, Tai Wu swing the heavy blade and smashed Kaito, making the latter fly off and crashing onto the stonewall. The blow was devastating and powerful, Kaito lay there, unconscious and in a rather deplorable sight.  Shocked, Karean rushed towards the unmoving Kaito, several footsteps beyond the door soon ensured. An uncanny feeling overcame Tai Wu; he realized he has done too much. Uncertain of the current situation and confused with this turn of events, Tai Wu ran off leaving Karean and Kaito behind…escaping into the dark tunnel with Flamer. 
     

        
</post>
<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      ???, “Prepare yourself stranger! Sen Arashi! Dai Kai Sen!”  Being totally unprepared of this sudden strike, Tai Wu realizes he has no way of defending himself from it. He has seen Karean used it and understands that the impact would be too fast to counter.  Suddenly, Karean leaped towards Tai Wu and brought him down…just fast enough to evade the lethal strike of this servant. His strike is so powerful and fast, that it resembled a bullet train ready to crash onto someone…no even stronger than that. The impact of the stroke pulled Tai Wu and Karean along; even though they avoided it, they were pulled close due to the high pressure and vacuum created. The crossing air cuts through their face and exposed skin while throwing them off balance as well, landing quite a distance away.  After experiencing the blow, Tai Wu lift himself up from the ground…he saw the servant standing with his right hand bent forward now while left hand stretch to the back, exactly the same position as Karean after she did the same move. Tai Wu stood up and retrieved Flamer that is placed nearby, this opponent won’t be easy.  ???, “Missy!! How are you?! Why did you defend this guy here?!”  Karean is laying on the floor, gradually sitting up…looking quite irritated, “Kaito, you idiot! I told you not to enter without my permission yet you did! Do you even have any respect for me?!”  Kaito, “But Missy, I was told to hunt down any guy or intruder who enters your room, even if you allowed him to.”  Tai Wu, “No way…Karean! Is this true?”  Karean remained quiet…looking rather apologetic. Seeing this, Tai Wu cannot believe it, all the things and story about the future may be just a lie…everything is uncertain for him now.  Karean, “Tai Wu, don’t get me wrong! I didn’t mean for this! Just that Master demanded for your presence and wants you to enter my room…even though I didn’t know why she wants me to…”  Tai Wu, “And you just listen to that master of yours?! How can you!” He shouted furiously.  Karean, “I cannot help it can I? I came to this strange world, helpless and nobody to depend on…Only Master provided help to me! What do you expect me to do?! Master took care on me and was the only one to believe that I’m from another world, she provided information and help me to survive in this world! I can’t disobey her can I?! Plus, I don’t even know who you are…she just wanted your arrival, I don’t feel it’s an unreasonable request!”  Tears are starting to emerge from her eyes; the emotions, voice and all were real.  Tai Wu couldn’t rebut…he didn’t have the reasons nor the heart to do so; he wanted to apologize but couldn’t bring himself to.  Kaito, “Stranger! You made Missy cry, I won’t forgive you!”  Once again, Kaito displayed the Sen Arashi’s Dai Kai Sen posture. Tai Wu focused on his opponent now; if he wants to live…he’ll have to win. He lifted the heavy blade and placed a relatively defensive position, ‘Dai Kai Sen’ is a very offensive strike added with the inflexibility of Flamer, defend is the only choice.  Kaito, “…Prepare yourself!”  As fast as a lightning flash, Tai Wu immediately felt a heavy blow onto his blade. Kaito has gone for straight confrontation and the force is unbearable. Tai Wu was knocked off balance and was thrown backwards, slamming into a wall behind him. Particles of stone came off as Tai Wu fell forward; the impact has made a dent in the solid wall  Tai Wu, “Damn…is this it…”  Kaito, “Not bad…you can still stand.”  Tai Wu heard the compliment or rather sarcasm…He knows that as long as Kaito continues this move, he won’t win…yet he has no way to counter it. However, Tai Wu stood up again, his body aching all over.  Karean, “Tai Wu! Enough! You can’t win this.”  Tai Wu, “…”  Kaito, “Hah, Good man…one more time!”  Tai Wu tried lifting Flamer, but his strength gave up.  Tai Wu murmured, “Hah…Flamer…is that all?”  Karean, “Tai Wu…”  Tai Wu, “Flamer! Is that all you’ve got!” Flamer started glowing a dim orange light.  Seemingly gained confidence, Tai Wu grabs firmly onto the handle of Flamer, “Flamer, if you’re really my fate…then let this arrogant fool see what you can do!”  Abruptly, the orange light emitting from Flamer erupted into flames, leaving only the hilt as something solid to hold as Flamer turned into a sword of pure fire. Since the main body of the sword was transformed into a non-matter fire, only the weight of the hilt remained.  Now, Flamer was weightless…Tai Wu easily lifted Flamer and faced Kaito.  Tai Wu, “Show me your Sen Arashi, Dai Kai Sen again. I’ll counter it!” 
     

        
</post>
<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
          F.I.R - same name album   CD Album  Language: Mandarin  CD contents:  01. Intro: The path of finding dreams 2min 44sec 02. Fly Away 4min 35sec 03. Lydia 3min 57sec 04. Song of Wanderers 4min 00sec 05. Our Love 4min 45sec 06. Light 3min 33sec 07. Lydia Piano Orchestra Version 3min 24sec 08. Your smile 4min 19sec 09. Tarot cards 4min 09sec 10. Fairyland 4min 16sec 11. Revolution 4min 05sec 12. You Make Me Want To Fall In Love 4min 44sec 13. Continuation 0min 43sec  (Titles of some songs have been translated to English)  Review:  Before I bought this album, I considered and pondered for quite some time whether to buy it or not. I have only bought Japanese album and never would expect to buy an album of other languages despite being more literate in Chinese and English. Well, I have never regreted my choice of buying this F.I.R, a new band that received many top awards for their first album, this is the band which broke my tradition of listening to purely J-Pop.  An album with two introductory songs, one instrumental karaoke version tune and ten superb songs, it is an album which I definitely recommend (to those speaking chinese anyway...). The songs can satisfy verious moods, ranging from the fast moving "Light" to the sweet melodic "You Make Me Want To Fall In Love." Each song has an infectious tune that could make one sing along to it after hearing it for just a few times.  Something special which I heard in this album is that there is a rather heavy J-Pop base to it. Almost every song have a strong and heavy bass which is rather familiar to the English pop band "Evanescenes" and J-Pop band "Do As Infinity." One thing that prevented this album from scoring full marks is the lyrics. The lyrics are raher repitative, which I notice is a small problem with all Taiwanese songs.  But no doubt, it's a very good album.  Song by Song Review:  The first song...not really a song, it's an intro, an intro inspired from the movie "The Beach" (As they said in their album) It first plays a feel of nature like birds chirping, soon followed by voices from the three person in the band. After that, a great rock and solid tune finishes the piece. The second part is identical to one of Ayumi Hamasaki's song, showing the band's songs closely related to J-Pop.  "Fly Away", this song is surely one of the better songs in the album. It has a very infectious flow and absorbs the listener to sing along "Fly Away..."  "Lydia", this song can be said to be, in my opinion, the best song in this album. It's not only infectious but also a rather moody song. Having this great melancholy tune, it can easily stir the feelings of the listener.  "Song of Wanderers" or "Rurouni no Uta" as I liked to say...I can't help but wonder why isn't this song included as one of their publicized songs. The song is once again, addictive but it also includes this slight tribal feel to it which complements with the overall mood of this song. Highly recommended.  "Our Love", I love this song very much. Not only is the lyrics great, not only is the tune superb, this song is also a proof of how powerful the lead singer, Faye's voice can be. The overall mood is slow but nicely coordinated and portrayed. Added with an addictive rhythm, one of the better songs in this album this is.  "Light", this song unlike the others, have a very cheerful mood and a fast moving rhythm, very suitable for lifting the depressing mood off. However, this song doesn't have as much "grabbing" power as the rest.  Song number 6 is an instrumental version of "Lydia" played using only the piano. Nice and soft, makes a great karaoke to the song "Lydia".  "Your smile", a song in my opinion rather similar to "Light" in terms of mood and feel. But it has added a slight Afro essence to it which complements great with the song, thus making this song unique in it's own fashion.  Song 9, "Tarot cards". This song challenges on the voal prowess of Faye. Not the power but the flexibility on the singer. The lyrics are really well made and it even rhymes at times. You can hear on how sharply Faye changes her pitch in this song. It has a mysterious feel and brings to the peak of this song, catching the attention of listeners. Faye's voice is the main focus in this song.  "Fairyland", one of the more soft and light song in this album. It shows of the band's ability to be able to adapt with heavy and light songs. Not bad in my opinion.  "Revolution", an extreme and fast paced song. The heaviest song in this album, it eludes the strength of singer/guitarist Real and once again the power of Faye. It contains an enraged tune and is rather infectious. Don't worry though, it won't make one go furious. ^^  Song 12, the second soft and light song in this album, slightly similiar to "Fairyland", Faye's voice turns gentle and smoothing, added with a sweet and melodic rhythm, a great song for couples.  The last song, is actually an ending for this album but an intro for their next album. The guitar and keyboard is the main element here. Well placed in my opinion.  Overall, when hearing this album, it's as if the album is trying to relate a story to the listeners. It plays with the hearer's emotion and feelings with their widely ranged and placed songs. The songs are addictive and the tune would stick in your head for sometime after listening to it. Great album...and it's their first!  Extra: Although not much mentioned, Ian the keyboardist and producer of this band planned the whole thing for F.I.R for almost 2 years. He can be said to be the founder of the band as well...So to say, without him, there's no F.I.R.  Songs Recommended: Lydia, Song of Wanderers, Our Love, Your smile, You Make Want To Fall In Love.  F.I.R consist: Lead vocal - Faye Producer/keyboardist - Ian Guitar - Real  Score: 4.5/5 
     

        
</post>
</Blog>