<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A question that I've always wondered is this, What is the point of human existence? Sure we've built a mass civilization, and conquered the struggle of evolutionary technology (well so we think). Of course every individual has accomplished his or her own goals, and pushed themselves beyond the realm of their abilities to succeed in their own life. But when you get right down to it, what is the point for us being here? Why were we created? Why are we the only species known to man to be able to build mass civilization, and to conquer technology? Why are we superiorly intelligent to the other creatures of this earth? Why were we the chosen inheritors of these seemingly amazing abilities? Is life really just that bland, and straight forward? No, I don't believe it is. We're living in an enigma, one in which man has not evolved enough yet to understand and be able to solve. Some people say that life has no plot. I oppose. I believe there is some reason we're here, some reason not yet known...
    
</post>
<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Deep inside your puny mind, I have already spawned the seed of hell. You know not what you sew yourself into, soul. I shall steal it away from you, like the eagle clasps the snake, and my vengeance shall wreak havoc on your body. You will gouge out your own eyes, once you lie them upon the hideous nightmares I will cast upon you. You're limbs will no longer function as your own, instead, they will be under my command. Feel yourself bleed from the self-inflicted wounds I cause you to manifest. Your soul will escape your broken, lifeless carcass, and enter beyond the the realm of mans' thought, into the hell spawned torture I have awaiting for you. Behold, slave, I AM GOD.
    
</post>
<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I wish it was so easy to arrive and see thing a new with out the hell humanity has unleashed upon us, Is there any hope for the ones who do not belief. I cant feel, This life has elapsed my already thing seem so blunt, The reality of things is staring to kill me slowly I cant comprehend every threat. When will humanity accept its mistakes and see the faults. Time has eluded me I cant tell when its where. When is now. To me time doesn't matter I cant help but feel alone. In reality there are so manna issues of life and I cant cover them all, please feel free to help out, If you would like to become a member or the project Inferno leave your email and a small sample of your views on life</post></Blog>