<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Life sucks right now.  Pray 4 me.
    
</post>
<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        I   got alot   of sweet stuff yesterday! I got some new blades. Their tight. I got some clothes, movies, and other things. I was like so hyped all last night. My parents totally went ballistic that night though, because we watched the movie Phonebooth, and the language in it was pretty extreme. So they got after me for not being very affected by it. They said that I would probly say     F***     the next time I got tied off.I told them no I wouldn't, but they always think their right. Kind of annoying. So, for the most part I liked the movie, but I really could've gone without the post movie lecture. :( Anyways, I got alot of neat stuff and I'm so spoiled. So I recommend the movie Phonebooth, but    DON'T     watch it with your parents... they might start a revival of sinners rpenting for every bad word you've ever said in your life.       Kaisfer James/Tommy Boy/Jesus Freak/Kase/Bryant/Me     
    
</post>
<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, it's my Birthday!! I've only opened 1 present and it was from Karsen, because she was leaving and she wasn't going to be here for my B-day. I got the Daredevil movie! It's so awesome!! Oh, I got to open Kody's present to me too. I got two CD's... they were Andy Hunter, and a compilation CD. I can't wait till cam! It's gonna be alot of fun. Friends, Freedom, and God... what more do you need to be happy? And that's only the half of it. Lyndsey is going too. I can't wait... a whole six hour drive with her. How lucky I am!!! 
    
</post>
<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Only like ten or nine days till camp!!!!!!! It's gonna be soooooo awesome! Hopefully I can make things right with God there. I've kinda slipped up a little bit the last few weeks or so. I think Karsen is really mad at me, but when she read thatnote, Iwas just venting. Because alot of the time I'll feel hurt or something, and I just keep it in... and every now and then I need to let go and speak my mind. Know gets me either. I feel like a forribidden book... closed to the whole world and never to be opened to anyone. Sometimes I get so caught up listening to veryone elses problems I just can't share my own cause I feel like my problems aren't as bad as everyone elses. But sometimes they are...and they get locked shut in my mind. Than God for this Blog. even though it's onnnly my second entry. :)I'm sphyched to make things up with Karsen and get things back to normal. She doesn't get me. Noone gets me... and I'm notabout tostart that right now. Karsen... don't worry about it. K? We'll talk later. By the way if I can't talk to anyone aboutyou, then who can I talk to about the things I don't want you to know? You talk about me with people! W/E No biggie.  
    
</post>
</Blog>