<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I'm Salvatore, 26 years old and i'm a student.  My blog is under construction....so...i'm sorry..!! I'm working to make this blog look prettier....!! ..see you
     
    
</post>
<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      ...finally after a long wait...the summer holidays arrived..!! Today is my last workday...so tomorrow i'min my country...!! I'm leaving tomorrow at 5 a.m. whith my car.....and i hope to arrive at home about 4 p.m. o'clock....so it's going a very hard trip....but i'm very veryhappy to return because i'm meeting my family and my friends...!! Tomorrowmorning my friendFabio...will be getting a degree in medicine.....so tomorrow night we aregoing to celebrate this....!!! ....now i go.....and i wish you....good vacation...!!!! ....see you... 
     
    
</post>
<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
        ...it's very very late and i standin my office...because today me and Ciccio have a very hard problem to solve...!!      Outside it's getting dark....but if we dont solve this problem...we are going to be here all the night..!!      see you     
     
    
</post>
<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      It’s 11:00 p.m. o’clock………..!!!!!!!!!  ….hola my friends…..how are you? I’m very well because I’ve just finished eatingand drinking…!!!  Today it has been a very hard day…because I have worked too much….but I prefer this rather than doing nothing..!!  Fortunately it’s Thursday so tomorrow is the last working day…and I can to go to the beach…under a wonderful sun…with my friends….( and can write a lot for my blog..)…!!!  I would like totell the story about “  The Barese ghost ”.  In my previous article i told about the presence of a ghost in all the houses in Bari city….This fact wastold me by my baresi friends!!  In their opinion……when a house is under construction…..the first person that is near the first brickwork...(of course except the bricklayer)...will became the house’s protector….because his soul willbe forever in this house……so this big person will have a soul in his body and another in this house..!!!  ..it is a real protector….in fact one must never say bad things about him…!!!  I don’t believe this facts….but may be in my house…ther’s a ghost…because I have seen a lot of strange things…!!  …One day…may be…..I will tell you all about my house..!!!  …I’m going to my bedroom…because I’m tired….i hope not to find some unpleasant surprises..!!!  …see you..   
     
    
</post>
<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      After a long wait....Roberto Mancini is the new INTER coach...!!!
     
    
</post>
<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
        ..it's 6:00 p.m. o'clock...i finished to work and i'm going at home....but i remember a typical sicilian sentence: "...e fu accussì ca passà nantra iurnata..!!! ..see you..  
     
    
</post>
<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
        ….it’s Monday evening…and of course I’m at home…in the garden around the swimming pool …!! I would like to go out but I’m very tired….so I decided to stay here!!! Now I’m with Cecio and he is cooking…but right now  Ciccio arrived … of course …he is very very hungry.. he is going to the restaurant with Mariella…because tomorrow she‘ll go back to Sicily…so this is the last night that we are all together!! …there is a little problem…!!!  There are a lot of gnats that prick all my body…that makes me nervous. I’m looking for an inspiration…but today it doesn’t arrive…may be there is a lot of noise…I need silence to write!! Because I’m feeling tired….i remember a barese’s legend that a friend of mine told me. She told me that in every house there is a ghost…but he’s generally a good ghost…he is like a house protector…!! Sincerely i don’t believe it….but often  funny things have happened…!! About this funny things I’ll tell you another day!! …see you  
     
    
</post>
<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
        … i’m sitting in the garden with my friends Cecio, Ciccio and Mariella, Ciccio’s girlfriend. Cecio is eating a big stuck of meat and Mariella is drinking a glass of red wine…!!! ..but just now Ciccio is going to the bathroom because he has eaten a lof of rise and………….!!! I have also eaten a lot of rise but the consequences have been differently from Ciccio…in fact I’m writing this article for my blog. Is the 30th of June…the top of the summer…and we are here, in Bari City, under a beautiful strewn sky!! Sincerely i would like to be under my real sky….Sicilian of course…but I’m here because I have to work…!! “GRANDE SALVATUR…GRANDE CECIONE….GRANDE CICCIONE…MITICA MARIELLINA..!!! WE ARE A  MYTHIC TEAM..”!!..that’s a typical sentence pronounced when we are very very happy…and now we are very happy. To complete the beautiful team we miss a lot of friend: DAVIDONE, standing in Rimini since four days, and a lot of pretty girls…!!! … I finish to write because it is very late…it is 00:00 o’clock..and tomorrow I’m working…so I must wake up very early…!!! ..see you later   
     
    
</post>
</Blog>