<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well this will be the last installment for my report to Honduras. I have also include a album, see the attach  urlLink link  at the bottom to see more of my pictures!    As I embarked on this mission, I really didn't know what to expect. Many times I have heard missionaries and their stories about how exciting the mission field is, or how God is doing great miracles in their ministries. However, to be honest as I look back, my ministry was basically providing dental care, as I would've here in the states. Granted that the villagers don't usually get this type of healthcare, but somehow I felt that I was not doing anything special, especially for God. In addition, the language barrier was a big factor, as I couldn't communicate or evagelize to them. Thus, in some ways I felt that my mission was a disappointment or at very least, limited. But as I really begin to reflect of the things we did there, I realize that its not about me or my feelings. Rather its about God, and I see that we did extend God's love to them, as many of them did the same for us. By seeing how they worship during the services and gratefully giving their hearts to Him, sometimes I felt like they were the ones ministering to me! They didn't have much, but they gave sacrifically. It was amazing to see how God's work has no boundaries or barriers, and that He is faithful, just, and gracious there as He is here. Furthermore, I learn that the mission work doesn't have to be some far off place to make a difference, but every Christian have their mission field, in their home, school, work, as well as family and friends. And one of the best way of witnessing is by living our lives as a shining example and reflection of Jesus Christ! If we put everything in perspective, we are so bless here in the states, and we are all call by Jesus in the Great Commission (Matthew 28:16-20)"to go and make disciples of all nations, baptizing them in the name of the Father and of the Son and of the Holy Spirit, and teaching them to obey everything I have commanded you. And surely I am with you always, to the very end of the age." God is good and I pray that if you are ever considering any type of mission to just go for it, because He will provide and remember "God is not unjust; he will not forget your work and the love you have shown him as you have helped his people and continue to help them." (Hebrews 6:10) So as for me, I can't wait to go back and maybe some of you will join me next year! God bless. 
    
    
</post>
<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Honduras urlLink    
    
    
</post>
<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Last month I had the chance to join BMDMI (in my favorite link) down to Honduras, where we spend a week ministering to the people through medical, dental, VBS, and evangelizing ministries. Above is a picture of our clinic, and under my profile is me and one of the kids, they are all just so precious and sweet! Also, I have a video in which you can check out our mission  urlLink site . It was a great experience, and I really just wanted to share with you all some of the things I saw and learned. And hopefully through my testimonies, you may be encouraged and may even open to the idea of mission.  Honduras is a very beautiful country comprised of 2/3 mountain ranges, filled with green pines. Most of the people there are living under impovished conditions, but they were very kind and grateful. The predominant religion is Catholicism, so most have some idea of God and Christianity. Each week a new BMDMI mission team minister to a village to provide medical and dental care. This is because Honduras only has 2 main freeways, and the majority of the peopel have no way to reach a medical facility. In fact, most don't even see a doctor or dentist for years, because of the remote area they live from the city. So they are always thankful and happy to see teams come. Our village is called Atima, and it was a 6 hour drive from the mission home (mind you, most of the path is mountain roads). When we arrived we immediately setup shop. we had 38 people on the team, divide into medical, dental, pharamcy, ophthalmology, VBS, and  evangelizing ministries. Because I am a dentist, obviously my ministry was to provide dental care. Unfornuately our time was limited and because of the overwhelming number of people seeking treatment, the only service we can provide was extraction. The way we reach them was that they are require to attend services, which was provided throughout the whole day at the local church, and then they would receive a ticket to see us. Again, most of the villagers were so thankful and gracious, and the children were just so precious, that it made our jobs that much easier to accomplish. I never felt tired even though we work long hours, and we have to also thank God for His grace and strengh throughout the entire mission. There are just so many other stories and things that I can't describe to you all, unless you were there. But God was definitely there working, despite the fact we couldn't speak their language, we can see that God works the same way there, as He works the same way here. He is faithful and just, and His love is never ending. Even though most of the villagers didn't have much by our standards, it was easy to see that their hearts were filled with the joy and peace of our God! In my second part I will talk a little more about what I've learned.  
    
    
</post>
<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hi! Everyone    Thank you for visiting my blog.  This is my first time posting my own blog and I'm very excited to share my life and my views with you all. Also, I would appreciated any comments and inputs.  A couple of things about me before we begin, I am a doctor as well as a Naval officer. But more importantly, I am a Christian. One of the main reason why I started this blog is to reach out for Christ, and have discussion of every sort about this faith.  My goal is not to convert everyone that comes to my blog, but to present the gospel in its purity and truth.  In addition, I will be deploying to Iraq this coming fall and I would like to keep everyone updated on my journey as much as I can.  With that say in mind, I pray that God will bless this site and everyone that visits. </post></Blog>