<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      There has been a lot of speculation over John Kerry's possible running mates.  This is obviously a big decision for his campaign to make, but I'm not sure if it's going to really matter in the end.  Firstly, LBJ was the last vice-presidential candidate to win a state that the presidential candidate wouldn't have won on his own.  And secondly, while I hope I'm wrong about this, Bush is going to win in the closest thing to a landslide that this country can muster.  Landslide may mean 54% in this election, but that could be huge in the electoral college.    As much as I want to see George Bush out of office, I don't think John Kerry is the man the nation would rather rally around.  Dubya may act like a cowboy or just a plain old asshole at times, but I think I agree with The Daily Show's assertion that if John Kerry were to be played by someone in a movie, it'd have to be that tree from "Lord of the Rings."    Yeah, he's that dull and gloomy.  I know that it's everything the Republicans want us to believe about Kerry, but the fact is that he's dark, old, and talking about the Great Depression.  People want to be inspired, not told to fear.  We want to vote for someone rather than against.  We want an optimist not a malcontent.  We want a leader.
     

    
</post>
<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The film ends with a quote from 1984 and I have to admit it made for some very powerful cinema.  It was one of those moments I snuck out of my body and floated to the back of the theater and watched the audience watch the film.  Excited that the idea was being sold to us in the only form of communication we notice anymore... BIG and LOUD.  These moments are few and far between, but this was one of them.  I'm glad to be able to say I took part in this film during its debut weekend.  One of the first to watch, cry, and recognize very clearly that I had been there for maybe not the best film of the year, but by far the most important one.   
     

    
</post>
<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        IN BETWEEN SMART AND WISE | YOU AND ME ARE ALIKE    I was talking with my friend who is about to have a little baby girl. In fact, in a matter of mere days he will beboth ahusband and a father. We were talking about the interesting times we live in. This period where you still feel likea kid, but are forced to walk like a man. Babies, wives and that primalneed for a grill in your backyard.    We bothspent our time after high school trying to get smarter.We read, conversed, took it all in. We believed that's why we were here. To get smarter andexperience life. Then, it happened.We created a life.After that, you go through this period where you realize the difference between smart and wise. Then, out of nowhere, you've got a whole new goal in life.    Not that the two pursuits aren't similar, it's just that I look at them this way. To be smart is to embarrass your entire family during a game of Trivial Pursuit by handily defeatingthem despite their best efforts to team up against you. To be wise is to know what to say to someone who has just found out their husband has cancer.    While I'm nowhere near wise yet, I hope I get there someday. I know I may not be the smartest person I know, but I can hold my own. I just hope that when my day comes, I'm able to leave my son with a few words of wisdom thathelp point himin theright direction.    Another thing we talked about was the revelation you'll stumble upon earlyon inchild rearing, that your parents were  totallyfuckin' winging it . Youspendyour formative years believing that your parents knew everything.They had an answer to everyquestionyou asked. Then, you become a parent and those questions start getting asked of you. When you don't know the answer to why the sky is blue, youjust make up shit! It's unbelievable.    "Don't sit so close to the TV, you'll go blind." Bullshit. "You shouldn't swim for an hour after you eat." Bullshit. "If you're not good this year, not only will Santa not bring you any presents, he'll kidnap you and put you to work on the North Pole making toys for the good kids." Ok, they never said that one, but the point is that they were the same age we are. They knew roughly as much as we do. They had the same dreams, thoughts, and worse yet, financialshotcomings as we do now. They wasn't any owner's manual or special Magic 8 Ball, they were just winging it.    I guess when it comesright down toit, I hope we do as well as they did.  
     

    
</post>
<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       IN THESE EXTREME TIMES  | THE LEVEL OF DEBATE IN THIS COUNTRY  Many people that hover over either side of the political spectrum seem to be calling these extreme times.  On one hand, you've got the Democrats and various liberal groups calling for President Bush's head.  On the other, you have the Republicans and the virtue scolds of talk radio saying things like, "Michael Moore hates America."    Unfortunately, that leaves folks, like myself, stuck here in the middle of a country that is too divided to have any real debate.  Take "Fahrenheit 9/11" as an example of this.  I've talked to a lot of people about the impact this film has had.  Some have hailed it as the best documentary they've ever seen, or a call to arms, or whatever.  I've also had plenty of conversations with people who assert that it's all lies and that he hates America, etc.  The only problem I have is that so many of the folks that are speaking out against the film haven't seen it.  They are taking the word of some assholes on the Internet who've got all the server space required to spew their brand of "truth" to an audience that doesn't feel the need to fact-check it.    I'm not saying you have to have an abortion to know you're against them, but I'm saying that it makes no sense to me to only listen to or read those people's work that you already know you agree with.    I believe that the truth has a way of being found somewhere in between the extremes and that until we seek it there, all we'll find are two people yelling at each other louder than anyone can truly hear.
     

    
</post>
<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       FOURTH OF JULY  | OUTDOOR BASEBALL AND AMERICAN PIE  What a day for outdoor baseball.  We sat in the stands of Midway Stadium watching a double-header between the Sioux Falls Canaries and the St. Paul Saints.  The $3.00 PBR, the hot dogs, peanuts, frozen lemonade, all of it was perfect.  The length of our visit hinged upon our son Jack's mood which was suprisingly great.  He really enjoyed the between inning shows and contests.  He probably didn't get the show called, "Karaoke With A Real Japanese Guy," but his broken English version of "American Pie" was quite possibly the most patriotic thing I've ever heard.   After that slice of Americana, we headed back to the suburbs for a BBQ.  Matt's parents had us to their place for turkey, yet more hot dogs, and a host of noodle salads.  The meal was great, but couldn't compare to the most amazing fireworks show I've ever witnessed.  Although it was disappointing that Jack couldn't stay up for them, I had a great time watching them for the first time in years.  Sitting outside inside a mosquito-free tent, we watched the Native Americans of Mystic Lake launch the most colorful explosives I've ever seen.  Oh sure, the obvious jokes have to surface when watching what has got to be the most ironic display of patriotism in the country, yet, I have to give credit to the folks of that casino, they sure know how to throw a party.  As one of our hosts said, "I'll have to go over there and drop a few bucks into the slot machines to thank them." 
     

    
</post>
</Blog>