<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
         urlLink   
</post>
<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I’ve been partying a lot lately.  Not in the sense of shit-faced, singing and dancing to a Beatles impersonator, but responsibly stoned.  With Adam With Rosy; with just about anyone in a 2 mile radius around my body.  The other day, I caught myself trying to get contact high off my piss.  And here I was worried about getting crabs.  Most of it took place at the Friendship Festival, next to the police station.  Yes, let’s stress  next to the police station .  There was a plethora amount of people there.  I was charged down by a group of screaming bodies with cotton candy hanging from their jaws.  Ironically, that was after I scared an elderly couple when they were jay walking.  I’m turning right, and the bastard old man thinks he still has his youth.  I stop, he does the ‘soccer-mom-I’m a grandpa-arm” And screams ‘goddamn kid.’   Seriously?   As I was leaving the other night, I’m pulled out and some fat bitch in a minivan started honking at me.   Oh hell no.  I was going 15 in a 20, but now I’m sitting at 5.   This is what set her salty ass off.  “Fucking go you dumb ass!  Jesus Mother Fucker.”  I take another right, and the blob flies by still honking.  But the traffic is another story.  In the actual nucleus of this foul atom, the trash isn’t caged in a steel frame.  Think the smell of fair food, about 300 of the fat bitches that drive minivans and honk at you, a few rides and it’s hell (that tastes good) on earth. 
    
    
</post>
<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I’ve met a lot of people these last few days.  Adam, Rosy, Mike, Elyssa, the garbage man down the street; the cute one with the farmer hat and boyish looks; a friendly bloke lost in the intricate designs of a railroad tie.  Yes, tie.  I might’ve seen Jesus roam through a mall rat-crowd, had it not been for the boyish farmer/garbage man.   Adam’s a keeper.  Not in a serious relationship way, but in a friendly way.  Definitely, although he isn’t too shabby lookin’.    He was totally not the person I expected him to be.  It tells me not to judge a book by its cover, or shitty review out of a Reader’s Digest (Ex-Boyfriend, tee hee).    I remember that day in Denny’s when I first talked to him.  Holy shit I thought I was going to go up in flames.  I’m gay, I admit, but there is a difference between gay, and ghey.  I couldn’t stand to hear his flamboyant voice for another second.    That weasel face is  not  looking at  me .  Oh you are ugly.    Yeah now we’re cool, and he can look at me all he wants.  Now the weasel look is in, and the flamboyant act is out.  Add some bud, and the blunt is growing; I mean glowing.  
    
    
</post>
<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Sometimes I guess it just isn't enough.   As I sit here staring unemployment and high school drop out in the face, there’s only one thing she can say.  Get a job.   Yes, I know .  You’re finishing school.   Duh .  I don’t want to be this person forever; my face will change before you know it.    Waltzing above conversations, I overheard the question, “Where do you see yourself doing, how old, when you die?”  75 years, in my death bed.   Crazy .  Road loadin’, tomorrow.   Pft, you should’ve road loaded long ago.  You ugly .   I don’t see myself living past tonight.  That’s how I see things.  It’s all about here and now, and if not, well it’s obviously in the past or future, and there’s not much I can do about that.  Let me define “future.”  The future is college and an ultimate career, settling down, and smoking marijuana without a sack of guilt; according to the “big picture” folks.  When you look at your mother and go “I told you,” After all those long years, “I’m not a failure.”  You welcome the long anticipated expression, the one given so many times before.  You know the “you go first” look in a long line to jump off of a cliff.   Me?  Right now, yes the me right now; the future is this week-end.  Will I have a job?  Will I finish school?  Of-fucking-course.  Will I have a good time doing it?  Of-fucking-course. 
    
    
</post>
<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    ADD BRETT 
    
    
</post>
<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       A dream where everything is technical. Where emotion does not exist.  I watched a young woman break down on her knees. Her blood and sweat became one as her fingers trembled on the trigger. Her eyes were as empty as her skin was pale. That was the end of her story.  One death is all we do not ask for. One life is all we do. Breathing is a habit that everyone breaks.   I watched a young man acknowledge fear for the first time. His actions were spontaneous and beyond reason.   Through emotion, scars appeared on his eyes. He did not fit. This dream is technical. Emotion does not exist.  
    
    
</post>
<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
         I have been spending a surprising amount of time adding features and interface improvements to my web site. It's about Ragnarok Online, which is a MMORPG (Massive Multiplay Online Role-Playing Game), and covers pretty much every aspect of the game. Or at least it will, once it is officially finished and launched.          I'm leaving for S. Carolina tomorrow for a week. I'm verbalizing my blatant disapproval of the choice of  where  it is we're going, but I'm secretly anticipating it. It's not too far from Myrtle Beach, and... I would say I'll go to the clubs there, but it just won't happen. What's the appeal of a club anyway? Incoherent, sweaty bodies having the sensations of their life. I don't belong there. Looks like baking in the sun on the beach is where I'll be.      
    
    
</post>
<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       It took me around an hour to get to Dave's house. Matt wasn't answering his phone so I was pretty lost. Once I got there, we practiced a bit in his basement. Brook was there, (I guess she's the girl that Matt wants to get with.) she's really nice. So I talked to her for a bit afterward, then met up with Kristina, Adam and Jana, and packed for the show.    It was everything I had expected it to be. A small garage with a bunch of scenesters loitering around. The paranoia was getting to people and someone said that the neighbors were calling the cops. Big lie.    So a band plays, and then they play. Yeah, they is my band. I setup my piano in front of the amp, and hooked it up, but had no idea what we were playing. We had all thought improvising it would be cool, but I guess it didn't slip their mind that that requires communication. 20 minutes into I'm still "WTFing" to myself, trying to get their attention.    Needless to say, it was a very disorganized show. None of the mics worked, and our main guitarist couldn't show up.    To top it all off, I locked my keys in my trunk, and they're still in there right now. Ian drove Kristina, Adam and Jana back to their car, and then he and I went back to his house.     They were singing Bright Eyes at the show, (the band before us) and they weren't very good. Poor Conor would have to kick some emo ass if he heard the tone-deaf poetry pertruding from the garage.     
    
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       The band I'm in (Next Day Flight) is having a show today at this kid's house in Oak Forest.  I have no idea where it is, but I'm meeting Matt at Dave's house at three to practice.  Our main guitarist (Tom) can't make it, so it looks like we're just going to be messing around out there.  It all depends on how practice goes...  Well, I have to go and I hope to see some familiar faces there.  There's a few shows coming up too, but I don't know when those are either.  Don't you love how I know what the hell is going on?  Something tells me no one does.   
    
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Awww. 
    
    
</post>
</Blog>