<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Time now is actually 1.15am, August 1... Man time files, 1 month gone in a flash, and what was those supposedly sad days seemed so near yet so far away... Start of a new month, maybe its a time for a fresh start in my life ?  Headed to Atrium at 12.30 today... didnt actually felt like going down, due to 5 tests coming on Monday, but had to hand the T630 over to the buyer at 1... so well, the trip there was inevitable... Saw TL and Alex not long after I reached the entrance of the arcade. Handed the hp over, got $350, and stayed till around 3.15 when I went up with Aaron and gang to PS to see them play ID and WMMT over at Star Factory. Felt hungry after that, went for lunch at the food court downstairs. Aaron accompanied me.  Backed down to Atrium again, to see some matches going on, and headed home at 6.30, to come back and do some stuff, at least before I head on to bed. Dont wanna hang out till 11 plus and then walk home again, lol, my legs ! Shacked out !  Just had a chat with Aaron on MSN, wah his words, kinda slapped me awake.... self induced depression.... ahh man... I have to just try harder, to get out of this mess, and live my life as was before, waiting for that special person to appear.  Night. 
      
</post>
<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today was Founder's Day at school, lessons were on only for the first 2 periods, and after that, its a assembly for the mass prayer in the hall. This time in our own school hall. Not the primary school's. And my, was it cramped.  Supposed to go Atrium after the dismissal at 10.30am, along with KL. But, decided that I'll go shift a 6 speed shifter than a tiptronic one.... so I PS-ed him and followed Joshua and gang to SuperBowl for a few games first. After all, it was still early. Had 3 games, and I headed home to bath and get ready for going out later. Dilly-Dallied my time, then went out at around 3.05pm. Down at CS, I played WMMT the whole way, and finished at around 4.45pm. Tried to plan out a time plan in a way that if I catch bus 72 then switch to 53, I'll get to Serangoon MRT on time. But.... still reached the darn place at 6, and had to wait 40 minutes for *Mr Hia Big Shot* to come.. =P 10 minutes late worr~~ =x  So we met Tong Lam, and headed to Atrium to meet the rest of the bunch. Walked to HMV, then to Ngee Ann City. My legs were really tired and heavy by the time we walked back to Atrium... lol, save on bus fees... (-.-") Yeah, and we stayed at Baker's Inn to drink a cuppa tea and to chit-chat (talk cock to be more precise). Thanks for the treat of Iced Tea Aaron ! *lol*  11 .30pm, we left and took one of the last trains home. Alighted at Serangoon Station, and walked with Aaron all the way home. After all, the last bus was long gone by then, and a midnight surcharge on a taxi didnt sound too good, since its quite a short distance, and its so non-economical. Talked a bit on the way, and after we parted, I kinda thought of some of my problems (yet again.. yes I know...) while dragging two "logs" that were heavy like hell and still managed to clock a time of 15 mins to home ! What a suprise. &gt;. .  Ahhh anyways, I had to adjust the time back to put in this entry, time now is 2.15am, so yeah, I guess I'm in need of some sleep... Dont want panda eyes to come and look for me... Enough problems for me le.... ~.~" 
      
</post>
<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Plain day. Didnt go to school as mentioned in the previous entry, went to see doc at 10 am. Got a MC, stayed at home the whole day. Somehow felt tired at around 1.30 pm, caught a wink till 4 whenI woke up and bathed.   Looking back at this month, didnt have much time to rest other than today, I guess its a good thing. Feels so tired lately I couldnt do much of a thing. Didnt study much today, just slacked my day through. Boring.   Just wonder if tomorrow's after-school event would see me playing WMMT at Tampines, or ID at Atrium. I feel like shifting a H shifter so badly. And my time of 4'43 obviously doesnt show I'm that seasoned in this game.   Founder's day tomorrow, let off at around 10 am if everything goes well.. I'm lostin my mindagain. Now my heads feels empty, cant churn out any more words to fill in. Guess that concludes my day.   Thot for the day-"You must be at peace with your mind, then you can form what you really wanna say." - Aaron.  Funny why this entry sounded so emotion-less. Nite. 
      
</post>
<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Maybe its time I stop blogging about day events. Maybe its a time where I should let my inner soul take over me for just this period of time, as I'm writing this, to actually let whatever's out in this heart of mine, to maybe just ease this wretched fellow of his pains for a while. Thats what he always wanted, yes, Peace. It doesnt have to be eternity, nor it be a millennium. Just a while. Maybe at most a hour ? Really... just let him be oblivious to the surroundings, and happy, contented. Minds free from thetroubles that revolve around his life.And maybe its time I sat down, thought hard, and made a decision on what to do next.  I feel so lost now, even lost for words,having argued with my mum about certain things that revolve around the one thing that make people berserk, MONEY. All started about one handphone bill being too costly for the month. And so the madness goes. Its like the third time this damn year. Thoughts and urges of suicide kept flashing through my mind and body, it just makes me wanna jump up from my seat, and just make a beeline for the window. But no, I didnt. And so I just kept on arguing, with no solutions whatsoever. Just going round and round in circles.   Somehow my parents mean good, but expressed it in the wrong way. I can get this when I'm alright and in a collected mood, but when its heated up, I just cant get sober to anything. Damn.. harsh realities in life... is there nothing it has in store... man.. I've got love, studies, and now, money to worry about. This is some big time shit I'm going through man... Just hope everything turns out well soon..  Cried myself out when my mum left the room, kinda felt good and relaxed after that. Couldnt even vaguely remember when was the last time I've cried. So numb to everything, couldnt remember anything. Actually this entry wasnt what its supposed to be, but since I've cooled down, my head became empty and lost. Forgot even what I wanna say just now.  Due to this event, I've decided to see the doc to get a MC tomorrow, to buy myself more time to study for the 3 tests that is bound tomorrow. Physics, Chemistry, and Maths. Killer subs if you dont remember them. Couldnt study now, mood's changed and all, and I couldnt pick up any info from the stacks of notes and worksheets. Hope a good night's sleep will help.  Thats all for today. Peace out. Yes, peace. 
      
</post>
<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today it kinda felt good,at certain times of the day. Why is it always Tuesday thatthe most ups and downs occur ?Lol... I'm baffled.Became thoughtful in class at around 11am, just tried to re-organise the jigsaw puzzle I've had in my mind for coming to a month. Still, it didnt help matters. Only became messed up again, and didnt know why. Dont know how many times I have to go through this before I can get my thoughts straight again. ITs like... so many thoughts just flashing in your mind... all in a split second. Before you get what that signal is, another one comes. Its just so... disorganised.   Had a talk with the VP today. Complained about that stupid, egoistic idiot whos been giving me nonsense when I did not step on his tail at all. At least it kinda settled the chain of unhappy events thats been going on since school term started. So much so for being a nice guy and keeping quiet for so long. Didnt see any need to go fight it out with him... when hes just aempty nutshell and I dont see the help of knocking some sense into him when its only deaf ears I'm reaching onto... Ah, to hell with him. Geta life, take a hike.   Had a shocking surprise when the geography test papers were handed out.. All the guys who were the usual passers failed big time, getting scores of 3 to 5 out of a max of 15... And I, gota 9/15 for it... and that made me the only passer out of the whole class. Even William, coming in second, missed half a mark for passing.. with only 7....  Which leads me to think... maybe it was just a stroke of luck... maybe it wasnt the full understanding I had which lead me to get this kind of mark.. I dont even dare to think I can even get a good mark... But looking at the content which I wrote, somehow, it just seemed I've understood it well... Why are there so many things that make me confused...   Went with Kun Long to Kovan, ate at Yoshinoya, since we had the discount coupons... but somehow my bill amounted to $8.50... guess that didnt help much... Then we walked around Heartland Mall, seeing comics and CD's. By the time we went out of the building, it was drizzling again, and it was extremely humid. I stood there, then slowly but surely I began to feel sticky and stuffy... yucks. The weather at that time.... really sucked.   Got home, bathed, saw Aaron's blog. Well he really is in the dumps.. again. Not surprising but, somehow, I feel hes kinda taking it too rough. Some people just choose to ignore the situation, and escape it from reality. On the other hand, he, took it upon himself, the suffering, the pain. Hes just carrying it all by himself....As he said,in the rainy hour, he shall lift up his worn sword, with that little strength he has left, with a body thats bruised and battered, andface up to the dragon thats ready to attack him anytime. Well I really hope he can get back to be himself again, and if u do see this, please, cheer up man. It just sucks to see myself in this state already.. and I definitely do not want this to happen to any of my friends... I know how it feels, and your state is worse than mine.. I do hope you canpick yourself up, and be yourself again. Soon.   Haha, I still remember what Mr. Denis Koh said to me the last time we chatted, "Practise what you preach". Told him those words he tried to encourage me with, were the ones I used on my friends, cheering them up, goading them to go on. I give advice from my POV, making my friends look at it from a "bright" side.But when it comes to my case, its a worse case scenario...a whole newcase to speak of again.I couldnt control it, goes into a total disaster, not knowing what to do.. and when I yearn for someone to be by my side at that time.. there is none. Me, myself,and my own thoughts. No POV's from other people. Bleah.   Ah well, still, things are as they were, nothing's changed, the same old me, in the seat, facing the PC, and blogging my stuff out. "People only remember bad things, good things dont last and slip by easily".   Nightz. Benedict signing out. Its been a thoughtful day.  
      
</post>
<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today was a bad bad bad day. Some unpleasant things happened, along with the prediction that Lucien helped me to predict... today WAS a bad day for me, in this week. Well... felt tired again... in class... somehow Monday Blues really can get me all the time.. just cant seem to run away... Ah well, the habit of sleeping at 11 pm... lol.. and I slept late with some tossing and turning on the bed before I settled down and reach slumberland...  Had my heads on the table (again) after recess, couldnt pick up any more spirits to really take the pen and write some stuff.... just wanna sleep... time passed by real slowly then.. jeez.  Hmm... after school I just headed home, didnt have some interesting stuff to blog today, it just seemed very okay, but marred by unhappy events in the morning. Sigh. Just in a dilemma.  Really, whats there to say today.  Benedict out. 
      
</post>
<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      As usual, per Sunday its a tuition day.. not that worth mentioning... but hey, its a real significant event on my Sundays.... haha. After tuition,I kinda had lunch, then sat on the sofa watching TV... until 3.30pm,a wave of tiredness hit me... and I slept on the sofa till 5.45pm.   Had a bath when I successfully dragged my body into the shower, and felt kinda refreshed after that. Still, a tingling blurness hung on to my senses...Then began doing my stuffs when Aaron called me up, not so long after. Time was about 6.20pm.. and he asked if I wanted to go eat out at around our area (Kovan, Hougang..)   So I agreed, still somewhat surprised and kinda glad someone actually called me out. And not too far at that. Yeah, so headed to the bus stop opposite PLMGSS to meet him, and we walked to Kovan.. had a little chat on the way, too. Time somehow passes by quickly if you have someone by your side talking to you...   Decided to get a plastic cover for my newly bought T630.. after all theblack cover cannot be taken out and washed, so i decided that a cover over it might be better... dont wantthe oil on my face to stain the hp... I do wash my 6230 sometimes.. thanks to the Express-On Covers... its just a breeze. Wash and dry. Thats it.  Although the guy took a long time to find the cover, I feel its great that its just $2, and I'm planning to buy another1 for my tuition teacher, and 1for myself as a extra cover (my neighbour didnt want it, he got the pouch liao)   Headed to Hougang Mall to test out the FDI bought from Aaron, met WanXiang along with his girlfriend I think. Argh, the FD wheel locks like no tomorrow ! Straightways also can wheel lock, and have u eating the wall... but its a good car overall... if I can counter the wheel lock, I suppose. Had a few battles with a Evo 4 with my half tuned FD... its gay how the Evo 4 dusted me on Irohazaka... &gt;.  Played till 8.15pm when me and Aaron headed to KFC to have our dinner, and talked a bit on my problems again... Well, what was not so surprising was that what Aaron said, was what everyone said. Studies first.Love, later.How many times did these words enter my ears... Still, my mood gets the better of me... and something good will happen if I'm in a good mood... vice versa. Anyonecan tell mehow to overcome this ?   So... it was home after that, took 62 home.. along the way Aaron showed his picture collection on his hp to me... damn ! Walking multimedia centre !! Powder-ful 6600.... haha. Will try to have him send the pics to me sometime... hehe.   Yeah thats about it, asimple day, but rather fun. Will be sleeping later, since I caught a wink this afternoon, and I've left quite a bit of homework to do for tomorrow... yeah, I expect to be sleeping at around 1.30am ? Haha... gotta catch up on my work.. otherwise the new week will have me exhausted... and left behind..   Night peepz ! and.. Happy birthday to Karie ! (Lol... forgot to wish it to her today... so yeah, I'll just leave it here, although she cant see this...)   
      
</post>
<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Guess I somehow woke up on the wrong side of the bed today. Had a spinning dizziness in the head when I opened my eyes at 9.30 am. Called up Whymobile at 10.10 am, they dont offer the door to door deliveryfrom 9 amto 9 pm anymore, since they're short of manpower, and the only available times are after 6 in the weekdays.. gotta take note next time... In the end decided to go collect the phone from them at the outlet, since its just above Zone X @ Atrium. Besides, he offered a further $5 cut on the price if I did so... lol, why not ?   Dilly-Dallied my time from 10.20 to 12 noon... played CS, listened to music, whatnot. Then decided to bath and then head on down to Atrium, since I'm meeting my friend there. Further broke the record of Steve's 86 from 2'47'162 to 2'46'366... haha... this is just too great... 1 sec down... And somehow, with that,I feel that my touch of IDAS is coming back soon.. didnt feel afraid of the oncoming corner, or that hairpin. Just tackle it with all my might. Yeah.. so I suppose I should be able to be back on form by the middle of next month... Hope the mood can stay away (at least for a while)while I'm driving out my best...   Headed to CTP to meet Yap and gang, played ID from 3 to about 7... didnt really care too much, the mood started to kick in, but its kinda mild. Felt kinda sian around 6.. didnt get too active after that. Followed Steve and Kun Long to Toa Payoh, had our dinner and headed to Toa Payoh Entertainment Centre to playlast few rounds of ID.. Irohazaka all the way... then it was a cab ride home.   Reached home at around 9.15, bathed, and felt kinda hungry after that. Had instant noodles cooking now.. gonna eatit once I finish this entry.   Hmm.... I guess thats about it for today, what else was there to be said ? I doubt it....   
      
</post>
<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Had a very happening day today. Had some ups and downs at different times of the day. Felt good and bad. As usual, got mixed up again while trying to sort out some things in my mind.   Didnt expect anything special to happen while in school today, but during recess time, when I just walked out of the classroom, Mr Denis Koh, our DM, saw me and signalled me to go over. I was thinking, hell, I didnt pull off any stunts these days wad... why he wanna see me for ? My doubts were cleared when he just patted me on my back and said 'how are you?' Became kinda surprised and glad that someone did notice my existence... lol~.. I replied that i was okay, not too bad, but feeling down lately (as this blog mentions)... So he asked why and well, it kinda became a personal talk in a corner, then when people were walking by, they all had the same idea that I've stepped on his tail.. the kind of stare they gave me... just felt so funny.. well but it wasnt unusual la, expected de.. so.. just like that lor.. Told him some personal stuffs, and he, too shared his stuff with me too.. and I felt that my talk with him wasnt so important, so much so he shoved off all the students that had to meet him, and just dismissed them, without giving them a piece of his mind.. I'm the saviour i guess... lol~ Yeah, so I might look up the DM or VP (they are a couple FYI) these days... didnt really seem to have anyone who had a listening ear le... is there ? Did I miss out anyone ?   Went to Sherman's house after that, took Jarael's hp to go trade in.. guess what ? Out of stock still.. and the price for the T630 still cant be lowered, and out of fun, I queried a Nokia 6230 cover, the guy said $45, but i already located one shop that sold it at $38... peculiar, seems to me they aint doing proper business...undermining some stuff maybe ? Hate this...  So, kinda decided on the vendor i'm gonna get my T630 from,Whymobile is the one. Calling them up at 9.15 am tomorrow, and get a delivery to my door beforeI head out to meet my friends to go out... At least got some time to test it out.. haha.. hopefully got discount, since I'm a repeat customer...Went home after that...   Then, didnt really expect this, but, BUT,I still went out, this time to Atrium, to play some ID with Kun Long. I successfully broke Steve's record of 2'47'446 on the 86 Trueno... Got it down to 2'47'162, but felt very happy with it le... i dont really expect a top form, since I'm just beginning to stand up again.. mood is still sad and bottled up, althoughI did let out some today.. to the DM.. he behavedlike a real friend to me.. not like his fierce usual self...  Went up to PS to eat dinner, and then headed down to Kovan to get some stuffs.. deodorant for Kun Long,facial wash for me... Neutrogena ? KL said it was kinda good, so I decided to give it a try... den headed to Comics Connection, bought a keychain (only at 50 cents, kinda cheap)and aNissan GTR R34 1/61 model by Tomy.. will take a pic with the T630 tomorrow, hehe... my 6230 cant focus, or rather, capture it that clearly... its only good for far shots.... so .. yeah, thats about it... Time we went home was 9... so, took a bath, and here I am, blogging this for the day events... Kinda happy today lor, andthat's pretty much about it lor...   T630, here I come !! :D   
      
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Great day i had today, man. At least it was a lot of joy and fun throughout the3 hours we had at Seoul Garden Tampines Mall. Although the food wasnt so good, the people who turned up were.. =)  But first off, let me blog down the events that happened in school today..   Everything was usual, when during Physics lesson, Mr Ganesh didnt come and instead the VP, Mrs Maria Koh, came in to talk to us.. kinda a inspirational pep talk and a goal setting one at that for us... she told us to be 'what you want to be', must pass the exams and at O levels.. since its a milestone for us in our career life.. She says that we, the retainees, have character, and the spirit to face the syllabus again, and to come to school, only to see that the people in the class changed, but the level hasnt. Still 3. Focusing on my studies is also a point that she stressed, but hey, with my current status, what can assure me that I can pull it off well this semester ? Yeesh, as if things werent going smooth enough, the problem of love has to come knocking at my door this period of my life...   Yeah... and that left me thinking about what i should do right now, to be a lonely driver, or go find one... but its a uphill task, I can say. Became a lost soul again, I might go approach her if i need someone to pour out to, after all, she says her door is always open, and she'll be all ears if anyone has any problem. Hmm.. it aint peer to peer after all... Always an adult coming into the picture in my wretched life...   Headed home after school, and rushed to bath and get ready to go out to Tampines Mall, where we met thebunch of girls and 2 guys... their 'ah pa' and 'ah gong'.. lol... but i'm the oldest there... -.-" Went into Seoul Garden after that, didnt eat too much, i still had a loss of appetite.. but we talked a lot, and i enjoyed it very much. Like i said, i kinda hate boredom nowadays, since it ignites my thinking of my problems yet again.... Used to walk aimlessly on long stretches of road, but now, if I have the time to leisurely walk over a substantial amount of road, I would definitely think of something these days.   Played Final Password (in chinese la) after our meal, the one that gets the number that the judge sets, he/she gets punished.. in this case it was a real exotic cocktail of desserts, and a plate of meat that is marinated with BBQ sauce, Chili, Chili powder, and wasabi. The dessert had raw egg, ice, attap seeds, jelly, and some other stuff that those girls wouldnt reveal... and basket, I didnt even get punished de, until the last round, guess wrong number.... :/ haha.. nvm la, i got tactic, swallowed the food quickly, by the side of my jaws, and thus didnt get the full scale hotness of the chili and wasabi... whahah... see themchoking and blowing, i kinda feel they kinda dumb... one of them took 2 mins to swallow down the piece of meat, but it already took him full scale le.. -.-"   Went to the hp shop to change the 3100, to a T630. Damn, the price of $280 was a white version.. Black one costed $330... felt like cheated lor,Whymobile selling at a nett price regardless of colour.. blah. Will think about getting from that shop. Cheaper somemore. $320 nia. See how tomorrowlor. Besides, Whymobile offers door to door deilvery service, that darn shop doesnt... haha.. chances are high neh...   Yeah that kinda concludes my day... Met Joei again today, felt a sense of attraction to her.. I just wonder if its my heart or my brain... trying to find someone only, orI really like her.. Man i dunno.. Wild shots in the dark ?   Can anyone give me a guide as to what I'm supposed to do... The aimless and clueless me is really in a spot...    
      
</post>
<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This morning kicked off with a moderate downpour.. felt cool though.. and there was a traffic jam on the way to school..   In school, I laughed a lot today. Was like going to go nuts anytime man... lol. We were so 'patriotic', singing national day songs during geography test ! haha.. couldnt remember whats the other one, I laughed too much, it slipped off my mind... =x   Yeah, was a kinda good day for me too.. sunny.. hehe. That stupid idiot came to school, but didnt disturb me or what... and i stayed back after school to do library duty for the first time ever since school started... lol, kinda slack sia.. but i did do my part ! =D  Didnt have much appetite at dinner just now, just ate a few mouthfuls and i pushed the plate away.. don't know why too...  Tomorrow after school, I'll be off to Tampines Mall to celebrate the girls birthday.. Joei's falls on today, Jarael's tomorrow, and Karie's on Sunday.. wah... all like very close.. den i spent a big bill on my gifts... T_T lol..  So thats about it, I'll be buying a gift for Jarael tml, in the form of topping up the money needed for trade in for a new X430... she wanna change the colour.. so yeah, forgot to buy gift, guess this is the best for her le.. haha.  Looking forward to tomorrow, and waiting for that someone.... 
      
</post>
<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Still somewhat having a trace of that happiness i had from yesterday....side effectperhaps ? Lol~ The whole dayI felt kinda good, and was very active, hehe. Had a rather brightened day..    Somewhat that idiot who did something unpleasantyesterday was suspended today, when he didnt admit to anotherwrong he did... i'm so damn happy he is suspended, to hell with that loser. Smooth day today. Loved this day at school, haha. Somewhat the thoughts in my brain didnt surface, and my mood stayed clear the whole day... guess this should be a rarity in a thousand days ? Lol.    Went to tampines to check out the price and the offer for EA classic.. basket, Challenger didnt have the offer around.... damn.. ended up with Kun Long buying his CD-Rs and DVD+RW... and got a CD for Joei's birthday... hope she likes it when she gets it... :)    Relatively short entry...I suppose.. but hey, its a contrast to all the other posts way back... the mood's different, yeah ? hehe... Yeah, thats for today...    Peace out. :)   
      
</post>
<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Just when I was about to search for my geography notes and head to sleep, a call came from my neighbour. It was their mum at the phone, and she needed help from me to print something from a floppy disk.  Qi Xiang came to my house , and i got ready the stuff for printing. Printer, paper, and the com. I slotted the diskette in, but found it to be unformatted (faulty) and thus could not access the data inside. Qi Xiang went back and I followed shortly after. Went over to QX's house, and saw their mum's friend there, along withherhusband and daughter popping her head over the door. I saw her for the first time, and had a better glimpse of her when her family walked out the door.  My.. she looked good ! She was the kind of girl I had in mind ! The looks.. so nice and innocent... ! Haha.. Bleah. =P  As she went out, i noticed she was kinda sad.. I think its due to her compo being lost.. I felt kinda sad too, lol, since i wasnt too big a help to her. =S  I just wonder if she'll come again.. with her new diskette and ready to print again.. hope i can get more chances to meet her.. perhaps fate is creating a chance ? Then again.. naw.. doubt she'll fancy me.. hmm... I wont push it ba.. like Aaron said, 'Unlimited amount of chasing will get you the opposite effect instead'. Moreover, I dont even know her at all..So, I'll leave it all to Fate...  This event really had brightened my day ! (or night :p) I'm happy enough to have seen someone so stunning ! Thanks God !  Hee.. a good night's sleep awaits me..... :D  
      
</post>
<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Didnt feel too good today. My day was ruined by some idiot who did something unpleasant which i would not say... and then i was like fidgeting the whole time in class after that. Well, it at least kept me from sleeping, haha. More or less got something into this empty brain of mine.    Was supposed to pop by at CS today. But didnt go as a result of Sherman and me couldnt accomodate to each other, he wanted to go play, but i didnt want to, since i, as usual nowadays, couldnt pick up the mood to play. Lost the interest. I justwanted to have a relaxing walk aroundthe two malls, CS and TampinesMall.To top it off, i didnt bring my home clothes either. Ended up going to Superbowl with Benjamin, Joshua, James and William. Sherman went to AMK Zone X to play, alone. Man, hes strong on these stuff, no go and he meant it. Bugger.   Saw Ben and Josh bowl, along with William. Spent my time till 2.30pm when we went to Mac's to catch a bite. Saw Kenneth there, wasnt kinda pleased to see him.. Sheesh. Went home after that, and so tired till i nearly fell asleep on the bus.. although it was a very short trip. Dont know... this fatigue kinda striked on me nowadays.. causing me to doze off into half conscious state whenever i'm inactive.. what's happening...    Another point to add is that i just found out and realised this.. after reading Aaron's blog..that I'm not good at expressing myself. At least if he's got something up his mind, he'll have a reaction to it. Cry, throw temper, whatever. But me, just quiet and moody. Seldom cry nowadays, dont know if i've lost the feeling to even cry.    Yeah i guess thats it for today, watching my favourite Channel U show where u gotta search around for some prize cards.. Basket... one of theparticipants... kept all his 3 cards hidden at home, none was found, and after that at the mall, he got 7 out of 9 cards... total amount of prizes amounting to $10077.. man hes nuts, kinda greedy too...after that i'm doing my homework... felt quite energetic today. Wonder why.   Hope tomorrow will bea finer day. Benedict signing out. 
      
</post>
<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Stayed at home the whole day. Had tuition, and nothing else was really that noticeable after that. Just a normal day, still couldnt pick up my mood to do some stuff, i guess its really time i stood up myself and really head on to a fresh start.. things cant go on like this forever... i've still got my life to live, and my commitments. i cant let this mood of mine dominate me on and on... its just not right..  Messaged Aaron today. Was supposed to meet him up today at wadever time hes free, and was looking forward to a soulful chat with him. at least to let out my cooped up emotions, that i had in me coming to 3 weeks now.. Alas, this was not to be, when he didnt reply any of my sms-es, man, its like... if he couldnt, then just tell me la... not as if i was gonna flame him off for not able to.. just let me know... jeez. with that i stayed home the whole time, listless and disappointed. Hope i could get him out sometime nextweek,the bottling up felt kinda stuffy. At least in my head.  Gonna do some homework for now, and well, maybe head off to CS to buy another EA Classic, Renegade. I dont even speculate i might play at the arcade, i somehow spent too much on the outing yesterday. So, yeah, i guess thats it, dont know what to say too. Lost for words.  And so i keep on waiting.. for my loved one to come to me... 
      
</post>
<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Just thought i might do a little bit of blogging before i turn in to bed. Today was a rather memorable day, having met a lot of peepz in the local ID scene, and had a mass makan session with them.. it was very enjoyable.    Met Aaron at the arcade at around 1.30 pm. he was playing some ID, so i thought i might go play some Wangan before i go with him to the second floor, where Seoul Garden is. met KC, Channon, Wayzik, Gwen, and a lot of other peepz... after that we went in and just whacked the food hard.... we took up a total of 5 tables, and were like so noisy throughtout the time we were there. Enjoyed the food, the self grilling, and got a little oil splats on my hand, and had great conversations with them.. even though they just knew me. Loved it. They were very friendly and a great bunch to hang out with.    After that we proceeded down to the arcade again, to play Wangan. i successfully completed my second round of story mode, and is on my way to full tuning my R34, wads left is 1 more round of playing the CPU, and i'm ready to take on challengers. My card name changed to The Steel Wind, and it sounded very strong, haha.    Headed to Atrium after that, and played some ID. As usual, i couldnt break any times. felt vexed at the way things are going... wasting money and couldnt see results. bleah. After that some of the peepz went up to see the movie King Arthur, but i stayed behind and watched all the way to around 10.15pm, and went home after that. Got to know Zheng Long, a member of X-T who lived very near me... just 2-3 blocks away.    Told my mum how i felt these days, she just said the usual stuff, try hard, dun waste money. and get urpriorites correct. i knew it all long ago. just that, i didnt have the heart, the mood to do it. Well i guess i have and got to pick up from where i left off, otherwise this semester, i'll be darn screwed big time.    After meeting Aaron for the first time today after talking to him so much on MSN, this is the first time i had a meal together with him. Or rather, same location, but 3 tables away. I kinda guessed that he was not wanting to sit with me due to the empty seats (i did feel a little sense of pung seh, when i hey-ed to him and he didnt look back, but i wont blame him) , and it would be occupied my Melissa and Zhi Sheng... the couple now, but the girl Aaron lov-ED. I felt he became kinda more depressed and disappointed when i told him how Zhi Sheng (Shiro), told mel that he was staring at her... He did tell me later at atrium, he just couldnt believe it. The words Shiro said.And yet, he cant do anything about it.    This situation was kinda confirmed when about now, i've seen his entry for his blog today, and it was a entry full of emotions. His phrase, '   I know I'm not any handsome suave young guy girls would fall for, but certainly, I'm human too. I've my emotions. I know my limits, but please God, stop fooling with my life anymore. I'm on the brink of death and destruction.  ',really pulled out what i've got to sayin this period of my life, and thanks to u, Aaron, i certainly didnt know what to type, but this, is really my point, that i have in my heart. Thanks a lot for putting it into words. I've been a bit too messed up these daysthat my previous entries was all kinda single-worded (i did notice it.. but my vocab couldnt pull anything else out) , darkness, lonliness, and all.. i know my english isnt as good as yours, and i, definitely couldnt express it out better than you. Thanks again.   Guess thats about it, had some time to think of stuff on the way home, on the bus, and felt verymessed upabout it. Still,nothing's been going right, and darkness is all around. What can i say, thats how my life is now.    Night peeps. Benedict out.    
      
</post>
<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      One of the moderately good days i had during this time of my life. i was occupied all day, and didnt have much time to think abt the matters i had... although i had time to sort out my feelings during assembly time and on the bus to AMK Jubilee..  Inchemistry class, Sherman told me about what happened before he slept with Bernice .. i was like... omg. her parents were like so open... and Berniceherself too, popping a question of 'when are you going to have *** with me...' , really contrary to her shyness of meeting pple... lol..    Still, i am envious of this perfect pair... i still wonder, how could i have made good friends with a guy who has been so fortunate to have his dearest, compared to me who lacks it... big time.. haha... fate really baffles me.    Went to Jubilee Zone X to play some ID.. didnt run too good a timing, but i was still contented. i just wonder when my form will come back.. all that i've been striving for, working for.. slogging it all out for... just gone.. when i get this kind of bad mood swings, once in a while. i suppose its the third time this year, heck, does anyone give a damn...    Perhaps few pple know the way i am, and i seldom disclose it, i mean, i dont wanna shun pple off when they hear that i got some sad thoughts, depression, and all the crap... i've always thought of other pple to be happier than me.. emotionally... i've a stable cash flow.. for going out and stuff, but.. for the things money cant buy, i've nothing by the name of love. Aaron told me today, certain things just cant push it, unlimited amount of chasing may get me the opposite effect instead. then again, we control our destinies.. so do i go push it, or do i sit on the fence, waiting for something to happen ? i dunno... i'm lost.    To pick up from where i left off before this started would be a tall order... it just seems that i've been given a mission to jump into a black hole... and finding nothing inside.. coming back up seems impossible ATM... guess i hope i'll not linger for too long before a ray of light comes shining in, and i can walk into it.. with the help of a kind helping hand.    Everyday i claim that i neededhelp from someone, hell, couldnt i just be independent ? things would still be the way they were, and the world keeps on spinning. the fact that i'm feeling down probably didnt matter to other peepz, since its my own private business, and it doesnt affect them, too.    Living here WAS a nightmare, IS a nightmare, and ALWAYS it is. Just felt this way. Let me free..   
      
</post>
<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well today wasnt as bad a day as it seemed, at the very least i felt kinda normal today. my heart felt empty. no bad emotions whatsoever. on a scale of 0 to 10, i'll rate myself 5... its darn normal.. i dunno, but when its always on the way home, i'll have that period all to myself, oblivious to the surroundings to me, and just sorting out my feelings for the day in school.  School isnt as enjoyable as it really seems.. to me, its just a place where i have to slog my guts out for half the day before the cold rounded metal rounded piece of metal rings, and a crowd of happy guys rushing out, all set to head back home, or just hang out, have some fun, before heading to the comfort where they always spend surfing, watching TV... all the things that teenagers can do at home.  Maybe Aaron was right, one tends to be the person he is behind a face. And that face, is the thing i'm looking to right now. the PC. I'm my real self here, having all said the stuff i've been keeping inside my hearts. All this blogging seemed to have freed me a bit from my bottling up of emotions, words, and expressions. Saved me from making things into a bunch of mess, and then just worrying and thinking of someway out. Do i really have that much to say? I mean, i'm quiet and all in school, with friends, and parents. But, in this blog, says a thousand words i would like to have poured out to someone. A listening ear, which i couldnt find.  These days the rain had the coolness going, despite i still havent the mood to pick up from where i left off before the holidays. Managing to scrape 3 passes out of 6 subjects isnt the scene where i would like to be caught in.. and i very much fear what i can pull off this semester, with all this stuff hitting me hard.  So who said i was vulgar. Who said i was nutty, crazy, and cracking jokes, funny or lame. I didnt really mean what the heck i'm talking about, they just came out of this mouth of mine. I'm lost... maybe my life has once again shattered itself into pieces that i'll have to try glue it back.. and the moment it didnt hold it all together, the low tide will once again approach me, and be with me for a period of time it feels contented, and i can get on with life. Move on, no one's gonna wait for you.. Time doesnt. Tide dont. Friends neither. The special someone... i have none.  Having the house all to myself tonight was a really great idea, no parents nagging for 1 night. But it really pulled the innermost tinglings of my hearts out into words i tried to type, but still, they just stayed as if they were parasites. Sad, but true.  She didnt give much of a reply after all, well maybe she wasnt interested at all. Hey, with someone of my quality, i find it common that loneliness will be here to stay. At least it did, for 15 coming to 16 years of my life. Worthless me.  Will anyone tell me what to do.... I'm in darkness trying to find some kind hand to lead me out....
      
</post>
<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today was kinda cool too, with all the rain coming thru and all.. didnt run today, was sick and had a bad cough.. at least the MC convinced the PE teachers...  Everything was kinda normal in class, nothing went too bad, until Sherman told me Joei said i was "very cute", after that day when we went to see Spiderman 2. i was like har ? (-.o") got ger fancy me ? or my looks ? wow... wad a surprise.  Before that the medicine i took had its drowsy effects on me.. i kinda laid my head in class the whole day... but hearing that, i kinda had a sudden burst of energy and vitality, dunno why.. haha.  Anyway, had a conference for 1 and a half hrs in the afternoon around 4.30pm with Karie and Sherman... i was, haha, the listener most of the time... was kinda fun tho.. hee..  Messaged Joei at around 9.30pm, she didnt reply.... ahhh~~ i was expecting her to ! den just now sent another one... still no reply, so i tot i'll just leave it up to her ba, to reply or not.. but i sure hope she does ! lol.. feel kinda funny now.. excited, yet disappointed. well, i guess its up to Friday whether i'll see her or not... den can talk more to her i suppose.. if she doesnt dao me, that is..   I'll be looking forward to your reply.... :)
      
</post>
<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      School was kind of okay today, with little crap in my class today.. they began the classroom locking when its recess or we need to go to other places like the science labs and after school too. this kinda sucks, since i always stay in class during recess.. now need to find some other place to go and while away the break time le..  CME lesson wise, what we did was just to complete the page where the CONDUCT is on, and have sentences formed from each letter of it.. and talked about racism.. blacks, whites, yellows, niggas. blah. our maths cum form teacher is going off for NS reservist soon, so we'll be having a relief teacher from now on.. duno until when, but i kinda look forward to his teaching...  Today was a real rainy day man, rained twice in the afternoon.. and i got a bit wet from the rain around 2.45pm... but yeah, managed to get a cab to go to CS, before the real stuff came... phew..  Actually wasnt planning to go to Century Square today, but since Kun Long and Kenneth were going, i tot it might be good to join in the fun too... kinda hate boredom these days... otherwise my mind will think of all sorts of things again.. sigh..  Played WMMT and ID v3 today, but again, its mostly WMMT... i got my timing on New Belt Line to 4'43... super happy, to top it off, my R32 in ID got its shomaru time reduced from 3'11 to 3'10'876 in the first run, but the second one was a real pleasant surprise.. a 3'05 !! a great leap !! Uber happy today !!  After that headed to Popular in Tampines central.. since the one at CS was too small and had nothing to see ard.. headed to the hp shop where Sherman asked for the price of T630.. wah.. drop again... need to pay $280 only if i traded my 3100... not the $318 before.. We bought 2 EA classics, and got 1 free. but we shared the price equally among the 3 of us.. since each taking 1 game... and i bought a box of CD-RW and DVD-RW too.. made full use of the 15% discount NKF voucher... haha...  Went back home to see doc, guess what ? they start at 7... i got there at 6.35.. decided to head home first, den go see.... come back, wah the crowd was like so many.. waited from 7.20 to 8... den see doc.. the doc was like pampering a small kid sia.. keep patting my arm.. and showered a lot of "motherly" care on me... whaha... but good la... better than one dao one.. hehe. Been sick for over a week le.. den see doc..  Btw, Bought a box of rojak home for my parents as a surprise, but they didnt really appreciate it.... or so i suppose..  When nearly reaching my house, suddenly 3 sms came at the same time, making my phone ring a big big beep. was wondering... got 3 pple send me sms at same time ? rarity leh... but all came from Karie.. she was like all urgent about getting a extra hp for her fren... but i think she got too urgent, and scolded me vulgarities in the last sms, say i didnt wanna reply.. i was like har ? O.O"?? Then i msged her on MSN... she, as per usual, was kinda the not interested to talk to me... with a tone that friends doesnt use.... i wonder, wads her purpose for doing this.. i see her blog, was like all happy and stuff, but to me, shes cold as ice. or maybe even colder. sheesh. i doubt Saturday i'll be off to the movies with her and her friends... since, i'm the only one, and i'm kinda short in that gang too, i suppose. bleh, one step at a time ba... -.-~  Well i hope shes cooled down, my medicine doing the work, and everything's gonna be OK tml... had a very happening Tuesday.. just like last week. oh, forgot to mention, yesterday was the first week old of my blog.. haha.. 1 wk, and this much crap le..lol.. blogger can tahan anot.. i wonder... Ok la, i'm off to do my things le, and to sleep early tml...   Man.. all this blogging... kinda takes up a long time.. this entry took like.. 40 mins ? i'm getting burned out here... saw the article.. on burned out of blogging.. disturbing the normal rhythm of pple's normal routine.. i guess i'm one of them too.. but i'll try my best to blog everyday, and whenever i have the time.... and not to be this lengthy, haha. &gt;.</post></Blog>