<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Now I wouldn't call myself a right winger but did anyone else have a hard time watching this Democrat love fest. First off why start off with Gore and then Carter as speakers. Gore's loss 4 years ago, and yes he did lose even though liberal after liberal will pretend he won. News papers went in after all the nonsense ended and did their own research and they all came back with the same conclusion which was that Bush won. Keep in mind also that many republican counties were still open when the election was called for Gore which probably lead many Bush voters to not vote. So this-I really won but am now eating pop tarts and watching soaps in my pjs with feet- has to stop. The anger always comes out in a Gore speech and in my humble view he was a rotten choice to speak first. Although Gore is a good attack dog if Kerry needs to bad mouth Bush without doing it directly but to start the show off...yuck.  Then Carter comes on looking old and talking about foriegn affairs and how badly Pres. Bush has messed things up. This coming from a President that basicaly lost relection because of how poorly he handled over seas crisis. Also Carter and Clinton shamefuly in my view broke the rule of past Presidents taking cheap political shots at a standing president. Something a little unclassy about that.   Anyways enough Politics. Good news on the wedding front. My old APD brother Rick is going to hit my sisters wedding with me. It will be fun to have a few brews and catch up with him. Good thing about close friends is that even if you don't see them for awhile they will be there for you when you need them.Rick and I had some wild times at college including a night where Rick pulled off a nice tripple flip falling down some stairs. Ahh drunken blurry half remembered college memories. SPeaking of the wedding my sis and herman come up this weekend to hang. Gonna prob hit up a few stores and get outfitten with a docker/button up/ tiething. I am the least fashionableperson I know so this should be fun.   Thats a wrap for now. I did some good landscaping and garden work in the sun today so I am pleasantly sore and in need of my comfy chair.  
     

    
</post>
<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Rain, Rain and more Rain.  This has been probably the most wet and overcast summer in Maine history. Gardens a little stunted from lack of sun and my tan is fading before it even had a chance. I need to find an old voodoo trick to bring out the sun because this is already old. If a Maine winter comes on before I get a chance to enjoy the summer I am hot footing it to FLA mark my words.  Cleaned up my room (needed it badly). Well cleaned might give the wrong impression. Not to imply that it is completed so I will say I am in the process of majorly cleaning my room. Found an old poem book from college. What a lameo haha. I am shocked I ever got laid writing the poems I wrote. A theory I have is girls like the lovey dovey stuff for a bit...but like this weather it gets old. A balance of the two is what you need. Yin Yang of Whipped and Ass hole. Always keep em guessing. Grin.  My sisters wedding is also coming up. August 20th. I sneaked out of wearing a tux so far...Gonna fly solo on this.No date because I am a firm believer of a female date at a wedding is bad buisness. Wanted to have a few drinking buddies go butblinded work horses can't make it on a Friday. Gonna have to handle the family thing on my own. Should be fun but a wing man would have been nice. My sisters friends already made me promise I would dance with them I might have been pretty damn good at soccer but for some reason that balance and skill doesn't convert to dancing. Maybe I will fake a sprained ankle. Woof.  Enough rambling for tonight. If it is sunny tommorow maybe I will hit a lake or do some chain sawing. If it rains I am gonnaturn onthe jacuzzi and sleep in there till next summer. 
     

    
</post>
<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Well it is the late end of a 4th of July and I feel like I have some things to write out.  I figured this would be a good way to release some rambles before bed time and give my brain a rest before bed.  Grin.  Will see how it works because my mind is quite the speed racer when i try to sleep.  So quick recap on today and what I learned.  Woke up today with deer eating in my garden so I spent 5 hours making a deer fence.  Not fun at all but had to be done.  Big fan of the garden action so in my posts you will see many a writing on that subject.  My aunt came and visited which was kinda nice but as with any family things can get kinda hetic.  The chinnese symbol for trouble is two women under the same roof.  Ha, and don't get mad at me for saying it.  Anyways a little red zin from cali put me in a good mood and prob gave me the creative juice to start my own blog.  What else what else....umm well in future posts I might give a low down on what I have been up to in the past and where I think I am heading.  A few poems and the like are a disticnt possability although I haven;t written many since I got broken by a chick.  Haha and no I am not gonna be all woe is me on past loves all the time, that gets old quick.    Wow guess I had more then I thought to say tonight.  Well let me hit post and see if I figured this out correctly.  There is a 67% chance that I fuck this up royaly and never figure out how to do this again.  Wish me luck.  PK
     

    
</post>
</Blog>