<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      From Midas To Medusa The Bad Boy Curse lives on    April 12, 2004  Words - 370    It seems everything Sean combs touches turns to gold, yet situations always turn  to stone.With P.Diddy's latest protege and former Harlem World member Chauncey "Loon" Hawkins being arrested (Fri. Feb 13/04 up on attempted murder charges), this is just one of Sean "P.Diddy" Combs' latest problems. On the heels of the Labels 10th year anniversary, the music mogul has been plagued with other incidents that have recently tarnished his empire. Faith Evans-drugs, J.Lo - club shooting, the death of Biggie Smalls, his Sean John line- sweatshop accusations (October 2003), Shyne - new artist sent to prison, 3 other acts who have "Requested" to be let out of their Bad Boy contracts (112, The Lox and Da Band) and now Loon.    Will this bad boy turn good? Aside from his charitable offerings including running the new York marathon to raise money for Children's Hope Foundation for children suffering from HIV/AIDS and his own Daddy's House youth organization. Will these events take the spotlight from the realness of the rap game that’s playing itself out more and more within the confines of the Bad Boy Family tree?    Mo’ Money, Mo’ Problems.        Top 20 Dirty Diddy Doo Doo’s      1. Biggie Murdered  2. Shyne – Went to jail …for him  3. Faith Evans – Charged with cocaine possession. (She needed to lose some weight anyway)  4. Loon-Charged with attempted murder  5. 112 – Wants off the label  6. The Lox- Wanted and got, off the label  7. Da Band – Wants off the label  8. Sean John – Sweatshop scandal  9. Dream – Their old agency says that PD Didd them wrong: Stole group from roster  10. J. Lo-Club shooting  11. Interscope – Beat the shit out of Record Exec and Nas’ manager Steve Stoute.  12. Black Rob- Jailed on a gun charge  13. Writers: Of No Way Out album, hit him with a $4 Million Suit  14. Limo driver - gets paied $2.45 Million for taking a Bad Boy Beating  15. Television Host : Sues PD Over Alleged 1999 Attack  16. Stampede Case – Our man has to settle.  17. Daddy's House Studio - Rounds emptied into the building  18. Blaze Magazine - Editor Reportedly Beaten by Diddy’s Dorks  19.Rock band: Goes tits up  20.Ex wife: wants and gets - more money      © 2004 E.S. Day, All Rights Reserved.   
    
</post>
<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      RIAA -708 words      March 11, 2004    With more and more big name artists spreading their career wings and soaring into the    open arms of independent labels everywhere this might give unscrupulous explanation    into why the big 5 recording labels and their dastardly henchmen (The RIAA) are trying    harder than ever to grasp a hold of an already economically failing industry. Label    merging is in. File sharing lawsuits are hot right now. Label exec switch-a roos are a    popular item. Folding subsidiaries back into the womb from which they born is now an    everyday occurance. Imprint absorption now has it’s own top 10 chart.                  "While the music industry continues to face serious challenges, we are pleased that trends    appear to be going in a more positive direction."             —Mitch Bainwol, RIAA Chairman/CEO on Year-End Figures            Trends? What trends? Bainwol should go A.W.O.L. – the only visable trends to surface    beyond buyouts and layoffs this year has been the trend of corporate giants succumbing    to the digital revolution. Not to mention a failed attempt at sweeping this profit crusher    under the industry’s carpet. When the RIAA released their annual report, it showed that    shipments to retail outlets went down 4.3% in 2003, which is less than last year’s 6.8%    drop. Total sales of recorded music and music videos slipped 6% to about $11.9 billion    last year. We all know by now of the iTune phenomenon, as well as Napster hitting the    million download mark. Let’s face it retail is dying and there is nothing the RIAA or the    Record labels can do about it Universal Music Group openly promotes downloading new    artist tracks from Puretracks.com in an attempt to scrounge any penny they can get their    hands on. Recently joining the ranks of the online community was Pepsi and their iTune    cross-promotion, (which got hacked) and of course along comes Coca-Cola and their    online jukebox. Now make way for VirginDigital. As if Mr. __________ and his giant    V logo weren’t on enough products and services already. Speaking of Cola giants, expect    to see “Pepsi Smash” returning to the WB on May 27th nationwide with appearances    already confirmed from Usher and Hoobastank. Yet another feeble attempt to push syrupy    carbonated water through the grace of music. Shame.Another shame on the caffeine    front everybody’s favorite $5 coffee servers Starbucks have announced that they too will    try a hand of digital roulette and hopefully hitting the jackpot with 30somethings that    missed the beat generation boat.the music publishing giant Dreamworks is apparently up    for grabs at a starting price of a mere $40 Million. They’re e dropping like flies I tell    ya!.The acquisition of WMG and it’s layoffs ahs also cause a domino effect with the    Lyor Cohen leaving Def Jam to be replace by the Arista outed L.A. Reid transition,    Arista is now being folded into its resurrected parent RCA Victor. Whew!. Artists are    getting dropped left right and center. Unless you’re name is Norah, I would start touring    as much as humanly possible and give away as much free music as you can! To get ticket    sales a hopping. Poor Clive Davis is going to have a coronary soon I’m sure of it. His J    records label just lost reknowned rapper Busta Rhymes to the profitable Dr. Dre owned    Aftermath label, leaving a stable of 3rd rate artists whom are more than likely looking to    abandon ship. Super producers The Neptunes had bailed (in the nick of time) to UMG    where right about now everyone seems pretty safe. Safe that is...until the Sony/BMG    merger takes full effect. Oh yes kiddies its not over yet lest we forget that on the merger    front Mr. Warner himself Edgar Bronfman had been re-negotiating his plans to tie    the knot with the”Other white meat” on the recording conglomerate: EMI. So the BIG 5    might be The Big 3. This could possibility flood the gates of opportunity for flreedhiling    artists on the rise, pushing established artist back to the Mom and pop frontlines, giving    the RIAA an upper arms on standardized pricing and download conformity. All of this    because after a hard days work I want to come home sit back and put on my favorites    songs and relax. I think when I get home today… I’m just going to read a good book.        © 2004 E.S. Day   
    
</post>
<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      1996: The Year Hip-HopDied- A Commentary    Words – 1650        When you look at some of titles below, and ponder the thought of the title of    this piece you might reminisce or might be too young to understand fans of Hip    Hop know what I mean when I say “The Year Rap Died” it did. Plain and simple.    Like all underground music, when the mainstream starts to smell money, and they    will, it then becomes a “public thing” it’s not ours anymore, like losing a    friend or family member, - I personally mourn the loss of an era or group of    songs/artist that became a part of my life. When I hear Mobb Deep or M.O.P on    mainstream radio, I shed an invisible tear. I appreciate an artist expanding    their listenership/audience, paying a few bills etc… but it was the underground    that created these waves that enabled them to secure larger deals, product    endorsements, large scale tours etc…. But are they really happy? True hardcore    fans aren’t - that’s for sure. But just like the big artists, the little ones    are replaced by the next big thing to come out of the underground. Everyone is    replaceable in this business. But the one thing that the labels, and the media    can’t; replace – is that feeling you get when you hear something for the first    time…that nobody knows about yet. That, can only come from the underground.        What I find really clinched the whole “Urban Embracement “ was a (at the time)    slept on album from Haitian hip hoppers: The Fugees. Wyclef, Pras and soon –to –be Soul Diva    Lauryn Hill dominated the urban charts that year and into 1997, selling well    over 17 million copies of their sophomore LP The Score. This release had execs    at Sony (their label) shitting in their pants from the overwhelming success of    the album due to its big breakthrough crossover – a cover version of Roberta    Flack’ Killing Me Softly. With it’s reggae overtones and smooth sway, this track had white    people across the country coming out of their hip hop closets and first time    beat junkies actually trading in GAP wear for FUBU. Yes this is when HIP-HOP was    born. Sony focused their attention on their fledgling urban dept with more    determination than ever. One would almost guess that the label actually liked    Hip-Hop with all the push they were giving. But keep in mind they are a label    were out to make a buck but it was nice too think that the industry was changing    for the better. Steven Rifkind Loud Records label had such a buzz on the street    that the big Tommy Mottola led label gave Rifkind and his band of merry men a    distribution deal that saw the likes of Wu Tang Clan, Dead Prez, M.O.P. and    Xzibit getting a marketing makeover. This was soon too end of course but once    again at the time Hip-Hop’s global takeover was just taking its baby steps.    Master P. and him no limit camp had made a dent min the indie sector moving    hundreds of thousands of units with Priority Records helping hand and other    labels and distributors took notice. From the desks of the largest music movers    in the world who normally flatly denied giving certain acts a chance were now    signing anything young, black and holding a microphone. Neo Soul was shaping as    a format in the womb of the urban industry. Once again, I believe due to the    success of the Score. Hip Hop and RB was becoming intertwined to form what  white America calls “Urban”.            Funny, I always called Country music Urban.      ©2004 E.S. Day            Important albums from 95-96      West/Down South      1. SOULS OF MISCHIEF No Man's Land Jive  2. JT THE BIGGA FIGGA Dwellin' In The Labb Get Low  3. SPICE 1 1990 Sick Jive  4. Rappin" 4-Tay "Aint No Playa" (Rag Top/Chrysalis)  5. Dr Octagon (feat Q-Bert) "Dr Octagonocologyst"  6. Ant Banks "Keep "Em Guessin"  7. 2Pac "All Eyez On Me" (Death Row)  8. Peanut Butter Wolf "Step On Our Ego" (South Paw)  9. Conscious Daughters "Gamers" 12" (Priority)  10. Suga T "Recognize" (Sick Wid It/Jive  11. Too Short "Gettin' It" 12" (Jive)  12. Master P "Ice Cream MAn" (No Limit/Priority)  13. Dru Down, Luniz from "Thin Line B/w Love  Hate" S/T (Warner)  14. 2PAC  DR DRE California Love- Death Row  15. XZIBIT Eyes May Shine Loud      East coast: If you were a beast from the east you were probably bangin’ these joints at one point    1. Fugees Fu-gee-la Ruff House  2. Mary J Blige/ Smif  Wessun I Love You Uptown  3. KRS-One Rappaz R N Dainja Jive  4. Group Home Livin' Proof Payday  5. Kool G Rap For Tha Brothaz Epic  6. Cypress Hill Boom Biddy Bye Bye Ruff House  7. Goodie Mob Cell Therapy LaFace  8. Pharcyde The Hustle Delicious Vinyl  9. Raekwon Incarcerated Scarface Loud  10. Heather B All Glocks Down Pendulum  11. RBX Rough Is The Texture WB  12. REAL LIVE Crime Is Money Big Beat  13. BRAND NEW HEAVIES Mind Trippin' Delicous Vinyl  14. MAD SKILLZ Extra Abstract Skillz Big Beat  15. BAHAMADIA Uknowwhowedu EMI  16. MIC GERONIMO The Natural Blunt  17. DOGG POUND New York New York Death Row  18. MAD LION Real Ting Nervous  19. SPEARHEAD Caught w/o An Umbrella Capitol  20. MOBB DEEP Still Shinin'- Loud  21. BIG NOYD Recognize  Realize Tommy Boy  22. GURU For You- Chrysalis  23. REDMAN Funkarama- Interscope  24. BUSTA RHYMES Woo-Hah- Elektra  25. KOOL KEITH Slide We Fly- Funky Ass Records  26. WHITEY DON w/KRS-ONE 'Lyrical Shot'-83 bpm [Jive]  27. SADAT X The Lump Lump 93 bpm [Loud]  28. FRANKIE CUTLASS 'You And You And You'-[Relativity  29. POSITIVE K 'Mr Jiggliano'-[Creative Control]  30. SMOOTH DA HUSTLER 'Murderfest'-[Profile]  31. SHYHEIM 'Is It Real'[Noo Trybe]  32. FAT JOE 'Envy'-88 bpm [Relativity]  33. NAS/If I Ruled The World/Columbia  34. Common/The Bitch In You ( The Ice Cube diss)/Relativity  35. Arsonists/The. Underground taking a peek out tha sewer  36. De La Soul/Stakes Is High/Tommy Boy  37. Defari/Big Up/Immortal  38. Trigger Tha Gambler My Crew Can't Go For That/Def Jam  39. EightBall  MJG/Listen To Me Now/East/West  40. PMD Rugged N Raw-without the E Parrish Makes Dick [Boondock]  41. BLAZAH BLAZAH Pain I Feel- [EMI]  42. NINE Lyin' King-Profile  43. Extra P/I Just Wanna Chill/  44. Ghostface Killa/Daytona 500/Razor Sharp  45. Beatnuts/Find That/Relativity  46. RZA/ CAPADONNA Wu-Wear-Big Beat  47. RAS KASS Soul On Ice Priority  48. JAY-Z Reasonable Doubt Roc-A-Fella  49. WESTSIDE CONNECTION Bow Down-Priority  50. AMERICA IS DYING SLOWLY Various Artists East West  51. CAPONE  NORIEGA Illegal Life-pm Penalty  52. DA BRAT Sittin' On Top Of The World SoSo Def  53. DA ORIGINAL GUNN CLAPPAZ No FearPriority  54. OUTKAST ATLiens LaFace  55. JERU THE DAMAJA Ya Playin' Yaself FFRR  56. LOST BOYZ Music Makes Me High-Universal  57. CHUCK D The Autobiography Of MistaChuck Mercury  58. SILKK The Shocker..LP No Limit  59. THE ROOTS Concerto Of The Desperado DGC  60. ORIGINAL GUNN CLAPPAZ No Fear Priority  61. BOUNTY KILLER My Experience Sampler..EP Blunt  62. New World Order by Poor Righteous Teachers  63. Put It in Your Mouth" by Akinyele  64. "No Diggity" by Blackstreet w/Dr Dre    D.J's that bumped in the club and on tour and opened a few more doors for D.J.’s    DJ Premier, Q-Bert, Funkmaster Flex, DJ Shadow and DJ Honda    Producers who shined from 95-96 and kept the streets alive with the sound of music    DJ Premier, Organized Noize, E-Swift, Beatminerz, Suge Knight, Puffy and Rza      Misc.95-96    * KRS-1 found he was the rap version of Jesus when he opened the Temple Of Hip Hop in NYC, to educate the youth and assemble the worlds largest street team for his future releases.    * Tupac hates everyone this year, evident on the ultimate diss anthem 'Hit 'em up" 'PAC takes shots (no pun) at virtually everyone before getting a few himself. From one time companion Biggie, to the entire Puff/Bad Boy camp with dishonorable mentions going out to Lil Kim and Junior Mafia. Mobb Deep took one to the ego dome and a gracious toast to Chino XL who could use some publicity right about now.    * Bone Thugs and Harmony saw us at The Crossroads. Must have been about the intersection where their banks, cause these fellas struck lucky gold with this one. Not only did they open the doors to the bank but as well for the top 40 chart. The Crossroads crossed over in to the mainstream giving true heads another group to cross off the list    * Biggie dies    * Roc-a-Fella Records is Founded by ultra-snob Damon Dash and the Blueprint (no pun again) for crossover appeal into white America is drafted. (1995)    * Quincy Jones Give us the first black music magazine - for white people: Vibe hits the newsstands and wiggaz go wild!(95)    * Eazy E dies (95)    * Source award fight - causing more drama and more record sales, but Record Label Execs are furious that there was no shootings or death(post-humous releases are guaranteed platinum. (their dreams come true the next year)-.(95)    * Coolio reminds use of the "Gangsters Paradise he's been living in. Refuses to change electrified cornrows and eventually falls off the charts. For good.    * C.Delores Tucker has a hard-on for the Rap community and it's lyrics. Publicly trys to outlaw profanity, causing more rebellious youth to defy the system by buying even more curse laden records. Metalheads take notice and now they're buying it too. Thanks Delores!    * Mobb Deep drop the soundtrack to my life that year-"the Infamous" is released. They would Eventually get crossed off the "Real" list mind you only after they started putting strippers in their videos. I know you got eat but c'mon!    * X Clans Sugar Shaft joins Eric Wright as another casualty of AIDS related complications  · The Fugees drop the Score sell 17 Million. Hip-Hop is born    * Rawkus Records IS Founded    * Battle/D.J./mixtape albums are released through major labels who once again have to get their filthy fucking hands on everything, thus enabling them to steal another part of Hip Hops underground origin.    ©2004 E.S. Day, All Rights Reserved.     
    
</post>
<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink http://thenerveonline.com/crystalpistol.html  
    
</post>
<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Nova”Fucking”Scotia    March 2, 2004    Words: 194    Nova Scotia, where the provincial government has released a list of words it wants banished from use by the news media.  Included on the list of are such words and phrases as "basket-case, cracked-up, crazed, demented, fruitcake, kooky, loony, lost their marbles, lunatic, madman, maniac, nutcase, and schizo."    Carol Toonton of the Canadian Mental Health Association says while the project sounds odd (hey, shouldn’t that be put on the list? – e.s..day) to many, it's all about using appropriate language and not relying on outdated negative stereotypes.    "We don't use the word Negro anymore when we're talking about people of colour in our community," she says.    No that’s right Carol! You just use the other ”N” word.    Leave it to the land of Keith’s Beers and sloppy donairs to come up with this one. To a lot of young people these days, the aforementioned “Phrases” are not always meant to be taken in true form.    “Cracked –Up” essentially refers to one being “Cracked out of it” you know, to be “On the pipe”. There, that’s one off the list. A “Loony” is a dollar, a “Fruitcake” is something you throw out at Christmas and if you’ve “Lost your Marbles” simply go out and purchase some more.    © 2004 E.S.Day, All Rights Reserved 
    
</post>
<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Brides Of Destruction – Here Come The Brides (Sanctuary/EMI)    March 8, 2004 349 words    "I tried doing Top 40, my heart just wasn't in it" - Nikki Sixx, November 1984      “We're a good band, a good top 40 band" - Nikki Sixx, Hit Parader, 1985      I’m starting to think that the (now) infamous King of rock n roll grandeur Mr. Nikki Sixx,    has finally lost control of his senses. I’m also beginning to understand why, through the    insidious lack of thought put into the debut recording from his Motley Crue offshoot.    Brides Of Destruction. Poor bastards must really be stuck in a rut. What the hell am I    saying they are! They - the Brides, which finds ex-G n R/L.A. Guns axeman (do we still    use this phrase? at 36 I certainly do) Tracii Guns and a zombified cast of spandex –clad tossaways    from the early nineties post Glam fallout, have certainly given it their all. All of what    they’ve giving? The same 3 chord catastrophes that separated the the Glam/sleaze genre    from the predominately rising 3 chord grunge scene that swept the airwaves and MTV during its    meager rise to the charts. The crew (no pun) informs us to “Shut The Fuck Up!” a    solidified first single that will have you accidentally chanting Skid Rows “Get The Fuck    Out!” they sound similar, they both have Fuck in the chorus and they both demand the    listener to pound their fist into the air with a narcissistic rage that has one questioning    who are we shouting at? Back in the day I was ‘Shouting At The Devil” to be exact.    Great tour as well!. So BOD’s debut “here comes the brides (sanctuary/EMI) is now attempting to    walk down the bloodstained aisle of mayhem  marketing. A successful Marriage of    recitative rants  ramblings coupled with the standard third-rate power ballad, and voila!    An instant classic for the .99 crate! A rumored opening slot on an upcoming KISS tour    should help recoup the production costs on this one. Let’s hope they head straight to Divorce CourtÔ    real quick before they bare the bastard children of a worthless attempt at resurrecting    something that was meant to stay at the altar      © 2004 E.S. Day, All Rights Reserved   urlLink http://www.edwardscottday.8k.com   
    
</post>
<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Snatch Catch Fever - Hemi Cuda Baffles the brain, boggles the balls and breaks our hearts. (except the guy)    E.S. Day confronts the Denver trio on world issues such as celebrity rapists, the state of punk today and bad wigs (We can stick this in Innards – AM)    The State of Colorado. The Land of Milk  Honey’s, chunky mountaintop chalets, Kobe Bryant’s pansy trial, as well as home to lunatic Hunter S. Thompson and a 3 piece outfit who seem to like cars. Denver’s Hemi Cuda: a brazen attempt at recreating a trash-a-go-go vibe that would make Russ Meyer proud. The band takes the time to let me find out if there is indeed a serious side to yet another female-fronted punk group trying to make it without the use of the terms “Angst-ridden” or “Grrrl” (enough already).    Nerve: Colorado. No offence, but it seems like the most boring piece of shit state to have an emerging punk scene, besides Hunter S. Thompson, there really isn't a hell of a lot going on is there. Why don't you just LEAVE!?    Karen Cuda: Well someone and their town have a case of low self esteem!!! Actually, Denver rocks - you should try it sometime.    Nerve: Influences seem to be all over the map, so when can we expect a new album of songs relating to those influences or are you going to continue to just play/write 3 chord wonders?    Karen: Here it is again - the most cliche interview question ever...the one relating to influences. I don't think anyone really cares what our influences are and if they do maybe they're just hoping to see their name in there somewhere. What would you say if I said my biggest influence was my high school counselor? We just do what WE do, and if it's 3 chord "wonders" then so be it. We're expecting to release our ep later this summer and a full length as soon as we find the right label to do it.    Nerve: Dream tour - what bands would you be sharing the stage with?    Karen: The Darkness and Gluecifer.    Nerve: Dream drummer? (besides Rikki Rockett  Todd Marino - Gaza Strippers)    Karen: Funny you mention those two. First, because I was obsessed with Rikki Rocket as a kid. I actually still have a poem I wrote about him - funny shit! Secondly, because Todd Marino only played with the Gaza Strippers for about 45 days of their 5 year existence. Mark Allen, who IS our dream drummer, played with Gaza Strippers for the last 3+ years... and he just happens to be playing with us now.    Nerve: 2 girls  a guy drummer - considering the wigs and all, why not dress up as 2 guys and a girl drummer?  Karen: Because I would never wanna stop waxing my chest and I would have to in order to really pull off the guy thing. Plus, you wouldn't be doing this interview right now... Or would you?????      Nerve: I noticed you cite author Harry Crews (A Feast of Snakes) in your bio, any other authors on your list? And do they have an influence over your lyrics?    Karen: So many authors, so many good books to read. I'm sure everything I read affects (in other words, influences – E.S.Day) my writing, but not necessarily my lyrics. I write about what inspires me at the time.    Nerve: When it comes to Punk Chix like The Slits, Bikini Kill, Girlschool (my fave) etc...do Hemi Cuda draw an influence from their mentors. If so, who and why?    Karen: What is it with all the influence questions??? I am influenced musically by everything that happens in my life. I will always have tons of respect for other women with rock in their blood but I wouldn't call any of those bands my mentors just because they are women playing rock. To me, music is an androgynous thing - if it moves me - cool. But if I must flatter you with some females who have been inspirational to me I would say Bianca Butthole (RIP), Alana Davis, and PJ Harvey.    Nerve: If you were in The Runaways, who would you compare yourself to: Joan Jett or Lita Ford    Karen: That question sounds kinda silly cuz if I were IN the Runaways, I wouldn't be comparing myself to them but I think I know what you mean; Joan Jett.    Nerve: Are you sick of car questions?    Karen: No, I'm sick of influence questions.    Nerve: Are drugs involved with the songwriting process or do you just rearrange the same 3 chords and slap a different title on it?    Karen: Drugs are involved with a lot and no.    Nerve: What’s Bumpin' in yo’ ride right now?    Karen: The new Gluecifer - Automatic Thrill.    Nerve: The Nerve Magazine can be found in both Vancouver  Seattle, so riddle me this Catwomen  Batboy, which city rocks harder and is by far the coolest?    Karen: Hmmm..... I love both places so much for different reasons so it's a toss up. But if YOU really need that reassurance (see question one) I'll say ......Vancouver. Happy?    Nerve: You have quite the trial going on in your town with a famous basketball player. Do you give a shit?    Karen: I don't give a shit about Kobe Bryant but if he raped that girl he should be punished. Cock amputation for rapists!!!!    Nerve: After appearing in "Nixing The Twist" have you considered straying from the music business to do more film?    Karen: It was my first shot at it - sounded like fun and it was. I'd consider doing more but I wouldn't give up music to do so. But shit I can be like Beyonce and be in the next Austin Powers movie. Yah Baby.    Nerve: If you were asked to do a reality show (god forbid) that centered around the rise and possible fall of a girl band gone awry, would there be scenes of Anika  Karen PMS-ing and kicking the be-jesus out of the drummer?    Karen: You betcha, minus the kicking our drummer’s ass. We don't do that. I don't see us going awry anytime soon though. We crossed that road once and decided it wasn't one we wanted to travel, at least anytime soon....as long as everyone behaves!!!!!        Well with all of the action-packed questions, and attitude driven answers, this writer has been put in his place. At 36 years old, I should be ashamed of myself for kicking off the interview with such a salty tone. How dare I embark on such a treacherous smear campaign! Boy, do I have some Nerve! (No pun) I shouldn’t approach such a sensitive and delicate matter, such as trying to get info for you our faithful (music buying) readers, on a band who’s put out one indie release in a 3 year period, that NO ONE has (really) heard of. Furthermore, I should have just realized that Hemi Cuda rock, after seeing that picture of them with Gene Simmons, which they posted on their web site. For Christ’s sake – he’s the God of Fucking Thunder!,. That alone is proof! He must be A great “influence” to the girls. Hopefully the novelty…won’t wear off.    Note: Since they don’t like talking about their influences and you’re curious what they sound like, we’ll just say – Gluecifer meets The Darkness. With tits. Mind you, The Darkness IS a girl band, aren’t they?        And so you have it folks. I, the arrogant, asinine music journalist, have stumbled upon my own flagrant attempt at getting an up  coming band to bear their souls - not their breasts. It is I who dove deep, down into the bowels of a decrepit society known as Rock n Roll, only to rise to the surface gasping for air. With my fist clenched, I still had enough breath to utter the only words that can save me now: Hemi!-Fucking!-Cuda!      Hemi Cuda will be performing ALL 3 of their chords LIVE! at Mikes Tavern on July 16  urlLink www.hemicudarocks.com       PLUS!  She’s A Stage Whore. He’s A Print Whore, Together; they are the funniest whores on tour!    “Karen vs. E.S. Day: Clash Of The Rock Whores” – Coming Soon To HBO!    © 2004 E.S. “Fucking” Day   urlLink www.edwardscottday.8k.com   
    
</post>
<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Velvet Revolver: Guns ‘N Pilots? Or Stone Temple Roses?    111words        So fucking backwards, I prefer to call them "Relvet Vevolver'or "Revolting VeVulva”    Hey that actually has a soft vicious twang to it!      I believe when the world was introduced to the band on everyone’s “Most Anticipated “    list with their atrocious cover of Pink Floyd's “Money” (a fitting choice) it was made clear as    to why this projected had even started in the first place: the almighty dollar. Strung out    lazy guitar work from Slash and string cheese lyrics from professional relapser Scott    Weiland provide a massive spotlight for the ‘other’ guys in this 2 man “Supergroup’.    This was not worth the wait      © 2004 E.S. Day, All Rights Reserved. 
    
</post>
<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Kayne West – All Falls Down    Mar 18/04    Words - 134    Hip-Hop’s Cinderella story – producer-turned-emcee Kayne West, has made an    impressive dent at retail this year with his debut album “College Dropout” (Roc-a fella)    the mainstream album with the underground vibe. The Chicago native’s second single; All    Falls Down will strike a chord with fans of Lauryn Hill, as the chorus seems to borrow    directly from Hill’s breakup song - Ex Factor. This form of jacking rests well with me    as Kayne pulls it off with no scruples. The background vocals provided just the right    amount of a sadness that doesn’t exist, for the 4min that it takes over your senses, the beat    has you head doing a half nod while Mr. West spits truths and reminds us to look at our    own insecurities. Finally - a strong -charting single meant for listening and not hearing.      © 2004 E.S. Day, All Rights Reserved. 
    
</post>
<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Review- Cypress Hill – What’s Your Number    233 words    Once labeled as “The Grateful Dead of Hip Hop”, one could imagine what possessed the    “The Phuncky Feel Ones” to churn out their highly anticipated new single in such a    contrived surrounding. Everyone knows that hip hop has just gone to shit these days. My    favorite blunt brothers should seriously consider changing their moniker to “Snipe-ress    Hill” for taking such atrocious shots at the buying public. If the lead single “What’s Your    Number” is any indication of what’s to come on their forthcoming “Til Death Due Us    Part” (March 23, Sony) their 8th studio album, I for one will have to put them in my    ”To see live show only” file.            What’s Your Number has “Help Us” written all over it, and granted with the poor sales    of 2001’s Stoned Raiders, B-real  Co. need any modern day gimmick that would    seriously help the Boomin’ Banditos right about now. The minute I heard B-Fake    spitting his amorous longing for the señorita he’s try to serenade. Talking ‘bout “getting’    her number” I thought maybe they are the Stoned Raiders they claim to be. Cause    homeboy you got to be stoned to spit that kind of game.      Let’s hope that Smoke Out DVD sells well, cause even with guest appearances from    Mobb Deeps’ Prodigy and production from The Alchemist, I don’t see the Killa Hill    niggas taking any hits from the SoundScan bong anytime soon.        ©2004 E.S. Day, All Rights Reserved. 
    
</post>
<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink     Hollywood Decapitates A Classic Posted by E.S.Day on Mar 18, 2004 With a string of semi-successful horror flicks (Cabin Fever, Jeepers Creepers) rising from the Post-Apocalyptic ashes of Box office hits such as the Scream trilogy, the only remake to take to the big screen in recent years has been the 2003 version of the Texas Chainsaw Massacre. I must admit, I actually dropped my popcorn for the sheer terror that ran through my mind that afternoon. Unfortunately those emotions were not to be felt again after watching the remake of George Romeros' Chopping Mall classic, Dawn Of The Dead. Effects aside, the campy cult feel from the original is what made it's impact on audiences back then. The underground appeal has been ommitted through a below average screenplay and a soon to be B-movie cast. Sad to say there is no bringing this one back from the dead.  
    
</post>
<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Lenny Kravitz _ Where Are They Running?    Words 130    Lenny The K. has once again walked through a revolving door of image and sound    makeovers, from his comparisons to Hendrix and Lennon to his sexy-soul flower-funk    Lenny Kravitz lands on planet rock again with “Where Are They Running?” The first single from his 9th    studio LP; Baptism. Kravitz must have had KISS’ Hotter than Hell album pulled from his    personal vinyl collection that month because that’s exactly what you get. The thin tin    3 chord bravado, that emanates from this outing has Simmons/Stanley written all over it    Enviably, Lenny's rebellious banter might be strike 3 minus the Greatest Hits package that    Virgin released a few years back. If this lead single is any indication, he might want to    consider growing his dreads back and dusting off the Wa Wa pedal from his musical shed.      © 2004 E.S. Day, All Rights Reserved.     urlLink http://www.edwardscottday.8k.com   
    
</post>
<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
            KKK - Korn On the Korporate Kob?     After witnessing the “Uncensored video for Korn’s latest “Y’all want a single” complete with anti-industry slogans flashing across the screen reminded me of a PETA campaign clip, reminiscent of Van Halen’s Right Now “ façade, Mr. Bucktooth and his Korn-row haired buddies have made a valid point. But is this just another publicity stunt?. The “Big 5” (Actually 4 ) record labels have their hands full right now with internet piracy and lawsuits galore, could it be that this is yet another marketing ploy to reach the cd buying masses.?. I think – Yes!. What a perfect way to make us confused consumers of Numetalrapcorerockrapmetal – rock, think twice about purchasing a cd to help support these corporate gluttons. But wait a minute if Sony –Korns label, refuses to endorse the video, and MTV won’t play due to it’s visual and lyrical content, doesn’t that mean I have to support Korn buy going out and purchasing the Sony manufactured DVD?    Duped again.    © 2004 E.S. Day, All Rights Reserved.     
</post>
<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        The Biggie Smalls legacy prepares to die again  by E.S. Day (07/09/2004)    Pros: Bonus DVD Cons: Blatant attempt at exploiting a masterpiece  Personally, there is no need to re-release this "classic" slice of hip-hop pie. The bonus dvd is nice, but if you havn't already heard/downloaded 'Who Shot Ya" the apparent ulti-diss to 2Pac,then maybe you need to discover Mr. Wallace from the beginning. And that starts here. The aforementioned song is one of 2 "unreleased tracks" available on this remastered version. The mix is crispier,but like most fried food, it tends to dry up after being left out too long.  E.S. Day www.edwardscottday.8k.com 
    
</post>
<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Will Somebody Shed Some Light On The Darkness?    Years ago listening to ‘Glam metal” meant unwittingly slipping into your best and   tightest black  white striped (no pun) spandex pants, all silky smooth against your   privates almost making you cum while on your way to the club, and then counteracting   with a masochistic display of studded wristbands and arm bands that made one look like   a walking stegosaurus with a hard on. Then the finishing touch: into Mom’s vanity we   go, stealing a dab of her best foundation to hide the zits, lip gloss to enable a consistent   pout while posing with the only beer you’ll purchase that evening because you’ve spent   all your allowance on Final Net. The soundtrack back then ‘82-88? A hybrid metal   crossover of what us pseudo-transvestites called – Glam. Poison, Warrant, Faster   Pussycat, Pretty Boy Floyd, shit like that. It wasn’t cool to like Winger, Stryper,   Nelson or any of the “Fag” bands who used too many 3 part harmonies. It was ok to look   like a drag queen, you just couldn’t sound like one.       This brings me to Britain’s newest chart toppings mongrels- The Darkness. First off let   me say this: British Glam Metal back then for us meant going off to the Record Peddlar and   having Brian Taylor (T.O punk connoisseur) laugh in our faces while we plopped down $22! ( a lot for a vinyl   import back then) just to be the first “Metrosexual Metalhead” on the block to pump out   the new new Tygertailz lp. Or worse yet that horrific outfit known as Wrathchild. Aside   from Hanoi Rocks or the Dogs D’amour there wasn’t a lot glam/sleaze stuff coming out   of Europe that was worthwhile. Once again, this brings me to The Darkness.       England has had it’s fair share of talented groups in the past 2 decades minus the   “Millionaire Whiners Club”: Radiohead, Starsailor, Coldplay and any other band with   suicide –tainted lyrics. But The Darkness and their single-handed resurgence of the   Glam rock scene from back in the day seem to have struck a chord with the youngsters.   Which is fine, but throughout various press releases and reviews I think the media has   mistaken the UK’s Definition of Glam: Slade, T-Rex, Gary Glitter – these artists pretty   well set the stage for their American counterparts who will admit their influences were   derived from such artists. So what the fuck is frontman Justin Hawkins doing in his Best   Kevin Dubrow (Quiet Riot) Outfit complete with receding hair line and ridiculous stage   antics . Is this a farce? Are the Brits playing an evil prank on the submissive North   American public? Who the fuck is working the AR dept. at Atlantic anyway? Their   debut album ‘Permission to Land” dominated the UK charts and the group recently swept   the Brit Awards leaving me in “The Dark” With appearances on a slew of Late Night   Talk shows in the U.S., I figured this obsequious tribute band was out to milk it for all   it’s worth. That, I will applaud them for       Upon getting an advance copy of ‘I Believe In A Thing Called Love” I thought I had put   in a burned copy of “The Right To Rock” by Keel. But when that annoying falsetto-   turned- yodel came through the speakers I thought “Oh! This is that Mindless Self   Indulgence remix my friend said I would enjoy”. I frantically looked everywhere for the   song credits. The first thing staring at up at me from my sty of a desk, was The Darkness   album. “Yeah right!” I thought, “Is this a joke?’ I swear to God I could have put on Tap’s   “Smell The Glove” and taken it a tad more serious than this “Party– Tripe” As the   chorus came oozing into the room, with Justin’s skittish Suffolk accent. I saw the title   emblazoned on the cover. I had   realized then what the fuss was all about. Nothing. Hey I’ll hand them a nod for trying ,   but handing them a Brit Award? Me thinks not. You want a resurgence? put on the   Probot album and call it a day.   A really “Dark” day, for Rock  Roll.   © 2004 E.S. Day, All Rights Reserved.  http://www.edwardscottday.8k.com   
    
</post>
<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         For Christs Sake!        Mel’s Lethal Weapon finally hits home     On the eve on the world’s most talked about and anticipated theatrical release “The   Passion Of The Christ’” audiences have been captivated by lengthy trailers, vignettes   and an over abundance of media propaganda, and spectacular marketing ploys.. Startling   figures show that U.S. audiences have embraced the movie before it’s even hit the big   screens . And I mean big screens, 4000 to be exact. But the irony involved in such a  complicated subject, that being religion, leads one to find answers which lie not within   the film itself, but with in the blatant greed that comes with Hollywood’s consistent   disregard for the films theme in the form of merchandising. Financially big budget films   anticipate sales on products related to the films release. Which can help it’s financial woes if   need be. The Cat In The Hat did not fare to well at the box office, but figurines to cereal   boxes were out in full force prior to it’s theatrical release. The Lord of The Rings  trilogy   has made millions in toy merchandise sales not counting the ever-popular fast food   promotions including Burger King.      Oddly with The Passion receiving flack on it’s apparent anti Semitic overtones   Shouldn’t the industry after rearing it’s ugly head once again let a film be a film.   Christianity and it’s own flock of followers control a $4 Billion to an estimated 5.6 billion   A year  empire .according to statistics provided by the Christian Booksellers   Association. T-shirts,, Plates etc.. displayed in a proud manner in the home are   representing ones beliefs in God , spirituality and themselves  But at the peak of Mel   Gibsons portrayal of the last 12 hours of Jesus’ life , amidst the bitter controversy,  media hoopla, we find this. The (God) almighty dollar. The Passion’ keychain, the coffee   mug all bearing the movies’ logo, picture-books from the movie, cannot be kept on shelves,   does the bible sell that much today or do we just continue to (thou shalt not)steal them from   hotel rooms. Then there’s the poster, the necklace, lapel pins, witness cards featuring themes such as   “Why Christ died for you’  complete with prayers. Are today’s youth purchasing   these items for their savior rests upon the cross depicted on these items? or is it a ‘got   got it , need it need it , trading system from the days when we cherished our baseball cards. What   must God be thinking right about now? I for one see a bolt of lightning striking the   forehead of Mr. Dwight Robinson, the marketing chief for Bob Siemons Designs who make   the witness cards and have sold over 1 Million of them since January. The  one item that   they can’t keep in stock mind you has too be the most ridiculous. The Nail. Yes the Nail   as in ‘driven through hands and feet. These are apparently to signify the spikes that had   kept Jesus stuck on that cross, long enough to keep up with the 10,000 a  day   demand for the these sacrilegious items of guilt that come complete with an inscription   from Isaiah ( by the way they come in two sizes) Critics and Human rights groups are   worried about the film?, I think the world has a much bigger problem to deal with   What a goddamned shame.   © 2004 E.S. Day  
    
</post>
<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey everyone!  E.S. Day here, sorry about the delay.  On this site you'll find a variety of published articles/reviews/commentary and of course interviews.  Please feel free to post any comments as well.  I'll also be posting snippets of articles, not yet published.  Parties interested in writing services may e-mail  esday@hotmail.com  www.edwardscottday.8k.com 
    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>
</post>
<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>
</post>
</Blog>