<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
                  The highest mountains, which are feeding the most rivers of Central Asia, beautiful canyons, hot valleys with subtropical climate, where cotton fields change into grape vines, apricot gardens and the highest plateaus, which complete on rigorous climate in Siberia- all this is Tajikistan. It is a sovereign country.             When describing the nature of this country you can’t do without the world “unique”. The lake Iskandar-kul is unique. It is as the pearl of Fan Mountain, the beloved place of the tourists of the world. Marghuzor lakes are also unique. You can’t compare their beauty with anything else in the world. Because every of them is a precious stone in the necklace of the beauty of colours.              Boris Nosik the writer who had been to many places of the world, wrote that he had often visited Tajikistan and he pointed out as “...the best place on the earth”. There may be a little exaggeration but anyhow he had a reason to state it. Tajikistan is unique not only by its climate conditions, has also the richest history. It is resting on the greatest civilization of the world.             Tajiks are the descendants of famous Bactria and Sogdiana. Many of archaeologists of the world aspire to Panjakent, one of the centers of ancient civilization. The famous Great Silk Way passed through Tajikistan. Ustrashan, now it is Uroteppa mentioned in the ancient manuscripts of the world. Once  Alexander the Great came to this town and took part in the holiday of Navrouz. He was charmed by its beauty. He wanted to make Navrouz the holiday of all his own land. But people’s tradions are not appear on the decree from upper state even if it was a genius military leader’s decree.             The archaeological finds and manuscripts state that the 1Y-Y centuries of AD was the period of consolidation of Tajiks ethnic. At that time there was formed a single whole territory, religion and language. In the Y century there appeared the first verse in Tajik language-dari. In the 1X century there was the complete formation of the Samanid Tajik State.             Tajiks inhabited nowadays Iranian Khorasan, Afganistan, Central Asia and south regions of  Kazakhstan of that period. The ancient cities of Central Asia which now are in Uzbekistan such as Bukhara, Samarkand were the monuments of the greatness of the Samanid State and the high culture of Tajiks. Related roods connect nowadays Tajiks with numerous nomadic and tribes of sakes inhabited the Pamires, Tien Shan, the valley of Sirdarya.             So, the Republic of Tajikistan. Switzerland became the model of beauty of mountainous countries. But Tajikistan may surpass it in some way. There are such places, which fascinate with clean beauty of human’s activity. The air is ideal clean. Flora is kept clean too. İt’s caused because of inaccessible places. There are no roads but paths and narrow roads. There is no any motorcar. So there one can find more than 400 kinds of ecologically clean medicine plants.             There is no wonder if you meet a brown bear Siberian goat, Asiatic leopard, Himalaya’s ular, Tibet wolf, and Asiatic muflon in the mountains. There are lots of other kinds of animals from various climate zones. They were not brought there on purpose. The contrast of landscape of Tajikistan, the contrast of the climate gives this variety of animals.             The Republic of Tajikistan is situated between 36 40 and 41 05 of the northern latitude and 67 31 and 75 14 of the eastern longitude. Tajikistan lies in the same latitudes of such countries as Italy, Spain and central part of Japan. Tajikistan occupies an area of over 143 thousand square kilometers, where live more than 6,5 mln people. It stretches from north to south in 350 kilometers and from west to east in 700 kilometers.             The total length of border is 3000 km. İn the south Tajikistan borders on Afganistan 1030 km, in the east on the People’s Republic of China 430 km. And in the west and north the main part of border on Kirghizistan and Uzbekistan.              The color of the map becomes lighter in the north and dark brown in the south. These are the colors of the mountains. The height on the map fluctuates from 500m(Vaksh valley) to 7,5km(The Pamirs) above the level of the sea.             Telling about Tajikistan you can’t do without word “the most”. It’s here where the highest ridge of mountains is situated: The Pamirs and a part of Tien-Shan. The powerful chains of mountains of Central Asia are Karakorum, Kuanglin and Hindukosh meet in the Pamirs. There is the highest peak-the peak of Ismail Samani (former Kommunism)(7495m), the highest mountainous salty lake Karakul (3941m), the biggest glacier-Fedchenko (the length is 77km, the thickness of the ice is above 800m).             In hydro energy resources Tajikistan takes first place in Central Asia. The total length of 947 rivers of Tajikistan is more than 28500km. Half part of ice-covered space in Central Asia belongs to Tajikistan.             There are more than 8000 glaciers with total area of 8,5 thousand square km, which surpasses sowing area of the Republic.             Geographical position of Tajikistan inside Eurasia is on the border of subtropical zones. This is the cause of peculiar climate. So as a matter of fact, there is high sun radiation, droughty, cloudless. The sun shines nearly all year round (an average quantity of the year hour are 2500-3000). Just cloudless sky during some months attracts there astrophysics from Europe, Asia, America. The Astrophysics Institute with its Hisar and Sanglokh observatories is well known to all scientists of the world. The main richness of Tajikistan is the sun. It gives favorable conditions for growing valuable sun loving cultures.]             There isn’t any need of advertising of some sorts of cotton, geranium, thin-skinned rich of vitamins Tajik lemons, Israfa apricots. By the way the wines are also very popular.              There are up to 40 species of fish in the rivers and lakes of Tojıkıston. Hunting is allowed to some kinds of animals, but many of them need preservation and protection and must be put in the Red Book. There are three reservations and 114 special reserved places. First of all it is the complex “Beshai palangon”(Bush of tigers) which was founded in 1938 to preserve the nature of southern deserts, the rivers of Central Asia, rate animals and plants. Recently there was founded reservation”Dashti Jum”. Its aim is to preserve the last population of the wild goat (morkhur) in Central Asia Mountain woods and valuable kinds of animals are reserve in Sarikhosor, Kamarob, Sangvor, Dashti Maidon, Childukhtaron and other reservations.             In the museums of Tojıkiston, especially at ethnography museum of Academy of Sciences there kept unique handicrafts of women’s decorations. They are made of gold, silver with precious of lal and other stones. Gold, silver and precious are not brought from anywhere, but it is the richness of Tajik land. Be the way they are being extracted from ancient ages. Today this list can be continued. Fs to mineral resources they are extracted up to 40 species. Nearly all known ore mineral are concentrated in three mountainous regions: in the north of country (Kurama and Mogoltau ridges) in the central pert (Zerafshan-Hisor zone) and in he Pamirs.             Geologists say that the whole Mendeleyev’s Periodic table is concentrated in the Pamirs. It means that three are practically all known ore minerals, but they can’t practically be extracted, though hold is washes there from ancient times. To prove it there are some old elaboration in Khovaling and Central Pamirs.             There are deposits of coal and oil in Tajikistan. But the most remarkable one is mineral water. And as matter of fact there are some sanatoriums and health resorts: Khoja Obigarm, Shambari, Yavros, Kaltuch, Obigarm is translated from Tajik as “holy hot water”. This health resort is situated in the mountains at the foot of famous Alpine meadows.             There are not only famous springs; they are also added by fresh clean mountainous air and by exotic landscape.             Garm-Chashma is the miracle of the Pamirs nature. It need not very much care to be among the best resorts of the world.             In summer lots of tourists from all parts country and from abroad come o Tajikistan and its capital-Dushanbe. Great is the wish of modern man to the places, where there isn’t any civilization, very little people and no industry.             There are a number of such places in Tajikistan in the mountain, where the air, the beauty of wild nature takes tension and stress and gives a person cheerfulness and relaxation. For example, it is Kamarov, Shirkent. It is not easy to get there. As people live very far there kept unique pistachio, maple, alycha groves, clean rivers and lakes. Tourist’s marsh on well know routs “Khutalli Kohistoni”, “To the blue lakes”, “on the snowman path”, “On the ridges of Pamirs –Alay”. They are met with great joy by inhabitants of rare mountain villages.             Statistic points out that only ten percent of population lives in mountains .As a rule people who live there are tall and slim. And in the mountain, which occupies 93 percent of the territory, is the realm of silence, rarely disturbed by slow-sides, and then in valleys, the life is very intensive. By the way, the passages of Anthon and Khaburabot (about 4000 m. above the level of the sea) where the cars and motorcars run all the time connect the Pamir with other regions.             Modern  cities, block of houses can’t live without comfort: hot water, central heating and gas. So this comfort, modern and architecture design decorate the oldest cities of Tajikistan: Khujand, Panjakent, Uroteppa, Kulob, and new ones Khorugh, Norak, Kayrokum, Kalininobod, Roughun.The most beautiful city is the capital of Tajikistan-Dushanbe, the population of which is more than a million people. These are industrial centers. The biggest industry centers are situated there. Kayrokum is well known with its carpets factory. Its production of carpets is spread all over republic.             A very beautiful and exotic is the town of Norak. It is buried in verdure. The road from Dushanbe to Norak lies through the passage Chormaghzak. Norak is famous for its electric power station, which supplies Tajikistan with cheap electricity. Must be said the power station in Norak is unique one. Many foreign experts were against building the dam 300 m in height, in seismic dangerous zone. Russian and Tajik scientist-seismologists approved it, because they carried out series experiments on the dam model.             More than twenty years this miracle of hydro technical mastership gives to people light and heat. It gives the light to all kishlaks in Hisor valley; it gives the energy to such power consuming enterprises like Tajik aluminum plant, Yovon electrochemical plant, and Tursunzoda china plant. Tajikistan has at its disposal vast potential of industry. It has 120 branches and 430 industry enterprises. Here should be related Tajik plant of textile machine- building, Vakhsh nitric plant Kurgontepa transformer-building plant, giant of textile industry of Dushanbe industrial corporation “Tajiktextile”. Silk-mils and canning industry are concentrated in Dushanbe and Khujand.Mining and chemical industry is developed in the north of Tajikistan. Putting into operation gold production in the towns of Chkalovsk and Tajik-Britesh joint venture in Panjakent  create conditions ear solving the important strategically taks-getting the high quality production on the level of world standards, creation of gold reserve in country, revival of jewelry production from local stuff.              Some words must be said about training of specialist and national ducation. There are 15 universities and technical schools. Tajik Techical University prepared thousands specialist such as engineers, builders, energetic, motor workers for the country. The Technological Institute adds specialist, who graduated from this educational establishment work in all parts of Tajikistan.It. Student of this institute go abroad to go better practice and to learn new technology and production.              The diplomas of Medical University, Tajik National State University, and Institute of Arts are highly appreciated. The scientific researches in the Republic are coordinated by the center, which is the Academy of sciences. It is founded more than 50 years ago and includes many scientific centers and laboratories where works about 3000 scientists solving the problems connected with economy, mathematics, geology, medicine, astrophysics etc.             The name of the famous Tajik historian academician Bobojon Ghafurov is highly spoken is many countries of the world. Tajiks are pound of such scientists as A.Bahovaddinov, S.Umarov, P.Bobojonov, and S.negmatulloev who greatly contributed in the development of   Tajik sciences.             We should mention the Institute of Language and literature by Rudaki, where recommendations to the Law of government language were developed. The Institute of Oriental studies and manuscripts reserve invaluable grant of the past. Scientists of the Institute introduce readers to wisdom of ancient philosophers and historians.             The Institute of seismology must be mentioned particularly. It is well known all over the world by its works and discoveries in the field of long-termed prognosis of earthquake. Especially must be mentioned names of specialists who are well known not only in Tajikistan but in the world of science abroad too. These are the names of Prof. H.Mansurov  the director Institute of gastroenterology, Prof. A.Pulatov the children surgeon, U.Ishoki, M.Gulomov, K.Tojiev etc. These doctors-scientists are caring on the traditions laid by the great Avicenna.             Much work is done by the Institute of geology, where they investigate mineral reserves of country.              It is already mentioned that there are more that 6,5 mln people in Tajikistan. So 1 mln.325 thousand from them are pupils, this is the whole state. They are taught by 90 thousands of teachers.             There are the Ayni Opera and Bullet, the Mayakovki Russian Drama, the Lohuty State Academic Drama theatres. On playbills one can meet only the names of east authors but also European. M.Vohidov Youth theatre is very popular Tajikistan.             There are some interesting dancing ensembles “Zebo”, “Lola”, “Jahonoro”. They go on tour to other countries also. Folk dances, melodies of “Shashmakom”, opera, bullet, drama old and new traditional competitions of bullet masters after Malika Sabirova bullet dancer, whose name is among best world stars.             Great was success among drama amateurs of national actor Hoshim Gadoev in the play “Edip” in the main role Tajik drama theatre after Lohuti was founded in thirtieth and gave a number of magnificent names such as M.Kasimov (farukh Kosimov is his son). T.Fozilova, S.Tuybaeva, A.Burhonov, H.Rahmatulloev and many others. We should also mention two wonderful singers. H.Mavlonova- opera singer and B.Ishokova- singer of Tajik classic songs, works of modern composers T.Shahidy, F.Soliev, F.Bshor and others. The songs of Akashrif Juraev, Odina Hoshim, Jurabek Murodov, Zafar Nozimov, Karomatullo Kurbonov are very popularly among the Tajik people.             In Tajikistan when people want to say something pleasant they say. “As handsome as a poet”, “As wise as a poet”.             There is some poetic in the nation’s blood. Tajiks have very rich literary heritage. These are their names: Rudaki, Firdavsi, Nosir Khisrav, Rumi, Khayom, Sadi, Hafız, Kamol Khujandi, Abdurahman Jomi and many other stars in the bright poetic world. So the stream of poetry couldn’t dry up today as many ages ago.             There are new names which became classics of nowadays: S.Ayni, A.Lohuti, M.Tursunzade, B.Rahimzoda, J.Ikrami, R.Jalil, S. Ulugzoda, Poets and writers of the lates period are A.Shukuhi, F.Muhammadiev, V. Kanoat, L.Sherali, B.Sobir, U. Kuhzod, Gulruhsor, A.Samadov, A.Hakim. The list may be continued.              There are famous producers of the films, whose names are well-known not only in Tajikistan, the names of B.Kimyoganov with his serial films on “Shohnoma” by Firdavsi, T.Sobirov, D.Khudonazarov, B.Sodikov’s films make a person suffer and take what is on to heart feel keenly what happens with his heroes.             Tajikistan is also famous for its libraries. The oldest National library is after Firdavsi. In its richest fund there are hundred thousands of books published by publishing house: “Irfon”, “Adib”, “Donish” and “Tajik Encyclopedia”.             Much can be said about the wonderful people of this country, its talented national healers, about the towns, where on can see combined Asiatic and European architecture, about famous Tajik cooking the art which is ancient, but it is better to come and see everything with your own eyes. There is very good saying in the east: “Seeing once is better than hearing twice”.             At present in the country carries out reforms and structure rebuilding of economics. Bank system and business, privatization and market are developed.             For increasing of efficiency of national economy foreign investments are attracted, joint ventures are created too, in particular for working mineral resources.             Today the foreign policy of the Republic of Tajikistan is based on mutual benefit and equality relations with all states, participation in strengthening of peace and international security. Tajikistan aspires to develop trade- economical cooperation with states of the region and world.             It is very important to have motor-highway and railways for extending trade-economical relations and the Government of the Republic of Tajikistan attaches great importance to it.  
     
    
</post>
<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      By Muzaffar HUDOYKULOV* Music and poetry are two spheres of art that are very close in every country, they always stand together, especially in the case of the Tajik people. The great poet Abuabdullo Rudaki was an excellent singer and musican, he even invented a new musical instrument. Many poets were also the performers of their works. Not a single festival took place without folk singers, musicans, dancers and funny buffoons, and without the maskaraboz- circus performers. By tradition to this day people are summoned to festivals by the trumpet sounds of the very long karnais, and even on ordinary days one often hears in the streets hte sounds of the doira, a tambourine, and the pensive sound of the nai. As to the rubob, it can be found in every home. Melodies from the shashmakom, a wonderful musical work of the past that was recorded on sheet music only in modern times, are known and loved in the country. The Tajik composers Z. Shakhidi, Sh. Saifiddinov, A. Saliev, D. Dusmukhamedov, A. Khamdamov, Ya. Sabzanov, A. Odinayev, Kh. Abdullayev and others preserve with care the traditions of classical and folk music, develop and enrich it with new forms. The Tajik music lovers now know the light music, pieces for single instruments and orchestra-symphonies, operas and ballets. The capital of the Republic has an opera and ballet theatre, three drama theatres, a philharmonic society, a symphony orchestra, and several song and dance companies. There are theatres also in other towns of Tajikistan. Professional training in music and the art is offered by the Art Institute, by music and art schools, and by studios functioning at theatres. Many envoys of Tajikistan  study in the country’s best establishments of higher learning. Music schools and palaces of culture, people’s theatres and people’s universities of culture, amateur art groups draw both children and adults into the world of music and art. In the past, the galaxy of cultural workers includes People’s Artists of the USSR M. Kasymov, A. Burkhanov, T. Fazylova, the singers Kh. Mavlyanova, B. Iskhakova  and A. Bobokulov. The star of Tajik ballet, People’s Artist of the USSR Malika Sabirova, a winner of the International Ballet Dancers Competition, is known by the whole country and she has performed in the best theatres of the world- Moscow and Sant Petersburg, London and Rome, Tokyo and Berlin, Delhi and Montreal.  Staged in Tajik theatres are works not only of local authors but also of Russian and world classics- Ostrovsky, Chehov, Gogol, Shakespeare, Moliere. Prize at the best festivals have been won by such films produced by Tajikfilm studio as “A poet’s destiny” and “Rustam and Sukhrob”, and “The death of a usurer”. The Republic’s composers and film makers, writers and artists are united in creative professional unions. Folk masters are continuing and developing the traditional handicrafts- wood and ganchu carvers, chasers, ceramics and pattern designers. A monograph was published recently about the prominent ornamentalist M. Olimov who worked in the “kundal” style. His ornaments adorn the famous “Rokhat” tea house in Dushanbe. As to this prospectus, dear reader, it is a small gift to you, a memento. We will be very happy if you come to like our mountainous country, described by poets as a land at the foot of the sun. Come and visit us...   Source: Books from Soviet Tajikistan * Ankara University, Faculty of Law  
     
    
</post>
<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      İnsan var olduğu günden bu yana hep hürriyet arayışı içinde olmuştur. Bu arayış yer yer onun kendi iradesini sezişi ve onu tam gerçekleştirmeye çalışması, zaman zaman da dinle, devletle, hatta örf, adet ve ahlakla savaşması şeklinde cereyan etmiştir. 2003 senesinin Mart ayında uluslararası gençlik festivalinde (ISFiT) Norveç’in Trondheim şehrinde katılımcılar arasındaydım. Batıdan gelen gençlerle “Doğu toplulukların mevcut durumlarını ve intihar eylemleri”ni tartışıyorduk, ama anlamaya çok zorlanıyorlardı. Nasıl bir ruh hali, insanın canına göz göre göre kıyabilirdi? Batı ülkelerin vatandaşlarını ürküten, anlayamadıkları bir olaydı bu.  “Bu kadar büyük bir cani olabilmek için insanlıktan nasibini almamış olmak gerek” gibi cümleler söyledi katılımcılar.  Oysa insanlığın görmediği tür katliamlar, seri cinayetler Batı'da meydana  gelebiliyordu. İnanmayan Michael Moore’un yaptığı belgesellere, aktüalite programlarına bakabilirler.   Batı toplumları, bu resimler yayınlandıktan sonra bir insanın nasıl canavara dönüşebildiğini belki biraz anlayabilir. İnsanlık dışı işkenceler, akıl almaz iğrençlikler sergilerken, bir de kameralara “işlem tamam” işareti yapan bayanın yüzündeki tebessümü gördünüz mü? Sanki normal bir fabrika işçisiymiş de rutin bir vardiyada görevini yerine getiriyormuş gibi… Şimdi kendinizi bir Iraklı yerine koyun ve eşinize, dostunuza, kocanıza, karınıza, ananıza, babanıza bunların yapıldığını varsayın. Bakalım ne hissedeceksiniz?  Bunu yapanlar bir de karşınıza çıkıp, size özgürlük ve insanlık getirdiğini iddia ederse ve hiç kimseye hesap vermeyeceklerini bile bile bunları yaparsa ne yaparsınız? Onlara sistematik karşı koyma gücünüz yoksa, çaresizlik ve bu acziyet tepenize binmişse nasıl bir ruh hali takınırsınız? Şark coğrafıyasında onur ve izzet-i nefs hayattan çok daha önemlidir. Dahası cennet ve cehennem temennilerinden de önemli algılanırlar. İntihar saldırıları dine sığmaz, ahlak kaldırmaz, vicdan kabul edilmez. Ama onuru zedelenmiş bir adam için oldukça rasyonel bir tavırdır. Amerikalılar Irak esirleri ne şekilde konuşturmayı planlıyordu bilinmez; ama birçoğunun canlı bomba olup konuşacakları da şüphe götürmez. Demem o ki, bu işkenceci ruh halinin, ne farkı var canlı bombadan? Yıllar boyu bir psikopat diktatörün çizmesi altında ezilmek. Sonra bambaşka kültürlerden, dillerden askerlerin botlarının altında çiğnenmek. Ne büyük bir imtihandır bu? Ne farkı var Sadam ile bu işkenceci işgalcilerin? Ne değişti Irakta?  Daha önce de o hapishanelerde çürütülüyorlardı, şimdi de üstelik işgal güçlerinin hayasız bin bir çeşit sadist uygulamalarıyla gururları, onurları, erkeklikleri, kadınlıkları yerle bir ediliyor. Bu mudur Batının vaat ettiği demokrasi, bu mudur insanca yaşamak? Amerikan ve İngiliz askerlerinin Iraklılara yaptığı işkenceler dünyayı ayağa kaldırıldı. Hele “Daily Mirror”  gazetesinin, bir İngiliz askerinin, başına çuval geçiren çekilmiş fotoğrafını yayınlanması herkesi dehşete düşürdü.  	Amerikan ve İngiliz askerlerinin Iraklılara yaptıkları, ilk bakışta dehşet verici görünüyor. Batılıların cibilliyeti araştırılıp sorgulandığında ise Iraklılara yapılan insanlık dışı işkencelerin hiç de şaşırtmıyor insanları….  1	Köleleri, vahşi kaplanlı arenalara mancınıkla atanlar, ne Asyalıydı, ne de Afrikalı, Avrupalıydılar. 2	İnsanları gaz odalarında veya Auschwitz kamplarında ölüme gönderen Hitler, ne Asyalıydı ne de Afrikalı, Avrupalıydı.  3	Engizisyon mahkemeleri Asya veya Afrika’da değil, Avrupa’da kurulmuştu.  İsviçreli tarihçi Walter Nigg, bakın neler anlatıyor: Baş parmağı sıkarak  işkence yapmaya yaran alet şöyle kullanılırdı… parmaklar mengenelere yerleştirir ve kemikler kırılana, kan fışkırana kadar aletin vidaları sıkılır. Suçlu, demir işkence sandalyesine de oturtulabilirdi. Bu sandalyenin sivrileştirilmiş demir çiviler vardı. Çiviler korlaşana dek aşağıdan ısıtılır, sonra da kurban üzerine oturtulurdu. Bot denilen işkence aleti ise kaval kemiğini kırmak için kullanırdı. Diğer popüler işkence yöntemi ise kişiyi askı ya da  tekerleğe bağlayıp, iki tarafında kol ve bacakları kırılıncaya kadar germekti. Bu arada bedenin üzerine taşlarla ağırlık yapılırdı. İşkencecilerin çığlıklara rahatsız olamaması için de kurbanın ağzı bezle kapatılırdı. Üç dört saat süren işkenceler çok yaygındı. Bu işlemler sırasında, işkence aletlerine devamlı kutsal su dökülürdü.  Kendi soylarından olan insanların sırf Katolik ve Protestan ayrımı yüzünden böylesi bir vahşeti reva görenlerin bugün Irak’ta Müslümanlara yaptıkları çok görmemeli! Eskiden işkence aletlerinin kutsal su döküyorlardı, şimdi işkence yaptıkları insanların üstüne işiyorlar! Onuru kırılan, işkence gören her Iraklı önce kendi günah galerimizi bize anımsatmalı. Cezaevi baskınlarını yanlı veren, insanlık dışı işkenceleri görmezden gelen, güce tapan medyanın başkasının üzerinden günah çıkartması inandırıcı olmuyor!  Dünyada bir tarihi gerçek (factoid) vardır. Bütün büyük İmparatorluklar son 15-20 yıllarını  savaşarak geçirmişlerdir. Örnek vermek gerekirse, Bizans İmparatorluğu, Roma İmparatorluğu, Osmanlı İmparatorluğu, Avusturya-Macaristan İmparatorluğu ve geçen yüzyıllımızın son İmparatorluğu sayılan SSCB  aynı akıbete  nail olmuştur… 
     
    
</post>
<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       MIDDLE EAST : 2 + 1 = PEACE FOREVER    By Muzaffardjon R. KHUDOIKULOV     I will start my work with peace. We have all to be friends and brothers to quiet down the situation. I will try my best to achieve these goals. Emomali Sh. Rahmonov    Middle East: The Key to the Global Economical, Political and Strategic Balances   After World War I (by the Lozan Treaty in 24 July 1923) map of the Middle East drawn by Lord George and Winston Churchill caused many confrontations and problems in the region. Along with the internal structures, of the states the politics of super powers seeking strategic interests caused  dramatic events. Super powers sought hegemonic politics over the region and in order to strength their influence over the region they successfully used social and political structure of the region. They took advantage of the clashes between different social groups of Middle Eastern peoples and even created some false clashes between the people and traing to implement their hegemonic politics with coercive means. They tended to set up the rules of the political game within the  region. These super power offered a model that drawn the boundaries of the politics and a model that tells what  is freedom. They manipulated the masses directly or indirectly. But all this coercive politics came to its limits. In the 20’th century war was seen as the only means to solve and settle the disputes. However, today we are coming to a point in which the war war is  exhausted. Region of the people with great sufferings have learned that war is not a solution. There established a social ground for compromise. Another factor that enforced people to think for alternative ways of solution other  than war was the socioeconomic conditions of the region. Each war had severe impact on the  economy of the region and raised the dependency on external powers. Petroleum rich countries  became the  victim of their greed for enormous arming expenses and thus countries in debt. Countries that are not petroleum producers have been affected badly from this instability of the  region. Agricultural and industrial production decreased, investments stopped because of the low  accumulation of capital, and they lost their compatibility in the international market. Economic  crises increased the social contradictions. Social problems started to shake the instable regimes.  States that were influenced by these developments obliged to enter the process of compromise. As a result, we may claim that the process of compromise in the Middle East started with the effects of  internal and external dynamics. (Yavuz Gökalp Yıldız, Global Stratejide Ortadoğu, Krizler  Sorunlar ve Politikalar; [Middle East in the Global Strategy, Crises, Problems and Politics] 2000; DER Publication).   Negotiation basis   The Middle East question has its origin in the issue of the status of Palestine. In 1947, Palestine was a Territory administered by the United Kingdom under a Mandate from the League of  Nations: it had a population of some 2 million, two thirds of Arabs and one third of Jews. The General  Assembly in 1947 endorsed a plan, prepared by the United Nations Special Committee on Palestine, for the partition of the Territory: it provided for the creation of an Arab and a Jewish  State, with Jerusalem under international status. The plan was not accepted by the Palestine  Arabs or by the Arab States. (Basic Facts about United Nations, United Nation Publication, July 1998, New York).   “Bona Fide” in Middle East Peace   In the Bible, two universal elements “justice and peace” are constently associated with  Jerusalem. Israel has created the reality of coexistence. It must now grant the Palestinians the  right to live their lives with dignity. In turn, the Palestinians will have to create new conditions,  consistent with Israel’s reality that will enable them to exercise their political independence in  part of east Jerusalem as their capital. This way both Israel and the Palestinians will find that Jerusalem will play its pre-ordained role as the catalyst for an overall settlement of the Israel- Palestinian discord and for permanent peace. (Foundation for Middle East Peace current analysis, A conference on prospects for a shared Jerusalem, Prof. Alon Ben-Meir, New University of Social Research). According to the belief “God threw a stone toward Earth, and everywhere where it passed it gave  a life. It created mountains, rivers, seas, forests and all the living habitats. After it landed on the  so assumed center of Earth, Jerusalem”. All the time through the history, the belief of Jerusalem  of being the center of Earth was the cause to many conflicts between nations. For the last  4000 years one may account for a lot of conflicts due to mixing of different religions and their  further challenges. If we fix one end of compass on Hayber and draw a circle of radius 1500 km. we will have within its boundaries the lands of countries such as Mesopotamia, South Eastern  Anatolia, Syria, Palestine, Eastern Mediterrianean, Egypt, Ethiopia and whole Arabia Peninsula  with Basra Gulf and the Red Sea. In Neolithic era, since classes were formed in this region, together  with the classes the sovereignity spirit also became stronger. Most of the groups originated there belong to the group of same language. Arabs and Hebrew are constituting the vast majority  of the Middle East culture. Although they are always conflicting they can be named brothers  because they have the resembling religion and language. (Süleyman Özmen; Ortadoğu'da etnik,  dini çatışmalar ve İsrail; [Ethnical and religious conflicts in Middle East and Israel]; March  2002; IQ Cultural Publication ).   Clashes in Holy Places   One of the holy places of Jerusalem, the “Last Dinner Room” and the mausoleum of the prophet  David if observed from above are the places where the conflict well known as “holy” are worth  solutions. The prophet David’s gate and the mausoleum are located a hundred steps away from each  other and the former is being known as a holy place for Christians and the latter as a holy place  for Jewish. These are found within the boundaries of the same Mosque which was first established by  Byzantine Empire as a church but later transformed into Mosque by Otoman Empire.  In the lower part of this building accomodates the tomb of prophet David and the upper portion of  the building bears the honour of being the place where Jesus the Christ had eaten his last dinner.  When looked at different projections one may observe that in horizontal projection they are in the  same place but in the vertical one they do occupy different places. This event is known as the Upper  Lower Floor Difference and it has a potential of being either a conflict or a key model to peace. As told  in a hadith prior to the creation of human being the angels formed a “circumambulation hose”  around Kaaba (not to be misinterpreted) and the illustration of the fire colon in the house of the  worship of Moses and formation of the holy path to the gates of heavens in Jerusalem the Christian belief shows that the holy place has its boundaries in horizontal dimentions but it  is continuous in vertical dimentions. This is also so because neither prophet David is disturbed by  the presence of  traces left by Christians, nor Jesus is disturbed by the presence of grandchildren of those who killed him. Moreover none of them is disturbed by the transformation of the church where they are resting into the Mosque by the Kanuni Sultan, the emperor of the Otoman Empire.    Now if we leave all these facts apart we may state that neither the upper one influences the lower  holy place nor the upper holy part undergoes the influence of those who feel passion to the lower  part. Thus if it would be possible to apply this model of solution to all holy places in Jerusalem,  that is if one could come up with the idea of not taking half of Halil Ibrahim mosque in Al-Halil  but building some extra floors, and for instance if Arafat not insisted on taking the lower portion  of Kubetussahra Mosque (leaving apart the doubts that Jewish tried to excavate the basis of  mosque to destroy it) and accepted the upper floor offered to him by Barak and if for instance the  building established on the tomb of prophet Joseph in the time of deep conflicts were destroyed  and rebuilt to have two storeys and if each of these storeys were submitted to the representatives  of different religions, the conflict which cost thousands of lives would not be at least due to the religious aspects, and therefore neither the Jewish nor the Christians and Muslims would feel the inferiority complex when the word “conflict” is mentioned.  People must understand the way  that prophets David and Jesus succeed to live under one roof built by Ottoman, so that Moses,  Jesus and Mustafa [Muhammad] be able to live in peace and harmony in one city of our planet.  (Kerim Balci; Jan. 26, 2003; Article from Zaman Newspaper).    2 + 1 = Peace forever    As you well know the platform for resolving the problems arising in the international arena is the  United Nations’ (UN). If we approach the subject from this aspect, the arena for the  implementation of the solutions on Israel-Palestine dispute, which concerns almost the entire  world, should also be the UN. In short, only the projects to be produced by the UN can bring a common reconciliation on the subject. The parties concerned must first participate in discussion on the proposals for solution and must make mutual sacrifices. Concentrating on the  status of Jerusalem, which is the core of the dispute, is important. Therefore, in order to reach an  agreement on Israel- Palestine dispute, it is necessary to work on the proposal for the solution to define the status of the city of Jerusalem which lies at the heart of the dispute.  Hundreds of  researches have been and are being conducted on the Middle East. Without doubt, the focal  point of most of these researches, is to establish peace in this holy land of the spiritual  religions. Radical reforms are necessary to reach permanent peace in the Middle East. Unless the parties are open to “solutions” other than their own, it is not possible to talk about peace.  Today, the existence of a Palestinian state in the Middle East, is as real as the existence of an  Israeli state. In these lands, which began to take shape after WWII, the differences of opinion on land between the “kin” cause more lives to be lost and the situation is working against them. The  land of prophets is shedding tears of blood.  Jerusalem was a city inhabited by nations long before  the revelation of spiritual religions and has maintained its importance in every era of history.  Therefore, the UN, whose role in insuring cooperation among world nations and consequently,  establishing peace, cannot be denied, should move to Jerusalem. In this way, the world community would be more sensitive for achieving peace in the Middle East. According to the UN plan made in 1947, it was intended to give this city an international status. This organization is playing a key role in the 21st century also to solve the Middle East problem. Some authors say  that the problem can be solved by establishing “two capitals” on these soils. There is talk by some people of unilateral compromise. However, such “solutions” only provoke the parties and do not serve any purpose other than deepening the differences of opinion.  We propose that both parties, in fact all parties concerned, come together, as soon as possible, and solve the dispute  with a rational, realistic “lose-lose” principle, that verifies the “win-win” principle in the long run, in which both parties will have to make sacrifices and come to an agreement.  Consequently, moving the headquarters of the United Nations from New York to Jerusalem, will contribute both to world peace, and to obtain more productive results from the “holy” cities of the world. Within  this framework, all the responsibility and authority for the administration of the city should be  transferred to the United Nations. This matter should be acted upon as soon as possible. As in the  past, without prejudice to all other international arrangements, all the nations of the world should recognize Tel-Aviv as the capital of Israel and Gaza as the capital of Palestine.   AUTHOR BIO: Muzaffardjon R. KHUDOIKULOV is the chairman of “Vatan” Club, (the club of Tajikistan youth in Turkey and Cyprus), founder of the “Patriot” Newsmagazine, “Universe News Agency” and Editor of analytical web-site “Kabutar”.  Senior student at Ankara University, Faculty of Law.  This article was presentated on March 7’th – 16’th 2003 in International Student Festival in Trondheim (ISFiT) / Norway. The original article you can take by sending mail to :  muzaffar@lawyer.com      
     
    
</post>
<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       İnsan var olduğu günden bu yana hep hürriyet arayışı içinde olmuştur. Bu arayış yer yer onun kendi iradesini sezişi ve onu tam gerçekleştirmeye çalışması, zaman zaman da dinle, devletle, hatta örf, adet ve ahlakla savaşması şeklinde cereyan etmiştir.2003 senesinin Mart ayında uluslararası gençlik festivalinde (ISFiT) Norveç’in Trondheim şehrinde katılımcılar arasındaydım. Batıdan gelen gençlerle “Doğu toplulukların mevcut durumlarını ve intihar eylemleri”ni tartışıyorduk, ama anlamaya çok zorlanıyorlardı. Nasıl bir ruh hali, insanın canına göz göre göre kıyabilirdi? Batı ülkelerin vatandaşlarını ürküten, anlayamadıkları bir olaydı bu. “Bu kadar büyük bir cani olabilmek için insanlıktan nasibini almamış olmak gerek” gibi cümleler söyledi katılımcılar. Oysa insanlığın görmediği tür katliamlar, seri cinayetler Batı'da meydana gelebiliyordu. İnanmayan Michael Moore’un yaptığı belgesellere, aktüalite programlarına bakabilirler. Batı toplumları, bu resimler yayınlandıktan sonra bir insanın nasıl canavara dönüşebildiğini belki biraz anlayabilir. İnsanlık dışı işkenceler, akıl almaz iğrençlikler sergilerken, bir de kameralara “işlem tamam” işareti yapan bayanın yüzündeki tebessümü gördünüz mü? Sanki normal bir fabrika işçisiymiş de rutin bir vardiyada görevini yerine getiriyormuş gibi…Şimdi kendinizi bir Iraklı yerine koyun ve eşinize, dostunuza, kocanıza, karınıza, ananıza, babanıza bunların yapıldığını varsayın. Bakalım ne hissedeceksiniz? Bunu yapanlar bir de karşınıza çıkıp, size özgürlük ve insanlık getirdiğini iddia ederse ve hiç kimseye hesap vermeyeceklerini bile bile bunları yaparsa ne yaparsınız? Onlara sistematik karşı koyma gücünüz yoksa, çaresizlik ve bu acziyet tepenize binmişse nasıl bir ruh hali takınırsınız?Şark coğrafıyasında onur ve izzet-i nefs hayattan çok daha önemlidir. Dahası cennet ve cehennem temennilerinden de önemli algılanırlar. İntihar saldırıları dine sığmaz, ahlak kaldırmaz, vicdan kabul edilmez. Ama onuru zedelenmiş bir adam için oldukça rasyonel bir tavırdır. Amerikalılar Irak esirleri ne şekilde konuşturmayı planlıyordu bilinmez; ama birçoğunun canlı bomba olup konuşacakları da şüphe götürmez.Demem o ki, bu işkenceci ruh halinin, ne farkı var canlı bombadan? Yıllar boyu bir psikopat diktatörün çizmesi altında ezilmek. Sonra bambaşka kültürlerden, dillerden askerlerin botlarının altında çiğnenmek. Ne büyük bir imtihandır bu? Ne farkı var Sadam ile bu işkenceci işgalcilerin? Ne değişti Irakta? Daha önce de o hapishanelerde çürütülüyorlardı, şimdi de üstelik işgal güçlerinin hayasız bin bir çeşit sadist uygulamalarıyla gururları, onurları, erkeklikleri, kadınlıkları yerle bir ediliyor. Bu mudur Batının vaat ettiği demokrasi, bu mudur insanca yaşamak?Amerikan ve İngiliz askerlerinin Iraklılara yaptığı işkenceler dünyayı ayağa kaldırıldı. Hele “Daily Mirror” gazetesinin, bir İngiliz askerinin, başına çuval geçiren çekilmiş fotoğrafını yayınlanması herkesi dehşete düşürdü. Amerikan ve İngiliz askerlerinin Iraklılara yaptıkları, ilk bakışta dehşet verici görünüyor. Batılıların cibilliyeti araştırılıp sorgulandığında ise Iraklılara yapılan insanlık dışı işkencelerin hiç de şaşırtmıyor insanları…. 1 Köleleri, vahşi kaplanlı arenalara mancınıkla atanlar, ne Asyalıydı, ne de Afrikalı, Avrupalıydılar. 2 İnsanları gaz odalarında veya Auschwitz kamplarında ölüme gönderen Hitler, ne Asyalıydı ne de Afrikalı, Avrupalıydı. 3 Engizisyon mahkemeleri Asya veya Afrika’da değil, Avrupa’da kurulmuştu.  İsviçreli tarihçi Walter Nigg, bakın neler anlatıyor: Baş parmağı sıkarak işkence yapmaya yaran alet şöyle kullanılırdı… parmaklar mengenelere yerleştirir ve kemikler kırılana, kan fışkırana kadar aletin vidaları sıkılır. Suçlu, demir işkence sandalyesine de oturtulabilirdi. Bu sandalyenin sivrileştirilmiş demir çiviler vardı. Çiviler korlaşana dek aşağıdan ısıtılır, sonra da kurban üzerine oturtulurdu. Bot denilen işkence aleti ise kaval kemiğini kırmak için kullanırdı. Diğer popüler işkence yöntemi ise kişiyi askı ya da tekerleğe bağlayıp, iki tarafında kol ve bacakları kırılıncaya kadar germekti. Bu arada bedenin üzerine taşlarla ağırlık yapılırdı. İşkencecilerin çığlıklara rahatsız olamaması için de kurbanın ağzı bezle kapatılırdı. Üç dört saat süren işkenceler çok yaygındı. Bu işlemler sırasında, işkence aletlerine devamlı kutsal su dökülürdü. Kendi soylarından olan insanların sırf Katolik ve Protestan ayrımı yüzünden böylesi bir vahşeti reva görenlerin bugün Irak’ta Müslümanlara yaptıkları çok görmemeli! Eskiden işkence aletlerinin kutsal su döküyorlardı, şimdi işkence yaptıkları insanların üstüne işiyorlar!Onuru kırılan, işkence gören her Iraklı önce kendi günah galerimizi bize anımsatmalı. Cezaevi baskınlarını yanlı veren, insanlık dışı işkenceleri görmezden gelen, güce tapan medyanın başkasının üzerinden günah çıkartması inandırıcı olmuyor! Dünyada bir tarihi gerçek (factoid) vardır. Bütün büyük İmparatorluklar son 15-20 yıllarını savaşarak geçirmişlerdir. Örnek vermek gerekirse, Bizans İmparatorluğu, Roma İmparatorluğu, Osmanlı İmparatorluğu, Avusturya-Macaristan İmparatorluğu ve geçen yüzyıllımızın son İmparatorluğu sayılan SSCB aynı akıbete nail olmuştur… 
     

    
</post>
<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      By Muzaffardjon R. KHUDOIKULOV              The highest mountains, which are feeding the most rivers of Central Asia, beautiful canyons, hot valleys with subtropical climate, where cotton fields change into grape vines, apricot gardens and the highest plateaus, which complete on rigorous climate in Siberia- all this is Tajikistan. It is a sovereign country.             When describing the nature of this country you can’t do without the world “unique”. The lake Iskandar-kul is unique. It is as the pearl of Fan Mountain, the beloved place of the tourists of the world. Marghuzor lakes are also unique. You can’t compare their beauty with anything else in the world. Because every of them is a precious stone in the necklace of the beauty of colours.             Boris Nosik the writer who had been to many places of the world, wrote that he had often visited Tajikistan and he pointed out as “...the best place on the earth”. There may be a little exaggeration but anyhow he had a reason to state it. Tajikistan is unique not only by its climate conditions, has also the richest history. It is resting on the greatest civilization of the world.             Tajiks are the descendants of famous Bactria and Sogdiana. Many of archaeologists of the world aspire to Panjakent, one of the centers of ancient civilization. The famous Great Silk Way passed through Tajikistan. Ustrashan, now it is Uroteppa mentioned in the ancient manuscripts of the world. Once  Alexander the Great came to this town and took part in the holiday of Navrouz. He was charmed by its beauty. He wanted to make Navrouz the holiday of all his own land. But people’s tradions are not appear on the decree from upper state even if it was a genius military leader’s decree.             The archaeological finds and manuscripts state that the 1Y-Y centuries of AD was the period of consolidation of Tajiks ethnic. At that time there was formed a single whole territory, religion and language. In the Y century there appeared the first verse in Tajik language-dari. In the 1X century there was the complete formation of the Samanid Tajik State.             Tajiks inhabited nowadays Iranian Khorasan, Afganistan, Central Asia and south regions of  Kazakhstan of that period. The ancient cities of Central Asia which now are in Uzbekistan such as Bukhara, Samarkand were the monuments of the greatness of the Samanid State and the high culture of Tajiks. Related roods connect nowadays Tajiks with numerous nomadic and tribes of sakes inhabited the Pamires, Tien Shan, the valley of Sirdarya.             So, the Republic of Tajikistan. Switzerland became the model of beauty of mountainous countries. But Tajikistan may surpass it in some way. There are such places, which fascinate with clean beauty of human’s activity. The air is ideal clean. Flora is kept clean too. İt’s caused because of inaccessible places. There are no roads but paths and narrow roads. There is no any motorcar. So there one can find more than 400 kinds of ecologically clean medicine plants.             There is no wonder if you meet a brown bear Siberian goat, Asiatic leopard, Himalaya’s ular, Tibet wolf, and Asiatic muflon in the mountains. There are lots of other kinds of animals from various climate zones. They were not brought there on purpose. The contrast of landscape of Tajikistan, the contrast of the climate gives this variety of animals.             The Republic of Tajikistan is situated between 36 40 and 41 05 of the northern latitude and 67 31 and 75 14 of the eastern longitude. Tajikistan lies in the same latitudes of such countries as Italy, Spain and central part of Japan. Tajikistan occupies an area of over 143 thousand square kilometers, where live more than 6,5 mln people. It stretches from north to south in 350 kilometers and from west to east in 700 kilometers.             The total length of border is 3000 km. İn the south Tajikistan borders on Afganistan 1030 km, in the east on the People’s Republic of China 430 km. And in the west and north the main part of border on Kirghizistan and Uzbekistan.             The color of the map becomes lighter in the north and dark brown in the south. These are the colors of the mountains. The height on the map fluctuates from 500m(Vaksh valley) to 7,5km(The Pamirs) above the level of the sea.             Telling about Tajikistan you can’t do without word “the most”. It’s here where the highest ridge of mountains is situated: The Pamirs and a part of Tien-Shan. The powerful chains of mountains of Central Asia are Karakorum, Kuanglin and Hindukosh meet in the Pamirs. There is the highest peak-the peak of Ismail Samani (former Kommunism)(7495m), the highest mountainous salty lake Karakul (3941m), the biggest glacier-Fedchenko (the length is 77km, the thickness of the ice is above 800m).             In hydro energy resources Tajikistan takes first place in Central Asia. The total length of 947 rivers of Tajikistan is more than 28500km. Half part of ice-covered space in Central Asia belongs to Tajikistan.             There are more than 8000 glaciers with total area of 8,5 thousand square km, which surpasses sowing area of the Republic.             Geographical position of Tajikistan inside Eurasia is on the border of subtropical zones. This is the cause of peculiar climate. So as a matter of fact, there is high sun radiation, droughty, cloudless. The sun shines nearly all year round (an average quantity of the year hour are 2500-3000). Just cloudless sky during some months attracts there astrophysics from Europe, Asia, America. The Astrophysics Institute with its Hisar and Sanglokh observatories is well known to all scientists of the world. The main richness of Tajikistan is the sun. It gives favorable conditions for growing valuable sun loving cultures.]             There isn’t any need of advertising of some sorts of cotton, geranium, thin-skinned rich of vitamins Tajik lemons, Israfa apricots. By the way the wines are also very popular.             There are up to 40 species of fish in the rivers and lakes of Tojıkıston. Hunting is allowed to some kinds of animals, but many of them need preservation and protection and must be put in the Red Book. There are three reservations and 114 special reserved places. First of all it is the complex “Beshai palangon”(Bush of tigers) which was founded in 1938 to preserve the nature of southern deserts, the rivers of Central Asia, rate animals and plants. Recently there was founded reservation”Dashti Jum”. Its aim is to preserve the last population of the wild goat (morkhur) in Central Asia Mountain woods and valuable kinds of animals are reserve in Sarikhosor, Kamarob, Sangvor, Dashti Maidon, Childukhtaron and other reservations.             In the museums of Tojıkiston, especially at ethnography museum of Academy of Sciences there kept unique handicrafts of women’s decorations. They are made of gold, silver with precious of lal and other stones. Gold, silver and precious are not brought from anywhere, but it is the richness of Tajik land. Be the way they are being extracted from ancient ages. Today this list can be continued. Fs to mineral resources they are extracted up to 40 species. Nearly all known ore mineral are concentrated in three mountainous regions: in the north of country (Kurama and Mogoltau ridges) in the central pert (Zerafshan-Hisor zone) and in he Pamirs.             Geologists say that the whole Mendeleyev’s Periodic table is concentrated in the Pamirs. It means that three are practically all known ore minerals, but they can’t practically be extracted, though hold is washes there from ancient times. To prove it there are some old elaboration in Khovaling and Central Pamirs.             There are deposits of coal and oil in Tajikistan. But the most remarkable one is mineral water. And as matter of fact there are some sanatoriums and health resorts: Khoja Obigarm, Shambari, Yavros, Kaltuch, Obigarm is translated from Tajik as “holy hot water”. This health resort is situated in the mountains at the foot of famous Alpine meadows.             There are not only famous springs; they are also added by fresh clean mountainous air and by exotic landscape.             Garm-Chashma is the miracle of the Pamirs nature. It need not very much care to be among the best resorts of the world.             In summer lots of tourists from all parts country and from abroad come o Tajikistan and its capital-Dushanbe. Great is the wish of modern man to the places, where there isn’t any civilization, very little people and no industry.             There are a number of such places in Tajikistan in the mountain, where the air, the beauty of wild nature takes tension and stress and gives a person cheerfulness and relaxation. For example, it is Kamarov, Shirkent. It is not easy to get there. As people live very far there kept unique pistachio, maple, alycha groves, clean rivers and lakes. Tourist’s marsh on well know routs “Khutalli Kohistoni”, “To the blue lakes”, “on the snowman path”, “On the ridges of Pamirs –Alay”. They are met with great joy by inhabitants of rare mountain villages.             Statistic points out that only ten percent of population lives in mountains .As a rule people who live there are tall and slim. And in the mountain, which occupies 93 percent of the territory, is the realm of silence, rarely disturbed by slow-sides, and then in valleys, the life is very intensive. By the way, the passages of Anthon and Khaburabot (about 4000 m. above the level of the sea) where the cars and motorcars run all the time connect the Pamir with other regions.             Modern  cities, block of houses can’t live without comfort: hot water, central heating and gas. So this comfort, modern and architecture design decorate the oldest cities of Tajikistan: Khujand, Panjakent, Uroteppa, Kulob, and new ones Khorugh, Norak, Kayrokum, Kalininobod, Roughun.The most beautiful city is the capital of Tajikistan-Dushanbe, the population of which is more than a million people. These are industrial centers. The biggest industry centers are situated there. Kayrokum is well known with its carpets factory. Its production of carpets is spread all over republic.             A very beautiful and exotic is the town of Norak. It is buried in verdure. The road from Dushanbe to Norak lies through the passage Chormaghzak. Norak is famous for its electric power station, which supplies Tajikistan with cheap electricity. Must be said the power station in Norak is unique one. Many foreign experts were against building the dam 300 m in height, in seismic dangerous zone. Russian and Tajik scientist-seismologists approved it, because they carried out series experiments on the dam model.             More than twenty years this miracle of hydro technical mastership gives to people light and heat. It gives the light to all kishlaks in Hisor valley; it gives the energy to such power consuming enterprises like Tajik aluminum plant, Yovon electrochemical plant, and Tursunzoda china plant. Tajikistan has at its disposal vast potential of industry. It has 120 branches and 430 industry enterprises. Here should be related Tajik plant of textile machine- building, Vakhsh nitric plant Kurgontepa transformer-building plant, giant of textile industry of Dushanbe industrial corporation “Tajiktextile”. Silk-mils and canning industry are concentrated in Dushanbe and Khujand.Mining and chemical industry is developed in the north of Tajikistan. Putting into operation gold production in the towns of Chkalovsk and Tajik-Britesh joint venture in Panjakent  create conditions ear solving the important strategically taks-getting the high quality production on the level of world standards, creation of gold reserve in country, revival of jewelry production from local stuff.             Some words must be said about training of specialist and national ducation. There are 15 universities and technical schools. Tajik Techical University prepared thousands specialist such as engineers, builders, energetic, motor workers for the country. The Technological Institute adds specialist, who graduated from this educational establishment work in all parts of Tajikistan.It. Student of this institute go abroad to go better practice and to learn new technology and production.             The diplomas of Medical University, Tajik National State University, and Institute of Arts are highly appreciated. The scientific researches in the Republic are coordinated by the center, which is the Academy of sciences. It is founded more than 50 years ago and includes many scientific centers and laboratories where works about 3000 scientists solving the problems connected with economy, mathematics, geology, medicine, astrophysics etc.             The name of the famous Tajik historian academician Bobojon Ghafurov is highly spoken is many countries of the world. Tajiks are pound of such scientists as A.Bahovaddinov, S.Umarov, P.Bobojonov, and S.negmatulloev who greatly contributed in the development of   Tajik sciences.             We should mention the Institute of Language and literature by Rudaki, where recommendations to the Law of government language were developed. The Institute of Oriental studies and manuscripts reserve invaluable grant of the past. Scientists of the Institute introduce readers to wisdom of ancient philosophers and historians.             The Institute of seismology must be mentioned particularly. It is well known all over the world by its works and discoveries in the field of long-termed prognosis of earthquake. Especially must be mentioned names of specialists who are well known not only in Tajikistan but in the world of science abroad too. These are the names of Prof. H.Mansurov  the director Institute of gastroenterology, Prof. A.Pulatov the children surgeon, U.Ishoki, M.Gulomov, K.Tojiev etc. These doctors-scientists are caring on the traditions laid by the great Avicenna.             Much work is done by the Institute of geology, where they investigate mineral reserves of country.             It is already mentioned that there are more that 6,5 mln people in Tajikistan. So 1 mln.325 thousand from them are pupils, this is the whole state. They are taught by 90 thousands of teachers.             There are the Ayni Opera and Bullet, the Mayakovki Russian Drama, the Lohuty State Academic Drama theatres. On playbills one can meet only the names of east authors but also European. M.Vohidov Youth theatre is very popular Tajikistan.             There are some interesting dancing ensembles “Zebo”, “Lola”, “Jahonoro”. They go on tour to other countries also. Folk dances, melodies of “Shashmakom”, opera, bullet, drama old and new traditional competitions of bullet masters after Malika Sabirova bullet dancer, whose name is among best world stars.             Great was success among drama amateurs of national actor Hoshim Gadoev in the play “Edip” in the main role Tajik drama theatre after Lohuti was founded in thirtieth and gave a number of magnificent names such as M.Kasimov (farukh Kosimov is his son). T.Fozilova, S.Tuybaeva, A.Burhonov, H.Rahmatulloev and many others. We should also mention two wonderful singers. H.Mavlonova- opera singer and B.Ishokova- singer of Tajik classic songs, works of modern composers T.Shahidy, F.Soliev, F.Bshor and others. The songs of Akashrif Juraev, Odina Hoshim, Jurabek Murodov, Zafar Nozimov, Karomatullo Kurbonov are very popularly among the Tajik people.             In Tajikistan when people want to say something pleasant they say. “As handsome as a poet”, “As wise as a poet”.             There is some poetic in the nation’s blood. Tajiks have very rich literary heritage. These are their names: Rudaki, Firdavsi, Nosir Khisrav, Rumi, Khayom, Sadi, Hafız, Kamol Khujandi, Abdurahman Jomi and many other stars in the bright poetic world. So the stream of poetry couldn’t dry up today as many ages ago.             There are new names which became classics of nowadays: S.Ayni, A.Lohuti, M.Tursunzade, B.Rahimzoda, J.Ikrami, R.Jalil, S. Ulugzoda, Poets and writers of the lates period are A.Shukuhi, F.Muhammadiev, V. Kanoat, L.Sherali, B.Sobir, U. Kuhzod, Gulruhsor, A.Samadov, A.Hakim. The list may be continued.             There are famous producers of the films, whose names are well-known not only in Tajikistan, the names of B.Kimyoganov with his serial films on “Shohnoma” by Firdavsi, T.Sobirov, D.Khudonazarov, B.Sodikov’s films make a person suffer and take what is on to heart feel keenly what happens with his heroes.             Tajikistan is also famous for its libraries. The oldest National library is after Firdavsi. In its richest fund there are hundred thousands of books published by publishing house: “Irfon”, “Adib”, “Donish” and “Tajik Encyclopedia”.             Much can be said about the wonderful people of this country, its talented national healers, about the towns, where on can see combined Asiatic and European architecture, about famous Tajik cooking the art which is ancient, but it is better to come and see everything with your own eyes. There is very good saying in the east: “Seeing once is better than hearing twice”.             At present in the country carries out reforms and structure rebuilding of economics. Bank system and business, privatization and market are developed.             For increasing of efficiency of national economy foreign investments are attracted, joint ventures are created too, in particular for working mineral resources.             Today the foreign policy of the Republic of Tajikistan is based on mutual benefit and equality relations with all states, participation in strengthening of peace and international security. Tajikistan aspires to develop trade- economical cooperation with states of the region and world.             It is very important to have motor-highway and railways for extending trade-economical relations and the Government of the Republic of Tajikistan attaches great importance to it.  
     

    
</post>
<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
        By Muzaffar HUDOYKULOV* Music and poetry are two spheres of art that are very close in every country, they always stand together, especially in the case of the Tajik people. The great poet Abuabdullo Rudaki was an excellent singer and musican, he even invented a new musical instrument. Many poets were also the performers of their works. Not a single festival took place without folk singers, musicans, dancers and funny buffoons, and without the maskaraboz- circus performers. By tradition to this day people are summoned to festivals by the trumpet sounds of the very long karnais, and even on ordinary days one often hears in the streets hte sounds of the doira, a tambourine, and the pensive sound of the nai. As to the rubob, it can be found in every home. Melodies from the shashmakom, a wonderful musical work of the past that was recorded on sheet music only in modern times, are known and loved in the country. The Tajik composers Z. Shakhidi, Sh. Saifiddinov, A. Saliev, D. Dusmukhamedov, A. Khamdamov, Ya. Sabzanov, A. Odinayev, Kh. Abdullayev and others preserve with care the traditions of classical and folk music, develop and enrich it with new forms. The Tajik music lovers now know the light music, pieces for single instruments and orchestra-symphonies, operas and ballets. The capital of the Republic has an opera and ballet theatre, three drama theatres, a philharmonic society, a symphony orchestra, and several song and dance companies. There are theatres also in other towns of Tajikistan. Professional training in music and the art is offered by the Art Institute, by music and art schools, and by studios functioning at theatres. Many envoys of Tajikistan  study in the country’s best establishments of higher learning. Music schools and palaces of culture, people’s theatres and people’s universities of culture, amateur art groups draw both children and adults into the world of music and art. In the past, the galaxy of cultural workers includes People’s Artists of the USSR M. Kasymov, A. Burkhanov, T. Fazylova, the singers Kh. Mavlyanova, B. Iskhakova  and A. Bobokulov. The star of Tajik ballet, People’s Artist of the USSR Malika Sabirova, a winner of the International Ballet Dancers Competition, is known by the whole country and she has performed in the best theatres of the world- Moscow and Sant Petersburg, London and Rome, Tokyo and Berlin, Delhi and Montreal. Staged in Tajik theatres are works not only of local authors but also of Russian and world classics- Ostrovsky, Chehov, Gogol, Shakespeare, Moliere. Prize at the best festivals have been won by such films produced by Tajikfilm studio as “A poet’s destiny” and “Rustam and Sukhrob”, and “The death of a usurer”. The Republic’s composers and film makers, writers and artists are united in creative professional unions. Folk masters are continuing and developing the traditional handicrafts- wood and ganchu carvers, chasers, ceramics and pattern designers. A monograph was published recently about the prominent ornamentalist M. Olimov who worked in the “kundal” style. His ornaments adorn the famous “Rokhat” tea house in Dushanbe. As to this prospectus, dear reader, it is a small gift to you, a memento. We will be very happy if you come to like our mountainous country, described by poets as a land at the foot of the sun. Come and visit us...  Source: Books from Soviet Tajikistan * Ankara University, Faculty of Law  
     

    
</post>
</Blog>