<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Hey Kids! Go to the Runamuk Comics website! tons of random fun shizzle to do!  urlLink http://www.runamukcomics.com     Anyways, in the last 20 hours i have: slept and had a funky dream about a "witch party" and Garza driving a hummer through a huge school...it was weird! before i went to sleep, however, i went to copelands to buy some shoes, which crashed and burned when my mom didnt like the the pair i chose (they had checkerd laces grr) but whatever...then i ranted on the phone to eduardo for about half an hour, and then crashed in my bed after watchin the last 3 minutes of clintons speech. oh yeah i went swimming, that too. then this morning i woke up and played dungeon keeper 2 for like half an hour, only to get killed by a rival dungeons minions...haha and then i went online. story of my life eh? and now i am going to jump in the pool after checking my email for the 3rd time today.     Listening To: Maahi Ve - Assorted Singers (Kal Ho Naa Ho)   Reading: Feed by M.T. Anderson  
    
</post>
<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Well i was in Frisco for the last three days...therefore you get a special deal! wooooo!   Day 1: Got into our hotel and ate at an indian place    Day 2: Walked around the peir for like the whole day, in the process pretty much turning my legs to very soft jelly, saw the Punisher    Day 3: Woke up at like 6 to rush to Karate at like 3, but my dad's car did NOT sprout wings and fly (faster than 60 miles an hour grr) so we got there like 15 minutes late...    Anyhoo, after i went to Devin's bday party, which was fun...watched Scary Movie 3 and Jeepers Creepers 2.   REVIEWS!!!   The Punisher:four words - random acts of violence...it follows the plot of the actual comic (i think) but its fun to watch...plenty of bloodshed. BEE!   Scary Movie 3: freaking hilarious.   Jeepers Creepers 2: Stupid slasher movie. Average noodles dudes, average.   ANYHOOi hope you all had a fun time...i really need to get some sleep now.     
    
</post>
<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       hey everyone! to begin this post i would like to share a few words that i found inlilly's AIM profile.  "HOT TOPIC: cashes in on convenience. Instead of directly supporting a band by mailordering clothing and cd's and waiting a week, kids can cruise on down to the closest mall in the family mini van and buy sh*t from there while mommy and daddy walk around JCPennys.  Hot Topic is no different than American Eagle, Gap, Pac Sun, A  F, etc. because when you get down to it, the companies thrive on deceiving people into blurring the line between fashion and personal identity. People want to become the clothes they wear."   can u sence the truth in these words? cuz i know i can. its sooo true...the only thing is that people tend to not want to see it. i mean, i dont mind the store, but its called "identity theft..."   anyhoo, ill be leaving to san francisco tomorrow for a couple of days... top fun! goin to hang at the wharf and eat fish and chips for 3 days straight. anyhoo, not much to post, exept that i saw saving private ryan for the first time yesterday...great movie, even with the immence amount of "extremely graphic intense war violence and language" that it packs the film with.   todays lesson: Hot Topic is exactly like A! but with a little bit better stuff. and prices, even thought HT prices arent really anything to brag about.      Listening To: Recognize - Flaw (Endangered Species)   Reading:Abhorsen by Garth Nix  
    
</post>
<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       monday is a wonderful day. its the day school starts, the day after the weekend. my favorite day of the week..grr i hate mondays. yesterday was fun stuff...woke up thinking it was like wednesday or something like that...went to this thingy at the valley crecent school...muslim stuff...FUN! eh it was alright,we were forced to take zara to it...there we hung out and ate...exept that they ran out of sodas MORE GRR! and got either a) forced to use our bodies for physical work i.e. moving chairs, or b) kicked out of the building...*sigh* or c) chastized for not praying...   came home, zaras mom wasnt home so she came over to our pad...shizzle...and we looked for junebugs to blow up but that dint work cuz all we found were praying mantises...or whatever...   then she left and i read some and went to sleep. not so eventful day eh.   so now its noon and im online, wasting my life on the computer. again.    and so ends monday's post.      Listening to: KRZR for a song GOD its not coming on!!!   Reading: When Dad Killed Mom by Lewis somethingorother  
    
</post>
<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       hey everyone.   wow todays saturday already eh? i woke up at 10: 35 with a rush of cold ice water down my shirt...FUN! as i felt this icy cold down my back, i hear the words, "GET UP AND TAKE A SHOWER, WE NEED TO GET TO KARATE IN 20 MINUTES!"   i took the shower. oh yeah, i took it all right.   fun stuff...got the wind knocked out of me 3 times...ayup. get home at 12:30, rush to a party thingy at hometown buffet, where i ate my heart out. all of it. jamal and i discovered that the more straws you drink with, the more fun it is...i also discovered that spitballs hurt like crap man! got home, took of my pants and PUT ON SHORTS! woooo! after reading for like 3 hours, im now on the computer typing this up. totally awesome dude. in an hour im going to again don the formal dress and go to a colombian gathering...GREAT.    acutally not, im planning to taking my cd player and listening to evil, dark satanic music the whole time as my distant relatives/relatives' familys' friends trying to hug me and tell me how much ive grown...   grr.   im 5' 5''! im so proud now though...i had my doctors appointment a couple days ago, that was an experience. especially the wearing-the-dress-with-little-snowflakes-on-it part. oh and the room with the little bunnies dancing, boarding, and eating pie around the upper corner of the room...*t-twitch* i SWEAR those bunnies were looking at me like seriously.       Listening To: Skulls - The Misfits ( Walk Among Us )   Reading: Wizards First Rule by Terry Goodkind  
    
</post>
<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       this is my first post on the legacy of izzy blog, considering i did not use the last one very much.   yes well im izzy for those people who enjoy knowing the name of their enemy.   i guess i should start ranting about my day...   so far, i woke up at 9:30. FUN. then, after an intense scratching of the back, and a yawnfest, i got out of bed and ate some cereal, which im still convinced was poisoned. its very slow acting. some of my colleagues from the effigy films movie production company have concocted an idea...nacho cheese chugfest! isnt that splendid? wed have a ref (yours truly), two chuggers, two clowns as entertainers, and an announcerman...john and eriks idea, fun eh?   i went to eriks house last weekend...and, unfortunately, broke his bed.   if you must know, i was NOT, contrary to popular belief, POLE DANCING, but i was swinging on his bedpost. yes...well details were withheld, and izzy was not available for comment friday.   anyhoo fun stuff, i hope this blog will go places. like new zealand n stuff. so syonara until like tomoroowwwwww....  
    
</post>
<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      HAAHHAHA YEAH RIGHT  school officially starts in about 6 days, how annoying is that??   my main thoughts on school involve both positive and negative sides on this...first off, school isnt that bad...its school i guess, i mean we need it to become succesfull rich people in the future, so i can see where they are going. i honestly think that they should make school longer, with the contition being to eliminate homework. i think homework is by far the worst aspect of this place they call school. schools kinda cool, cuz i get to c my friends (those people who claim to be my friends, at least) and i suppose actually learning things isnt to bad...but homework. *shudder* this is the evil incarnate...this year however, ive decided to imprint some tips in my mind for an easier, if more working, school day.   1. DO HOMEWORK IN CLASS. in the words of my cousin eduardo, a college freshman this year, "dude, you'll always have a stupid class. just do it in that... and in class, so you hav a free day for the rest."   thats really all there is...and all that "dont procrastinate" crap...which acually isnt crap...grr.   ive decided on starting water polo...not cuz its the sport for dorks and rejects, which it isnt so much, i am a relatively ok swimmer, and anything having to do with water i will eagerly jump to,...of course there is a rope holding me back, that i call "speedo"   this rope has moved however (up to my neck...), making me realize that i have to DEAL WITH IT, or of course use the religious modesty excuse to get something as skintight *shudder*, but at least like shorts grr.   and i have also decided to do swimming as well, just cus its...swimming!   i went to zachs house last saturday, for a "night of scary movies" which, while the movies werent scary, was not dissapointing. we first started it with the bad seed, a 1956 movie which apparently was the story of a little girl turned evil,....very black and white, not scary.   then, we watched the shining, based on stephen king's book, which is pretty great, if mildly freaky, and VERY confusing...im still figuring it out,...and trying to get redrum out of my head....then we watched identity </post></Blog>