<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
         The cops just left.    The same two that were here before.    They told me that Sally had convinced them to come out and talk to the boys.    But the boys are gone.     The cops also said the restaurant is closed down and there is no sign of Mama Jiroles.     Sally is gone to.    She declined to return to the condo with the cops.    I called the newspaper and Janis told me Sally hadn’t called in.    No word from her.     My review of Jiroles appeared in today’s paper.    Not a word was changed.    They got a bad review on their omelets.             This is the last from Marcos Beach.    I appreciate everyone who stuck with me through the ordeal.     Bye.   
     
    
</post>
<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
         It’s almost eight-thirty in the morning.    I don’t see any sign of the boys outside, and Kevin is asleep.         I figure it’s about a hundred yards to my car – back out through the condo complex along a narrow walkway then into the open lot.    My car’s on the far end.     I’m going to carry a cup of hot coffee with me.    Boiling hot.           
     
    
</post>
<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
         We took a drubbing.     The boys came at us right after we signed off late yesterday.    Couldn’t post anything because Sally and I had to hunker down behind the sofa.     I admit I’m a coward.     These guys are football players.     I think they were drunk, or frustrated, or just really angry for some reason.     We really can’t figure this out.    Did they kill the park ranger?    Do they think I’m onto it after reading my review from six months ago?     The boys pounded on the door incessantly.    You would think the neighbors would call the cops, but there it is, the cops.    Are they in on this too?     This whole thing is way over our heads.             Sally here.    They did more than pound on the door.    They threw a rock through a side window and stuck the garden hose in and flooded the bathroom.     I’m outta here.    It’s almost eleven in the morning and as soon as I get my courage together I’m walking out and going to my car and driving to the sheriff’s station.    The local police won’t help and I don’t know why.     Before it gets dark, I’m outta here.    This is crazy!   
     
    
</post>
<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
        I shot up with a start and quickly swiveled my head expecting the boys to have silently broken in somehow.    Nothing.    “We fell asleep.”          Sally opened her eyes and stared at the ceiling.     I went to the curtain.    No glowing cigarette.    “They might be gone.”     “Don’t bet on it.”    She was at my side and did her own peeking.    “They may be taking shifts to watch the place.”     A match suddenly flared.    The glowing red dot reappeared.    We both shrank back.     “I’m going to call the police again.”    I grabbed the phone but my stomach plummeted.    No dial tone.     “What’s wrong?”     I gently set the phone down.    “You have your cell phone with you?    Mine’s dead.”     Sally shook her head.     “You should always keep it with you,” I admonished her.     “You should always keep yours charged,” she shot back.     I had no idea how long it would take to charge the little thing, but it was worth a try.    I hit the button on the lamp and just got more darkness.    “Shit!    They cut the phones and the power.”     I pulled the cord on the laptop and raised the lid.    “Well, this battery is fat,” I said with some satisfaction.     “You can’t get online without a phone line, sweetheart.”     My smile increased.    “This house is in a hot zone.    I can get out.”     “Who will you contact?    Who will believe you?”     “Well, we know we can forget the police.”      (The above was my last “diary” posting.    Sally has convinced me that we need to go real-time or else nobody will take this seriously.    If you have read this far, we will post again in a few minutes.    Hang on.)      
     
    
</post>
<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
         “They can’t be making a big deal out of a report that they delivered food to the park ranger.    His place is less than a hundred yards from the restaurant.    Seems natural that he would order from them.    What are you reading in that?”     “Look at the date?“     “Well, that’s around the time the guy was found dead.”     “That’s the day they figure he was killed.    Murdered.”     I stood and quickly reread the story.    The resident ranger monitored the state beach and the park adjacent to it.    “I remember the police saying his death was suspicious, but nothing conclusive.”     “Well, if anyone remembers your story and connects the dots, an investigation might get reopened and the boys would be questioned.    Maybe they’ve got something to hide and they’re tired of your nosing around.”    She took a quick look through the curtain.    “They’re still out there.”     I threw the printout to the floor.    “How do you know that’s not someone else?    Could be some kids.”     Sally gave me a look filled with considerable disdain.    “That’s where I saw the boys park their asses this afternoon, the cigarettes have been constant and in the exact same spot.    And those two oafs don’t have to worry about being run off by some kids.”     “Then we should call the police.    We’re like, like prisoners.    This is stupid.”    I was getting increasingly testy.     She waved a hand as if she didn’t care if I told our stupid little story to the cops.    “They wouldn’t believe me anyway, not after calling them to report my omelet.”     “May sure you tell them that Jay has a baseball bat.    No.    Call it a blackjack.    Those are illegal and it just might get the cops out here.”     The phone rang once.     “I need some assistance with a couple of guys hanging around my place.”     “You sound like the guy that reported the omelet?”     I hesitated.    He may have recognized my voice, but to me he didn’t sound like either one of the cops that looked at the omelet, but now was not the time to go into voice analysis.    “Yes, look, we’ve got another problem.”     “What?    You got a malicious slice of pie now?    Okay, okay, so what’s happening now?”     “They’re Mama Jiroles boys and they, well, one of them at least, one of them served me that omelet this morning.”     “So?    Looked like a pretty good omelet to me.    We can’t arrest waiters ‘cause they serve omelets with funny little cheese designs on them.”     Now I was getting really steamed.    “Okay, let’s forget the omelet.    I’ve got two guys that have been standing outside my front door now for over seven hours and one of them has a blackjack.”     “Loitering.    Okay, we’ll send a unit out there as soon as one comes available.    We’ve got some rowdy college kids in town tonight, might be some time before we can make it out there.”     “What about the blackjack?”     “What  about  the blackjack?”     “Aren’t they illegal?”     “That’s just an old story.    No, they’re not illegal and neither are small souvenir baseball bats.    Now, we’ll get a unit out there when we can.”     Stunned, I couldn’t think of anything else to ask and hung up.    I looked up at Sally.    “He said blackjack and souvenir baseball bats aren’t illegal.”     Sally matched my surprise.    “Of course blackjacks are illegal!    We wrote up a story on some guy getting arrested for possessing one last year.    Get back on our web site and pull it up.    It was, May, no, June of last year.”     I pulled up the article and shook my head.    “It was a shiv and the guy was on parole.”     “I know blackjacks are illegal.    That’s just the wrong article.”     “Doesn’t matter.”    I closed the laptop.     “What?    Of course it does.    Our next call will be to the chief and he’ll smack those two lazy bastards for not knowing the law.”     I shook my head again.    “Those weren’t cops I was talking to.”     “What?    What are you talking about?”     “I’m sure that was a different voice and besides, those cops never saw the boys.    They wouldn’t know about the souvenir baseball bat.” 
     
    
</post>
<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
         “Are they still out there?”        “I can still see a cigarette burning.”    Sally turned from the sliver of an opening in the curtain.    ”I think it’s them.”     “For crying out loud!”    I was frustrated, angry, and yes, scared.    “What in the hell is this?”    I stood up but didn’t move.    “I should just go out there and find out what the problem is.”         “Well, if you’re gonna do that I suggest you wait until morning when it’s light and there’s other people around.    I think I saw Jay with one of those little baseball bats, you know, like the ones they hand out at baseball games.”     I gave her a disbelieving look, then plopped back down in front of my laptop.    “Do you have any idea what this could be about?”     Sally shook her head.    “Tell me exactly what you did yesterday morning.”     “I decided to do another review of Jiroles.    So I went down there early in the morning with my laptop, took a table on the patio, ordered an omelet, and started writing the review.    Next thing I knew I was staring down at an omelet with this threatening message written in cheese.”     She ran the back of her hand across her chin, then stopped in mid-stroke.     “Go to our website and download that review.”    A moment later  The Marcos Beach Searchlight  appeared over a picture of a setting sun and shimmering water.    I printed my review of Jiroles from about six months ago and handed it to her.     Sally scanned the copy then seemed to go over it, slower this time.    She took a pencil, underlined something, and handed the review back to me.    “I think you had better look at this again.”         
     
    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
         The knock at the door nearly catapulted me to the ceiling.    I had always thought that peeping through the peephole in the door was senseless.    The idea was to see who was there and be able to ignore them without them knowing you were really there.     Then I was told by an expert that burglars would sometimes knock and then . . . NOT IMPORTANT, I told myself.     “It’s Sally.    Open up!”     I did.    She was frantic.  "I know I told you to ignore anybody at the door, but here I am."       “What’s happening?”    I quickly closed the door behind her.     “Mama Jiorles.    She’s gone.”    Sally seemed to be trying to catch her breath.    “The boys are gone and the restaurant is shut down.    They came to the office asking where you were, where you lived.    Janis gave them nothing.    They left.”     “Why in the hell are they after me?    My tip wasn’t big enough?    This is crazy!”     The two of us froze at the knocking.    Sally, more brave than I, walked in a stooped fashion to the door.    I thought her peer through the peephole was fearless.    She crept away from the door and slid to the floor, her back to the wall.    Her eyes told me her thoughts were rampant.    Her face tightened into a mass of horizontal lines.         I easily recognized the words she silently mouthed.    “THE BOYS!”   
     
    
</post>
<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
         It was Sally at the door with two big cups of coffee.     She asked me where the omelet was, I told her I tossed it, but that I had taken pictures of it.    That’s me, always considering the options. Preserving the evidence.    Looking at the small things.    Maybe that’s why I was the only one who could read the cheese, I told her.     Then she blew me away with an admission.    She could read it too, but didn’t want to say anything in front of the cops.     “Why?”     “The boys.”     “The boys?”     “Mama Jiorles’ boys, Richard and Jay.”    Sally took a long sip of her coffee.    “You make a police report, the police pay a visit to the boys.    They’ve been in trouble before.    They may be football players but they are not too small to play stupid pranks, even on customers.    If Mama Jiorles found out she’d kill them, then they would come looking for you.”     I shook my head.    “You mean one or both of them took the time to arrange cheese on a customer’s omelet just as a prank?”     “Probably.”     “Where are we on the deadline?”     “Electronic submissions . . . “ Sally glanced at her watch.    “You’ve got an hour.”     Sally let herself out and I got busy on my laptop.     Jiorles Cafe.    Marcos Beach.    It is unfortunate when a trusted old-time business in this small beach town suddenly turns into . . .     I finished the review and zapped it off.    Twenty minutes later I heard Sally’s voice on the other end of the line.     “We can’t print this.”     “Why?    It’s true.”     “Prove it.”     “The pictures.”     “They’ll have us in court for the rest of our natural lives.    But more important than that, I’ve heard that the boys are looking for you right now.    This has turned into something bigger.    I can’t talk now, I’ll have to call you back.    Don’t open your door for anyone.” 
     
    
</post>
<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Got up at five this morning.  Couldn’t sleep.  Couldn’t believe what went down yesterday. Sally said she could not see any writing. Couldn’t smell a thing.  Nothing like glue.  Nothing. Okay.  I’m losing my mind. Sally left.   The cops left.  One of them still shaking his head. I’m going to write a review of the restaurant and blast them. Stand by. 
     
    
</post>
<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      “You called us over here because of this omelet?”  Both police officers were understandably upset. At that moment Sally appeared in the open doorway.  I was glad to see her.  “Sally!” I called out.  I motioned her in.  She kept glancing back and forth between the police officers and me.  “I want you to see this.”  I pointed down to the omelet. She swept her long black hair to one side and twisted it over her shoulder as she leaned down to examine my uneaten breakfast. “Okay,” she said, straightening.  “What am I supposed to be looking for?” “Yeah, you can go ahead and give us a clue,” one of the officers said. “Look!”  I said, getting a bit irritated with all three of them.  “Can’t you see?  The writing!  Right here!” All three leaned forward over the omelet.  After a moment one officer slowly shook his head and stepped back.  “Can’t make out a thing.” “Right there!” I said pointing, my finger an inch above the food.  “The cheese.  They used some kind of yellow shredded cheese it looks like.  I ordered cheddar.” That is one of my problems, relating useless information.  Sally kicks me for it all the time.   “Look,” I pressed.  “The letters, here, a ‘Y’ and then an ‘E’ and, well, you can read it, Y-E-R-G-O-N-N-A-D-I-E, and then on the inside, look, my name with more cheddar.” The second officer now started shaking his head.  “I’m afraid I just don’t see it, do you see anything like that, Bob?” The other officer had never stopped shaking his head.  “Nope.” “Sally!”  She was my last hope.  “You can see it, right?  Look.  The ‘R’ is a bit shaky, and the ‘G’ is kind of tough to make out, but you can see it, can’t you?” 
     
    
</post>
<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      With my battery recharged I was eager to record my last few minutes at the restaurant. After examining the omelet, I asked for a container to put it in and take it home.  What they had served me had to be further examined and photographed. Mama Jiorles son, Richard, gave me a disbelieving smile when he saw I hadn’t taken a bite of the omelet. “We coulda wrapped it for you in the kitchen if all you wanted was a takeout.” I matched his smile and told him that I had just received a call that there was a minor emergency at home so could I just get a container?   I didn’t have my cell phone with me and there was no ‘minor emergency.’ Richard reached for my plate, I held up my hand.  “I’ll just do it myself, if you would just get me the container.  I’m kinda in a hurry.”  I didn’t want him alone with my omelet.   I opened the Styrofoam container and there it lay.  Yellow egg folded over once, the now-darkened green avocado, the brown of bacon, a slightly less appealing glob of sour cream, and hardened yellow cheese. On a television commercial this would all look delicious.  But this was no commercial. I suppose the cold coffee put my senses on alert.  Something, my palate told me to be aware, on the lookout. I grabbed a fork from a kitchen drawer, for inspection, not eating. Now I knew I was right to be wary.  As I lifted the edge of the supposed omelet, it came up hard, leaden.  This was not egg.  It was something synthetic, perhaps toxic.  An odor rose up.  Glue or melted plastic!  I leaned back.  I was nonplussed.  Confused. The rest of the ingredients seemed real, though I had no intention of setting them on my tongue.  I had no idea what I was dealing with or what in the hell Richard, Mama Jiorles, had intended. I stared at the open omelet.   My mind reeled. This was quickly turning into a police matter.   
     
    
</post>
<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      It is Saturday morning and with my laptop in hand I head down to the beach for breakfast (and to secretly review) Jiorles.  This small restaurant sits on the sand and offers a variety of food from pancakes to pizza. Mama Jiorles has run the place for over forty years, first with her husband and now with the help of her two sons, both of them football players at the local junior college.  Her husband disappeared about fifteen years ago, reportedly to dig for gold in Brazil. I take a seat on the patio and scan the fog shrouded ocean. I seem to be the only patron here.  A menu arrives, but I hand it back and order the Denver omelet and coffee.  Mama Jiorles son, the older one, a bench-sitting guard on the team, nods and leaves. The low battery light on my laptop begins to glow and my food arrives. The coffee is cold.  I don’t mean just not hot, it is absolutely cold. But I can’t take my eyes off the omelet in front of me.  Something is really wrong here. Battery about gone.  I’ll have to finish this at home. 
     
    
</post>
</Blog>