<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tavasz nyár ősz tél tavasz:  urlLink http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0374546/     Monumentálisabbnak képzeltem, az élet értelméről vagy valami... inkább egy buddhista példabeszédhez hasonlít. Tetszett azért. 8/10.    IMDB mondja:     Summary:  A beautiful Korean Buddhist pastoral   If you are not familiar with the basics of Buddhism, you will be after watching this movie. You might not realize it, and you won't know the terminology, but this whole movie is not only about a boy who becomes a man and then raises a boy, but also about the core Buddhist beliefs.    (NOTE: Some of the following comments might spoil some of the plot elements. However, the official movie website has a "synopsis" that spoils the entire plot, without explaining the Buddhist themes, so at least this review is better than that!)    The first lesson we see is that creating suffering for others, no matter if they are fish or snake or frog or person, causes suffering for yourself. Most people know this as Karma.    The second lesson is that desire causes suffering. The Old Monk warned the Young Monk of this, but the Young Monk did not resist, and ruined most of his life as a result. (I laughed very hard when Yoda, in Star Wars Episode I, explains this same lesson: "Fear is the path to the dark side. Fear leads to anger. Anger leads to hate. Hate leads to suffering.")    If you listen carefully to the conversation between the monks, you will understand both how desire causes suffering, and how letting go can prevent the suffering.     The third lesson is that you can purify yourself and get rid of the negative thoughts that cause desire and suffering. Some people achieve this by studying the teachings, some by meditating, and some by spiritual tasks, such as repeated bowing or chanting. The Young Monk, instead, drags a millstone and a statue of Tara, the Compassion Buddha, up to the top of a mountain overlooking the lake, where she can keep an eye on things.    The fourth lesson is that the cycle repeats, and does not necessarily have to degrade because of the imperfections of the people involved. The Young Monk purified himself and became a capable teacher, and the teachings also transcend the imperfections of the teachers.    In addition to these lessons, the movie touches on some of the superstitions about Buddhism which want for a little explanation. These appear in the scenes where the Old Monk leaves this life.    Most important is the fact that the Old Monk, like many famous very enlightened Buddhists are reputed, can tell he is about to die. He therefore is able to prepare himself. Some Buddhists, especially enlightened masters, are cremated. Since there is no one to help him, the Old Monk builds his own funeral pyre and then sits in it. It's not suicide -- he knows that he will die soon, and picks the moment of his death, as great masters are reputed to be able to, just before the flames engulf him.    We also see a snake emerge from the pyre, and we kind of get the idea that the snake is a reincarnation of the Old Monk. You will find this kind of thing in Buddhist legends, as well.    When the Young Monk returns, he digs in the ice for remains of the Old Monk. In Buddhist lore, these remains are considered magical and sacred, as if the Buddhist teachings themselves were somehow compressed into fabulous jewels (some of the remains are said literally to resemble jewels). In civilized areas, these remains are often put in special monuments called stupas, and these monuments literally radiate peace and enlightenment into the surrounding area.    However, the Young Monk instead wraps the remains in a cloth and puts them into a Buddha sculpture made of ice. In this way, the remains are released into the water when the ice melts, and this will release the purified goodness into the area for the benefit of all the entities in the area.    But put all that aside, and you'll still see a beautiful fable about peace and sanctity and about how it's possible to regain them even if you've gone far away, and about how each life has its own chance to achieve them. 
     

    
</post>
<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Mindenhol jó, de legjobb Sopron - éljen újra otthon!  
     

    
</post>
<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Lehúzunk majdnem egy hétre Sopronba, nem sok bejegyzés fog idekerülni asszem.  
     

    
</post>
<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Megkaptam a google mail accountomat! Most boldog ember vagyok. :) Köszönet Bara Tamásnak, bárki is legyél!   
     

    
</post>
<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Láttam végre a Fantomot a Madáchban... Nincs rá panaszom, talán csak az hogy fél évre előre kellett a jegyet megvenni :)  Kíváncsi vagyok Király Lindával milyen lett volna.  
     

    
</post>
<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Vajon honnan van ez az idézet?      "Nem érdekel, hogy miből élsz.  Azt akarom tudni, hogy mire vágysz,  és hogy mersz-e találkozni szíved vágyakozásával.  Nem érdekel, hogy hány éves vagy.  Azt akarom tudni, megkockáztatod-e,  hogy hülyének néznek a szerelmed miatt, az álmaidért  vagy azért a kalandért, hogy igazán élj.  Nem érdekel, hogy milyen bolygóid állnak együtt a holddal.  Azt akarom tudni, hogy megérintetted-e szomorúságod középpontját,  hogy sebet ejtett-e már valaha rajtad árulás az életben,  és hogy további fájdalmaktól való félelmedben visszahúzódtál-e már.  Azt akarom tudni, hogy együtt tudsz-e lenni fájdalommal,  az enyémmel vagy a tiéddel.  Hogy vadul tudsz-e táncolni, és hagyni, hogy az eksztázis  megtöltsön az ujjad hegyéig anélkül, hogy óvatosságra intenél,  vagy arra, hogy legyünk realisták, vagy emlékezzünk  az emberi lét korlátaira.  Azt akarom tudni, hogy látod-e a szépet, még akkor is,  ha az nem mindennap szép, és hogy isten jelenlétéből  ered-e az életed.  Azt akarom tudni, hogy együtt tudsz-e élni a kudarccal,  az enyémmel vagy a tiéddel, és mégis megállni a tó partján  és azt kiáltani az ezüst holdnak, hogy óh, igen!  Nem érdekel, hogy hol élsz, vagy hogy mennyit keresel.  Azt akarom tudni, hogy fel tudsz-e kelni egy szomorúsággal  és kétségbeeséssel teli éjszaka után, fáradtan,  csontjaidig összetörten és ellátni a gyerekeket?  Nem érdekel, hogy ki vagy, és hogy jutottál ide.  Azt akarom tudni, hogy állsz-e velem a tűz középpontjában  anélkül, hogy visszariadnál.  Nem érdekel, hogy hol, mit és kivel tanultál.  Azt akarom tudni, hogy mi tart meg belülről, amikor minden egyéb már összeomlott.  Azt akarom tudni, hogy tudsz-e egyedül lenni saját magaddal,  és hogy igazán szeretsz-e magaddal lenni az üres pillanatokban..."   
     

    
</post>
<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Kezdődik az  urlLink Ember a Holdon.  Lássuk mit tud Jim Carrey! ...   ...   Hűha! 9/10. A legjobb JC-film amit láttam. Persze még a Truman Show hátravan. 
     

    
</post>
<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Scotch -ot hallgatok meg  London Boys -t... Éljenek a 80-as évek! :)     
     

    
</post>
<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Mi a második legjobb dolog a világon? Na mi? Naná hogy lexikoncikkeket írni, meg másokéba belekontárkodni! Teljesen rákattantam: http://hu.wikipedia.org . 
     

    
</post>
<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Július 30-án Alsóörsről levonatoztunk Tapolcára, onnan busszal mentünk Taliándörögdre... Akkor már egy hete szakadt ott az eső.  Rájöttem,  miért nem jön be nekem ez a Művészetek Völgye fesztivál; olyan ritkásan vannak a helyszínek meg a rendezvények, falusias az egész, én meg a városokat szeretem. Nyilván sokan meg ugyanezért szeretik.  Szakadó esőben egy templomkertben megkínált minket egy papocska "lelki fröccs"-csel - egy pohár igazi fröccs, és húzhatunk egy idézetet. Óriási ötlet! Ha mindig ilyen kreatív lenne az egyház (bármelyik), nem lennének üresek a templomok.  Ja és az idézet is stimmelt. 
     

    
</post>
</Blog>