<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Take notice of the hyiena to the right of the tree.  I bet you wish you could do that.
     

    
</post>
<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I could blab about a lot of things on this early morning. So I will.   Yes, how about starting with my surroundings - Mexico. This past weekend, Iembarked on a littletrip to a town called Puebla. In Puebla, I met-up with a friend of a friend, his name was Tony. I have been around many interesting characters in my life. Tony was recently added to the list. Simply put: what a talker. Thisfella has a silver tongue, smarts, anda clever whit. All of thesemix and bubble to expell an absolute potent capacity to network. In a mere26 hours of being in the same proximity of this man, I witnessed him razzle and dazzle a professionalmexican baseball coach (during a game, ontop of the dugout),shoot-the-bull with countlesstaxi drivers,and verbally wrestle withseveral night club managers. Did I mention he did all ofthis in Spanish? Smooth cat. Oh, the actual town of Pueble was super sweet. Acceptionally different from that which goes on here in the D.F. (Mexico City).   Yesterday, I went on a little field study/hunt. "Study/hunt" becausethat is what it was. Ocho (8) peeps hopped in a van that seats 7 and drove into a surprisingly lush, rural town, south of the D.F. The study - a parasite called Taenia Solium. The hunt - infected piggies. What a freaking blast. (I would use one of these " ! " but I think they are gay). Have you ever attempted to rope and wrastle with a pig? Well, try to imagine painting your favorite album cover while flying mid-air on the left wing of a small aircraft, because its way different than that. Almost as fun as taking asit-down bath.  There is something that I was reminded of this past week when I went to a musem. I try, and sometimes I even fool myself into believing that I understand the concept of art. Painting art, not art in the context of music or theatre - those appear to serve a purpose. Paintings on the other hand, especially abstract ones, just perplex me. I mean, yeah, I get curious and stare at them and think " just what the hell was this moron thinking?" Two minutes or less later, I realize in fact, that I have become the moron and that I am wasting valuable brain nutrients that could be utlized in formulating thoughts to rationalize why I walked into a Contemporary Art Exhibt. And for those who have not been into one in the past decade or so, contemporary art has become synonomus with porn. All of the specimenssay: "Look, I have an angry face and a piercing in a place that every other super hooker has....but look who paid $10 to verify that he is and idiot for questioning his prudence." And then I think as I walk out...I could have gotten a churro.   You know what rarely makes sense to me? Sleep.  Except for now. Be good. 
     

    
</post>
<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hola, that means "Hello," sometimes even "Hi." I bet you think you would be real creative to answer your next phone call with this Spanish greeting. However, if it happened to be a Mexican native on the other end of the line, your attempt would be met with stout puzzlement. Reason being, Mexicans use the word "bueno" to answer their telephone calls, not "Hola" - you moron.    By the way, I am living in Mexico City or Distrito Federal this summer. This is how I know the above information, you idiota. Translate that yourself.    In regards to living in Mexico, I wanted to dispell a few common misconceptions about living in Mexico City. I actually returned to Texas for a week at the start of July. Upon my arrival, more than one person mentioned that I did not look any darker. This is the first misconception and here is my response: 1) Mexico City is in the mountains 2) The summer is the rainy season here 3) All of the tanning places here are booked until November4) There is notransfer across human GI epithelialtissueand incorporationof the skin pigment, melanin, into the skin ofpersons who eat Mexicans....this concept however does occur in the avian species frequently referred to as the Pink Flamingo after it consumes special aquatic life, otherwise thisbird would be white.Oh, there is also another related situationwith one of the big cats - the panther orpuma or mountain lion- they eat criminals and solve mysteries, which is how they landed their own cartoon series and two movie deals, both of which were freaking hilarious by the way.    Another frequent misconception that I have encountered with USAians in regard to Mexico City is that this town does not have electricity or paved roads and is a grand collection of adobe huts. My response: 1) Mexico City is currently home to over 24 MILLION people, which ranks it #1 in population for cities on the planet Earth.......urbanization as it is known in USA, was accomplished some years ago. Out of those 24 million I previously mentioned, there were like 9 smart ones who figured out how to call the Bush (Sr) administriation in the early 90's and get in on that North American Free Trade Alliance thing. *No disrespect to the other 23, 999, 991 Mexicans that did not contribute to that phone call, I didn't mean to imply that you all are not smart, you neaderthals * 2) Turns out, here in Mexico there is somewhat of a labor force avaliable, so yeah, they have paved roads. They suck, but they are hard. 3) Adobe is not really the material of choice here in Mexico City for housing, its more like string and tarp, adobe has cement-like compounds in it that makes it durabaster and more sturdy.   That will have to do for the misconceptions of Mexico City for now, I am tired of rambling on about them. Come visit. We can take the public transportation here, its better than your favorite ride at your favorite theme park. You hozer.      Props to:  Lacey, Adam  - he actually invented the concept of a props list to which I have not yet credited him for, cheers.  Danby, Michael  - for being the author of "Woman in Black."    Confession: I actually did notcome up with the super clever name "Brett onthe Net." That whim of ingenuity came from mi amigo,  Guillermo Prieto . Who also knows me as"Beto Oeste" which is my Spanish alias...I did come up with that though. Translatethat and you will bereassurred that mycreative naming prowess is still first rate.     Ok, here in Mexico City the time is now 2:25 am, that would make it 2:25 am Texas time. So you can understand the reason I am feeling a bit more ready for the bed and beauties than you are.      Be swell     
     

    
</post>
<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I love Adam Lacey. That is all.    
     

    
</post>
<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yes, I was so intensely upset with a number of humans that I decided to create my own blog. Simply to complain. It would take entirely too much out of me to detail the day, so here is the jiffy:   I have 4 freinds this summer, 3/4 go to bed at 8:30pm.   Tres (3) let downs today, all involving females. How do you say "Does this suprise anyone" in Spanish?   Do you know how to respond to modern media (email, IM, telephone)? Wow, hi. We should be friends.      Props to:  Danby, Michael  - for being the genius he is.  Prieto, Guillermo  - for taking me on a fantastico tour of downtown MC and to the sweetest eatery/cantina.  Swoops, Bill  - why not?  Lacey, Adam  - for his applauding of Jamie Story on her recent accomplishment.  Rogers, Nathaniel  - cause I know he will actually read this and because he is cuddly.    Cuddly is a nice way to end this.  
     

    
</post>
</Blog>