<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My freind wants me to front in his band, he wants me to vocal. i aint doin it. i aint gettin in front of a bunch of ppl. i got attcked by a dog. i won. im superman. not really, but still. we both got chewed up. that dog an i never got along. hey, the squirrel dont attack me anymore...i called him sparky. i know its him cuz of his torn ear. he needs to hurry an run into traffic or somethin, he almost got hit the other day. i luv the guy nyway. I havent been getting online all too much lately, an lately somethin's tellin me i dont need to be on much anymore. but i dont care, im still gonna get on when i can. oh well. im cold, gettin a little warmer, but oh well. there's been less an less violence round here...wasnt very violent on 1st glance, talkin about where i was concerned. im done with it all. an Im proud of myself:) my freind Robby wants to fight me, he int ever fought me or seen me fight. i might take him up for it. and i just got alot of clothes. 400$ worth. i aint arguin, my life is gettin bette.r...i think. and i smell pasta. 
    
</post>
<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I did nothing today. xcept excercise. and fix the house. again. and playvideo games. and watch tv. and eat 3 plates of red beans and rice. and ate ice cream puffs. and listened to music. And poked fun at our dogs ears. and played with the tinyest chuahua. however u spell the midget mexican dogs name. he's got a big head. 
    
</post>
<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       This is new. Never done in internet journal log before. very...odd. Oh well. I am a tired son of a *%^#$. been workin all year...its showin though, ive gotten big. ive been workin on my nw house...i aint done nothin to my room yet though. xcept hang my flag up. and my entertaniment center...and my computer-look, i havent unpacked everything yet's what i mean. I would very much like to go back to bed. but i ant gonna, cuz i wont be able to sleep. I havent even eaten yet. I finally quit the violent stuff ive been doin, im a regular person now...i hope.Doubt it. No1 is normal. Especially me. I wonder if people will even read this stuff...if u do, let me know, just to make sure i aint gettin arthuritus in my fingers for nothin...haha. X_x  
    
</post>
</Blog>