<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      On Friday night, I found that I had nothing to do. I informed this to my friends, Josh and Natalie,in La Mesa and they invited me down for the weekend. At 9:00 PM, I jumped in the car and set forth on a two hour drive down the coast.  Saturday morning, Josh, his son Jacob and I took off for Coronado Central Beach. It was overcast, so I neglected to put on sunscreen. That was a mistake. By the time we left, I was burnt to a crisp. My back is bright red and quit painful.  Later that night, we headed to a local Thai restaurant, where we feasted on Red Curry Chicken and Panang Chicken. While we were there, I downed a few Singha's. Pretty good. The restaurant had extremely slow service, but the waitress was very cordial.  That night, Josh and I headed down to a local pool hall/bar, Joltin' Joes. We drank a couple pitchers of Bass, bs'd a bit, ogled the waitress, shot some sloppy pool and staggered afew blocks home.  It was nice to get out of town for the weekend. I think next weekend I will take another short road trip.  
    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My week has been rather dull. Spent almost every evening home alone this week. I am content with this. I have not been very sociable.   I finally got my plane ticket to Mexico. I am leaving August 15 Guanajuato, where I will be spending two nights. I will also be spending two nights in San Miguel de Allende, two nights in Mexico City and my last two nights will be in Acapulco. I am really looking forward to this trip. This will be a quintessential backpacking trip. The only things I'm bringing is money, backpack and my passport. The only thing I have arranged is my accommodations (hostels) and really do not know what I'll do once I get there.   I'm really ansty to get out of the house this weekend. I am tempted to go on a short road trip, but I really don't know where to go. Perhaps I will go to San Diego, or head north or out to the desert...in reality, I will probably not go anywhere...we'll see. 
    
</post>
<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I have read about 100 pages of John Kennedy Toole's "A Confederacy of Dunces." This is a great novel, one of the best I've ever read. Ignatius Reilly is one of the more interesting characters I have encountered. He seems to me to be slightly autistic, perhaps suffering from Asperger's Syndrome. Here are some of the symptoms of Asperger's Syndrome I believe Ignatius Reilly exhibits. I found this list of common symptoms on   urlLink WebMD     Problems with social skills:  Children with Asperger's syndrome generally have difficultywith others and often are awkward in social situations. They generally do not make friends easily.   Eccentric or repetitive behaviors:  Children with this condition may develop odd, repetitive movements, such as hand wringing or finger twisting.   Unusual preoccupations or rituals:  A child with Asperger's syndrome may develop rituals that he or she refuses to alter, such as getting dressed in a specific order.   Communication difficulties:  People with Asperger's syndrome may not make eye contact when speaking with someone. They may have trouble using facial expressions and gestures, and understanding body language. They also tend to have problems understanding language in context.   Limited range of interests:  A child with Asperger's syndrome may develop an intense, almost obsessive, interest in a few areas, such as sports schedules, weather or maps.   Coordination problems:  The movements of children with Asperger's syndrome may seem clumsy or awkward.   Skilled or talented:  Many children with Asperger's syndrome are exceptionally talented or skilled in a particular area, such as music or math.     Apparently, there is a movie interpretation of this book in production. Will Farrell has been cast as Ignatius. I believe he can effectively convey the character, but he doesn't really embody the physical traits of Ignatius. I will definitely see it when it is released.     
    
</post>
<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      These two are my favorite. I amalgamated images of revolutionary zeal and bourgeois oppression.        The picture below is my first attempt at Photoshop.I like how it looks, but it is somewhat derivative.    urlLink     Click on the image for a full-sized view.   
    
</post>
<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      On Friday, the federal government declared obesity a disease. This will open up radical treatments, such as gastric bypass, to be covered under Medicare. The major consequence of this decision will be that it will allow Americans to absolve themselves of any personal responsibility for their behavior. American's love to hear, "Oh, it's not myfault, I am (the world, society, etc.) this way because of __________. You can fill in the blank with anything, be it genetics, illegal immigrants, Islamic Fundamentalists, liberals, conservatives, whites. But the truth is, we are a slovenly, uncouth, passive aggressive society. All the traits that made this society great, such as the Frederick Jackson Turner's, mythical "rugged individualist"are dead and buried.     
    
</post>
<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      and I have nothing to do. My phonehasn't rang forseveral hours. The onlyphonecalls I have receivedtoday have been from my landlord. I've been calling her to complain about the sorry state of myplumbing. She has been assuring me for several days that the plumber is on his way.    I've been sitting around most of the day waiting for the plumber who never showed up. Tomorrow, I suspect, I will be doing the same. Nothing makes me feel like I've wasted a day like waiting for someone who never shows up.    I did hang out with some friends last night. Weplayed Texas hold'em. I lost$20. I was getting shitty cards the whole night. It was an uncomfortable experience. I did not really want to be there. I tried to mask my discomfort with alcohol, but the only thing it accomplished wasmaking me really tired.    I didn't get homeuntil around 3:00 AM. I fell asleep almost immediatly.I had a bought of sleep paralysis. It usually only happens whenI sleep on my back after a night of drinking. The first time it happened to me it was scary, but now I recognize what it is. During sleep paralysis, thebody is shut down, but the mind is awake. People sometimes have the sensation that someone is standing on their chest, smothering. I believe that is where many of the alien abduction stories originate.           
    
</post>
</Blog>