<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        E ai pessoas!!!!!!      Estamos colocando algumas coisas aqui antes que vocês estejam querendo me matar.        Ontem eu assisti um show que o KoRn fez na CBGB EM 2003. Só pra variar foi muito loko,        eu to colocando ai embaixo a letra de Right now musica que abriu o Show . E por falar em show , o Linkin Park        Definiu o local do show. Sera no Estadio do Morumbi, e pra variareu vou nem que seja pra meu entrar pelao esgoto do Morumbi !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!    Bem chega de besteira, a letra para satisfazer seus desejos:         Artista:Korn       Álbum:Take A Look In The Mirror       Título:Right Now              I´m feeling mean today Not lost, not blown away Just irritated and quite hated Self control breaks down Why´s everything so tame? I Like my life insaneI´m fabericating and debating Who I´m gonna kick around Right now Can´t find a way To get accross the hate When I see you Right nowI feel it scratch insideI want to slash and beat you Right now I rip apart the things inside That excite you Right now I can´t control myself I Fucking hate youI´m feeling cold today Not hurt just  Fucked awayI´m devastated and frustrated God I feel so bound So why´d I feel the need? I think it´s time to bleedI´m gonna cut myselfand watch the blood hit the ground Right now Can´t find a way To get accross the hate When I see you Right now I feel it scratch insideI want to slash and beat you Right now Irip apart the things inside That excite you Right now I can´t control myself I Fucking hate you You open your mouth againI swear  I´m gonna break it You open your mouth again, Oh God  I cannot take it Shut up, shut up, shut up or I´ll Fuck you up Shut up, shut up, shut up or I´ll Fuck you up Shut up, shut up, shut up or I´ll Fuck you up! Shut up, shut up, shut up or I´ll Fuck you up! Shut up, shut up, shut up or I´ll Fuck you up! Shut up, shut up, shut up or I´ll Fuck you up! Right now Can´t find a way To get accross the hate When I see you Right now I feel it scratch insideI want to slash and beat you Right now I rip apart the things inside That excite you Right now I can´t control myself I Fucking hate you I Fucking hate you [x4] I Fucking hate you (Shut up!) [x2] Shut up!        
    
</post>
<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       E ai pessoas        Estamos melhorando!!!!    Parece que ja parou de Chover(com C maiusculo mesmo pela chuva que deu ontem rsrsrsrsrsrs!!!!), e eu como de costume estou postando algo.    Ah!!! Me desculpem por eu não ter postado alguma coisa interessante ontem ,masé que como a chuva eu estava frio e pensando em muitas coisas,mas deixa pra lá.    eu to colocando algumas coisas para vocês darem uma olhada,depois comentem ou me manda um mail     Até    Estranho    urlLink http://'http://www.palavraestranho.theblog.com.br/hoobastank.doc'    urlLink http://'http://www.palavraestranho.theblog.com.br/My hero.doc'    urlLink http://'http://www.palavraestranho.theblog.com.br/One Last Breath.doc'    urlLink http://'http://www.palavraestranho.theblog.com.br/velvet revolver.doc'   
    
</post>
<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       E ai Pessoas        Eu estou Fazendo o possivel para colocar o maximo de coisas possiveis para vocês lerem , mas não estou conseguindo,        Bem hoje pra variar ,chovendo e fazendo um frio do c******(até agora não sei pro que não fui pra casa),eu acabei de criar esse blog,que parece ser melhor que os anteriores ,que eu ainda não desativei ,mas não estou postando mais nada neles por causa dos problemas técnicos do Sites,como eu já estou aqui vou falar mais uma vez, Lilian se você ler isto eu somente quero conversar com Você em um digamos assim um Campo Neutro.        Voltando a ETE, eu vi hoje o meu indice de faltas que não sei como esta em 18% com 87 faltas(bem eu sei que eu faltei pra caramba em Matemática, mas não tanto assim!!!!!)   Éisso então pessoas até amanhã !!!!!!           Estranho        
    
</post>
<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       E ai pessoas       desculpe eu não estar postando nada ,mas é que eu estou vendo se eu mudo a template desse blogger por uma melhor      se alguem tiver uma sugestão me manda um mail    urlLink mtbgrft_estranho@yahoo.com.br    fiquem com três letras do  tio Ozzy  ,  Perry Mason,No more tears  Mama I come home :     Artista: Ozzy Osbourne Álbum: Ozzmosis Título: Perry Mason  On His Way To Dinner When It Took Him By Surprise And With One Pull Of The Trigger He Would Vanish Overnight Dancing By The Roadside Holding On For Dear Life Then A Gun From Out Of Nowhere Made A Widow Of His Wife  I Don't Mind Single File Down The Runway Feelin' Fine And I'll See You My Friend Over And Over Again  Who Can We Get On The Case? We Need Perry Mason Someone To Put You In Place Calling Perry Mason Again, Again  Riding Painted Horses Oh The Kids They Love It So You Can See It On Their Faces How They Love The Wind To Blow Minding My Own Business Like My Mama Always Said But If I Don't Try To Help 'Em They Could Wind Up On The Front Page  I Don't Mind Draw The Line, Then Draw Me An Arrow Feelin' Fine And I'll See You My Friend Over And Over Again  Who Can We Get On The Case? We Need Perry Mason Someone To Put You In Place Calling Perry Mason Again, Again  Wake Me When It's Over Tell Me It's All Right Just Keep On Talking Baby I've Been Doing This All Night How Much Did You Give Me Tell Me It'll Be All Right  Who Can We Get On The Case? We Need Perry Mason Someone To Put You In Place Calling Perry Mason Again Again Again Again Again                 Artista: Ozzy Osbourne Álbum: The Ozzman Cometh Título: No More Tears   The light in the window is a crack in the sky A stairway to darkness in the blink of an eye A levee of tears to learn she´ll never be coming back The man in the dark will bring another attack  Your momma told you that you´re not supposed to talk to strangers Look in the mirror tell me do you uthink your life´s in danger here, yeah  CHORUS  No more tears  Another day passes as the night closes in The red light goes on to say it´s time to begin  I see the man around the corner waiting, does he see me? I close my eyes and wait to hear the sound of someone screaming here  CHORUS  So now that it´s over can´t we just say goodbye? I´d like to move on and make the most of the night Maybe a kiss before I leave you this way Your lips are so cold I don´t know what else to say  I never wanted it to end this way my love my darling Believe me when I say to you in love I think I´m falling here  CHORUS      Como eu queria cantar essa musica!!!!!       Artista: Ozzy Osbourne Álbum: The Ozzman Cometh Título: Mama, I´m Coming Home   Times have changed and times are strange Here I come, but I ain´t the same Mama, I´m coming home Times gone by seem to be You could have been a better friend to me Mama, I´m coming home  You took me in and you drove me out Yeah, you had me hypnotized Lost and found and turned aroound By the fire in your eyes  You made me cry, you told me lies But I can´t stand to say goodbye Mama, I´m coming home I could be right, I could be wrong Hurts so bad, it´s been so long Mama, I´m coming home  Selfish love yeah we´re both alone The ride before the fall But I´m gonna take this heart of stone I just got to have it all  CHORUS  I´ve seen your face a hundred times Everyday we´ve been apart I don´t care about the sunshine, yeah ´Cause Mama, Mama, I´m coming home I´m coming home  You took me in and you drove me out Yeah, you had me hypnotized Lost and found and turned around By the fire in your eyes  CHORUS          
    
</post>
</Blog>