<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ANGEL      I don’t think much about it anymore, but there was a time I couldn’t get it out of my head.    It was a day I didn’t think I would survive, the metropolis of intuition that was vacuumed in my mind was endless. I wanted to get it out and fast. I hate myself when I am so inconsistent and incoherent. I am in a state that cannot be reversed or understood. I can’t remedy it.    Sex was never as good with her as it was in my mind.    There is nothing like cotton t-shirt sheets.    I feel creative but can’t understand why. It’s been months since I have written.    The sunlight wakes me again, and I want to die.    I hear Massive Attack in my head…..the soft ambient noise in my mind that seems to always be there. Angel, Angel, Angel. I love that girls voice.   
    
</post>
<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        I understand    It is defined by truth and reality, it is not the love I feel for you that is truest, and it is my action in response to that love. I love you because in china a butterfly flapped its wings. I love you because the centrifugal force of the earth’s rotation makes me. I love you because you are whole and sane and so beautiful it hurts to touch you. I love you because at night your sweet dreams move your body closer to mine, skin touching for days it seems. I love you because when I wake next to you and the sun shines over our bodies, Mother Nature tells me this is the most natural thing I can ever have. Human life is but a mili-second in the big picture so there is no time to waste. In the morning you smell of sweet vanilla when I press my face into your neck. Your breasts curving so gracefully, I watch the lines of your body and try to memorize them. Your fingers so soft and strong…not to dainty and not to hard. It’s the kind of thing you wish for when you are single, or at least when I was single, and lucky enough I got what I wanted, no less and no more. At night when you wrap your legs around me I almost melt. Your sweet lips covering me like a cotton sheet of sweet desire. True is your love for me.  
</post>
</Blog>