<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Been looking at getting back into cycling, it was something I used to enjoy but have not really done for some years. So I went to the big smoke; ostensibly tolook at what modern cycling technology has to offer, but really to just get out and about a bit.I am afraid to say that three grand is somewhat excessive for a pushbike, I don't care if it is made from rare elements only found on distant planets, bonded with Kevlar and carbonfibre using strange hitech space age polymers and that it weighs less than a gnat's fart. It is still too bloody much. Besides, who needs that level of engineering in a pushbike? Maybe check out E-bay later.  I also think I need a change in career... Actually, I should probably get a career first, just to see if I like it.  Pretty much an uneventful few days.Which isbecoming a habit, and a tiresome one at that.    
    
</post>
<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ennui...A feeling of weariness or languor : Boredom.  Languor... Pining : Listlessness : dreamy inertia(?)   Had aslow and miserableday, filled with "dreamy inertia" and decide what I needed was a treat. So I toddled off to "world of stuff" to purchase somethingthat wouldreaffirm my life, infusing happiness and joy in me once again and make me realise just how dang goshed good this li'l world can be. What I got waseight assorted Donuts in a flimsy box. And while I was waiting in the queue with my happiness placed squarely on the conveyor and my crisp money clutched in my hand, and after I had got bored looking at other peoples idea of happiness layed out on afore-mentioned belt (Golf mag, cat food and denture cream -what a shitty life he's got!) I decided that I hate the word "Donuts"... I keepthinking it should be"Doughnoughts"but that looks pretensious and arsey. While the spelling "Doughnuts" is neither one thing or the other and just looks wishy washy and unsure. So I began to try and think of other names for themthat would annoymy sensibilities less - queue boredom is a terrible affliction and I find that I think the utmostshite when trying to combat it. Butall I thought of either soundedreally lame(Pastry Oh) or likea homoerotic pet name (sugar ring). So Donuts it is.   Apropos of nothing: The spell checker tried to replace "homoerotic with hemorrhoids" which made me laugh.    
    
</post>
<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am confused,    Couldn't sleep, so ambled about online and suddenly I'm doing the blogging thing. This can only mean that it is no longer fashionableand "like, so last year"or I'm somehow being conned out of heaps of money.But who knows, maybe some wealthy fool will mistake my navel gazing rambles for genius and give me large sums of cashand/orkudos. Then again maybe not.    I am not exactly sure what is expected of me, or of this document.I dislike people who appear self obsessed, self indulgent and arrogant and this kind of activity seems to portray exactly those traits. Just another nobody with nothing to say andmaking a bloody big song and dance about it in the process. - "An empty can rattles the most". But, I am going to do it anyway, which probably makes me a hypocrite and I hate those as well.       
    
</post>
<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Another pair of nailclippers vanishes into the Ether.  That's seven this year.  Where do they go?  Are they biodegradable?  Do they dissolve after touching air?  I don't understand why I keep losing them.  After much thought I decided to approach the problem in the style of the great fictional detective Sherlock Holmes who said "Once you eliminate the impossible, whatever remains, no matter how improbable, must be the truth." so I have come to the conclusion that I have an infestation of Kleptomaniac Pixies with a penchant for chrome nailclippers. I am assuming they worship them as some kind of God totem thingy. It's either that or something to do with Worm holes in the space-time continuum, but I feel more at home with Sticky fingered fairy folk. There is something deeply unsettling about cutting your toenails with a big pair of scissors and I don't want to do it anymore. Now, it is my intention to capture one of the pilfering little sprites (red handed no less!) and become filthy rich and famous, or atleast reasonably well off and vaguely familiar.   And, I'm bored now...  Sleep beckons! 
    
</post>
</Blog>