<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   So I'm in this hotel, and there's a sign on the bathroom wall:     HELP SAVE MOTHER EARTH Every day, millions of gallons of water and tons of detergent are used to   
</post>
<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Expanders. My 15 year old daughter used the term in a tone that was not the least bit disparaging. As in, "so-and-so has expanders". For all I knew these could have been some new kind of athletic shoes, but from the context, I correctly concluded that she was referring to the practice of placing barrel shaped rings into one's earlobes, and incrementally increasing the size of the rings until the orifice has stretched to the desired diameter. I am relieved that my daughter has no desire to enlarge her lobes, but I was a bit surprised that she did not seem as repulsed by the idea as I was. Not that I have anything against creative self-expression. If someone wants to mutilate their body, that's none of my business - except when they want to serve me food. Case in point: The day after my daughter told me about her friend's earloops, I went into McDonalds. I was only halfway in the door when someone yelled at me, "WELCOME TO McDONALDS." (This in itself irritates me, but I'll save that rant for another day.) As I approached the counter I saw the source of the yelling: a teenage kid who apparently was absent the day they taught how to wear a cap. But the yelling and the cap and the fact that he had no idea what he was doingwere only minor annoyances compared to the earlobe abuse. The last thing I want to see while trying to choosefrom a menu ofMcDelicacies is a see-through earlobe. If I want to see something behind your ear, I'll just ask you to tilt your head, thankyouverymuch. Restauranteurs take note -many of usconsider the following items to be unappetizing whendisplayed on waitpersons: ear expanders, eye-brow piercings, lip and/or tonguestuds, bones through the nose, and lower lips stretched over dinner plates.   I have never understood the attraction to poking holes in one's body just because one can. Even the "harmless" tradition of regular old ear-piercing has always seemed a bit primitive to me. Just because we have those things called ears hanging out there, we think we need to hang decorations from them. When I was growing up in rural East Texasduringthe sixties and seventies, this seemed to be a right of passage for young teenage girls. At the time it seemed like a big deal, requiring highly trained specialists and follow-up visits. Now you can have your ears pierced at a mall kiosk in the time it takes for mom to buy a cell phone, also from a kiosk.    The serious issue here, along with the whole tattoo thing, is a cultural trend in our society thatpreaches we can do whatever we want with our bodies, including desecration. If it offends others, good. If it dishonors God's creation, even better. America's departure from Judeo-Christian values is giving rise to a neo-paganism which is expressing its values through rituals, including "body modification". The pagan origins of this behavior is perhaps what makes it so repulsive to those us of us raised in 20th century America. Ironically,its popularity among mainstream young people probably has little to do with paganism; instead it stems from a basic human need to irritate parents, coupled with the current trend of"herd individualism". But when combined with the increasingly secular nature of our society,such rituals are indicative of a generation not simply playing at neo-paganism, buttruly becominga new form of a very real pagan society. We see plenty of evidence of this shift around us. Ancient pagan cultures did not value human life. They often honored plants and animals above people. They engaged self mutilation. Some engaged in infanticide. Sound familiar?   Body piercing may be just a pop culture fad, but I believe to some degree it reflects a major shift in our society. Those who teach that the concept of God is a dangerous, primitive myth,who believe that an enlightened society will emerge from the abolition of moral absolutes, are instead leading us backward into a culture much more primitive, and much more dangerous than they imagine.    

						
</post>
<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   It's 10:35 on a Monday night and I have to work tomorrow. I should be in bed by now, but instead I decided to type "Blog" into Google to see what all the fuss is about. So here I am. I've entered the blogosphere. We'll see what develops.  

						
</post>
</Blog>