<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Usually, i'd do 4-5 games for a quick review. But damn it's been a quiet month when it comes to gaming . I know that ESPN NFL2K5 and Madden 2005 just came out, but i'll do a review on them in my next gaming update.   Tales of Symphonia-92% I'm quite suprised that this RPG is so damn good considering it's for the Gamecube.   Pros- 80 hours of gameplay, storyline changes based on character relationship, cel-shaded graphics done by Kosuke Fujishima, and tons of mini-games and sidequests.   Cons- Battle System can get very confusing at times when it comes to controlling your three other characters.   Wow, it's the first review i've ever done here on GAMING of TODAY and the strange thing is, Idon't have a Gamecube. Well, I borrowed it from a friend cause I heard this game is so damn good. Anyway, i'll give you people a dash through the past giving you the scores of games like Halo, Gran Turismo 3 and all that.     
    
</post>
<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I will update this every once in awhile when I doGBA(SP)reviews.  Here are the scores:  COMING SOON!  
    
</post>
<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I will update this every once in awhile when I doXbox reviews.  Here are the scores:  COMING SOON!  
    
</post>
<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I will update this every once in awhile when I doGC reviews. Here are the scores:  COMING SOON! 
    
</post>
<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I will update this every once in awhile when I do PS2 reviews. Here are the scores:  COMING SOON!  
    
</post>
<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am pretty much collecting votes to see which are YOUR Top 10 Games of the Month. See how it is this month(July). I managed to get over 2,000 votes this month. Not alot, but it's not bad for a new site.   As of right now, this is how it stands forthe Top10 Games of the Month.  ( )- Previous Ranking * *- Number of Weeks #1   1. Halo Xbox  2. NCAA Football 2005 PS2  3. ESPN NFL2K5 PS2  4. Otogi:Myth of Demons Xbox(I was quitesuprised to see this rankedeven in the top 5!)  5. Red Dead Revolver PS2  6.Super Smash Bros. Melee GC  7. Driv3r PS2  8. Ninja Gaiden Xbox  9. Metroid Prime GC  10. Custom Robo GC    
    
</post>
<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've noticed that alot of great games have been ignored lately. Games like Breakdown, Eternal Ring, Otogi, or even Viewtiful Joe. None of these games sold like hotcakes. What suprises me even more is that crappy games like The Hulk, Smashing Drive, and Arctic Thunder have sold more than any of these games. Are people just insane or do they just not listen to game critics? Cause it seems like they do when you see them go to a site like Gamepro and post how they got ripped off. No,  YOU  ripped yourself off. Don't be blaming the company for making you spend 40-50 bucks for a game. Trust me, if you don't read a review these days, your vulnerable to wasting 40-50 bucks on a really crappy game. It's not the 1995's as I said5 freaking minutes ago in that other post, you can't just buy a game like back then and expect it to be amazing. One example: Enter the Matrix, OOOHHHHH!!! The Matrix! Yeah, you don't wanna spend your money on that game... "BUT MOMMY! IT'S THE MATRIX!!!" Get aclue dude, the game sucks, open your eyes to the better games out there. For those that bought Breakdown or any of the games listed in the beginning of the paragraph, then I must applaud you for knowing your games. Yes, just because people don't buy a game, doesn't mean it sucks. But just because people buy a game, doesn't mean it's good. Doesn't make sense? Just read the damn reviews! Tons of sites to recommend to you:    urlLink http://www.gamingevolved.com The bestsite on the World Wide Web, I am also a staff writer here, check out all the amazing reviews!    urlLink http://www.gamepro.com  A site you should rely on only if they are reviewing console games, they usually just go with 5/5's on all PC games so ignore those reviews.   urlLink http://www.gamespot.com Errr... a little bit on the harsher side. Honestly, i've seen some good games go down the drain in this site. But they know their games nonetheless.    urlLink http://www.ign.com  A great site too, check out their reviews!   urlLink http://www.gamerankings.com  Well, if your too lazy to check gamepro, gamespot and ign, then just go here to see the  average  score of a game from every game site combined.   Now, you have no excuse to buy yourself a crappy game. Unless, you don't know how to read.  
    
</post>
<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Many people expect things to  stay  the same in the gaming world today. True, it was better than, but if you keep looking back, you'll never know what's ahead. Like for example, people complain so much about how games these days don't have the same  replay  and  gameplay  value as back then. But thenagain, it does, not in the same way. It's what you call  online  gaming, something that has gotten bigger. Just like VHS and DVD, they play movies, yes, but not the same way... sort of the same analogy, but in the same sense, different. Remember people, it's the year 2004, not the year 1995, so if you want much of the same, your stuck playing a handheld like the GBA, or just going old school with your SNES, NES and any other systems you have from back then. But don't be looking for old school in new school games, cause apparently, these game developers are looking to move  foward , not  backward  in the gaming industry.  
    
</post>
<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What the hell is up with kids these days. It seems that console sales matter to them so much that they will make a big deal out of it in every game site possible. Ooooh! My console sold more than yours! Yeah, act like a moron and see how far your getting yourself. Honestly, it just doesn't matter. All you need to know is that as long as the title " *Insert Console Here* is DEAD" doesn't show up, then you shouldn't really care about how much it sells. Infact, what you SHOULD care about, is how much a particular game you like sells. That way, there "might" be a SEQUEL for it's success. See where i'm getting at here? Fanboys don't think... Not enough gamers get an education, and the whole world falls to where every possible sale number counts. So in conclusion, what i'm trying to say here is that... you need to get yourself a life if sales numbers make you really happy(unless of course, you work for that company, then you know you won't get laid off).   
    
</post>
<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay, so who actually bought this crap? I am actually a bit suprised that it even sold like five thousand or more. What was Nokia thinking anyway? Handhelds = Nintendo right now, and that's the way it's gonna be until Sony comes out with their PSP handheld. Which then, it will probably be Handhelds = Nintendo and Sony. But Nokia? What crap... honestly, did they actually think they could just barge into the gaming industry and be successful? So anyways, it's a good thing it's only like 100 bucks now, cause now, I still won't buy it. As I said before and yet, I will say it again, N-Gage is for losers.  
    
</post>
<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Seems like everyone has been making a big deal out of the whole "August 24th" thing regarding Halo 2. Face it, when you got a guy who tattoo's his arm with a date just to prove to people it will come out that day, I don't think it would go any other way. November 9th ladies and gentlemen... if the game though SOMEHOW comes out August 24th, then that'll be the biggest damn shocker ever. Of course, I would also be proven wrong in my opinion that this August 24th rumor was all a lie. We're all waiting for Halo 2 yes, but i've been waiting for other games too. Some of them like Fable, Kingdom Hearts 2, Devil May Cry 3, and who could forget, the new Legend of Zelda game. So many great games coming out this year and next, but one thing that bugs me is that the PS3, Xbox 2, and GC2 are coming out ALREADY. 2005 or 2006, yeah, I mean 4 years apart? How long did it take me to save up for my systems? Yeah, a LONG time. I'm 16 and I don't have a full-time job where I can just get paid a thousand bucks a month, so yeah, I hope i'll be able to afford at least one of these systems. To conclude this, i'll be making my "Top Games List" in a few minutes and make a link to that.  
    
</post>
<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Alright, I made this blog just for my site Xtreme Halo.  Am I big fan of Halo?  Well, I wouldn't making this blog now wouldn't I?  Anyway, with all the anticipations, here are a few things you HAVE TO follow:  1. Don't follow crap, as in November 9th is the release date, any other release dates for Halo 2 just DOESN'T MATTER.  2.  No Demo UNTIL THE GAME COMES OUT!  Yep, so ilovebees.com... no no, it's just hyping you up for tons of info on August 24th, nothing more.   3. NO ONE HAS THE GAME!!!  If someone says they have the game or something, you know what you have to do, no, not get proof with pics, but actually SEE THE GAME for yourself, although it will only be a BETA game, hey, proof is proof, and even pics can't prove crap.   So there you, I know EVERYONE has been waiting forever for this game, but just hang tight, what makes me NOT want to wait for this game is the fact that school is two months in already.  Which means homework... projects and yeah, sleeping early.  So maybe that would be a way to get you "less" hyped up for the game.  I'll be updating frequently with matches I have had, and remember this is MY MULTIPLAYER NAME:  Deadmeister, so if you hear that name around the blog, yeah that's me!  
    
</post>
</Blog>