<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Here I sit in my non-airconditioned office, feeling each degree of humidity affect my body, while my parents and brothers tour Germany.   I will visit Subway for lunch, where I will eat a boring six-inch Pizziola sub and drink 32 ounces of Diet Pepsi, when I could be eating at a German restaurant enjoying a nice glass of beer.   I will later spend my entire evening in meetings, missing out on dinner and games with my wife and kids, when I could be seeing places of historical significance.   I'm the one who took German in college.   I'm the one who studied Dietrich Bonhoeffer, Martin Luther, and Karl Barth.   I'm the one who thinks that stollen is the greatest Christmas treat.   But no, I am in Pennsyl-boring-ia, and my parents and brothers are in Germany! 
     
    
</post>
<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Yesterday Jennifer and I discovered that we are expecting another child!       We were not planning to have any more children, but the Lord has a different plan for us!      
     
    
</post>
<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       "The Ten Commandments were never intended as a prerequisite of God's favour, a list of essential qualifications for blessing. Rather they are God saying, 'I love you and I've already proved it to you. So trust me. Keep these commandments because not only do they make sense for you, but they are a way of demonstrating and reflecting who I am to the whole world - the God of love and mercy, not of arbitrary power and revenge.' But this liberating message is often lost today." (51)        Instead of seeing the Ten Commandments as a list of rules and regulations stated to gauge our ability to receive God's blessings, they should be seen asGod's instructions on how to live a life that reflects upon who God is.      "I am the Lord your God, who rescued you from slavery in Egypt." (Ex. 20:2, NLT)       The Ten Commandments reflect upon a God who is a loving rescuer. He is a God who does not only identify with those who have much, but with those who have little. He is a God who chose to deliver a group of people who were slaves to those in power. Only after their redemption did He showHis peoplea way to livethat would speak more aboutHis redemptive love thanHisjudgment and wrath.          
     
    
</post>
<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Underneath a partly cloudy skyscape, covered in a thin layer of humidity induced sweat, wondering why I haven't done a better job romancing my wife, I welcome everyone to the unveiling of my blog.  
     
    
</post>
</Blog>