<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Me and my friend were thinking one day, how could there be like 5 or 6 Guys to come before Neo? in the span of 30-40 years there's the Matrix Mr. Anderson as a child and the Real World Neo. they must have been alive at the same time. BUT... How? Would that not indicate another Mr. Anderson on the rise? or was it he was killed to cause Neo to pick the other door, The door to Trinity. They are a great trilogy and I suggest that any sci-fi / fantasy lover watch them, if you have not already, which like half the population of the worldhas. So many puzzles maybe when i finally get to play MATRIX: ONLINE they will be answered. i'll go in search of this Mr. Anderson... If he indeed does exist. Many of ym thoughts may sound ludocrist to many but you are not in my mind so do not criticize me. and questions or comments email me b/c my posts are bein gay..........im me also. BUT...aww forget it... 
    
</post>
<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tell a limitless being to create a rock it cannot lift...........can it be done? if it is limitless how can it not pick it up?  
    
</post>
<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Prologue To give a short summery of the history of the human race, it can be summed up into one word: Greed. They craved nothing but more money, more power, more land, always more more more. They never stopped. The thing about this is they wanted it all by doing nothing. Well actually by someone or something else doing it for them. The glorious artificial intelligence was the key to their dreams. It could plan, fight, build, and make anything MAN wanted. These robots, being able to think, realized all they did for the humans and all they could do for each other. The rest went down hill for the human race. They were all corralled in small cities, loaded onto space ships and launched into space to be sent to a little place called the sun. Some got free of being captured and made small rebel groups to try and retake the planet. Humans regretted the invention of A.I. they also lost all belief in any kind of deity because they weren’t answering their calls and so they all became a unified people against the machines (A.K.A the mechs).    This section of the history of the humans starts with a small band of rebels that have utilized the special technology of converting the mind of a mech. This unique thing could be the answer to the rebellion. They hoped. M A R C H 1 5, 5 0 9 3 “God damnit close the doors!” came the screaming voice of the Captain. The loud screaming and screeching of joints and gears becoming louder and louder. “Sir, the doors are closing too slowly.” Said the voice on the radio. “I know we will need to do a manual override- NO TIME GET THE AUTO GUNS ONLINE NOW!!!” the three men just reaching the door went straight for the door controls. “No, too late, use the EM guns.” Said the captain. They ripped them out of the cabinet and instantly turned them on the mechs bolting at the door. Seconds before they were inside they shot bolts of electricity out and shut down the mechs. Too late. They already impaled one man, luckily that was it. “Please bring the mechs up to the lab, oh and dispose of little Seederman.” Said the radio. M A R C H 1 9, 5 0 9 3  One person in the lab was intensely busy at fiddling with wires and chips inside the head of a mech. This mech was humanoid in its head shape but its arms were flexible and snake-like with small claws on the ends. It had no legs but one slithering tail, in the likeness of its arms. There were three of them. The other two already were “cracked open”. “It’s finished!” he said. Over the PA system came his voice” All personnel please report to the laboratory, I have the key.”  “The key, what’s that moron talking about?” said Jones.  “Hey, just leave Kylan alone, he’s all we have for technical work.” Said the Captain. As soon as they were all gathered there he began to tell them of his discovery. He has learned how to “convert” the mechs to help and fight for the humans. At that moment all the crew, all 10 of them that is, started yammering on about “mechs are mechs we should just scrap them all”, and “no way this will work”. Then the Captain spoke up, right before Kylan activated them, “what if your “work” won’t work?” “Well then I guess we all die right here right now.” At that second they all jumped back 10 feet as the mechs were coming back online. They stood up and surveyed their surroundings, but did not leap at the crew. Then they looked at the Captain and asked in unison “What is thy bidding Master?”  “Oh my god, Kylan you did it!” said the Captain. Again they asked “What is thy bidding Master, we seek your jurisdiction.” “Well, I order you to patrol the perimeter of this compound and alert the systems of any sight of mechs, other than your selves” “As you wish, Master” and with that they were off. “That’s really cool Kylan did ye make ‘em say master and all that?” asked Jade. “No actually, I guess that’s what they say to the mechs that are higher up.” He replied. Within minuets of the departure of the mechs the alarms sounded, “Masters we detect some aerial mechs heading this way. Also a small group of hover tanks moving directly underneath them.” Instantly the Captain ordered”Everyone to your stations NOW” the compound exploded into action five went to the gun towers and five went for the main door. All the defense systems became animated in seconds, doors were closed and locked tight, and energy shields were up. “Well,” said the Captain, “let’s see how these mechs do against their old buddies.” By the time the five got into their gear and out the door one friendly mech was already destroyed. However, all the hovTANKs were completely annihilated. The Aerials came down fast on the second mech and swept it away into the sky. Next they tried to drop it on the remaining mech. This one, being a special one, could almost “sense” the imminent danger. It did not detect it regularly, but knew what was happening. This mech could think and all but this was different. He quickly darted out of the way, and reversed direction instantly to intercept one of the aerials. He brought it down with an attack of utter rage, if ever a mech could have rage. He leaped from one to the other, again and again. He brought them all down. This small skirmish took place far from the compound, meaning they were out of the radius of the explosion as the mechs dropped a bomb on it. The Captain turned to the mech, “hey, err, you well what ever your called, can you take care of us?”  “Master that is the reason mechs turned on you humans, do not revert me back.” It replied, “But I am called ZeTrappLaxicaNtrellador875341.”“Uh-hu, well we will call you Zet is this ok?” asked the Captain. “That shall be acceptable.” He replied. “Well is it possible that you will help us?” wondered Jones. “Indubitably,” said Zet. In the distance everyone could hear the humming of an engine. This humming has not been herd for at least a year. The noise was the smallest, quietest, most deadly mech. being so unique, they are in very short supply. The humans simply call it The Reaper. “Hey, yall are ye hearin that?” asked Jade. “Yea Jade I hear it, it sounds very familiar.” Said the Captain.  “I am very sure you recognize the sound of what you call The Reaper.” Informed Zet. “We are all aware they not one person has faced one of these things and lived?” said Jones. “Yea, so what do you mean?” asked the Captain. “I’m just saying WE ARE STILL STANDING HERE!” he screamed. At that moment The Reaper became visible, and they had no chance of escape. It passed straight through the group and they were all dead in seconds. Before he died the Captain asked Zet to continue their fight. He graciously agrees. As the Reaper passes through Zet leaped onto the back of the mech and lashed out at its circuits automatically shutting it down. They fell to the ground and he began rushing in the direction of the main Over Mind of the mechs M A R C H 3 1, 5 0 9 3   He reached the Over Mind within a few days. When he got there he was met by a defensive wall of hovTANKs. They were no match for him. He destroyed them all with an extreme pittance of work. It does not take Zet long to find and infiltrate the Over Mind compound. After he was inside Zet was ready to plug into the computers when he sensed something……..something right behind him. He turned around to find a Reaper. One thing was different about this reaper. It was a new model fresh off the assembly line. He had no idea how to deal with it, and saw no weaknesses. Zet then noticed he was standing inside the Over Mind. If he was damaged it was possible to self-destruct and wipe out the Mech center. He lunged straight into battle with the Reaper. Instantly it severed his left arm and pinned him to the floor. Just flailing out Zet hit the reaper on a small plate in the middle of its chest, exposing its central power core. Snatching it the Reaper was shutdown. He had done it. Zet crawled out from under the mech and plugged into the computers. He then took control of the Over Mind and all machines were under his control. Zet was the mechs now. Seconds after he plugged in he saw the entire human race was already gone. The Captain and his crew were the last surviving humans. So from then on he just spread and populated the entire earth. Well he did not stop there, ZeTrappLaxicaNtrellador875341 spread mechism to all planets and explored the unknown. Finding and living along side other very intelligent alien life. 
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Happy Birth Day To You, 
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Why must people be involved in what they have no right to be involved in?  I love the input of people, but not the intervention. If you have cold hard evidence, and you can prove to me what you are worried about with PHYSICAL, TANGEBLE, EVIDENCE please do so. Other wise . STAY THE F*** OUT OF OUR BUSINESS! 
    
</post>
</Blog>