<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    TEXT:  Ecclesiastes 3:1-8   THEME:  The seasons of faith   I.  SEASONS    A.  Season - a time or part of the year during which a particular type of weather prevails. The time when something specified flourishes, develops, takes place, or is popular, permitted, or at it’s best.   B.  God wants you to know today that no matter what season of your life you are in right now that a change of season will inevitably have to come. Good or bad, happy or sad there will come a change of season. Are you willing to change also?   II. CHANGES  A.  We as people some times fight change we want things to stay the way they always have been. We want the things that worked before to continue to work.Change is necessary  good when it comes to growing spiritually.   B.  Each new season brings about a change for the earth. The leaves change colors  fall from the trees, the weather changes, days get shorter, nights longer    **You can’t wear your winter coat in the summer. Some   seasons spiritually require more fasting than others. Some   more prayer, more faith, more patience.  The things that comforted you last season     won’t  do this nextseason!**    III. FOUR SEASONS OF FAITH    A. Summer    1.   Summer is the time of enjoying the presence of the sun. The time  of blessing.   2.   This is the time to relax  enjoy the benefits of your life. When  you can take time to enjoy leisure activities.   3.   In the summer you not only see the Son but you feel His presence. The warmth of the Spirit as He touches you.   4.   It is also a time when you don’t have to cover yourself so much for   protection from the elements.   B. Autumn/Fall  1.  Autumn is the time the trees shed their leaves. Those extra things    that also draw precious energy. Energy that will be needed to last   the coming winter.   -There is a season in your walk when you will need to get rid of   those things that are a drain upon your time  shed the things that  hinder you like leaves drop them to the ground. Those habits   attitudes have to go if you are going to survive winter.   3. In autumn the farmer turns over the ground so last year’s stalks  stems can   become next year’s harvest. The freshly turned ground covered with   manure form the mulch you need to prepare the ground  replenish   the starving ground.Like the ground that has received little, you too need to be broken    turned over, allowed to rest for a time, and prepared for the next growing season.   **ALL OF THAT GARBAGE  MESS YOU WENT THROUGH IN THE  PAST. GOD IS GONNA USE THAT TO FERTILIZE THE SOIL OF   YOUR FUTURE! THAT’S WHY YOU WENT THROUGH WHAT YOU DID. TO PREPARE YOU FOR THE BLESSING THAT’S TO COME!**    C. Winter    4. When winter comes everything looks cold  almost dead. This is when trees build up their   strength for that burst of energy needed to grow in the spring.   5. Winter is also a time of waiting. There is no growth, the nights grow   longer, you see the sun but it’s rays don’t warm you. Winter can be a   sad, lonely time.  -This is the time most of us cry out to the Lord out of desperation.    Like a child waiting in line at a carnival. You see other people   getting their turn but you are forced to wait. But your turn will come.  The important thing about lasting a season is a patient perserverance    that is sensitive to the timing  divine purpose of God.   -You see a sense of timing cannot be faked. It’s like watching a choir    there’s that one guy desperately trying to clap on beat. Or in basic   training when you’re learning to march  there’s always that one   guy not only tripping over his feet but everyone else’s.   TIMING IS   CRUCIAL TO LASTING A SEASON     -When winter is particularly cold  bitter some people wont make it   through. They did not prepare for this season when the blessings   where falling this past summer. They thought summer would last   forever. But it didn’t.  -Sometimes it may warm up for awhile but then during the night   temperatures drop below zero. Some of us took that as a sign that winter is over  started to bud  blossom out of season  die. This is when the planted seeds of promise will be watered thoroughly with the tears of   struggle.   Remember…     (Psalms 126:5 NIV)   “Those who sow in tears will reap with songs of joy”     **No one can water these seeds in your life but you. No matter   how many people hold your hand, you still must shed your   own tears. Others can cry WITH  you but no one can cry FOR  you !    ** Some folk may get mad  try to fight the season. Trying to   protest the fact that they have to endure this. That’s OK you   can protest all you want. You can put on a bikini or a speedo    grab a sign  protest until your little heart is content. But   when you get over your pneumonia it’ll still be winter.     ONLY GOD CAN CHANGE THE SEASONS!!!!!!!!!!!!       **Spiritual winter may bring tears. Crying is good. Tears must   flow. But you must know when you have shed enough tears.   Don’t get stuck in a pity party. Don’t flood the crops. A certain   amount of tears are needed during the season of sowing but   don’t let the devil keep you weeping.   - LORD IT’S BEEN A LONG WINTER. I DON’T KNOW WHEN   IT’S GONNA END BUT I KNOW THERE’S A REASON FOR   THE SEASON!!     -TEARS MAYBE FOR THE WINTER BUT  JOY  IS FOR THE   SPRING!!!    B. SPRING      (Psalms 126:6 NIV)    He who goes out weeping, carrying seed to   sow, will return rejoicing ,bringing his sheaves with him.   1.   Spring is a time of renewal. The time of growth. The time when those seeds that were planted burst forth in all their beauty. The time to cast off the weight off that winter coat. To shake off the sluggish spirit of slumber.    (Psalms 1:3 NIV)  Like a tree planted by streams of water, which yields its fruit in season and whose leaf does not wither. Whatever he does prospers.    2.   Spring is the green light season. You feel as though you have been waiting without seeing any results. Suddenly the light changes from red to green  you are free to move. You can now accomplish things you tried to do at other times but could not perform.     *** THE DEVIL HAS CAUSED SOME OF YOU TO MISS   YOUR SEASON. HE’S BEEN TRYING TO TELL YOU   THAT “IT’S NOT THE RIGHT SEASON FOR THIS IT’S   NOT THE RIGHT TIME FOR THAT.” BUT I’M HERE TO   SAY THAT THE DEVIL IS A LIAR!!! ONLY GOD   CONTROLS THE SEASONS  GOD IS ABOUT TO MOVE   SOMEBODY INTO A NEW SEASON!!!***     

						
</post>
</Blog>