<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      So, we've all read "A Brief History of Time" by famed English astrophysicist, Steven J. Hawkins; we’ve all heard the hullabaloo about blackholes and the conservation of energy-matter. Well, I read the back cover and, you know what?   Hawkins: WRONG! Get a job.    Energy-matter can neither be created nor destroyed; and, sure-as-shit, doesn't disappear into somefantasticparallel universe. Dolt.    
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Survey says, Yes.I should be working right now. But, why aren't I?  Here are the options:  1) I'm leaving for the DNC tomorrow and, frankly, don't have much to do here.  2) After an introduction to "blogging" by Czarina ( urlLink http://czarinaofeverything.blogspot.com ), I've undergone an existential paradigm shift and will now devote my life to wasting time (including that of allwhoread this tripe)  3) I'm eating a burger;a shitty burger from the Senate 'Chef'; and, after I eat the shitty burger, will spend the rest of the day prostate in abdominal horror, before renouncing God sometime this evening  4) I am on the lookout for terrorists       
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I'm going to weigh in on the issue of the Notorious R, and that ridiculous organization she 'works' for: SPIRG.    This is, of course, U.S. PIRG—which stands for god-knows-what—and is pronounced, as I have articulated, "SPERRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRRG." The new name of U.S. PIRG is to encapsulate the emotional and olfactorydynamicof putridcarsickness; the kindexperienced on 5thgrade field trips.I'm sure you all can identify with that acidic smell which lingered in the back of your throat, emanating fromsomewhere in thebus. Just imagine upward pressure on your esophagus and stomach. What justifies this caustic connotation?This cult—excuse me! environmentallobby—indoctrinates listless intellects with not-so-accuratetalking points about various environmental issues, so they may openly terrify, cajole, and harass people for money. SPIRGERS roam the streets over the weekends, pestering everyone who walks by or opens the door with faulty information and scare tactics. For example, SPIRGERS clam that the mecury levels in fish lead to a pantheon of neurological disorders in children, including Autism. Here’s a little dramatization of a typical Sunday afternoon in Eastern Market (Washington, D.C., for all you out of The Know):    SPIRGER: Excuse me, Dude?  Innocent pedestrian: Yes?  SPIRGER: You and your children are going to—fucking die!—from mercury poison. That is, Dude, unless you give me fifty-bucks.  Innocent Pedestrian: Oh, god. Really?  SPIRGER: Yes. And before you die, you—and everyone you know—will get autism. Autism is in the water; the fish; the mercury; in the bed you sleep; under the bed; goes bump in the night; and, raises your taxes. I hope you wash your hands after going #2—if not, you’ll get Autism.  Innocent Pedestrian: …yes—I try? I don’t know.  SPIRGER: It’s worst than I though: Better give me $100. GIVEME, GIVEME, GIVEME! DEAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAATH!    The most recent Institute of Medicine (IOM) report concluded that there is no causalrelationship between Autism andfetalmercury exposure. SPIRGERS still make the claim.      My recommendations:  1) R sucks and should go away  2) Eat fish           
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Is it vain to devote my first posting to defend myself against theslanderous invectives, lobbed without consideration to the truth (or God in heaven),by a megalomaniac,Russki-pinko communist sympathizer? I think not. In fact, I’ll even indulge for a moment and speak of this vitriolic villain in perspicuity: Czarina is a Geek. Worse yet, she’s a commie-geek—and damn bitter that claw foot bathtubs don’t coincide with her neoburtalistic notions of interior design. If I were she, I’d swap the little red book for  Redbook .Maoism is so  passé.   
     

    
</post>
<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The DNC Qua Esoteric   For one who is so seldom lost for words, I’ll admit, I’m running dry to describe the Democratic National Convention. Not for lack of excited, though, for there was plenty of that. Rather, what’s lacking is a sense of reality to adhere each memory to my essential self. Sure, the memories are lucid; no, I wasn’t that intoxicated. But, no matter how well I remember it, the DNC is still alien.   The DNC—with all the glamour, glitz, and full-throttle egos of its participants—was but a flash in the pan: A moment of amorphic calamity, momentarily subsuming the collective consciousness of the Democrats, wresting away any good sense and bellowing a storm of Dionysian flame. After meeting celebrities and power icons, chatting with rockstars and actresses, I awake hung-over. After emerging from the torrid confluence of power and wealth, I reflect not on the events produced by it, but the feelings of normalcy. As the storm dissipates into clear placidity, I discover myself wrecked on shores of boredom—August recess.    
     

    
</post>
</Blog>