<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    This is Tenor_Man looking as goofy as possible...... urlLink   
     

    
</post>
<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         We all have to start somewhere.    And of course, we also know where ultimately we are headed...well in a gerneral sense anyway. I have done my best to avoid this whole blog thing. The problem I have with it is that most people are boring, stupid, or both. I know that sounds arrogant but I am not putting myself on high. I am simply stating a fact. I am a singer. Specifically, I am a classically trained opera singer. A tenore. I try to avoid saying opera singer really, mostly due to the numerous associations people have and the pictures they get in their minds. Like I said most people are stupid and they tend to generalize (" You're not fat" ). I call myself a singing actor beacause I am an actor. I am an actor that happens to sing. As i said i am a tenor (to be a real opera-geek I am what iscalled a Lirico-Spinto tenor by Italians, and a Jungendlicher Heldentenor by the Germans....in boxing terms I'm a middle weight). I live in NYC (Astoria, Queens) and am trying to get a performing career underway. I'd like to make my living perfoming in opera, musical theater, theater, or film. I don't have to be a mega-star or the 10th fourth tenor or anything of the sort. I simply want to be able to do what I am on this earth to "do" (aside from being a Dad, Partner, Son, Brother, Recovering Addict, etc). I want to be able to create characters and go through my "process" and inspire people, to move them to consider love, hope, compassion, beatuy, and other higher human truths. I have a need to express my humanity and I have something to share. But it ain't easy. Thus this blog is called a Tourney (for those of you who do not know what that mean please look it uphere:   urlLink  http://dictionary.reference.com/   .) And let me tell you this performing thing AIN"TFREAKINGEASY. This blog will be a a series of post about my progress or lack there of in trying to do this thing. This idea just came to me so I am not sure what my format will be exactly...it'll just be. Iwill stick mainly to the present or the very near future but I may also on occasion have a flashback or two(yes,THOSE kind as well). So have a look see, take a seat.....the show's about to start. Toi, toi, toi    !             
     

    
</post>
</Blog>