<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      yesterday cum home veri late cos my ah ma(my father side)she was sent to hospital(when we call her,she didnt ans)....i was there till bout 2am then reach home,my mama tell mi tdon go for my 2.4km run today and i never turn up......i scare mr cheen don belive mi ,then i die la.....run the whole skool 10 runs then mi bout 3+ then woke up...now mi going to see my ah ma again,so today is short but mi hope got good news bout her,,,,,,, 
      
</post>
<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       i think today is my most happy day in july!!!!    ya can say that my july is veri sad wan la and lonely    today b4 we go back to class,miss loy came to mi to find her during my recess go and find her    i thought i got do anything wrong(i think and think i didnt do anything wrong wat this week.)    as my recess today is on 10.30 after my dnt,but my dnt teacher veri good before 10.25 let us go for recess liao......    i went to recess and eat 2 serving cos no other class wat so veri free no need to line up!!!after i ate finish, i went to find miss loy(with a heavy heart)    i call her out,donno wats wrong with her la, veri late then came out bout 5+min like tat....    she came out with a form.....    she ask mi whether i know how to swim anot ,    then ask mi whether i know how to cycle...i said ya for both the que,then she pass mi the form,    the form is  (   NATIONAL CAMP 2004   )   i so happy bout it cos mi cant go OBS mahz    then after tat i go for SS, i so happy bout the camp thing.my teacher is giving out the commom test paper that i was veri scare bout it cos last sat i anyhow do,then my teacher read out my name,i was so scare and then my mark, i go    8/10    i so happy,1st time my SS got so high....    then lata, after skool i wait for didi to come back lorz,then we chat go eat then go home,now still veri happy    
      
</post>
<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       today the1st 2 hours,i am having math and i onli do sum onli so during class, listen and do at the same time...then to the graph part,i ask my friend to help mi to do but alot of blank and sum wrong 1(a....onli i correct but i never say anything la,cos she so good help mi to do)[hope miss log don look at my blog]  then after that is geo, we got back the commom test paper lorz then i got 4/14because i hate geo!!!!! i not the lowest la horz(kenn) [sorri kenn] haha then we got chinese but nothing much happen la then ENGlish,we got chance to watch movie again,after ENGlish, ms tan tell mi to help weidi to take his journal.... then lata after my australian math, i go to npcc room and slack!!!then i and my gand go to canteen and wanna to eat la then see my chinese teacher and she was eating and we ask her to treat us,then she give us money=$3but she look veri sad la haha then later my gand go help to put ndp thing la then i help them to take care of the npcc room and their bag.... a few hours lata, ms tan came in to npcc roomandask whether i got saw weidi journal.....i say ya and give it to her and she say why izzit with mi then i say she ask mi to take wan but she say don have,don have don have lorz she big mahz,WAT to do then she ask wat happen to mi,i say nothing,then she say whether i ok anot?? then i say of cos la....she say i don look good...    smtime feeling is hard to express out wan lorz and is harder to say it out   !!!  and 1thing, i hate ppl dun belive mi when is tell the truth from this point,i not writing journal le,if u wan to see cum here la!!! 
      
</post>
<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      wow,today my SS teacher didnt came ,dunno why la.... then free 1hr again..... from monday till now got 8hr gone cos teacher didnt came,how should i return to my hours wasted!! althought everytime,i don like teacher to came la but donno Y now mi like teacher to came or my day is like wasted.now i put time in the 1st le...finally!!! today veri sian lorz....afther skool still got npcc hai~ from 2.30pm-5.30pm(but stay back till around6.25pm) today mi take sec1 for drill, i veri happy bout it,but i like takie them, also like doing nothing cos i pick their mistake onli....haha usless rite......but at least my group i got give them break lorz....seee i so good haha then stay back till so late bacause sir say our drill not good,so stay back lorz,after that, mi,sam, kenneth leong and guo wei go eat lorz....we tok bout npcc ppl....their bad point and good point(see sum 1 must see their heart and not by how they look onli)!!!! 
      
</post>
<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      aiya today not much thing to say ......good thing is today 1hr free...i sleep during to recover my sleepness....but after that, but i still veri tired!!!!!but bad wan is miss MdM tan la,she 2days never cum and 4days dont see her liao...so sad,today mi dunno why go so earily?then mi sit at the place....and dunno Y i will go and sit there la...cos at there can see sum1  OH.....my chem dropping liao from close 1 eye can pass,now open 2eye and fail and KNA TSM shoot mi,saying my chem droping le.....ARH!!!  aiya today so good no HW....my classmate say got phy test tml,but i don even study!!!vos my phy teaacher really didnt teach us anything lorz,everytime tell us read the text book ourself..... oh shit tml go npcc haven pack my things,gtg to pack my thing liao ,, 
      
</post>
<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      just copy the link any paste it at the address there and can listen   Jay Chou - Qi Li Xiang (Original Version) :  http://www.angelfire.com/ill/dreamstar/JayChou-QiLiXiang.mp3   Jay Chou - Wo De Di Pan (CD Version) :  http://www.angelfire.com/ill/dreamstar/JayChou-WoDeDiPan.mp3   Jay Chou - Wo De Di Pan 2 Minute Preview (Music Video) :  http://www.angelfire.com/ill/dreamstar/JayChou-WoDeDiPan.wmv   Unknown Demo from the album Qi Li Xiang :  http://www.angelfire.com/ill/dreamstar/UnknownDemo.mp3    
      
</post>
<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       today boring day for mi sia, althought today mr wee didnt came and came another mr wee . write write lot of fun thing lorz  ....laught till my stomach pain!!!but the my dear english teacher didnt came...miss her so much,then mdm TAY s.m take over for chem!!!!!  then today i have 2hr chem lorz but the last 2 lesson, i was reading book(1st time)and sleeping,some more, i put my hp on the table and i sleep, she don even know lorz........  wow today got math lesson thought don have cos ms loy last week say no lesson for us this week ...lucky got la or my math will be dropping down again!!!!    One thing to say,   realli cant stand    TAn wei hong,go back to malaysia la   ENG!!!!!!!!!  
      
</post>
<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       long long ago, there live an ugly, stupid,smelly,dirty,irritating wood cutter named wee Y.J(it is written on the name tag so i know)  he have 3cows name"sodium,helmet and ENG".  sodium produce salt,helmet produce protective gear and eng speak english.cow like to drink ink ....T Cos's milk turn to ink...Ink become sodium.  he wood cutter got ink,he found ink out that he doesn't have paper.So he cut the trees to make paper . while he is cutting paper,a live Enormous "SOTONG"jump out of the bushes and thread then the wood cutter   stop make ink out of the rubber trees.  but suddenly remember his girlfriend MEI "yING"  but suddenly that HONG appear in nowhere.  they involed in a relationships  
      
</post>
<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       long long ago,woodcuter was a poor man,   his wife is a greedy pig.by the way  , his name is wee y.j.(written on the name tag so i know).  then one day a postman came to his house and give him a cow.  . he called it chair because it's spot look like chair .  then.......and the cow friend spots have many ink .  so he decided to call him many children'ink'.....  but he then found a cute boy name sodium .   later ,the cow give birth to a dragon. but the dregon have a cow legs that cant do anything.  The dragon can only sing"bob the builder!can we fix it!bob the builder yes we can!"  when he was a cute baby.            all behind is #%#@%$@#%#@  
      
</post>
<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       LONG LONG AGO, TWH BECAME THE PRINCE OF EQGPT . OOh lyke ral only .. and he was dying to meet a gal and have babies with him and married her ,  but he was very stupid.  i think he better jumo down from 15storet flat and hopefully he go to hell.  he may die because of shock.  but he became an angel.  HE became a stupid smelly angel and the other angels call him "ink".  but later god give him a special cow that produce only ink.  in the next few days he did funny thing with the cow.  he use the ink and draw it on the cow.   the cow like ink and he ate voth the "ink"and the ink.....  the ink is his body turn into blue to red colour ink  .""stop saying ink"say muhaimin.  Don't get so angry .   and the cow die   
      
</post>
<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      long long ago,there was a poor woodcutter. He is sitting on a chair.H  e think that this chair give him good luck.  Butthe chair has a curse on it.  The name of the chair is called the evil choon chair.  But one day,the chair give wishes to him and he want a cow.  He used that cow to make a chair   and the cow cried"moo moo moo"  Then he decided to paint the chair with ink......  But in the end,the chair turnrd into sodium powder.  Sodium then moae into a helmet.  But that helmet is too smaill to fit in.  So he hrow the helmet.  The helmet suddenly say "moo!moo!moo!"  and he die  
      
</post>
<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      sian veri sunday...to mi is a unless day but can relax la...cos no skool work!! today mi woke up at bout1310,then brush teeth,eat till 2like tat,my break1st for sunday is always after noon wan cos every sat donno do wat tat will make mi so tired!!!even i sleep veri earily on tat nite!!!maybe sunday is family day ba...cos seen like no1 wan to go....or every1 is tired!!!tml more die,my dear weidi go OBS,sure make mi feel alone wan,so sad!!!5day cant see him mi sure will miss him1....sian now no1 pei mi home,hai~ alone again,the last time i alone go home is when he like SUM1 la then he everytime wan to see her till late late or sent her home!!!i alone sia,but i cant spoil his life wat(mi think till too far liao)o i next time dun main being alone le........... 
      
</post>
<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      oh this guy is my brother,look alike ???no!haha urlLink     urlLink   
      
</post>
<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      this photo is mi and weidi take wan&gt;&gt;&gt;&gt; urlLink     urlLink   
      
</post>
<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      oh tis is my primary skool slass photo when i am in P5 urlLink     urlLink   
      
</post>
<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      oh gay!!! sleeping together urlLink     urlLink   
      
</post>
<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      SeE.....mi extre urlLink     urlLink   
      
</post>
<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      pic of mi and gwen in skool! urlLink     urlLink   
      
</post>
<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       today realli is a suk day for mi,during npcc,those sec2 realli make mi mad sia ..... ask them things ,they donno how to ans....then help sec2 gal to open the door,they scold mi,WTF ....  then last week ,GOT ppl say wan to go out on today wan ,then ppl ask mi out,i of cos say don wan la cos promise ppl liao wat .... then lata today,they say dun wan to go out liao....leave mi alone sia,reason"veri tired la"feel like sleeping,wat kind of frine d izzit !!!! then PS mi ,make mi alone doing nothing!!!!! 
      
</post>
<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      People thinks that I m silly, To hold on something not so worthy. They even think it’s a pity, That I wouldn't face the reality.  It’s the feeling that I’m seeking, If I deny my true feelings, Then its me myself tat i'm cheating. Hence…  I keep on waiting…  Its true she once hurt me deep, But she too gave me the love I need.. So I won’t admit my defeat, Stand up,n dance with the music to the beat.  Yet autumn after autumns, spring after springs, Time passes, just in a wink… He was mine, only in dreams, The dreams were sweet, like cookies n cream!!  One day she called, “its just another chat” I thought, He said, “I feel for you”, THAT gave me a shock!!~ Was it April fool’s day? I realized its not, I felt as if I’d conquered the mountain top!  sHe asked if I was willing to wait. Leaving the relationship to the fate. He hopes by then its not too late, To make up for her past mistakes….  Dear fate, play me out not, I really love her lots n lots... give us the chance to b together again, its the only cure to my greatest pain.. 
      
</post>
<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      i've already done my best, but my hopes begin getting less, my heart stil can't get to its little nest, so tired,i tink,it badly needs a rest...  why is my love still in a mess? i always tot, God's giving me a test. but the tests seems never end, breaking the heart more, yet to mend..  my life's meant to b like tis, i guess.. though breathing yet lifeless, so depress!! all i wish,is he'll confess, whether he loves n misses me...... as much as i'd always stressed...  hmm..are the lovely messages sent what he really meant??? why then,since the day away Love went its till not back to get my heart tended??? 
      
</post>
<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      wads so great abt her? some1 kindly hint? she got me head over heels, i loved her so i strongly feel. she glanced over n caught my eye, my face felt burnt...was that shy? i felt so lost in her eyes... like there's no way out,i don't know why. she read my heart from my eyes, n sensed i'm melting away just like ice... she smiled, but it seemed so sly, was it something he wanna imply?? but the smile took me for a fly to the clouds of hapiness in the sky. lurking behind could all be lies, i couldn't see, coz love is blind. 
      
</post>
<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Night has fallen, I sensed Darkness, Along came Silence, Acompanied by Lonesome.  Darkness, is there any end? Lonesome, is it a friend? Shh...Silence, ryhmns like a song... Why does the night seem so long?  My lost soul wandered in Darkness, Humming the song of Silence, Every corner i saw Lonesome there, Why does it follows me everywhere?  Thank God, he sent Daybreak, fought away Darkness for my sake, Silence song? it did not stay, So Lonesome, too, went another way. 
      
</post>
<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Fresh air in the morning,   For kiri darl on the way go working,    The dews on the leaves are sparkling,    Just like how your eyes keep glowing.   Thanks for all your words of caring,    It makes me feel the warmth in sharing.    Finally, my crystal has got back its shining,    Only some blue within that needs some healing.   If only I had done more readings,    Then I could do better on all the rhyming.   But this is just the beginning,    I’ll practice on it and get it going!~!~  
      
</post>
<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      In the middle of the night I heard myself shout, It was my heart coz my mouth was shut.  My heart bled when u told me “I’m sorry,”  That we were incompatible just that I wasn’t wary  I had to agree to end this feeling, But my heart protested by all its bleeding. I need your love to keep me breathing, Without your love I dun feel like a living…  I want to know why, u wanted to leave so abruptly, Decided to follow up behind ur steps secretly.. There…I saw you giving your heart away, And crushed my heart along the way.  As time passes, the heart is healed.. But scars remain hard to conceal. Kisses n hugs can only be reviewed, By the memories that’s left so few. 
      
</post>
<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      knowing she'll never be yours again, though love's there but so is pain. ppl says that time will heal, but time can't control how u feel. yes,this song used to b a love theme, but listening to it alone isn't happy as it seems. bear in mind, the harder u try forgeting, will mean the more u will be missing... so let the 'love' n 'miss' go on, someday it'll unconciously be gone, probably it's gona take quite long, but 1 day.... the love theme would just be a normal song. 
      
</post>
<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Though a failure in love I am, But gd friends reached out their hand, Telling me, “ I noe u can.” “Take my hand n UP u stand.” A handful of them I adore most, To my heart they live so close… Adoring they are just like roses.. Can’t do without, like medical doses. But as we grow, we all change, So one rose fell out of the range. As it fell, the thorns pierced into my heart,  The cut was deep n really hard. Then I realized how far we were, apart. She told me,  “like this, is what I am! I don't wana give a d*amn !!!”  and these words drowned me like quicksand... Coz only seeing her own stand, How I feel, she won’t wana understand.  Love n friends, these two gems,  To go on, I feel weak without them. Hope that fallen rose, one day, will fall back in place,  n Let me,  once again, see its glamorous grace. 
      
</post>
<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      mi ytd wanna write blog wan but,my com la,cant connect internet la...wow...then mi sleep from 7pm to today 6am....so long sia...i cant belive...then ytd wanna write wat,mi 4get liao.....haha mi today got phy test....sian lorz...mi last min studies again ...hope pass la....oh ytd got common test....mi also never learn chap5,7,8,9 then onli got 5que.......veri wat lorz......hai ...today in the morning thought mdm tay never came...so happy....but lata she came...hai~~~~~~~ today my father didnt came(mr Li)then we had meeting in class....so funny....meeting bout class outing.... but is sum1go mi don wan to go la......but cant tell whu is he/she  la mi muz do english liao tml date line....and ya tml got geo test....this few week back, i slep in geo...it is so boring!!!!!ok the teacher is ok...labut is juz ok...not veri ok...hahah...mi gtg going to do english.....and friday got D test.....hai~~~~so many test  
      
</post>
<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      wow,today kana aim by so many teacher becos of sum stupid ppl!!! i think those ppl in my klass should know la....today mi get so many hw(math and english)..wow,today can say veri bad luck ....hai,last time ..tat i came back from camp rite....relli sumthing lost from mi but not totaly la.....mi left with 20% onli la....but soon all will be done so sian muz do math liao hai~ 
      
</post>
<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      national camp rock mi urlLink     urlLink   
      
</post>
<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      national camp rock mi urlLink     urlLink   
      
</post>
<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      national camp rock mi urlLink     urlLink   
      
</post>
<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      so many day never write blog liao so tired.....mi come back from  camp liao go back skool...see friend(see i so good) camp was so fun...hope more day la,but too bad...miss all skool friend and BRAVO la...met alot of news friend...from alot of cca...i thounght tat my cca is the best onli,till now then i know that every cca is the same...every cca have it strengh and weakness.. this camp,my group is call BRAVO....going back skool bout sumthing,shen chan say my class will be in trouble...they say bcos of weihong,i do nothing scare wat scare!!!aiya tired le...tml then write again 
      
</post>
<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      mi now happy and sad....today is singapore birthday!!wee wee!!!  happy birthday Singapore   mi tml go camp liao.....sian mi must 5+ woke up cos 7must reach 1 place veri far(mi donno how to spell)   then mi and nicole wanna take cab there lorz...hai~waste $$$ but no choice la   mi pack my thing 7788 liao (haha)   mi so miss my fun...i sure miss alot of fun and laughter in my class and in npcc room...and math class......must wait till friday(maybe going back to skool after camp,must see nicole wan anot la)...   hope not much hw ....gtg now mi going to my ah ma house.....   bb....see u all on this friday or next monday lorz...take care...i will miss u all de for sure  
      
</post>
<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      hai~ mi got a feeling tat when i go camp,i will lost sumthing tat can say important to mi......wan to know??? fat hope!!haha pass 2 day never write blog cos my com keep hang...then evern go play game also veri hard....yesterday wow......mi veri early go out and reach home veri late,cos after skool follow jiamin thet alll go out then after that bout 7+ liao,i went o my ah ma house at cck,then sum1 sms mi to meet him(it is a guy ok and hr not gay)he pass mi mass tin and"sumthing"(the sumthing not for mi wan)...dun say out batter...then mi walk to my ah ma house.... then lata my papa was at my ah ma house,then we go hm together... today mi woke up veri early donno Y ?i wake up at around 11 then mi eat and watch cartoon after around1130,i felt tired...i went bed and slep till4pm,then i woke up and play com.then.............. 
      
</post>
<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      止戰之殤 (zhi zhan zhi shang)  光 guang 輕如紙張 qing ru zhi zhang 光 guang 散落地方 san luo di fang 光 guang 在掌聲漸息中它慌忙 zai zhang sheng jian xi zhong ta huang mang 她在傳唱 ta zai chuan chang 不堪的傷 bu kan de shang 腳本在台上 jiao ben zai tai shang 演出最後一場 yan chu zui hou yi chang 而全村人們在座位上 er quan cun ren men zai zuo wei shang 靜靜的看 jing jing de kan 時間如何遺棄這劇場 shi jian ru he yi qi zhe ju chang 戰火弄髒 zhan huo nong zang 她的淚光 ta de lei guang 誰在風中 shui zai feng zhong 吵著吃糖 chao zhe chi tang 這故事一開始的鏡頭灰塵就已經遮蔽了陽光 zhe gu shi yi kai shi de jing tou hui chen jiu yi jing zhe bi liao yang guang ㄎ一ㄤˋ biang 恐懼刻在孩子們臉上 kong ju ke zai hai zi men lian shang 麥田已倒向戰車經過的方向 mai tian yi dao xiang zhan che jing guo de fang xiang 蒲公英的形狀 pu gong ying de xing zhuang 在飄散 zai piao san 它絕望 ta jue wang 的飛翔 de fei xiang 她只唱 ta zhi chang 只想 zhi xiang 這首止戰 zhe shou zhi zhan 之殤 zhi shang 惡夜燃燭光 e ye ran zhu guang 天破息戰亂 tian po xi zhan luan 殤歌傳千里 shang ge chuan qian li 家鄉平饑荒 jia xiang ping ji huang 天真在這條路上 tian zhen zai zhe tiao lu shang 跌跌撞撞 die die zhuang zhuang 她被芒草割傷 ta bei mang cao ge shang  孩子們眼中的希望 hai zi men yan zhong de xi wang 是什麼形狀 shi shen me xing zhuang 是否醒來有麵包當早餐 shi fou xing lai you mian bao dang zao can 再喝碗濃湯 zai he wan nong tang 農夫被燒毀土地跟村莊 nong fu bei shao hui tu di gen cun zhuang 終於拿起槍 zhong yu na qi qiang 她卻慢慢習慣放棄了抵抗 ta que man man xi guan fang qi liao di kang 孩子們眼中的希望 hai zi men yan zhong de xi wang 是什麼形狀 shi shen me xing zhuang 是否院子有鞦韆可以盪 shi fou yuan zi you qiu qian ke yi dang 口袋裡有糖 kou dai li you tang 刺刀的光被仇恨所擦亮 ci dao de guang bei chou hen suo ca liang 在遠方野蠻 zai yuan fang ye man 而她卻笑著不知道慌張 er ta que xiao zhe bu zhi dao huang zhang 
      
</post>
<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      園遊會 (yuan you hui)  琥珀色黃昏像糖在很美的遠方 hu po se huang hun xiang tang zai hen mei de yuan fang 妳的臉沒有化妝我卻瘋狂愛上 ni de lian mei you hua zhuang wo que feng kuang ai shang 思念跟影子在傍晚一起被拉長 si nian gen ying zi zai bang wan yi qi bei la chang 我手中那入場券陪我數羊 wo shou zhong na ru chang quan pei wo shu yang 薄荷色草地芬芳像風沒有形狀 bo he se cao di fen fang xiang feng mei you xing zhuang 我卻能夠牢記妳的氣質跟臉龐 wo que neng gou lao ji ni de qi zhi gen lian pang 冷空氣跟琉璃在清晨很有透明感 leng kong qi gen liu li zai qing chen hen you tou ming gan 像我的喜歡 xiang wo de xi huan 被妳看穿 bei ni kan chuan 攤位上一朵豔陽 tan wei shang yi duo yan yang 我悄悄出現妳身旁 wo qiao qiao chu xian ni shen bang 妳慌亂的模樣 ni huang luan de mo yang 我微笑安靜欣賞 wo wei xiao an jing xin shang  我頂著大太陽 wo ding zhe da tai yang 只想為妳撐傘 zhi xiang wei ni cheng san 妳靠在我肩膀 ni kao zai wo jian bang 深呼吸怕遺忘 shen hu xi pa yi wang 因為撈魚的蠢遊戲我們開始交談 yin wei lao yu de chun you xi wo men kai shi jiao tan 多希望話題不斷園遊會永不打烊 duo xi wang hua ti bu duan yuan you hui yong bu da yang 汽球在我手上 qi qiu zai wo shou shang 我牽著妳瞎晃 wo qian zhe ni xia huang 有話想對妳講 you hua xiang dui ni jiang 妳眼睛卻裝忙 ni yan jing que zhuang mang 雞蛋糕跟妳嘴角果醬我都想要嘗 ji dan gao gen ni zui jiao guo jiang wo dou xiang yao chang 園遊會影片在播放 yuan you hui ying pian zai bo fang 這個世界約好一起逛 zhe ge shi jie yue hao yi qi guang 
      
</post>
<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      困獸之鬥 (kun shou zhi dou)  我在陰暗中降落 wo zai yin an zhong jiang luo 世界在雨中淹沒 shi jie zai yu zhong yan mo 畫面與現實交錯 hua mian yu xian shi jiao cuo 無法抽離卡在胸口 wu fa chou li ka zai xiong kou 軀殼如行屍走肉 qu ke ru xing shi zou rou 陷阱漩渦我已受夠 xian jing xuan wo wo yi shou gou 掙脫逃離這個空洞 zheng tuo tao li zhe ge kong dong 如果 ru guo 我衝出黑幕籠罩的天空 wo chong chu he mu long zhao de tian kong 就別(想)再綑綁我的自由 jiu bie (xiang) zai kun bang wo de zi you  在狂風之中 zai kuang feng zhi zhong 嘶吼 si hou 作困獸之鬥 zuo kun shou zhi dou 我奮力衝破 wo fen li chong po 封閉的思緒震開裂縫 feng bi de si xu zhen kai lie feng 燃燒的花朵 ran shao de hua duo 升空sheng kong 消失在空中 xiao shi zai kong zhong 記憶在剝落 ji yi zai bo luo 殘留的影像輪廓 can liu de ying xiang lun kuo 潰散在薄霧中 kui san zai bo wu zhong 
      
</post>
<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      亂舞春秋 (luan wu chun qiu)  那混亂的年代 na hun luan de nian dai 朝庭太腐敗 chao ting tai fu bai 人禍惹天災 ren huo re tian zai 東漢王朝在一夕之間崩壞興衰 dong han wang chao zai yi xi zhi jian beng huai xing shuai 九州地圖被人們切割成三塊分開 jiu zhou di tu bei ren men qie ge cheng san kuai fen kai 讀三國歷史的興衰 du san guo li shi de xing shuai 想去瞧個明白 xiang qu qiao ge ming bai 看看看就馬上回來 kan kan kan jiu ma shang hui lai ㄎ一ㄥ kieng ㄎ一ㄥ kieng ㄎ一ㄤ kiang ㄎ一ㄤ kiang 刀劍棍棒 dao jian gun bang 我隨口講 wo sui kou jiang 原來真有時光機這麼誇張 yuan lai zhen you shi guang ji zhe me kua zhang 穿梭時空過癮又囂張 chuan suo shi kong guo yin you xiao zhang 萬一有去無回怎麼辦老實說有點緊張 wan yi you qu wu hui zen me ban lao shi shuo you dian jin zhang 啊 a 啊 a 江山 jiang shan 我站在雲端 wo zhan zai yun duan 慢慢 man man 往中原方向 wang zhong yuan fang xiang 前方 qian fang 散落著村莊 san luo zhe cun zhuang 長安 chang an 在兵荒馬亂 zai bing huang ma luan 望著天 wang zhe tian 眼看北斗七星墜入地平線 yan kan bei dou qi xing zhui ru di ping xian 瞬間 shun jian 英雄豪傑猶如鬼魅般地出現 ying xiong hao jie you ru gui mei ban di chu xian 我呸 wo pei 誰也不服誰我是龜你是鱉 shui ye bu fu shui wo shi gui ni shi bie 啦啦啦啦啦 la la la la la 啦啦啦 la la la 妖獸擾亂人間秩序 yao shou rao luan ren jian zhi xu 血腥如浪潮般來襲 xie xing ru lang chao ban lai xi 我小命差點沒續集 wo xiao ming cha dian mei xu ji 還好有時光機我謝謝你 hai hao you shi guang ji wo xie xie ni 人魔開始重出地獄 ren mo kai shi zhong chu di yu 叛軍如野火般攻擊 
      
</post>
<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      擱淺 (ge qian)  久未放晴的天空 jiu wei fang qing de tian kong 依舊留著妳的笑容 yi jiu liu zhe ni de xiao rong 哭過 ku guo 卻無法掩埋歉疚 que wu fa yan mai qian jiu 風箏在陰天擱淺 feng zheng zai yin tian ge qian 想念還在等待救援 xiang nian hai zai deng dai jiu yuan 我拉著線 wo la zhe xian 複習妳給的溫柔 fu xi ni gei de wen rou 曝曬在一旁的寂寞 pu shai zai yi pang de ji mo 笑我給不起承諾 xiao wo gei bu qi cheng nuo 怎麼會怎麼會 zen me hui zen me hui 妳竟原諒了我 ni jing yuan liang liao wo  我只能永遠讀著對白 wo zhi neng yong yuan du zhe dui bai 讀著我給妳的傷害 du zhe wo gei ni de shang hai 我原諒不了我 wo yuan liang bu liao wo 就請妳當作我已不在 jiu qing ni dang zuo wo yi bu zai 我睜開雙眼 wo zheng kai shuang yan 看著空白 kan zhe kong bai 忘記妳對我的期待 wang ji ni dui wo de qi dai 讀完了依賴 du wan liao yi lai 我很快就離開 wo hen kuai jiu li kai 
      
</post>
<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      05.將軍  時間的箭頭 shi jian de jian tou 都指向你鎩羽而歸的地方 dou zhi xiang ni sha yu er gui de di fang 你會前進 ni hui qian jin 但終究還是得要習慣投降 dan zhong jiu hai shi de yao xi guan tou xiang 想當然耳 xiang dang ran er 第六步是你最大的致命傷 di liu bu shi ni zui da de zhi ming shang 我按兵不動 wo an bing bu dong 出於習慣凡事沈默的醞釀 chu yu xi guan fan shi chen mo de yun niang 當頭炮 dang tou pao 純粹出於我禮貌的開場 chun cui chu yu wo li mao de kai chang 屏風馬 bing fen ma 神華內斂才能以柔克剛 shen hua nei lian cai neng yi rou ke gang 第二十六著炮五進四 di er shi liu zhuo pao wu jin si 只是在試探性衡量 zhi shi zai shi tan xing heng liang 三十三著車二平七 san shi san zhuo che er ping qi 的出手你恐怕就暗箭難防 de chu shou ni kong pa jiu an jian nan fang 這一場不流血的仗只有自尊會受傷 zhe yi chang bu liu xue de zhang zhi you zi zun hui shou shang 成王敗寇的鐵則跟現實沒啥兩樣 cheng wang bai kou de tie ze gen xian shi mei sha liang yang 提著烏籠的老頭站在一旁拍我肩膀 ti zhe wu long de lao tou zhan zai yi pang pai wo jian bang 我猜他想的應該和我一樣 wo cai ta xiang de ying gai he wo yi yang  看我 kan wo 我手指放鬆 wo shou zhi fang song 我目光如龍 wo mu guang ru long 當敵人是空 dang di ren shi kong 我戰法無窮 wo zhan fa wu qiong 我攻勢如風 wo gong shi ru feng 用單車入宮 yong dan che ru gong 輾過你懊喪的臉孔 nian guo ni ao sang de lian kong 管我 guan wo 我手指放鬆 wo shou zhi fang song 我目光如龍 wo mu guang ru long 當敵人是空 dang di ren shi kong 我左右開弓 wo zuo you kai gong 我氣勢如虹 wo qi shi ru hong 將炮馬盡用 jiang pao ma jin yong 兵臨城下想逃都沒用 bing lin cheng xia xiang tao dou mei yong  我對著潮汐推敲什麼是 wo dui zhe chao xi tui qiao shen me shi 以靜制動 yi jing zhi dong 山林間迷霧能不能當障眼法的內容 shan lin jian mi wu neng bu neng dang zhang yan fa de nei rong 月轉星移的軌跡跟臨軍布陣相同 yue zhuan xing yi de gui ji gen lin jun bu zhen xiang tong 風林火山是不是用兵之重 feng lin huo shan shi bu shi yong bing zhi zhong 到最後 dao zui hou 必然是我運籌帷幄你最後放棄抵抗 bi ran shi wo yun chou wei wo ni zui hou fang qi di kang 我仰望著夕陽你低頭黯然離場 wo yang wang zhe xi yang ni di tou an ran li chang 聽我說勝敗是兵家之常 ting wo shuo sheng bai shi bing jia zhi chang 你不用放在心上 ni bu yong fang zai xin shang 是因為我只適合無雙 shi yin wei wo zhi shi he wu shuang  看我 kan wo 我手指放鬆 wo shou zhi fang song 我目光如龍 wo mu guang ru long 當敵人是空 dang di ren shi kong 我戰法無窮 wo zhan fa wu qiong 我攻勢如風 wo gong shi ru feng 用單車入宮 yong dan che ru gong 輾過你懊喪的臉孔 nian guo ni ao sang de lian kong 管我 guan wo 我手指放鬆 wo shou zhi fang song 我目光如龍 wo mu guang ru long 當敵人是空 dang di ren shi kong 我左右開弓 wo zuo you kai gong 我氣勢如虹 wo qi shi ru hong 將炮馬盡用 jiang pao ma jin yong 兵臨城下 bing lin cheng xia 想逃都沒用 xiang tao dou mei yong (陽光從樹葉細縫 (yang guang cong shu ye xi feng 露出了笑容 lu chu liao xiao rong 溫暖了我的美夢 wen nuan liao wo de mei meng 只有籠裡的畫眉羨慕著天空 zhi you long li de hua mei xian mu zhe tian kong 卻從來沒有人懂) que cong lai mei you ren dong) 
      
</post>
<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      to hear this sound,click on the title on top  外婆 (wai po)  天是外婆生日 jin tian shi wai po sheng ri 我換上復古西裝 wo huan shang fu gu xi zhuang 載著外婆開著拉風的古董車兜兜兜風 zai zhe wai po kai zhe la feng de gu dong che dou dou dou feng 車裡放著她的最愛 che li fang zhe ta de zui ai 找回屬於是她的時代 zhao hui shu yu shi ta de shi dai 往大稻埋碼頭開去把所有和外公的往事靜靜回憶 wang da dao mai ma tou kai qu ba suo you he wai gong de wang shi jing jing hui yi 外婆她臉上的漣漪wai po ta lian shang de lian yi 美麗但藏不住壓抑 mei li dan cang bu zhu ya yi 失去了愛情只盼望親情 shi qu liao ai qing zhi pan wang qin qing 彌補回應 mi bu hui ying 大人們以為出門之前桌上放六佰就算是孝敬 da ren men yi wei chu men zhi qian zhuo shang fang liu bai jiu suan shi xiao jing 一天到晚拼了命 yi tian dao wan pin liao ming 賺錢少了關懷有什麼意義 zhuan qian shao liao guan huai you shen me yi yi  外婆她的期待 wai po ta de qi dai 慢慢變成無奈 man man bian cheng wu nai 大人們始終不明白 da ren men shi zhong bu ming bai 她要的是陪伴 ta yao de shi pei ban 而不是六佰塊 er bu shi liu bai kuai 比你給的還簡單 bi ni gei de hai jian dan 外婆的無奈 wai po de wu nai 無法變成期待 wu fa bian cheng qi dai 只有愛才能夠明白 zhi you ai cai neng gou ming bai 走在淡水河畔 zou zai dan shui he pan 聽著她的最愛 ting zhe ta de zui ai 把溫暖放回口袋 ba wen nuan fang hui kou dai  記得去年外婆的生日 ji de qu nian wai po de sheng ri 表哥帶我和外婆參加 biao ge dai wo he wai po can jia 她最最重視的頒獎典禮 ta zui zui zhong shi de ban jiang dian li 結果卻拿不到半個獎 jie guo que na bu dao ban ge jiang 不知該笑不笑 bu zhi gai xiao bu xiao 我對著鏡頭傻笑 wo dui zhe jing tou sha xiao 只覺得自己可笑 zhi jue de zi ji ke xiao 我難過 wo nan guo 卻不是因為沒有得獎而難過 que bu shi yin wei mei you de jiang er nan guo 我失落 wo shi luo 是因為看到外婆失落而失落 shi yin wei kan dao wai po shi luo er shi luo 大人們根本不能體會表哥他的用心 da ren men gen ben bu neng ti hui biao ge ta de yong xin 好像隨他們高興就可以徹底的否定 hao xiang sui ta men gao xing jiu ke yi che di de fou ding 否定 fou ding 我的作品 wo de zuo pin 決定在於心情 jue ding zai yu xin qing 想堅持風格他們卻覺得還歐顆 xiang jian chi feng ge ta men que jue de hai ou ke 沒驚喜沒有改變 mei jing xi mei you gai bian 我已經聽了三年 wo yi jing ting liao san nian 我告訴外婆 wo gao su wai po 我沒輸 wo mei shu 不需要改變 bu xu yao gai bian 表哥說不要覺得可惜 biao ge shuo bu yao jue de ke xi 這只是一場遊戲 zhe zhi shi yi chang you xi 只要外婆覺得好聽 zhi yao wai po jue de hao ting 那才是一種鼓勵 na cai shi yi zhong gu li 外婆露出了笑容說她以我為榮 wai po lu chu liao xiao rong shuo ta yi wo wei rong 淺淺的笑容 jian jian de xiao rong 就讓我感到比得獎它還要光榮 jiu rang wo gan dao bi de jiang ta hai yao guang rong 
      
</post>
<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      翻著我們的照片 fan zhe wo men de zhao pian 想念若隱若現 xiang nian ruo yin ruo xian 去年的冬天 qu nian de dong tian 我們笑得很甜 wo men xiao de hen tian 看著妳哭泣的臉 kan zhe ni ku qi de lian 對著我說再見 dui zhe wo shuo zai jian 來不及聽見 lai bu ji ting jian 妳已走得很遠 ni yi zou de hen yuan 也許妳已經放棄我 ye xu ni yi jing fang qi wo 也許已經很難回頭 ye xu yi jing hen nan hui tou 我知道是自己錯過 wo zhi dao shi zi ji cuo guo 請再給我一個理由 說妳不愛我 qing zai gei wo yi ge li you shuo ni bu ai wo 就算是我不懂 jiu suan shi wo bu dong 能不能原諒我 neng bu neng yuan liang wo 請不要把分手當作妳的請求 qing bu yao ba fen shou dang zuo ni de qing qiu 我知道堅持要走是妳受傷的藉口 wo zhi dao jian chi yao zou shi ni shou shang de jie kou 請妳回頭 qing ni hui tou 我會陪妳一直走到最後 wo hui pei ni yi zhi zou dao zui hou 就算沒有結果 jiu suan mei you jie guo 我也能夠承受 wo ye neng gou cheng shou 我知道妳的痛 wo zhi dao ni de tong 是我給的承諾 shi wo gei de cheng nuo 妳說給過我縱容 ni shuo gei guo wo zong rong 沉默是因為包容 chen mo shi yin wei bao rong 如果要走 ru guo yao zou 請妳記得我 qing ni ji de wo 如果難過 ru guo nan guo 請妳忘了我 qing ni wang liao wo 
      
</post>
<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      click on the title to hear the song  七里香 (qi li xiang)  窗外的麻雀 chuang wai de ma que 在電線桿上多嘴 zai dian xian gan shang duo zui 妳說這一句 ni shuo zhe yi ju 很有夏天的感覺 hen you xia tian de gan jue 手中的鉛筆 shou zhong de qian bi 在紙上來來回回 zai zhi shang lai lai hui hui 我用幾行字形容妳是我的誰 wo yong ji hang zi xing rong ni shi wo de shui  秋刀魚 qiu dao yu 的滋味 de zi wei 貓跟妳都想了解 mao gen ni dou xiang liao jie 初戀的香味就這樣被我們尋回 chu lian de xiang wei jiu zhe yang bei wo men xun hui 那溫暖 na wen nuan 的陽光 de yang guang 像剛摘的鮮豔草莓 xiang gang zhai de xian yan cao mei 你說妳捨不得吃掉這一種感覺 ni shuo ni she bu de chi diao zhe yi zhong gan jue  雨下整夜 yu xia zheng ye 我的愛溢出就像雨水 wo de ai yi chu jiu xiang yu shui 院子落葉 yuan zi luo ye 跟我的思念厚厚一疊 gen wo de si nian hou hou yi die 幾句是非 ji ju shi fei 也無法將我的熱情冷卻 ye wu fa jiang wo de re qing leng que 妳出現在我詩的每一頁 ni chu xian zai wo shi de mei yi ye  雨下整夜 yu xia zheng ye 我的愛溢出就像雨水 wo de ai yi chu jiu xiang yu shui 窗台蝴蝶 chuang tai hu die 像詩裡紛飛的美麗章節 xiang shi li fen fei de mei li zhang jie 我接著寫 wo jie zhe xie 把永遠愛妳寫進詩的結尾 ba yong yuan ai ni xie jin shi de jie wei 妳是我唯一想要的了解 ni shi wo wei yi xiang yao de liao jie  那飽滿 na bao man 的稻穗 de dao sui 幸福了這個季節 xing fu liao zhe ge ji jie 而妳的臉頰像田裡熟透的蕃茄 er ni de lian jia xiang tian li shu tou de fan qie 妳突然 ni tu ran 對我說 dui wo shuo 七里香的名字很美 qi li xiang de ming zi hen mei 我此刻卻只想親吻妳倔強的嘴 wo ci ke que zhi xiang qin wen ni jue qiang de zui 雨下整夜 yu xia zheng ye 我的愛溢出就像雨水 wo de ai yi chu jiu xiang yu shui 院子落葉 yuan zi luo ye 跟我的思念厚厚一疊 gen wo de si nian hou hou yi die 幾句是非 ji ju shi fei 也無法將我的熱情冷卻 ye wu fa jiang wo de re qing leng que 妳出現在我詩的每一頁 ni chu xian zai wo shi de mei yi ye  雨下整夜 yu xia zheng ye 我的愛溢出就像雨水 wo de ai yi chu jiu xiang yu shui 窗台蝴蝶 chuang tai hu die 像詩裡紛飛的美麗章節 xiang shi li fen fei de mei li zhang jie 我接著寫 wo jie zhe xie 把永遠愛妳寫進詩的結尾 ba yong yuan ai ni xie jin shi de jie wei 妳是我唯一想要的了解 ni shi wo wei yi xiang yao de liao jie 
      
</post>
<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      click on the title to hear the song  我的地盤 (wo de di pan)   在我地盤這   zai wo di pan zhe   你就得聽我的  ni jiu de ting wo de 把音樂收割 ba yin le shou ge 用聽覺找快樂 yong ting jue zhao kuai le 開始在雕刻 kai shi zai diao ke 我個人的特色 wo ge ren de te se 未來難預測 wei lai nan yu ce 堅持當下的選擇 jian chi dang xia de xuan ze 在我地盤這 zai wo di pan zhe 你就得聽我的 ni jiu de ting wo de 節奏在招惹 jie zou zai zhao re 我跟街舞親熱 wo gen jie wu qin re 我灌溉原則 wo guan gai yuan ze 培養一種獨特 pei yang yi zhong du te 觀念不及格 guan nian bu ji ge 其他全部是垃圾 qi ta quan bu shi la ji  用態度擴張地盤到底什麼意思 yong tai du kuo zhang di pan dao di shen me yi shi 怎麼一回事 zen me yi hui shi 廣場的鴿子 guang chang de ge zi 佔領頭板的報紙 zhan ling tou ban de bao zhi 一種全新的解釋 yi zhong quan xin de jie shi 標題關於這座城市 biao ti guan yu zhe zuo cheng shi 關於一種學習考試 guan yu yi zhong xue xi kao shi 和年輕就該有的本事 he nian qing jiu gai you de ben shi 動感地帶的交通號誌 dong gan di dai de jiao tong hao zhi 到底離我有幾公尺 dao de li wo you ji gong chi 我說老師 wo shuo lao shi 我是不是真的不懂事 wo shi bu shi zhen de bu dong shi 聽我唸繞舌歌詞 ting wo nian rao she ge ci 欣賞我打拳的樣子 xin shang wo da quan de yang zi 我站在教室 wo zhan zai jiao shi 練拳方式 lian quan fang shi 妳的樣子 ni de yang zi 線條一致 xian tiao yi zhi 隔壁的小姑娘 ge bi de xiao gu niang 公開表演需要勇氣 gong kai biao yan xu yao yong qi 別人玩線上遊戲 bie ren wan xian shang you xi 我偏耍猴戲 wo pian shua hou xi 我用形意猴拳在練習 wo yong xing yi hou quan zai lian xi 引你注意 yin ni zhu yi 如果覺得有趣 ru guo jue de you qu 不要吝嗇 bu yao lin se 示個好意 shi ge hao yi  青春是幹淨的純白 qing chun shi gan jing de chun bai 像一遍綠地的窗外 xiang yi bian lü di de chuang wai 我將記憶的門打開 wo jiang ji yi de men da kai 把所有發生的事記下來 ba suo you fa sheng de shi ji xia lai  在我地盤這 zai wo di pan zhe 你就得聽我的 ni jiu de ting wo de 把音樂收割 ba yin le shou ge 用聽覺找快樂 yong ting jue zhao kuai le 開始在雕刻 kai shi zai diao ke 我個人的特色 wo ge ren de te se 未來難預測 wei lai nan yu ce 堅持當下的選擇 jian chi dang xia de xuan ze 在我地盤這 zai wo di pan zhe 你就得聽我的 ni jiu de ting wo de 節奏在招惹 jie zou zai zhao re 我跟街舞親熱 wo gen jie wu qin re 我灌溉原則 wo guan gai yuan ze 培養一種獨特 pei yang yi zhong du te 觀念不及格 guan nian bu ji ge 其他全部是垃圾 qi ta quan bu shi la ji  那彈鋼琴的孩子 na tan gang qin de hai zi 正用他們的手指 zheng yong ta men de shou zhi 彈奏未來的歷史 tan zou wai lai de li shi 我用手機傳中文字 wo yong shou ji chuan zhong wen zi 那傳輸的速度絕對會讓你們豎起大拇指 na chuan shu de su du jue dui hui rong ni men shu qi da mao mu zhi  生活不該有公式 sheng huo bu gai you gong shi 我可以隨性跳芭蕾舞 wo ke yi sui xing tiao ba lei wu 照節拍 zhao jie pai 手放開 shou fang kai 靜下來 jing xia lai 像一隻天鵝把腳尖掂起來 xiang yi zhi tian e ba jiao jian dian qi lai 講究速食的這年代 jiang jiu su shi de zhe nian dai 也可以很天真的說愛 ye ke yi hen tian zhen de shuo ai 
      
</post>
<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      a....today ar not much thing happen,oh ya today get back my phy paper,mi got 4th in class 17/24mi last min studies wan all i studies cum out so happy..... aiya today so sad,npcc room not open, weiwei, bolu, zhiwei go play BB ithink , ps mi la...... then mi ,jinhua, chair go watch inter house soccer.....and  weidi go sent gal home,make mi 1 ppl go home....  haha today sasi own goal!!!haha,sasi sure man of the match wan sian tis week never even 1day mi in npcc room for long,sian haven pack my camp thingy...still got so many thing dun have 
      
</post>
<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       a,today not much thing happen, i think till chem ba,oh ya got during english,i had to pass up homework today  and i never do,so i call sum1 help mi do la, the lata,my english teacher say veri short,aiya also not i do wan(if she see,see la)   then chem the best thing!!!cum liao,we walk normal speed back to class,the stupid tay.s.m scold us for walking slow,she wan to scold, scold mr cheen la, he dismiss us late wan wat!!!then during chem ppl name had been record at 1st, my name was not dere because,i was sleeping...also muz thx to kenny and weidi la cos they tok then TAY.s.m look at them and then never look at mi so i can sleep ...thx brother   then around 1230+++++(cos she use up cme thing for chem)then my name kana on te board,,for dunno wat reason ,then she anyhow how write my name and she say fun wan so now is my turn  (  SU mo,sup moi,sup moooooooooooo    ) hope she see it horz  su mo !!!     then we go jin hua house(drink beer,gamble,do stupid thing)haha jus jking la,maybe sleeping soon ZzzZzzZz 
      
</post>
<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      good news 1st,my ah ma is discharge liao from hospital,i think now she at home le!! then bad news is today got alot of math homeworks!!!!!!!!!sian now today also got chem homework cos never do, donno what happen to  mdm tay ,today she anyhow scold ppl,without any reason..... and the best thing is she is my CME teacher,to during my recess,i lind up for my turn to order food, then i saw mdm tay at the side and she is cutting the line, then i say  mdm tay  ,line up, she she u line up can liao....wat kind of CME teacher is she...... gtg,got lot of HW    
      
</post>
<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       http://myweb.hinet.net/home9/night7318/kusoscom/kusos.com.642.bk.wmv  
      
</post>
<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      arh..........yesterday i sms nicole and ask her bout the date for camp thing and today she around 8+sms.....after i saw tat msg , i wan to go back to sleep and cant liao ,cos kana woke up by nicole!!!so then i 9+the leave my bad,i on the tv to watch cartoon and do math together, so sian the graph, draw 1 graph,need bout30min liao siao, i at exam sure die wan!!!!sian tml got PE scare mr cheen don belive the letter then the poor mi had to run 10 round!!!now mi still haven do finish my math,got to go now or i cant see my ah ma in the hospital liao!! 
      
</post>
</Blog>