<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>


    

        Date: March 23, 2004  Place: Dallas, TX   Everyday, I get in my truck and drive to work. This day was the same as all the others. I drove a little ways, got on the highway, and started the journey. I usually listen to the radio and sometimes have a glass of juice or something. So, I had been driving for about 5 or 10 minutes, when I looked in my rear view mirror. I saw something that most people wouldn't like to see. I saw a car coming and it looked as if the driver is looking for something below the steering wheel. I started to slow down because the vehicle in front of me was coming to a stop. Iagain looked in my mirror and once again saw this lady not looking where she was going, which is sometimes important when driving on a highway. I thought to myself, "She will slow down, because that is what people do, they slow down when the vehicle in front of them does". But she was not slowing down. She maintained her faster than needed speed. Once again I felt that she would look up, slow down, and everything would be just fine. Oh, how wrong I could be.      She kept on going and eventually slammed into my truck at a pretty good pace. You could say that I was not the happiest person in the world at that time. I pulled over and she eventually got there as well. I got out and first went and looked at my damage, which suprisingly wasn't much at all. I then looked up and saw a car that needed a long vacation. There was smoke coming out of it and the driver lookedjust as bad. She got out and was pretty shaken. I asked her if she was hurt and needed any help. She said that she needed to go to the hospital. So I called 911. While we waited, I asked her what happened. She said she was asleep. I thought to myself, "That's odd, to be sleeping while driving on a highway". Like I said before, I usually listen to the radio or have something to drink while driving. Never have I thought of taking a nap while cruising down the interstate. She felt she was special. Hey, I think i'm going to take a little nap here. I've taken them at home, why not now. I'll tell you why not now, because you will  hit something!       So,the fire fighters and police show up and basically shut down the highway and took her to the hospital (she was OK). I got back in my truck, which only had the bumper moved down about 1 inch, and continued my journey to work. About a month later I received a check in the mail for $700.00. I didn't realize that it cost that much to adjust a bumper, but i'm not a mechanic. So, I paid myself $700.00 to adjust a bumper. Best money i've ever made.   What started out as a bad start to the day turned into a nice check, which turned my frown upside down.      

  

    
</post>
<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


    

        urlLink Despair, Inc.    Check this out. Pretty funny if you ask me.   

  

    
</post>
<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


    

        urlLink    So True, So True urlLink    

  

    
</post>
<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


    

       I walked into my bedroom closet a few weeks ago and saw that in the corner, the carpet was damp. I said to myself, this isn't normal. I went to the office the next day and filled out a work order. The maintenance guy came by a few days later and said he couldn't find anything. He actually wrote me a note that said there was not a leak. So, I guess the water appeared out of thin air. Then, about 2 days ago, I am washing my hands in my bathroom when a small stream of water ran down my mirror. I look up, and see that it came from behind my bathroom light. I then look up and see that the sheetrock is a little wet. I guess there was more water appearing from thin air, or maybe a  pipe  in the wall has a leak. I don't know, but it seems they might have a problem here in a few months. At this point, I don't really care. I don't own the place. Good call maintenance guy! Ha! Ha! Ha!   

  

    
</post>
<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>


    

       As I left for work today, everything seemed normal.  It felt normal.  But, what I didn't know was, it would be very different.  As I exited from the highway, a bird flew down in the middle of the road.  The bird was still about 40 or 50 feet away.  At that point, no big deal.  As I flew down the road, I realized the bird was not looking in my direction.  I yelled, "Watch Out !!".  Yes, I actually said, "Watch Out !!", which thinking back now probably wouldn't have helped, even if the bird could hear me.  Anyways, the bird is no more.  It is now in bird heaven.  I felt bad.  The End  

  

    
</post>
</Blog>