<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I finally met my roommates mother tonight. Its interesting to meet your roommates parents because you get to see who they get their habits from. Anyways I had a great time at dinner she bought beers and food what else could you ask for? We ate at Dick's Last Resort, which by any means isn't the most normal place which is probably why I liked it so much. After Dick's my roommate and I went to our favorite bar across the street from our place. This place is your typical neighborhood bar. From the lack of service to the lonely people looking for good conversation then to your run away husbands this place has it all. Typically we go their to play darts, I enjoy the regularity of a place that only confines to the walls within everyone has a say. I have nothing left to say today. Goodnight.   
    
</post>
<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I think the reason why I never voted before was because I lived in Nebraska and they only elect republicans in that state. Now I live in Chicago a democratic city. Everyday this city seems smaller and smaller. Someday it may disappear. I hope that I can find my way home.   
    
</post>
<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am official now. I registered to vote in the city of Chicago. Chalk one more vote up for Kerry this fall. I can't understand how anyone could vote for Bush after the last four years. But according to Gallup polls this years election is going to be very close. This is a popular topic of debate on Friday nights when my friends and I are having a few pints. I always tell them that I think Clinton was one of the best modern day presidents we have had. Of course they don't agree with me. What I don't understand is how can you argue with peace and prosperity for eight years? Granted some people say Clinton didn't do anything to stop the terrorists from becoming what they are today but what was he supposed to do start a war to flex the US's military muscle? Which reminds me, I love the new Beastie Boys album. It reminds me of 80's rap. They got very political on this last album I guess that is what happens when you start to grow older and wiser. My favorite song is Open letter to NYC, reminds me of when I lived in NYC.      
    
</post>
<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just woke up from a after work nap. No gym for me today. I feel like a new boy. I am currently playing poker online and losing! I can't wait for Friday because I am broke. I am staying in all week. No drinks or smokes for at least a week.  
    
</post>
<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My sister and her friend were in town last weekend. I am so run down today because we went out everynight last weekend and I gave them my bedroom and I had to sleep on the couch which means I basically didn't sleep. I am going to sleep for 12 hours tonight to get myself back to normal or as close as I can get. 
    
</post>
<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I don't feel well so I am going home early from work today.  
    
</post>
</Blog>