<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If select a town to study, I will choose Keele. 
If select a city to work, I will come to London. 
 If I have a chance to pick one city out to spend my life, it will be Liverpool. - a decadent, drawling and historic town   

 urlLink    
 urlLink    
 urlLink    
 urlLink    
 urlLink    
 urlLink    
 urlLink    

[Photos] April, 2004, Liverpool
     

    
</post>
<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Yeah...Got it finally. 
  
 Bin's Tips: Dande Voy is 'Where I go' In Spanish.  
  
  
Dande Voy 
 
 
</post>
<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    
 I don't know who is the man with sword, but everyone stood there was taking photo of him. For this reason, I took it and tried finding out who is the famous man...but I've got no result so far. Could someone tell me? 
  
 urlLink    
 The Great Wall of Roman? hahah, what a little one. The chairs and holes on the wall are the only interesting things. 
  
 urlLink    
 The river in the cloudy York. It helps me memorise the trip... no other sense 
  
 urlLink    
 I call it tunnel, and it is really a tunnel:) took it in York's railway station.  
  urlLink    
 The church of York, or cathedral? 
   urlLink    
 Here is for bishops  
  urlLink    
 Amazing gate with stone guards  
  urlLink    
  urlLink    
 Architecture style  
  urlLink    
 Main entrance 
  It is a wonderful journey with many friends, although in a such special day. I want to write down right here apiece of lyric of 'Girl singing on the wreckage' which from Black Box Recorder. 
  --My first trip, my expectations. I had a dream that it would end like this. No destiny, No destination. You hit the ground and then it stops. 
  [Photo] Saint Valentine's Day, 2004, York, United Kingdom  urlLink    



     

    
</post>
<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    

 urlLink    

 urlLink    

 urlLink    

 urlLink    November, 2003, Keele, United Kingdom
     

    
</post>
<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    
 urlLink    
 urlLink    
 urlLink    
 urlLink    
 urlLink    December, 2003, United Kingdom 
Was busy on my Master's study at that time.
     

    
</post>
<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    

 urlLink    

 urlLink    

 urlLink    

 urlLink    

 urlLink    

 urlLink    


[Photo] November 2003, Keele, United Kingdom 
This series of photos was taken in autumn 2003. That's a really depressed season. 
 
[PS.]I am not a professional grapher, so don't comment me technically.
     

    
</post>
<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    


 urlLink    


[Photo] March 2003, Forbidden City, Beijing urlLink   

     

    
</post>
<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink   

 urlLink   

 urlLink   

 urlLink   

 urlLink   

 urlLink   
[Photo] June 2003, My previous office, Nanjing, China urlLink   

     

    
</post>
<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    My portrait urlLink   
     

    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       
 
突然我又想起你的脸
突然我又想起你当天的叮咛
明明灭灭星光的夜里
恍恍惚惚我又看见你的脸
点点滴滴往日的眷恋
寻寻觅觅又再回到我的身边
苦苦安顿抚平的回忆
骤然散落一如繁星的碎片
曾在寒夜中
偷偷的会面
攀越银河远岸
你在月牙旁
轻颦浅笑
你伴我渡过星尘
沉醉晚风中
我不愿回头
不舍不弃
不忘忘不掉
一见一回心底一阵痛
故人故事故情只落得一场空
回忆之前茫茫如梦醒
忘记之后方知梦中还有梦
曾在寒夜中
星空间徘徊
走至银河无路
你在断云旁
轻轻告慰
你替我拭去星尘
浮沉寒风中
我心乱如麻
一脚踏空
坠落回忆中
突然我又想起你的脸
突然我又想起你当天的叮咛
 

     

    
</post>
<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    [Photo] A memorable summer, August 2004, BlockZ3, Horwoord Hall,Keele urlLink   
     

    
</post>
<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    
August 2004, Car park,Keele University, United kingdom
     

    
</post>
</Blog>