<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Spent $140 at Catnips and Carrots vet on my rabbit, Bouncy. She was infor a nasal lacrimal duct blockage this time...The past three times she went in for some dental. My fiance and I spent so much on her care, but it's worth it. Bouncy is like a daughter to us. Hopefully she'll live a long life.      Tomorrow I will be going to Country Mazda to have some warranty work done on my car. Basically the rear bushing broke and the muffler has two 1 inch cracks on the tip. Hopefully they don't try to deny it. If they do, I will give them so much trouble that they'll think twice about denying me again. I may use a law called "Holder in due course." Basically, I will need to notify my bank, Mazda, to let them know that I will be applying this law until they honor their warranty. Under this law, I will deposit my monthly payments on a separate checking account until the problem is fixed. So basically Mazda won't get any of their money until the problem is fixed. I'm sure the dealership will be in a lot of trouble if I do use this law.  
     

    
</post>
<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Never heard of a blog until two weeks ago when I happened to come across one. I thought I would start one on my one just to get my feelings out. Since it's summer now and school restarts on Aug-16, I have some time to rest now. I was supposed to be studying for the boards now but I guess I just can't get myself motivated to do so. After all the step one is given in June and I still have a year.        These days, I've been having some car trouble. My 2003.5 Mazdaspeed Protege (laser blue) is having a few problems and as usual the service departments that I've been to are bastards about upholding warranty work. What's the point of having a warranty when it just gets denied because it doesn't affect the drivability of the car. The last time I went to the dealership, they only changed ONE of the rear suspension bushings...That's like changing one of your bad tires. So about 4 days ago, my car has been serverly clunking and my steering has been at best vague. Here's what my bushing looks like  urlLink now (right click-open in new window).       As most of my friend noticed, I'm pretty picky when it comes to my car. I just can't seem to be satisfied with dealerships. They are always so troublesome to go to and it feels like going to a Jiffy lube or something. Great Neck Mazda were really careless with their workmenship the last time my intercooler pipe came loose on the road. The car came back to me with a paint chip on the door, intake cover off, and missing engine cover. I was never given an apology by anyone at the dealership and was in fact labeled as a bad customer because I complaint to the General Manager after I had informed the Service Manager about my problems. Well, I was toldby the SM that they (we) "don't want trouble customers like you here."        Today, I spent the whole day at home with my fiance (which is rare). She complaints that I can't stay home and treats money like water. It's true, those two are my major character flaws. It's hard for me to stay home because it's boring and money is hard to save because I'm idiot. I'm trying to save, but it's just so hard to do so. Money is just so hard to keep around. I guess I gotta work in a field that pays a lot or I'll be in trouble...Maybe nephrology or surgery...    
     

    
</post>
</Blog>