<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   This piece got the most play of any of my articles, distributed throughout  urlLink indymedia  and other online boards. It is dry but an important topic for progressives, especially African Americans, to bring up to Democrats and John Kerry. Why haven't the Ds championed this issue? Are they so afraid of seeming soft on crime that they are willing to let their potential voters live and die without full citizenship? If so, then a plague on both political parties!   9. One More Step Toward Universal Suffrage (11/20/03)     There was a time in America when only rich white men were allowed to vote. But as history progressed, so did we. Today, every able adult citizen enjoys this most fundamental democratic right with one notable exception: convicted felons.   Due to a patchwork of state disenfranchisement laws, more than 4.2 million Americans -- one in 50 adults -- are denied the right to vote. These people include more than one million who have fully paid their debt to society, yet still face sanction, sometimes for their entire life.   At the turn of the 20th century, criminal disenfranchisement laws -- in conjunction with poll taxes, literacy tests and other structural measures -- were retooled with the intent of denying black men their newly won right to vote.   One hundred years later, black men represent more than one-third of the total disenfranchised population, or 1.4 million people. Sixteen states disenfranchise more than 10 percent of their black citizens, according to a study in the December 2002 issue of the American Sociological Review.    This is no coincidence. The racially disproportionate impact of felon disenfranchisement is the direct result of inequalities within the criminal justice system. With 5 percent of the world's population, the United States holds 25 percent of the world's prisoners. How did this happen in the land of the free?   urlLink [more here]      

						
</post>
<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   My title for this piece would have been "The Momentum of Big Words." It is a philosophical idea that I would like to explore in-depth in the future.   8. Who's American? (11/13/03)     I'll never forget the first day of high school history, senior year: Mr. Smith (I've changed his name for the sake of anonymity) entered the classroom, removed an American flag from the wall and hurled it to the ground.   "How does this make you feel?" he asked, stomping on the flag after every single word. The class was slack-jawed.     "Remember this feeling," he said. "This is what 20th century history is all about."    Patriotism.    It's one of those words -- like art, terrorism, evil, love and God -- that I cannot define, except to say, "I know it when I feel it."   And I felt a patriotic rage that morning watching Mr. Smith step on the Stars and Stripes, especially since he was a well-known socialist and draft-dodger. The feeling surprised me. I didn't think I was the patriotic type.    After the Sept. 11 terrorist attacks, many Americans who never thought of themselves as patriotic were suddenly overcome by a similar rage. Rhetoric changed overnight. The Mr. Smiths of the world -- the self-identifying proud anti-patriots -- joined the dinosaurs as an extinct species. The question, "Can one be unpatriotic and a good citizen?" fell away into thin air.    Now, the guy burning the American flag at an anti-war rally claims to be a patriot; that dissent is patriotic. The most unpatriotic legislation in my lifetime appropriates the word, along with a tortured, Orwellian title. And CEOs trip over themselves to market their product as the most patriotic brand of toothpaste or fabric softener.   The natural momentum of big words is to grow ever bigger and more inclusive, so inclusive that they become meaningless: Everyone is patriotic, everything is art, any act of violence is terrorism, everyone bad is evil, every good feeling is love, God is everywhere and everything.     I usually denounce these definitions as philosophically lazy, but, in the case of patriotism, I think it is a good thing...      urlLink [more here]      

						
</post>
<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   This article got me in trouble with  urlLink Dennis Kucinich  supporters in Eugene -- the topic of an upcoming article so stay tuned -- but it also eventually landed me an exclusive interview with the man himself. I will be posting the full transcript of that interview here shortly so stay tuned for that as well. This was the first in a series of articles offering my insider's critique of the progressive movement. This article explores why progressive Democrats need to abandon the party.   7. The Real, the New and the Kucinich (11/6/03)    I feel bad for Dennis Kucinich.     According to a recent Washington Post-ABC News poll, he would receive fewer votes than Carol Moseley Braun if the election were held today. He is losing in a presidential race to a black woman. How embarrassing! She has at least one good excuse for not getting votes; mainly, many white Americans would sooner vote for French President Jacques Chirac for president than a black person. What's Kucinich's excuse? He should change his campaign motto to, "Hey, I'm a white man over here!"   Carol Moseley Braun must contend with a hallowed tradition in the media: treating black congresswomen poorly. If they mention her name -- and that's a big if -- it is usually in connection with her past failures and controversies. They rarely mention that she was the first and only black female U.S. senator in this nation's history, the first black democratic senator and the first female senator from Illinois. If anybody could break the White House's gender and color barriers, it would be Braun. That's another big if, which is why she is fighting for not-last place with Kucinich and the other two bottom-feeders, John Edwards and Al Sharpton.   That leaves a handful of white men who are still serious contenders with the election one year away and counting. They can be divided into two different groups: the so-called New Democrats and the so-called Real Democrats.    The New Democrats scare me the most. Their true believer is Joseph Lieberman; John Kerry and Wesley Clark are honorary members. They rally under the corporate-funded  urlLink Democratic Leadership Council (DLC),  a group formed in the mid-80s for the purpose of pushing the Democratic Party further and further to the right, in much the same way the Christian Coalition pushed the Republican Party to the right.    On their Web site, the DLC claims to "believe in a Third Way that rejects the old left-right debate." Funny, this Third Way, summed up in the "Hyde Park Declaration," reads exactly like the Republican "Contract with America." The DLC couches their beliefs in thick rhetorical code designed to put conservative swing-voters at ease without upsetting their liberal base.   urlLink [more here]           

						
</post>
<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    After all this time the  urlLink website  that I mention in this article still hasn't changed. I guess they never read my article. Oh well. Maybe they will catch it this time around.   6. Freedom Press (10/30/03)   Apparently the feds are just plain fed up with us media types and our cup-half-empty, if-it-bleeds-it-leads attitude about the war in Iraq.       With 20 to 30 attacks on U.S. soldiers daily -- and, on average, more than 10 injuries and one death per day -- we don't have to look far to find a story that will satisfy our bloodlust.         Since the security situation shows no sign of improvement anytime soon, the Bush administration has decided to launch a pre-emptive strike on bad press and the bad liberal media responsible for it.        According to The Washington Post, the president has banned reporters from covering the arrival of dead soldiers in flag-draped coffins, a staple of wartime photojournalism. And, according to Newsweek, reporters are barred from hospitals and morgues in Baghdad, stymieing any attempt to independently verify the numbers of dead and injured.         Here at home, several members of Congress are doing their patriotic part by starting  urlLink www.freedom.gov , a new Web site designed to give fair and balanced coverage of the Iraqi reconstruction effort. It looks exactly as one might expect: pictures of happy soldiers, happy Iraqi children and as many American flags as is technologically possible to cram on a single screen.         If you click on "Accomplishments" at the top of the page, you will find eight links to positive articles about the war.         I know what you're thinking: Have there really been eight separate accomplishments in Iraq? That sounds a little high. Well, you're right. I discovered, upon closer inspection, that two of the eight links go to the same article.          You have to get up pretty early in the morning ...     urlLink [more here]                

						
</post>
<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   The first time publishing the word "fuck" is a special day in the life of any writer. This article is one of my favorites and it is as applicable today as it was when I first wrote it. The various AIDS funds are still relatively dry. This really should be the number one issue in the world, but I don't know that I've heard much about it recently. The Democrats should be making more of this, and the Republicans should be moving on it, if for no other reason than to save political face among swing voters. Of course, there is a much more compelling reason; it is the right thing to do.   5. Deadly Lies (10/23/03)   A friend from Kenya once told me that she was writing a book about Africa specifically for American readers entitled: "Send Money and Shut the Fuck Up."  That always sounded like sage foreign policy advice to me.  Unfortunately, the Bush administration is following the exact opposite doctrine, a fact that was made painfully clear last summer during the president's "historic" five-day, five-nation African tour.  Bush was the stereotypical tourist: According to the New York Times, he spent three of his four nights at a luxury hotel in South Africa, visiting Botswana and Senegal for six hours each and Uganda for only three.  On the first day of his trip, Bush took 15 minutes to visit Goree Island, once the center of the West African slave trade. Eschewing my friend's "Shut the Fuck Up" doctrine, he delivered a speech carefully crafted to denounce slavery without actually apologizing for America's rather significant role in the enterprise.  Bush also managed to find the bright side of the slave trade when he insinuated that God allowed it to happen so that America's racial conscience could be awakened. God sure has a funny way of teaching white people life lessons! Mysterious indeed.      urlLink [more here]      

						
</post>
<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Salman Rushdie, in a brilliant essay about his post-fatwa isolation, writes, "It has been bewildering to learn that people do not care about art." That is what the following article is about.     Rushdie says, "[art is], for a secular, materialist culture, some sort of replacement for what the love of god offers in the world of faith." That is why we need a separation of art and state as much as we need a separation of church and state.      4. War Against Poetry (10/16/03)     It's not the first (truth), and it's not the second (human beings), but poetry has become one of the casualties of war.     Many a foolhardy critic has penned "poetry is dead," only to have it rise again from its coffin. I know this. I'm aware that this mission is sure suicide. But ever since reading the following poetic lines dealing with the war in Iraq, I've lost the will to live:    "Isn't it their duty to their Country / more to become a poet / than a brainwashed murder robot?"    "Why don't you tell those bastards not to fight? For Pete's sake, send an angel! Burn a bush!"    "I weep for justice."    "Tell these eerie people that killing children is wrong, that the U.S. becomes everyday more and more frightful."    Amateurs did not write these verses, nor preschoolers; they belong to past and present poets laureate in work collected by the organization Poets Against the War....    urlLink [read the rest]          

						
</post>
<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I wanted to call this piece Supreme Kangaroo Court, but copy editors always know better. Yeeaah...Oh well. I plan on writing Supreme Lunacy Redux in October. There have been plenty of  urlLink questionable decisions  from the justices so far this year and plenty to come.  urlLink Here  is a great resource for all things law related.      3. Supreme Lunacy (10/9/03)     In July, evangelist Pat Robertson launched what he described as a "prayer offensive," formally known as Operation Supreme Court Freedom. On his television show, the 700 Club, he instructed viewers to kneel down and pray for God to remove a liberal justice from the high court.   "One justice is 83 years old," Robertson said, "another has cancer and another has a heart condition. Would it not be possible for God to put it in the minds of these three judges that the time has come to retire?"    He then added: "Retire permanently! Bwuu ha ha haaa!"   Well, I am happy to report that all nine justices survived the wrath of God this summer and on Monday returned for the official beginning of the 2003-04 term. They will be glad they did, for this year promises to be another wild ride. Separation of church and state, capital punishment, the USA PATRIOT Act, medical marijuana and campaign finance reform are just a few of the high-profile issues that the Supremes are expected to tackle before the year is over.    In the coming months I will be writing about these cases, but first I would like to take a brief look back at the top five wackiest, zaniest or just plain stupid Supreme Court decisions from last year. Frankly, it is hard to narrow it down to five, but here they are...    urlLink  [read more]          

						
</post>
<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    This article was my first attempt at sarcasm in print. It was a valuable lesson: Not everyone gets sarcasm, at least not in print. Why do we tend to take the written word so literally? Is it because we are such a religious country? I don't know. Anyway, the experience didn't stop me from using sarcasm in later articles. I never learn.    2. Colorblind Politics (10/7/03)     Today, as Californians flock to the polls, the question on everybody's mind is: Who will get more votes in the recall election, the porn star or the pornographer?    (Both are 500-1 shots in Las Vegas. Seriously.)    In addition to the recall, Californians will be voting on Proposition 54, a serious proposal with serious consequences. Dubbed the Racial Privacy Initiative, it would, if passed, forbid the government from collecting data on race. It reads, in part:   "The state shall not classify any individual by race, ethnicity, color or national origin in the operation of public education, public contracting or public employment."   Proposition 54 is a "Don't ask, don't tell" policy for minorities. Opponents call it statistical ethnic cleansing. Supporters say that race -- like sexual orientation -- is no business of the government and that this initiative represents a major step forward in America's quest for a color-blind society.   I agree, but the initiative does not go nearly far enough in protecting racial privacy. Government employees and school administrators would still be able to figure out an applicant's ethnicity and use it against them. If Oregonians are interested in protecting their racial privacy, I would suggest they adopt a proposition similar to Proposition 54 with the following important additions...      urlLink [more here]            

						
</post>
<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						             I am currently writing an article about blogging for my local daily newspaper. As part of my research I decided to start my own personal blog. I will use this space to post new thoughts and opinions on current events as well as post links to my previously published columns.     To start off, here is a link to the first opinion column I wrote for my college newspaper.     1. Schoolhouse Discrimination (10/3/03)         Then-governor Ross Barnett called it "the moment of our greatest crisis since the War Between the States": During this week in 1962, James Meredith became the first black student at the University of Mississippi.    Barnett's words sound exaggerated to our ears, but make no mistake: The civil rights movement was, in fact, civil war. Our public schools were freed from all-white control through military intervention. Our universities were liberated by force....   urlLink http://www.dailyemerald.com/vnews/display.v/ART/2003/10/02/3f7c35c49bf91?in_archive=1              

						
</post>
<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Personally, I think this man says what most white Republicans feel but know they shouldn't say. I like guys like this because they force Americans to face an embarrassing truth: Racism is alive and well in America. After all, he got over 7,500 votes.  From Associated Press via  urlLink Common Dreams :    MEMPHIS, Tenn. - An unabashed racist will represent the Republican party in the November election for a congressional seat after a write-in candidate failed to derail his effort.      With 86 percent of the primary vote counted Thursday, write-in candidate Dennis Bertrand had just 1,554 votes compared to 7,671, or 83 percent, for  urlLink James L. Hart , a believer in the discredited, phony science of eugenics.       In November, the GOP candidate will oppose Rep. John Tanner, a Democrat who has represented the northwest Tennessee district for 15 years.      Hart, 60, vows if elected to work toward keeping "less favored races" from reproducing or immigrating to the United States. In campaign literature, Hart contends that "poverty genes" threaten to turn the United States into "one big Detroit."      "I didn't expect to win," Hart said. "I thought their network would beat my ideas."       He has run for the 8th District seat before and drawn little attention. But people began to notice this time because he was the only Republican on the ballot.      Since the deadline for getting on the ballot had passed, Bertrand, also a Republican, began a write-in campaign, saying he wanted to protect the party's honor.      "I think his beliefs are not beliefs of any party that I know of," Bertrand said Thursday night. "I knew it was going to be a really long shot, but in good conscience, I had to at least give it an attempt."      Bertrand, a financial analyst and former military officer, was on active duty with the National Guard when the deadline to get on the primary ballot passed.      Hart said he will have lots of time to campaign for the general election since he was forced Wednesday to resign from his job as a real estate salesman because of the attention he drew during the primary.      "They didn't say 'You're fired' in exactly those words, but it was pretty clear what they wanted," Hart said.       While campaigning, Hart sometimes wears a protective vest and carries a .40-caliber pistol, but he said he has run into no trouble.      "When I knock on a door and say white children deserve the same rights as everybody else, the enthusiastic response is truly amazing," he said.      If a black person opens the door, he says he simply drops off campaign literature and leaves.       From James Hart's website:  "Genes have a more devastating effect on civilization than nuclear bombs, and the reason for Detroit's decline is that there are less 'favored races' in Detroit with an average IQ of 85 and more 'favored races' in Japan with an average IQ of 104. (It is noted there are less 'favored races'* in Africa south of the Sahara with an average IQ of 70-75, which accounts for the extreme poverty there.)"    

						
</post>
<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Eh. Not sure what this is, but okay....   There are by some estimates more than a million weblogs. But most of them get no visibility in search engines. Only a few "A-List" blogs get into the top search engine results for a given topic, while the majority of blogs just don't get noticed. The reason is that the smaller blogs don't have enough links pointing to them. But this posting could solve that. Let's help the smaller blogs get more visibility!This posting is   urlLink  GoMeme 4.0.    It is part of an experiment to see if we can create a blog posting that helps 1000's of blogs get higher rankings in Google. So far we have tried 3 earlier variations. Our first test,   urlLink  GoMeme 1.0   , spread to nearly 740 blogs in 2.5 days. This new version 4.0 is shorter, simpler, and fits more easily into your blog.       Why are we doing this? We want to help thousands of blogs get more visibility in Google and other search engines. How does it work? Just follow the instructions below to re-post this meme in your blog and add your URL to the end of the Path List below. As the meme spreads onwards from your blog, so will your URL. Later, when your blog is indexed by search engines, they will see the links pointing to your blog from all the downstream blogs that got this via you, which will cause them to rank your blog higher in search results. Everyone in the Path List below benefits in a similar way as this meme spreads. Try it!       Instructions: Just copy this entire post and paste it into your blog. Then add your URL to the end of the path list below, and pass it on! (Make sure you add your URLs as live links or HTML code to the Path List below.)   Path List 1.  urlLink Minding the Planet  2.  urlLink When Knitting Was a Manly Art  3.  urlLink Preemptive Karma  4.  urlLink Drunk With Ink  5. (your URL goes here! But first, please copy this line and move it down to the next line for the next person).  (NOTE: Be sure you paste live links for the Path List or use HTML code.)  

						
</post>
<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Courtesy of    urlLink  People For the American Way, August 2004           Alan Keyes, a right-wing pundit and former presidential and senatorial candidate who lives in Maryland, is reportedly considering a run for the U.S. Senate on the Republican Party ticket in Illinois. Here, in his own words, is a sampling of Alan Keyes record and rhetoric.   Keyes on Running for Office in another state in 2004: Former GOP presidential candidate Alan Keyes told Illinois Republicans Monday that he is "open to the idea" of taking on the Democrat in the U.S. Senate race ... Keyes lives in Maryland. Chicago Sun Times, "GOP wooing Keyes to take on Obama," August 3, 2004  Keyes on Running for Office in another state in 2000: "And I deeply resent the destruction of federalism represented by Hillary Clinton's willingness to go into a state she doesn't even live in and pretend to represent people there. So I certainly wouldn't imitate it." Fox News, "Special Report with Brit Hume," March 17, 2000  Alan Keyes on principle in 2004: "I do not take it for granted that it's a good idea to parachute into a state and go into a Senate race," he said before meeting the Republican leaders. "As a matter of principle, I don't think it's a good idea." Chicago Tribune, "GOP Wants Keyes," August 5, 2004  Alan Keyes on principle in 1996: "This must be a terrible feeling," Keyes tells his would-be supporters. "You make a decision based on expediency, and it doesn't work. And then you are left without expediency and without principle. With nothing. This is sad, I never want to wake up the day after an election or any time else with that emptiness in me, knowing I have given away the things that matter most for the sake of what I thought would win and finding that I have lost and have nothing." Minnesota Christian Chronicle, "In ignoring Keyes, Christian voters choose expediency over principle," Feb 22, 1996  Keyes on the Republican Party: In 1992, according to the Washington Post, as Republican nominee in Maryland's U.S. Senate contest that year, Keyes denounced the national leadership of his party as racist, saying senior GOP officials had ignored or disparaged his campaign because he is black. GOP leaders "basically are sending the message that beyond a certain level blacks need not apply," Keyes said. "If I can work out in the fields, I think I ought to be allowed to come into the house for dinner." Washington Post, "GOP Hopeful Says Party Is Racist" August 14, 19 92   Keyes equates abortion and genocide: "I think it would be a terrible shame to abandon the fate of America or the black community to the likes of people who are speaking as Julian Bond has spoken, but more importantly, the likes of people who have supported policies that have destroyed the black family, that support abortion, which is committing genocide against black people in this country with devastating demographic results that we have already seen in the course of the last census." Hannity and Colmes, "Interview with Alan Keyes," July 12, 2004  Keyes equates abortion and terrorism: "The violation on [sic] innocent human life is the same whether you commit terrorism or commit abortion." People For the American Way Foundation, "The Vocabulary of Terror: Anti-abortion politics since 9/11" April 10, 2002  Keyes resorts to the lowest form of rhetoric and calls homosexuals Nazis: "Hitler and his supporters were Satanists and homosexuals. That's just a true statement." He added that, "The notion that is involved in homosexuality, the unbridled sort of satisfaction of human passions" leads to "totalitarianism, Nazism, and communism." People For the American Way Foundation, "Hostile Climate 1997," p.26        

						
</post>
<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Once again, attention copy editors: this piece should have been titled "Starving the Beast." They make me so mad! I wrote this in the middle of the night at a Seattle hotel lobby. I was in a weird mood. There is much much more that could be said about Bush's economic policies.  Today:  urlLink Surprising Jobs Report . Funny, I'm surprised at all.   15. Robbing from the Poor (2/5/04)     On Monday, President Bush released his projected budget for 2005, and ever since I have spent every spare second of my free time pouring over all 3,000 pages of ...   Okay, I'll be straight with you. I haven't read one page of Bush's budget. I didn't know he had released the damn thing until I read it in the newspaper today. Look, the Emerald is giving me 10 bucks and a good-job-old-chum pat on the butt per column. What do you want from me? Investigative journalism?   Furthermore -- and I'd like to stress this point -- I am not an economist. I am not good with numbers and really don't understand budgets. I can't even balance my checkbook. I am probably the last person on this campus who should be commenting on Bush's $2.4 trillion proposal.   That being said, I am absolutely outraged by this budget. Outraged! I mean, I knew Bush was "starving the beast," but who could have guessed he would be so obvious about it?   "Starving the beast" refers to a counterintuitive strategy whereby tax cuts and over-the-top spending are used to starve the government of money and force cuts to public spending. It is spending for the sake of cuts.   Ronald Reagan's budget director David Stockman coined the phrase, or so it said when I Googled him. Again, what do you want from me? Actual research? Why don't you read a real newspaper, you cheap bastard?   Sorry. I didn't mean to snap. It's just that this budget has got me hopping mad! Bush's spending priorities are so fiscally irresponsible that even some Republicans are starting to bristle.    Sure, it took projected deficits of $521 billion -- much of which is going to a useless war in Iraq that is threatening to suck another $50 billion of taxpayer money not included in the budget -- before these conservatives raised their heads out of the sand. But better late than never I guess. Bristle away!   I have an idea: Let's just scrap that new Medicare package that was recently enacted, which is going to cost one-third more than originally estimated. Then we would have a surplus of $13 billion. Or, if you are partial to health, let's junk that whole Social Security thing. That would have us $29 billion in the black.    My point: Cuts alone are not enough. We need a progressive tax structure in this country that would dramatically lower the burden on the middle class while forcing the rich and their multinational corporations to pay a fair share.     Bush, by contrast, wants to use the deficits that he created through unnecessary spending as an excuse to cut an array of useful social programs. Here are a few examples:   urlLink [more here]      

						
</post>
<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I think we can all agree this article should have been titled "Blowing Our WOD." Speaking of the War on Drugs, here is the problem: In 1986 the Congress adopted a 100-to-1 ratio for crack verses powder cocaine, after hearings tinged with racism. That means, with manditory minimums, 5 years for 500 grams of powder verses 5 grams of crack -- 10 years for 5000 grams of powder verses 50 grams of crack. There is a five year minimum for possession of crack!  Bush said he would support removing these ratios in January 2001. Yeah. That never happened.    Message to progressives: When you talk about the war on drugs, could you mention the racial issue? Let us fix the racism of drug laws before we work on legalizing marijuana.   14. The Anti-Bush (1/29/04)     Many people have asked me, after reading my column, whether or not I do drugs. That is a fair question and the answer is no. Sure, I'm usually drunk when I write, but I refuse to take drugs, even marijuana, because I know that it could destroy my life.   For example, if you smoke marijuana I know that you will eventually get raped, shoot your best friend in the head, run over a small child with your car, drown a completely different child in a pool and give material support to al-Qaida.   I learned this, as I learn most things, from watching television commercials. For the last five years the government has doled out more than $600 million to lecture us via the boob tube about our drug use. And we love it. We can't get enough.    Lucky for us, the Super Bowl is only days away, and you know what that means: New anti-drug ads!    I can't wait to see what terrible calamities will befall those lousy bong-loving hippies. Sources close to the White House tell me the new commercials will show that marijuana smokers will contract mad cow disease, get crushed by falling grand pianos, get punched in the balls by Gary Coleman and buoy the spirits of Kim Jong-il.    Pot really is more dangerous than we thought.   For the sake of balance, there will be a host of pro-drug ads during the Super Bowl as well, including one for the erectile-dysfunction drug Levitra, the erectile-dysfunction drug Cialis, the erectile-dysfunction drug Viagra and nine Budweiser spots.   One commercial that you won't be seeing on Super Bowl Sunday is a 30-second spot sponsored by the liberal group Move On, which highlights the fact that President Bush is plunging the country further and further into debt. CBS -- which, if I'm not mistaken, stands for Conservatives Broadcasting to Seniors -- has refused to air it. The Viacom-owned station defended its hypocritical decision to run anti-drug spots but not an award-winning anti-Bush spot by saying it was "too controversial."   Are they suggesting that the White House's anti-drug ads are not controversial? One puts the culpability for a rape on the victim and her drug use. Another blames pot use for an accidental shooting rather than the parents who keep a loaded gun in their desk.    During last year's Super Bowl, CBS aired a spot that said smoking pot aids terrorists. (They eventually pulled these ads for fear that the excessive eye rolling would cause permanent damage, leading to increased use of medicinal marijuana.)    And if you've seen the ad where a group of black guys are hot boxing a beat up car at the drive-through window of a fast food restaurant, then you know I'm not exaggerating when I say it's the most racist thing I've seen on television in a long time.   urlLink [more here]       

						
</post>
<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   This article really began my constant mocking of President Bush. I'll tell you, it never gets old. Note: the night before this was published, Jon Stewart told a joke almost identical to one in my article -- of course, I wrote it two days beforehand. Just goes to show how easy it is to mock Bush.   13. Uncertain State for the Union (1/22/04)    If you are like me, you spent Tuesday night anxiously awaiting President Bush's State of the Union address.      OK, OK, OK. If you are like me, you were watching reruns of "The Daily Show" and "Late Night with Conan O'Brien" on Comedy Central while President Bush gave his State of the Union address.     But during a commercial break I downloaded a transcript of the speech and skimmed through most of it, thus allowing me to pontificate about it like the rest of my media pundit buddies.    Back in 2002, Bush was still a little rusty at the whole presidential thing. During a speech in Connecticut he said, "And so, in my State of the -- my State of the Union -- or state -- my speech to the nation, whatever you want to call it, speech to the nation ..."    This time around he seemed to know exactly what the speech was called. And he wasted no time in going immediately to the patriotic rhetoric. My favorite part was when he tried to justify the Iraq war as part of the war on terrorism.     "Let us be candid about the consequences of leaving Saddam Hussein in power," Bush said. "We're seeking all the facts. Already, the Kay Report identified dozens of weapons of mass destruction-related program activities ..."     Weapons of mass destruction-related program activities? Well, no wonder we couldn't wait for the weapons inspectors to do their job. No wonder hundreds of Americans had to lose their lives. It is just like the Bush administration has said from day one: Saddam was harboring weapons of mass destruction ... -related program activities, and we cannot allow related program activities to fall into the wrong hands.   urlLink [more here]        

						
</post>
<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    This was a nice surprise. Probably won't be many more of these in my future, so I am going to enjoy it.   urlLink AWARD    

						
</post>
<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						     In January I was asked to write where I stood on the Democratic candidates for president. This is what I wrote:    Support of death penalty moratorium necessary in Democratic candidate       There are two Democratic candidates who strongly and impenitently support an immediate moratorium on the death penalty: Dennis Kucinich and Al Sharpton.   Any candidate who weakly supports (Wesley Clark), flip-flops (John Kerry, John Edwards and Howard Dean) or strongly rejects (Dick Gephardt and Joe Lieberman) a moratorium on the death penalty does not deserve the Democratic nomination.    Capital punishment is the most sinisterly racist institution in America today.   Since reinstated, 80 percent of those receiving the death penalty have been executed for murders involving white victims, even though blacks and whites are murdered in nearly equal numbers, according to an Amnesty International report.   Furthermore, 20 percent of blacks receiving the death penalty are convicted by all-white juries. Study after study shows that white jurors place more value on the lives of whites than on the lives of blacks, consciously or unconsciously, when it comes to decisions about capital punishment.   Where a candidate stands on the death penalty is a racial litmus test. If they aren't going to stand firmly for a moratorium, I doubt they will seriously address other examples of institutional racism like the war on drugs, felon disenfranchisement and the public school system.   They will always choose to appear soft on racism rather than appear soft on crime because they know the latter will cost them more votes. Blacks can no longer afford to support this kind of politician. That is why I am so disappointed that Carol Moseley Braun, a vocal supporter of a moratorium, has dropped out of the race and thrown her support to Howard Dean.   My vote (if I were a Democrat) would go to Dennis Kucinich or Al Sharpton. The fact that neither has a chance of winning speaks volumes about the misplaced priorities of the Democratic Party and of Democratic voters themselves.     

						
</post>
<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    I'm attaching an email that I received when I first published the column below because it is one of my favorites. It is rare to get postive feedback. It is also rare to write something that truly speaks to somebody. It is so easy to get burned out in this business. I was almost there. But after reading this email I became as energized to write as I was during my first month at the Oregon Daily Emerald.   This is my first term at U of O, and on my first day of class when I   saw the King mural in the EMU, I was appalled.  My first thought was   that King's message and life work had, indeed, been disgustingly   appropriated as a decoration for the school.    For me, if the U of O is going to have this mural, shouldn't there be   a second half that says:  "And what are the rest of us who have the   power and privilege to do so, going to do to change things?"    I tried to talk about this with a few people, and the reaction has   been that I am crazy and that *I* am the one who is being insulting to   King.  For several days I gave up talking about this.  Then I saw your   article, immediately cut it out and put it in a page protector, and   now when I talk with other people about this and they treat me like   I'm crazy, I show them your article.  I hope you don't mind.  :)    It's just not OK to use the names, life work, and ideals of oppressed   peoples for decoration or entertainment--we all have a responsiblity   when we know that others are being oppressed, to do something about   it.  So I've made the decision that not talking about this is as   disrespectful to King as the mural itself, and I've decided to keep   talking, no matter what.    Thank you for your article.  It has given me strength to see how   important it is to not get discouraged, and to keep talking about the   importance of making a commitment to dismantle the mechanisms that   perpetuate oppression.     12. Distorting the Dream (1/15/04)    As Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. stood before the Lincoln Memorial and delivered the keynote address for the March on Washington, D.C., he couldn't have realized that a single sentence from his speech would come to encapsulate his entire career in the collective consciousness of white America:    "I have a dream my four little children will one day live in a nation where they will not be judged by the color of their skin but by the content of their character. I have a dream today!"    We're all familiar with this quote. We were taught these words in high school. A mural with these words greets us in the foyer of the EMU. The majority of Americans know nothing about Dr. King except for his "I Have a Dream" speech. It is quite possibly the most beloved speech of all time.     As a young, black man I have learned to hate Dr. King's dream.     Or rather, white America has made it near impossible for younger generations of blacks to love the dream in the same way as the older generations. Because, for us, Dr. King's dream of America has been twisted into America's dream of Dr. King, a dream that has nothing to do with the reality of the man or the substance of his message.     Conservatives for years have ripped the words "content of their character" away from its context in order to suggest that Dr. King would be against affirmative action programs.     Last year in our University's own conservative journal of opinion, the Oregon Commentator, Colin Elliott wrote, "Dr. Martin Luther King Jr., a patriotic, rational American activist, put it best when he hoped for a world where his children 'will not be judged by the color of their skin but by the content of their character.' Dr. King knew that character, not race, was more important."     Let us forgive Elliott for describing the greatest civil rights leader in American history as "rational," which could be interpreted as a tad condescending.   urlLink [more here]     

						
</post>
<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						         The Draft   I asked the congressman if young people should be concerned about the draft.  “Oh, are you kidding,” he said. “They should be very concerned. If we stay in Iraq there is going to be a draft. There is just no question about it.  “People don’t get excited until they get a notice in the mail. But let me tell you something. Do the math: 130,000 troops; they are keeping people more and more past their time; look at all the guards persons that were called up, all the reservists that were called.  “The longer we stay, the longer we are going to be there and the deeper we are getting into it. You have got to realize, 100,000 Iraqis marched through the streets of Baghdad a few weeks ago in a show of solidarity opposing the United States position. Our soldiers are being asked to protect a policy, which the Iraqi people are in revolt against. This is dangerous.  “So are we looking at the possibility of a draft? Yeah, we are. And it’s very dangerous. Very dangerous.”        I agree. Compulsory military service has no place in a free society. A war that cannot be supported by volunteer fighters is not a war we should be fighting.  I am appalled at Democratic congressmen Fritz Hollings and Charles Rangel, who have introduced legislation, in the Senate and the House respectively, that would restart the draft, dubbed the Universal National Service Act.     Democrats should vote these men out of office for this unforgivable act.    A draft today would be very different than the draft in the past, says Maureen Farrell of  urlLink www.buzzflash.com .      First, we would not see college deferments like we saw during the Vietnam War. That practice ended in 1971 when reforms were enacted designed to make the draft more equitable. Were a draft to be reinstated, students could defer service only until the end of the semester, or for those graduating, the end of the academic year.         Moving to Canada to escape the draft would be a less manageable solution thanks to the “Smart Border Declaration.” This anti-terrorism measure has the added affect of keeping draft-dodgers in the country.         We need to stop the draft before it starts. Conscription would be political suicide, so it is unlikely that this would happen before the 2004 presidential election. But, as Kucinich said, any candidate without a plan for getting U.S. troops out of Iraq is flirting with the issue, and does not deserve our vote.    It is up to young people to make this a central issue during the elections.          

						
</post>
<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						      Cell Phones, Supermodels and PUD  </post></Blog>