<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Everybody tells me i use that line toomuch "IM TIRED", well you know what, I am tired all the time. don't ask why, cause I don't know. Today was the same. Went to work and came home. Kind of pissed off today though. We were supposed to goto see Randy Rogers band tonight. I get on their website and notice that they aren't here tonight. Oh well. Im listening to a song right now called "its hard to kiss the lips at night that chews your assout all day long" Thats funny right there, i dont care who u are. Randy is on right now, i guess that will do for tonight for missing the show. not really but thats what im going to go with. I really like this band more and more everytime i listen to them. Got a different sound to them. Went and saw them at some LITTLE bar in Galveston. Got to talk to them after the show so that was cool. Then we went to the beach after. Thats for a later post. Going home this weekend to see family. The mrs. is staying home to work, somebody has to pay for the trip. Just kidding. Ill admit it, she's the bread winner in the family. Ill try to get back on sometime sat. or sun. Untill then "Tonights not the night". TTTTM  T   
     

    
</post>
<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink http://www.galleywinter.com    urlLink http://www.patgreen.com    urlLink http://www.randyrogersband.com    urlLink http://www.blainespub.com    urlLink http://www.gruenehall.com    urlLink http://www.partypoker.com     
     

    
</post>
<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I figured I would get into the blogging that has been going around. Seems like everybody has a blog these days, so i thought i needed one too. It's been rainy here the last couple of days. An outside job isnt fun in the rain. I would just go home and sleep, but i dont think the mrs. would like that. And if i did go home, she would make me clean or run errands. I would rather work and just get wet. Its past midnight and im still up causing of a pounding headache. I hope these things end when i get my glasses. Starting to make me mad. I titled my blog "who's to say?" because i think it fits for a lot of things in life. It part of a Pat Green song. If you are readingthis and u know who i am, you know that i am a "Greenhead" or just a big PG fan. Watched Starsky and Hutch tonight, i liked it but Kris didnt. (kris is the mrs.) She fell asleep half way through it which is nothing new. Dont think she has made it through a whole movie in a couple of years. Well im off to bed, till next time. TTTTM   
     

    
</post>
</Blog>