<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       With an extensivebackground in BroadcastJournalism as a TelevisionAssignment Reporter,a Television Morning Show Host, aMovie Critic, a Television Weather Forecaster, andas a Radio On-Air Personality, I havethe rareability to reportThe News, commentabout anything of interest and conduct Informative Interviews, Rate the latest Film Offerings from Hollywood, explain Weather Events and even critique the latest Music in The Top 40. As a Print Journalist, I have acted as an Editor, a Staff Writer, and a Magazine Columnist, and I authored and illustrateda Children's Book entitled "The Frightening Lightning" under the pen name of "David Cooper," (a play on my real surname,Cubero,)published by Candlestick Press, copyright 1984, therefore I am more than capable ofbringing to you writtenreports that may or may not directly effect you, but will nonetheless make for a VERY interesting read.   My experienceisn't simply limited to reporting News via the various mediums listed above, I have also made The News Headlinesand been a part of News Events and Historyas alocal Politician, when Iran anunsuccessful campaignto unseata long-timeSchool Board Member in 1986. Although I took 39% of the overallvotes in the general election and wound up in a run-off against the incumbent, I was ultimatelydefeated and vowed never to dabble in politics again.Ihave also been a U.S. Soldier, seeing battlefield action in both The Grenada Invasion andTheU.S. Invasion of Panama. I am presentlya Part-Time Police Officer and I once workeda Part-TimeLos Angeles County Paramedic.Having these particularexperiences, Ihave insiders insights into many areas of Public Interest, from U.S. Homeland Security to War to Crimeand Punishment to Emergency Medical Care and Treatment to Politics.   From the age of 10 months until my early 20's I was a working Film and Television Actor in Latin America and in Hollywood. In childhood I reached a certain level of stardom in Mexico and Puerto Rico. In Hollywood and New York I was at best a character actor.However, by the time I reached my earlyteensmy acting opportunities began to fade into the sunset-just like the ending of a bad B-Western Movie. As time marched on, my acting rolesbecameso occasional that I just gave it up altogether, what withALL my other pokers in various fires. Nevertheless, I have this insider's experience as an actorand Ievenmaintain Hollywoodcontacts that I can call upon to provide the latest information fromThe Hollywood Scene. Just a side note, in recent months I have landed a couple of film roles, small though they are, I may be making a bit of a come-back. One can always hope.  I am always asked how thatI have managed to squeeze all of this experience, knowledge and activities into my 42 years of living on thisPlanet. It's quite simplereally,Igave up sleeping long ago. Well, I sleep sometimes, but this propensity to "over-achieve" comes from theteachings of my beloved latePuerto Rican Jewish Parents who taught me thatthis world is a huge placeand full of opportunities for adventure, while life is tooshort. I learned that if I wanted to delve into the excitingthings that are out there for all of us to explore, I would have to work hard and sacrifice such luxuries as sleep and "me-time."Armed with thisrecipe for exhaustion,I have made it my goal to grow old without ever having thoughts of the things of life that I might wish  that I had done.  My hobbies include Flying Airplanes as a Private Pilot, Scuba Diving, Amateur Astronomy, Internet Surfing, and Amateur "Ham" Radio Operations. These also give me the abilities to report to you the latest from the Worlds of Aviation, Aeronautics,Astronomy, Aquanautics, Internet Activities and The Various Aspects of amateur Radio. This promises to make this BLOG one with something of interestfor all  readers.      
     

    
</post>
</Blog>