<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What a week it has been. First the belts on the car start slipping and need to be replaced ($185 at C Auto, money well spent), then I blow a rear strut mount, shattering the rear seatbelt retractor (replaced strut and mount myself for $115 + $36 in Canadian Tire money, plus 4hrs of my time). Now, after thinking that all is well, and the things are running just fine, my brakes give out on the way to work this morning (no price yet, still need to get it towed to the mechanics, I'm not driving it with no brakes...crazy yes, stupid.. NO ). This car has been an adventure...I wish I had kept my Intrepid...I think in the end it would have been more cost effective. While I've been calling my car Sparky (thanks to Napkins), I think it's time for a new name....The Purple Smurf. In honour of it being a small blue car that I would love to choke until it turns purple.   Today would also have been my 4thanneversary, had I still been married. Being the second year apart, it will be far easier to deal with. The two parties I'll be at tonight won't hurt either (until the hangover settles in). It will be good to have a drink with my co-workers after work today, and even better to see the old college gang later tonight for our annual pub night. E-Hugs from Boo have been helpful as well. She's such a sweetie, I'm incredibly glad that I met her.   In so many ways, I think that Boo and I have lived parallel lives. We're like two people who are so much alike in so many ways...of course we have our differences, but it just seems that we have a great deal in common, personalities, life experiences, and emotional outlooks. She is very close to my heart.   Through the past year or so, many things have changed in my life, and I'm glad to be able to say that for virtually every negative, there have been at least two positives. I have met some phenominal new people. Boo, Napkins, and Myst are the closest. They have all been such sweethearts. Boo for her free spirit, Napkins for her moral guidance, and Myst for her creative energy. Without them, I fear that I would be lost, or at least I wouldn't be having as much fun.   Okay, CAA has been called, and I have worked out a deal with C, I may once again get a vehicle that functions.....I hope. If it turns out that bad things happen in fours, the Purple Smurf is really going to earn it's new name.   The call has come in, needs new master and wheel cyls. More money than I have to spend, but it needs to be done. A car that goes is good, a car that also stops is better. The downside is that it won't be ready until tomorrow...oh well, at least I have a ride for tonights festivities. 
    
</post>
</Blog>