<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So here I am in San Jose at a tech forum which is cool. I have xanga but I've never used this and thought I would try it. 
    
</post>
<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I leave tomorrow, awesomeness. As for then I will not touch my normal xanga, I will write here. I lost it, a stupid piece of paper with my name and picture on it and you would have thought it was the end of the world if you were here yesterday. For the second day in a row I felt physically ill even though I knew I was fine, I thought I was going to throw up (the other day being 2 days ago after being asked about boys twice, I hate that my grandma's friends not knowing, but I dont know if she would be mad if she told. It becomes too much sometimes though, always lying through my teeth...it sucks) and I just laid on the floor trying to keep myself calm. I honestly don't know where it went...that is what bothers me so much. I didn't know it was gone but they keep saying I do. I'm sorry but some piece of paper wasn't on my mind. If it was in my room (which I honestly, whole heartedly, would tell Oniichan to her face (and I would never lie to her) don't think it was) it probably got lost in the big cleanup. Funny thing, if my room were still a mess things might be fine. I wanted to see Monica, but I didn't get to, which sucks I actually cried when she left I didn't want her to go and I wanted to say goodbye so bad. I cried about it last night...ya I'm lame I know. Oniichan is picking me up when I get home which makes me a super happy Sami, even happier that it was her idea ^_^ Well, take care all, and hope that some lame baby doesnt throw up on me (my dad told me about it...ughhhh...my liking for babies/little kids has died very quickly in the last year or so and that didnt help lol) ~Sami 
    
</post>
<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I found a safety pin! Hehe, just thought I would mention that.I got hit on in the elevator going to breakfast -_- how annoying is that. Anyway just went out and found another one of the Starbucks around hehe, yay. It's kinda cold right now though.So first we went to see this speaker this last night who was talking about using biology to make new technology (Dr.Full was his name I believe) it was actually really interesting and entertaining. Then we had a tech talk meeting...there are only 3 girls in my group and from what I heard that is how all the other groups are. We had fun though there is one other person from San Diego there. Lots of Texans too, hm. Anyway today we have a speaker from Nasa, site visits, and seminars wow. If I can I'll drop a line at dinner but I need to email Oniichan and she comes first :p I wish she were here should would like this a lot. My bed has 4 pillows lol I got buried in them last night. I went to breakfast this morning it will pretty good, I like having to walk to everything sometime I want to check out the workout room it's on the same floor as my room. Well I'm going to go back to my room and read some stuff we have to read by tonight and I'll check in later~Sami 
    
</post>
<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I found a safety pin! Hehe, just thought I would mention that.  I got hit on in the elevator going to breakfast -_- how annoying is that.  Anyway just went out and found another one of the Starbucks around hehe, yay. It's kinda cold right now though.  So first we went to see this speaker this last night who was talking about using biology to make new technology (Dr.Full was his name I believe) it was actually really interesting and entertaining. Then we had a tech talk meeting...there are only 3 girls in my group and from what I heard that is how all the other groups are. We had fun though there is one other person from San Diego there. Lots of Texans too, hm. Anyway today we have a speaker from Nasa, site visits, and seminars wow. If I can I'll drop a line at dinner but I need to email Oniichan and she comes first :p I wish she were here should would like this a lot. My bed has 4 pillows lol I got buried in them last night. I went to breakfast this morning it will pretty good, I like having to walk to everything sometime I want to check out the workout room it's on the same floor as my room. Well I'm going to go back to my room and read some stuff we have to read by tonight and I'll check in later ~Sami 
    
</post>
<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi all!Just blowing time before my meeting at 7. Ok so I was majorly annoyed this morning. After the huge (and I mean huge) deal made about it the guy couldn't have cared less about my stupid card. He hardly looked at it! After all the stress that has come out of it I wanted him to atleast say something, but noo it didn't matter. That darn paper has made my last days at home very unpleasant I am sooooo happy to be here now. This place is hugeeee. My roommate is one of the few girls I met right after I got off the plane yay. There are more guys than girls here, blah. I didn't know we could leave the hotel but we have a BIG area outside of it where we are aloud to go which rocks. Had dinner at the Fairmont it was good so I was happy lol. They have flat panel moniters here! I want one! *sob* I need safety pins, these shirts I got dont have top buttons &gt;</post></Blog>