<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
        This is NOT from McGregors. But I thought banner was a nice touch…   Hi all. I don’t know about you but these 36-hour lecture sessions are beginning to wear deep into my brain. Sunday after I left, I was standing in the parking lot at Broadacres, and at least a dozen people came and stood behind me and looked up to see what I was staring at.   Entrepreneur Assignment  I don’t know if I’m the only one who didn’t get the assignment brief. It apparently came amidst a stack of accounting lecture notes. If there are any of you who didn’t get all the relevant information, please let me know, so I can take it up with GIBS. I think distribution of course notes needs to be more reliable. Unless it’s just me with my head in the clouds.   OD  No one picked up on the obvious solution to Mandla’s debate around race, the oak tree and the fruit orchard relocation. What is required is to change the white oak at the top otherwise everything goes pear shaped. Are you nuts?   Theme Song  I seem to have managed to have touched Steve and Mandla in the recent performances. I’m not sure how badly that will affect my results for these two courses. The lyrics are attached. Knock yourselves out. The performance time of the theme song seems to have worked well at 1:45, so we’ll inculcate that into our cultural pear shaped oak tree. And to those of you who were disappointed you didn’t get an impromptu performance - apart from rapidly rehearsing the theme song two minutes before gong live, I never see my guitar. Believe me, it was for your own good. And I prefer not to throw my name away when I’m sober. One good thing has come out of all this - I’ve found a number of musicians hiding in the pine forests who wish to remain anonymous. So don’t worry Lisa &amp;amp; Pieter – your secret’s safe. Pieter will be joining me on Electric Guitar next time, right, Piet.  Sam (now appointed my manager) had a suggestion to make a medley of all the songs we wrote on the first ‘getting to know you’ week. Please will each group send me the words and the tune your song was based on. I’ll work something out. Theme song suggestions, lines, phrases, tunes or even just a word or two can be dropped in my hand any time. Or emailed to me – it’s becoming a much more collaborative thing. I could do with a drummer and a keyboard player (not QWERTY, ok!)   Network News  This rag seems to at least be read by most of us, so I’m suggesting we make it a networking medium too. Share information about your company’s activities, strategic partnerships or resources you’re looking for and so forth. I’m sure I’m not the only one who wants to get my message across.   No news is still no news  There’s still no sizzling gossip, news of promotion, success stories or anything interesting about our colleagues to publish. Reporters or snitches required. Apply within.   And the coffee machine  Still on the trail of nailing the right person to make the arrangements with @ Gibs – been moved from Linda to Derek – let’s hope. You can always hope.  My boss is breathing down my neck, and he has halitosis, so enjoy singing in the car:   Oh where is the music…     This really enrertaining newsletter was created by Adam Rabinowitz Email:  urlLink adam@alexanderfrances.co.za  Website:  urlLink www.alexanderfrances.co.za    
     
    
</post>
<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       We’re gonna rock this country – Shenaia Twain   (c) Adam Rabinowitz   I woke up this morning and my market share had taken a dive Yesterday was 70% , today it was five So I filled the boardroom with every executive, every manager, every soul I said “make sure your UIF’s paid up, because tomorrow you’ll be on the dole”  I said come on, come on Let’s to do something now I said if we don’t we’ll be eviscerated, disemboweled  We’re gonna rock This company We’re gonna drop The oogklappies Break down every wall, pull out all the stops From the beverage distributor right up to the top We’re gonna rock This company Right out of this hole  Oooh, we’re burning platforms beneath our feet Oooh, if we don’t we’ll all be on the street  I created a vision to get the urgency across to the masses I said imagine a line, and on that line is every one of your asses Now imagine that line is a fuse, and on the other end is a stick of dynamite You get the picture, there’s work to do, and our deadlines are pretty tight  Come on, we need A cross functional team If you’ve read the case You’ll know just what I mean  We’re gonna rock This company We’re gonna rock Is’t nie so nie Get a coalition, get a cross functional team Create short term wins, before everyone screams We’re gonna Rock This company Right out of this hole  Oooh, Emanual from pola park, looks like the police! Oooh, Mandla gets white socks from woolies  Here we go … (guitar bass run)  We had a presentation from Cadbury’s Peter Bester He didn’t bring a chocolate, not a sample, not a tester You know us MBA’s want to know , what’s in it for me Next I want to hear from the head of SAB  We’re gonna rock This company We’re gonna rock This company From Aircon Ant to Projection Piet Just remember Syndicate 11’s been split  We’re gonna rock This company Right out of this hole  Oooh, size does count, just ask Charmaine Oooh, If I mention Lisa’s name, will she go bright red again Oooh – if we’re good, we’ll end early Oooh – It looks like that’s it for OD 
     
    
</post>
<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       “Complicated”  (Avril Levign) - reworked   (c) Adam Rabinowitz   Work out what to sell it for          Did you do your maths before     Change from absorption base,     To a variable set                         What you measure, you get.         You’re at the Business Flight Deck now   You’ve got to make it work somehow     Who’s read the case, tell me Can anyone                                         Answer question 3?                               Ask Somebody else                              Try anyone else                                   So much in my head                            I haven’t prepared             Ask the pony tail brigade                      Maybe they have made A dent                                                           Tell me Why has all this stuff got to be so          complicated You do the steps                                  Take your company’s value chain and     disaggregate it                                             Every time you                                     You take, and you break You split then you crit                          Then check your results and say ‘‘Oh shit’, And by the time you quit it’s whiskey intravenously you’re takin’ Oh uh-uh  Close your sandwich shop, it’s a wrap Don’t spend your millions on SAP It’s things like that that made my hair-archy Turn silver, see    The point I’m making here is this A gun held to your head won’t miss Is Jean du Randt in here? No, he’s not He passed last year   Ask somebody else Ask anyone else If I have to choose Which of us will lose What I’m gonna do Is say “Better it’s you Thank me!”  tell me First you got to ask yourself “What is the decision you’re makin?” You see the way you’re Look into the toolbox to decide the tools you’re taking And then you’ve got to Absorb, and apply Estimate  It might work if you try your ABC and after you’re promoted you can buy A BM. Oh no, no.  If all this talk has made you weak And it’s an easy life you seek Don’t do your MBA Take your eighty grand And book a holiday  Chill out, exams are in two weeks With a few assignments inbetween What are we doing here We should be interviewing An Entrepreneur  Ask somebody else Ask anyone else I forgot where I was I think it was because The union’s on strike for Telkom to hike their pay  Tell me When did this MBA get so complicated You see the way we’re Always getting new text books gets me frustrated First you’ve got to Unlock and Unpack The you cram for exams But if you get it right, What a fat salary you’ll be raking Oh. Oh, oh!   
     
    
</post>
</Blog>