<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       "O uísque é o melhor amigo do homem. É o cachorro engarrafado." ( Vinícius de Moraes )      "Bebo para tornar as outras pessoas interessantes." ( George Jean Nathan )      "Na realidade, basta um drinque para me deixar mal. Mas nunca sei se é o 13ºou o 14º." ( George Burns )      "Nas vitórias, é merecido, mas nas derrotas é necessário."( Napoleão,sobre o champanhe )      "Nunca confie num homem que não bebe." ( Provérbio escocês )      "A penicilina cura os homens, mas é o vinho que os torna felizes."( Alex Fleming, inventor da penicilina )      "Uma cozinha sem saca-rolhas é apenas um cômodo a mais na casa." ( Keith Floyd )      "O álcool não faz as pessoas fazerem as coisas melhores. Ele faz com que elas fiquem menos envergonhadas de fazê-las mal." ( William Osler )      "Se for para morrer de batida, que seja de limão." ( Anônimo )      "Eu aproveitei mais o álcool do que ele se aproveitou de mim." ( Winston Churchill )      "Era um homem sábio aquele que inventou a cerveja." ( Platão )      "Quando li sobre os problemas que a bebida causa, deixei de ler." ( Henny Youngman )      "Se Deus soubesse que nós beberíamos cerveja, nos teria dado dois estômagos." ( David Daye )      "A cerveja é a prova viva de que Deus nos ama e nos quer ver felizes." ( Benjamin Franklin )      "Eu bebo quando tenho ocasião e às vezes quando não tenho ocasião."( Miguel de Cervantes )      "Podem me chamar de bêbado, pois vou negar até a última dose!!!" ( Conde de Bicardin )      "Bebe! Pois não sabes de onde vieste, nem por quê. Bebe! Pois não sabes para onde vais." ( Omar Khayam )      "Vinte e quatro horas no dia, 24 cervejas em uma caixa...Coincidência?"( Stephen Wright )      "Faça sempre lúcido o que você disse que faria bêbado. Isso o ensinará a man ter sua boca fechada." ( Ernest Hemingway )      "Algumas vezes quando reflito acerca de toda a cerveja que já bebi, e me sinto envergonhado. Mas logo vejo além do copo e penso nos trabalhadores da cervejaria e seus sonhos e esperanças.Se eu não bebesse esta cerveja,eles poderiam perder seus trabalhos e todos os seus sonhos veriam-se desfeitos.Portanto eu digo, "É melhor que eu beba esta cerveja permitindo que seus sonhos se tornem realidade do que eu seja egoísta e me preocupe com meu fígado." ( Jack Handy )      "Algumas vezes um homem inteligente é forçado a ficar bêbado para passar um tempo com os burros." ( Ernest Hemingway )      "Quando bebemos, ficamos bêbados. Quando ficamos bêbados,dormimos.Quando dormimos não cometemos pecados.Quando não cometemos pecados vamos para o céu...Portanto, vamos ficar bêbados para ir ao céu!!!" ( Brian O'Rourke )        E ESSA É A MELHOR...MENSAGEM PUBLICITÁRIA EM UM A CERVEJA DA NORUEGA  : "Ajudando as feias a fazer sexo desde 1862"         
     
    
</post>
<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
        BCL     (To be typed on Bank Letterhead)       Date:     To: Transaction Reference: Purchase of___________________________________    Dear Sirs:     In providing this capability letter, we (name of the bank) do not assume any financial liability or any contractual relationship with parties. We certify only that (client name) has the credit, or the financial capacity to initiate the transaction indicated above. Should our client wish to do so.    Transaction in amount of approximately (total transaction amount in US Dollars)          (Bank officers # 1 signature)                                     (Bank officers # 2 signature)    ______________________                                        _____________________    Bank officer name and title                                       Bank officer name and title       ABA number:                                        Bank contact person: (English speaking)    Swift number:                                        Telephone:    Telex:    Fax:       Buyer information   Account name:    Legal Name:    Address:    Contact Person: (English speaking)                            Tel:    Fax:     (Bank Seal)    **********************************************************************************   In order to minimize misunderstanding and enable us to furnish a quick and proper quote, please in future ensure that the following information is provided when a quote is requested for: 1. whether LC will be a SLC, DLC or ARLC.    2. whether LC will be transferable and issued or confirmed by a top 25 world prime bank in US or Europe    So following information is requested:   ==== Commodity with EXACT Specification   ==== Total Quantity   ==== Destination with Unloading Port -   ==== Discharge quantity and rates (if available)   ==== Shipments   ==== Payment   ==== LC will cover each shipment or the total amount?Also we need your target price not to waste your and our time I thank you for your support to conclude this deal for our all benefits.     
     
    
</post>
<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
           (LOI)            (LETTER OF INTENT/IRREVOCABLE PURCHASE ORDER COMPLETED ON LETTERHEAD OF CONTRACT SIGNATORY.)    Date of Issue: DD/MM/YY       THE UNDERSIGNED_______________OF____________HEREBY STATE AND REPRESENT THAT IT IS OUR CORPORATE INTENTION TO PURCHASE THE COMMODITY _________IN THE QUANTITY AND FOR THE PRICE AS SPECIFIED IN THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS AS STATED BELOW.       THIS REPRESENTATION IS MADE WITH FULL CORPORATE AUTHORITY AND ALSO RESPONSIBILITY OF THE ABOVE STATED BUYER.       COMMODITY:    ORIGIN:    SPECIFICATIONS:    QUANTITY:    PACKAGING:    DELIVERY SIZE AND SCHEDULE:    MODE OF PAYMENT:    TARGET PRICE:    DESTINATION PORT DISCHARGE RATE PER DAY:    INSPECTION:    GUARANTEE:    DOCUMENTS:        BUYERS INFORMATION    COMPANY NAME/ADDRESS:    CITY/ZIP/COUNTRY:    COMPANY TEL/FAX:    LEGAL REPRESENTATIVE:    NAME/TITLE:       BUYER BANK COORDINATES BANK NAME/ADDRESS:    CITY/ZIP/COUNTRY:    BANK TEL/FAX:    BANK TELEX/SWIFT CODE:    BANK OFFICERS NAME/TITLE/DIRECT TEL/FAX:    ACCOUNT NAME/NUMBER:      CONFIRMING BANK COORDINATES:    BANKS NAME/ADDRESS:    CITY/ZIP/COUNTRY:    INT.L TRADE DEPT. TEL/FAX:    BANK OFFICERS NAME/TITLE/DIRECT TEL/FAX:         SIGNATURE:     PRINTED NAME: (CORPORATE SEAL)     TITLE:     NOTE: ALL REQUESTED INFORMATION MUST BE PROVIDED IN FULL DETAIL.      
     
    
</post>
<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
         EXW -  Ex WorksA delivery term where the Seller's only responsibility is to make goods available at his own premises. He has no responsibility for loading  the goods. The Buyer bears the full cost and risk in transporting the goods from there to the final destination.         FAS -  Free Alongside ShipThe Seller's obligations are filled as soon as the goods have been placed alongside the ship on the quay. The Buyer bears all costs and risks from then on.         FCA -  Free Carrier (Named Point)The Seller's obligation is met when the goods are transfered into the custody of the Carrier, at the Named Point. The risk transfers from Seller to Buyer at this point. "CARRIER" is defined as "any person by whom or in whose name a  contract of carriage by road, rail air sea or a combination of mo des has been made".         FOB -  Free On BoardThe goods are put on board the ship by the seller at the Port of shipment named in the contract. The risk transfers to the Buyer as the goods pass over the ship's rail at the Port of loading.         CFR -  Cost  FreightThe Seller pays the cost  freight of the goods to the named Port of destination. The risks are the Buyer's responsibility from when the goods pass over the ship's rail at the Port of loading.         CIF -  Cost Insurance  FreightSimilar to CFR but here it is the Seller's duty to arrange all the insurance on behalf of the Buyer and pay the premium.         CIP -  Carriage  Insurance Paid To (Named Destination)The Seller now has to obtain Insurance to cover all riks to the Named Destination.         CPT -  Carriage Paid ToThe Seller pays the freight for the carriage of the goods to the named destination. The risk transfers to the Buyer when the goods are in the custody of the first carrier.         DAF -  Delivery At Frontier (To Named Place)The Seller's obligations end when the goods have arrived at the Frontier but before entering the Customs process at the Country named in the contract.         DDP -  Delivered Duty PaidThe most obligation to the Seller, who is required to pay all charges involved in delivering the goods to the Buyer.         DDU -  Delivered Duty UnpaidThe Seller pays all costs involved in delivering the goods to the Buyer, with the exception of import duty, taxes and any other official charges levied at importation.         DES -  Delivered Ex ShipThe Seller's responsibility for all charges to deliver the goods to the Port of destination named in the contract. The risk transfers to the Buyer onboard ship.         DEQ -  Delivered Ex Quay (Duty Paid)The Seller makes the goods available to the Buyer on the quay at the port of destination named in the c ontract the risk transfers to the Buyer then. (Duty On Buyers Account) In this variation the liability to clear the goods for import are met by the Buyer."It is recommended that the full description is used to avoid misunderstandings. Do not rely on "Ex Quay" on its own".                  
     
    
</post>
<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
          Luna Serena   urlLink http://looking4somelight.blogspot.com/   
     
    
</post>
</Blog>