<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Chorus: Trapped inside this dark place I can’t see the light at the end of the tunnel. What lies in front is all that I fear, it creeps over me like its my own shadow  No one is here with me only the haunting memory of my past it hangs over my head like a poisoned moon. Only it shatters over me leaving me as a rotting corpse.  A sheet of darkness has come over me I broke what only faith I had I flushed it out of me it covers only my weakened soul.  Here tonight I will conquer all the odds I will rise back from the grave making my name known. If I could just get one foot out of the door but my feet are so heavy and my past is weighing down on me I think only of myself and my heart starts to collapse when nothing good comes from my mind.  What’s my mind been up to? It is no longer apart of me soiled enough from the shades of the world. I can’t turn myself around, fallen too far down the rabbit hole what’s left is only an image of what people see me as. 
     

    
</post>
<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Shadows falling down As the sun creeps away And starts to drown The other side of the world They suddenly disappear The only thing left is black The skyscraper lights Illuminate the city and Keeps us unafraid of the dark Many different colors Fulfilling our lives They create a painting in our reality Showing us rays of a rainbow Blowing away our sorrows and Causing us to forget our days But each morning you wake up And you start your day anew You find that it’s so hard to see The difference you can make Forgetting the pain of yesterday Will show that sunrise once more The one that brings hope Where everything becomes a dream And keeps us fueled for the long road ahead Where brighter things will come your way And challenges shall await you You must never look back You must never look back Because this day belongs to you Take your paintbrush and paint your sunrise too Take your paintbrush and paint your sunrise too 
     

    
</post>
<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I can get used to this, the sweet goodbyes, the soft kisses. I am twisted up inside only you know how to smooth me out. The night is young where shall we go to be alone with just you and me together. The moon lights up your face and it lights up my heart when I look in your eyes.  Chorus: Can this universe be made for 2 perfect lovers? Can it stand the test of time? Or are you just a dream?  You and I have had our share of challenges, I only can’t wait to face the next one with you. All I have to do is dream and we sail together right into the sunset, we are launched into somewhere not quite real.  Are you just a dream? Are you just a dream? Oh. If you are then how are you in my living color? It comes to me that I only see you when I rest my head on the pillow case, its there where I am truly awake. 
     

    
</post>
<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Day by day things may change or stay the same, but if you look far away enough the grass is greener on the other side. Don’t look down, find something to lean on but know I can be your shelter, your raincoat when skies look cloudy, and when you find yourself tumbling down you can hop on a train and come to me.  Unpack your things and stay for a while. Embrace the feelings of being home, these chances but come 3 times a year. You got Christmas time and Easter morning and waking up in your own room for the first day of summer. Smelling the smells you knew as a kid. The hometown has changed but seeing the friendly faces makes you know you’re home.  When you’re feeling sad and nothing seems to come your way I’m just one call away from you coming to me. It’s easier when the wind is at your back your sails can be hoisted and you can be made ready to face the world again its true coming to me will give you that final push you need. 
     

    
</post>
<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I cancer vive come into your body there to thrive, hide in your deepest  corners to torment you. I cancer vive without your help will crumble, sleepless night can seem like a nightmare. Am I awake am I dreaming? Chances are I’ll make to see tomorrow but I cancer vive will not be beaten. Your strongest will can give its best shot but you know better than that.  A battle ground where fate’s soldiers fight an epic war inside of me. A place no where to run, out in the open. If I won’t survive than someone’s going down with me, but friends and family may come to your aid, I’m so scared I don’t know where to turn, and when I look up at the clouds they look like the devil’s pitchfork now, what more can’t I ask of you I think.  Back to when I cancer vive will fall if not climb higher down, down back to the top where you can’t reach me, if you try hard enough you’ll just lose your strength when it seems you’re trying to tackle a sound. 
     

    
</post>
<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Going to a big city not seeing any familiar places, I’m lost in the lights in the city that never sleeps. I am suffocated by so many people am I just a dot on the map, you can’t see me from an airplane so what do I need to do to make my mark on the world. Just let it flow give it a go. I’m on my own no one is twistin my arm I’m paying my dues. The sleepless nights sometimes get to me but I’m seeing the hills from my window and I know if I rest my head on the pillow I’ll be there I’ll be living a happy ending.  Interlude  Makin my way across the country seeing the things my eyes have always wanted to see. My ears hear for the first time the quiet sounds of rural life. I know what I am and that’s looking down from my own airplane I’m flying high, high than my dreams can lift me, through the sky with nothing above me. I am ready to go, I better fasten my seatbelt because, darkened clouds are coming but I’m so ready for what ever decides to make a straight line with my destiny, we’ll see if I become somebody. 
     

    
</post>
<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      We’re gathered all around just havin some fun tonight. Its our day off and its time to put up our feet. We’re all best friends and I don’t want this to end. Its Friday night and let’s say we live it up.  Chorus: Let’s take this life for a spin and find out where it goes. See the twists and turns, and bumpy roads to make it all worthwhile. When we’re low on gas we sure know where to fill ourselves.  Who knows where we’ll end up but what we know is we didn’t let anything bring us down. I don’t wanna be another has been. Where to next lets hit the road and never look back.  I’m throwing my chips all in thinking I’m gonna win big. I’m takin a chance there’s nothing holding me back. I’m gonna use my wild cards, and then I gonna take the jackpot and see what’s in store for me. 
     

    
</post>
<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Times have changed and I’m stuck in this rut. There’s a void growing inside of my heart. It longs for you but I know that you aren’t coming back, you were takin away, what’s left to say?  Chorus: I hope I’m everything you wanted me to be, it shouldn’t have turned out this way. My road is now weary since you’ve been gone, and I can no longer stand on my own two feet.  When I’m lost for you, my heart winces when I see a picture of you. My mind is numb and the worries of the day now seem so small.  I need help carrying on, but no one is here to pick me up. Your grave is all I have left of you. Since you’ve gone, I don’t know how to be.  Putting one foot in front of the other is something I can no longer do. Since you’ve been gone I can’t remember the way you talked. You are leaving me, since you’re gone. 
     

    
</post>
<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I travel down this never-ending road Thinking I know where I’m going But I can’t see what’s in front of me An unavoidable tragedy  I must be mistaken to think that I could have been someone Now I know how it feels to have your luck run out And have not a clue what life is about  This turn of events I did not intend It’s too soon to be at a dead end Time has now passed me by Since my life has become such a lie  Oh dear friends of mine I have to go When I see you again I’ll say hello This promise I could never break I won’t make the same mistake  If I had a goal in mind It would remain a puzzle Figuring it out would be Too long for a lifetime  I have nothing else to lose or gain My life has gone down the drain It’s doubtful that I actually meant Something to the world  Of dear friends of mine I have to go When I see you again I’ll say hello This promise I could never break I won’t make the same mistake 
     

    
</post>
<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Way back when we used to play by the docks, and stare aimlessly at the stars we were up to our necks with some big eyed fish, and then we’d call it a day and go to celebrate.  Chorus: its a place where I can go to dream. it’s a place where everything is free. I never wanna leave this place again, in fear that when I return everything has changed  I’ve traveled several miles, I’ve seen Many things, but none gives me the feeling Of my home sweet home, it’s a place where we can share and laugh, it’s a place where all my dreams come true   I hope my dreams come true in other places, the big ones, you see in movies, I want that, but for now I’ll settle down and go back to my special place.  My feet splash all up on the wood its gets all soggy for maybe the last time. The sun falls down behind the trees, and its time to leave “so long” and pack up my things. I guess this is goodbye, it sure looks that way, until next time. 
     

    
</post>
<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      A day gone by or taken away, the rain is pouring and we’re stuck inside, just waiting for the sky to clear up and bring something new. For better or for worse, it’s comin to me.  Chorus: Each day has a new beginning, a story to be told; now I’m thinking did I make the best of what came my way? I used to have a plan and I’m gonna see it through to its conclusion.  The way I see it my glass is always half full. If I’m running on empty someone’s always there to fill me up.  Bridge: I get stuck worrying about the small things, the big things just pass me by. I only look two feet in front of me and I can’t see through all of the raindrops.  The clouds have gone away now, its time to play outside. How meaningless was it to worry if it was ever going to clear up? Its raining on someone somewhere else now, but I hope not on their parade. I hope their glass gets filled up by the rain that just filled mine. 
     

    
</post>
</Blog>