<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just uploading some pictures now that I finally got my computer working right again. I've promised them to some people and I'm trying to make good on that. Right now it's focusing on where we live and our QRF (Quick Reactionary Force). I have some more pictures of conditions outside the wire and of the people and college but I have to get them cut down in size first. I'm also trying to get Professor Ali (mentioned in the article below) to be able to write up a small article about his experiences when he was back in the States. Hope you enjoy.     This is probably the highlight of people's time in Iraq. It means they are going home on leave for 15 days. Probably one of the only times we don't mind waiting around in the sound.     This is a collection of trucks that our QRF uses. As you can see they are all mostly cargo vehicles that have been heavily modified with 1/2 thick steel plating. Since the Army didn't seem it neccesary at the time we moved into Baghdad to think that all vehicles would need some armor protection our welders did it themselves. The LMTV (big truck =) ) has over 2 tons of steel added to it. While its not perfect its better than nothing.  The vehicle to the right is a M1114. Its the standard patrol vehicle for our Brigade in Baghdad. Once you put a .50 machine gun on top its not something you want to mess with. Too bad we only have one.     This is one of our QRF teams waiting to be called out. While not overly active on combat patrols they do provide a pretty damn important job of escorting our of our officers outside the wire and help a lot with getting the goodwill projects done around here. We couldn't do it without them. For reference there are 18 people on the team.     Finally is a small view of our lifestyle. I think there are close to 3000 of these trailers on Victory. This place is huge. We recently got blast protection in the form of these HESCO barriers. Its a nice touch about 6 months too late.  Thanks for looking today. Hope to get some more up soon when I'm not so busy. Good luck to everyone. 
    
</post>
<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sorry I haven't been around much recently but I have been really busy and working quite long hours. Everything here unfortently seems like things are heating up a bit. The frequency of attacks against US forces is increasing and I hope this isn't a sign of stuff that will be coming soon.  On a slightly different note I know I promised some more pictures to some people and I hope to be able to fulfill that request within the next day or so. The internet has been crawling over here and I have barely been able to even browse the web much less upload any pictures. So hopefully that will happen here soon.  Our commander is currently stuck in Jordan and on his way back from the States. Following is a somewhat long a</post></Blog>