<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Nick Halloway grinned into the wind as he drove his red Mustang through town. Top down, of course, so his highlighted blond hair could catch some breeze. He felt high from his victory in court. He’d been right, and he proved it. After stopping by his apartment to change, he now sped to see his cousin at the Halloway Estate.  His summer trip here to Oregon turned into a move. Nick had instantly liked Portland, where people knew the Halloways and respected them. And the summer weather was nice with daytime temperatures staying between eighty and ninety degrees. Shadows now tilted and a cool breeze blew as it neared four pm.  At the gate to his uncle‘s house, a voice greeted him by name and let him in. “Go on in the house, everyone’s out back by the pool.”  Yeah, he liked this life. Inside he headed down to the basement to pick up his sports jacket that he’d left the last time he visited. The door was shut so he raised his hand to knock.  “Ummph!” At the sound, Nick paused outside the door.  “Hello?” No one answered him. Slowly, he turned the handle, opened the door, and took one step into the room. A shove from behind and a kick to his shins sent him falling forward. He groaned as he hit the floor and then wondered what brought him there. The person whipped him over, jumped on his midsection, and held a bronze statue of an eagle in flight over his head.  “Whoa, girl!” He held up his hands, shocked this little woman had knocked him down for fast.  “Who are you?” Her dark blond hair hung everywhere like a fountain around her face, but her crystal blue eyes still blazed out at him.  “I’m Nick, who the heck are you?” She sat up straighter to study him. A minute later, she answered.  “Cora Evans. Why are you here if you don’t know about me?”  “I’m visiting the family. And you? Why are you hiding in their basement?”  “They stuck me here!” She followed his eyes to the weapon in her hand. Cora set it down with a thump to the side of him. “Are you armed?”  “No, what do you take me for?”  “A thug like the family upstairs.” Her eyes moved over his face, and he hoped she concurred with the other women who’d shared their opinion of his appearance. This Cora Evans sure was hot. Nice, full lips, cute nose and little eyebrows. Nick raised his eyebrows at her statement so she’d explain. “They accused my father of stealing from them. But he didn’t! Now they got me in here so he’ll go get their money.”  He had to shake his head, wondering if maybe she’d hit him before. “Are you serious? Or on drugs?”  “I’ve been down here two days.” The corners of his mouth had been lifted in a cocky half smile, but now his face sobered. “But . . .”  “But what? Are you going to help me or not?”  The smile flickered back on, “You’re really turning me on.” He pushed his hips against her, then laughed as she flew up to her feet with a red face. Cora grabbed up the statue again, so Nick leaped to his feet as well. “Hey, I can’t help you if you knock me out.”   Wow, the man was tall. Cora Evans stepped back, and then casually set the statue down again. Folding her arms, she said, “So you’ll get me out of here.”  “Uhhh . . .” He checked her out, elevator style, and forgot to answer.  “Never mind, you probably couldn’t get me out of here anyway.” Mr. Movie-Star-Good-looks wasn’t much help. But he’d unwittingly unlocked the door for her.  “Wait, Cora. It’s Cora, right?”  “Oh, good grief. I’ll see you later.” She stepped out, but her grabbed her shoulder.  “You won’t get far. Not with the cameras, the locked front gate, and the guards watching it.” Cora looked down at his hand on her and back to his face. Nick looked like a limber quarterback, one with a healthy tan that wasn’t too dark. His hazel eyes didn’t go with his attitude because they looked warm and caring. “How can you get me out of here?”  “What do I get if I do?”  “Excuse me?”  “A date. I get you out of here and you go on a date with me.”  Her expression went sour, then laughing. “I have to find my father.”  “Hmm. We’ll get to that after we get out of here.” He took her hand and headed upstairs. “My car’s in the garage. I’ll hide you in back and leave.”  Great, she thought a minute later when “in back” turned out to be the trunk. Nick gave her a wicked grin as he shut the hood. Maybe she’d gone from a dangerous situation to something much worse. No, anything had to be better than being trapped in that house, not knowing what they’d do to her.  Several minutes later, Nick stopped and helped her out so she could join him up front. New car smell mixed with leather and pine, adding to the luxury already projected by the interior of the car. Pulling on a pair of designer sunglasses, Nick looked like he fit. Cora didn’t feel like she did.  “Thanks.” I think.  He laughed, “Sounds like that was hard to say.” The guy did have a nice laugh that sounded rich and light at the same time.  “Well, you’re usually the type of person I avoid.”  “Prejudices aside, tell me about your father.”  Cora looked out the side of the car to hide her smile. But when she started to look back, she caught his face in the side view mirror, with a smirk on it. Darn him. Nick said, “You look good in my car. Long hair like yours goes with it.”  “Maybe I make the car look good.” Oh, brother! She sounded like him already. “Listen, my father’s out there somewhere, trying to find a million dollars to repay Keith Halloway.”  “How’d your father steal that much money?” Nick glanced over. She started to wonder how he drove straight when he kept looking at her. Not that her eyes were on the road, but her hands weren’t on the wheel. Cora liked how he kept his hair long. Oh yeah, his question.  “He didn’t. I know he wouldn’t do something like that. His name is Jerry Evans and he’s been Keith’s top accountant for ten years. He has assistants, but he oversees the hotels’ accounting and Keith’s personal finances.”  “Doesn’t sound like you know much about him.”  “Keith? What does that mean?” She leaned closer to hear over the wind’s noise. While it was true, he seemed to be saying he knew a great deal more than her.  “Well, there are things I’m not supposed to acknowledge because I’m a lawyer. But I guess I’ll tell you the hotels are a front for their real business.” His openness about it shocked her. Drugs? She didn’t want to know. But she did want to know more about Nick. “How do you know him again?”  “Well. …” Oh no. Cora held her breath. “He’s technically my uncle.”  “What?” She grabbed the door handle. “Stop the car!” Nick pulled over, but she didn’t jump out.  Looking self assured, he asked, “Didn’t think I would, did you? Now what?”  “I can’t trust you.”  Nick turned and looked behind them, stretched and looked over her head, then out his side.  “You know, I don’t see anyone else around here to help you.” When he turned back to her, Cora narrowed her eyes at him. “Ok, ok. Where’s your father?”  She told him what she knew: pretty much nothing, and he suggested she call Jerry on his cell. Cora asked, “You think Keith let him keep it?” Keith’s name made her shudder as she remembered his self-inflicted ugliness caused by his always angry eyes and oversized gray mustache. After spending two days in his basement, she never wanted to see the man again.  “Keith will need a way to get a hold of Jerry to exchange the money, and to keep track of him.” She took the cell phone Nick offered and dialed her father’s number.  “Cora? Thank God, did you get out of there?”  “Yes, where are you?”  “Be careful what you say, Cora. And watch your back. Meet me at your mom’s favorite diner.” They ended the call and she told Nick.  “I haven’t been to the Restaurante Del Mar since before my mother died.”  Nick’s head jerked her way. “How old were you?”  His sincere question, and his softened eyes, made her want to answer. “Eight.”  “I was six when my mom died of cancer.”  Now her head jerked over. “Are you lying?”  His brows came together. The guy had a nice profile, but she couldn’t think about that now. He said, “Why would I say that? Who would want to lie about something like that?”  “Sorry . . . it’s just that my mom had cancer, and it seemed . . .” When she never finished, he left it alone. He glanced over, not smirking or laughing this time.  “Forgot to look at that part?” She spoke, and then closed her eyes in embarrassment. “I’m sorry.” But he was grinning.  “Everything’s nice.”  Was that a compliment? “Ok, we’re pretty close, aren’t we?” She remembered her father’s words and checked the mirrors, then looked around. Of course, she didn’t know how to spot anyone following them. Nick used the ally to pull around behind an adjacent building, and they used the side door to enter. Cora spotted her father’s salt and pepper hair. He watched the door through his black rimmed glasses. “Over there.”  Nick walked beside her to the table. Jerry jumped to his feet, flight ready. “They sent someone with you? I thought you got away?”  “Hang on, Mr. Evans.” Nick held both hands out, palms up, to show he wasn’t a threat.  “Dad, he got me out of there.”  “You know who he is?”  “He said he’s Keith’s his uncle.” As she spoke, she had to ask herself again why she’d trusted him in the first place. Apparently she’d left her common sense back in Keith’s basement and now used a totally different sense to decide matters. Jerry eyed Nick, then Cora.  “I didn’t have a choice.”  “Thanks.” Nick grunted the word from behind her in a low tone that tickled its way down her neck. After glancing back at him briefly, she nodded to the booth. She slid in across from her father and they scooted to the wall. Nick sat on the end on Jerry’s side where he could watch the place. The waiter came, so he ordered something to keep their cover while Cora talked to her father.  “Dad, tell me everything so I can help get us out of this. Do you know who framed you?”  “Framed me?”  “You didn’t steal from your employer!”  “I’ve been doing the books for so long . . . I didn’t think anyone else ever looked at them.” Cora’s mouth dropped open at her father’s confession. He turned red in the following moment, quiet except for the soft Mexican music playing.  She fell back against the booth. “Now what?”  “I can’t get to the money, so I need your help.” She waited. “I put the money in a trust fund. In your name.”  “Dad!”  “Cora, I’m sorry. I still can’t believe they found out.”  “It’s wrong to steal, even if you’re stealing from someone corrupt themselves.”  “Are you going to help me or not?” His eyes pleaded, and she did feel for him, but her angry still burned.  “I guess I have to help myself since the money’s in my name. Why did you do that?” His shrug added to her anger. Jerry handed her a paper with the bank name and account number.  “Let’s stay clear of each other. You can get the money, and then maybe Nick can take it back.” Cora looked over at her newfound friend. “Wouldn’t that make him look guilty of something?”  Jerry shrugged. Boy, he wasn’t much help. “Nick, let’s get out of here.” They looked around when they stepped outside, then headed for the car.  “How much of that did you catch?” She asked him as they both shut their car doors.  He laughed, laughed in a time like this. “So your old man’s guilty as charged.”  Seeing her teeth showing in a snarl, he dropped the smile. “Sorry. It’s just funny because you strike me as being high on your morals.”  “Why’s that?”  His face got thoughtful. “Don’t know. Let’s just forget that. Where’s the money?”  Should she tell him this part? He looked over and touched her leg. “He put it in a trust fund in my name.”  Nick hooted a big, “Woo hoo!” and slapped the steering wheel.  “Don’t laugh too hard.” She wished she could reach out and slap him, but he was driving.  “Ok, let’s go to the bank.”  She turned in her seat to face him, “And what, ask for a million dollars?”  “It’s yours. But the banks are already closed today.”  Cora leaned her head back and closed her eyes, wishing all this felt more real so she could think clearly. They should have brought Jerry with them. That way she wouldn’t have to worry so much about him, and she’d have a chaperon.  She felt Nick’s hand on her leg again, but this touch wasn’t a nudge. He’d laid his palm flat on her thigh.  She cracked her eyes to look over. “Uh, excuse me.”  “Yes?”  “Your hand.”  Nick looked down at it like he didn’t understand her meaning. But, yes, he did.   He needed all of his will power not to smile at her response. “They’re so nice. Your legs.” Nick added for clarification and kept his hand there.  “I’m not going to sleep with you, if that’s why you’re helping me.”  Now he couldn’t help the smile. “I thought we agreed to a date.” He loved the confused look on her face and the pout on those coral colored lips. “If things take off, then that’s fine.”  “They’re not going to.”  Oh, he’d see about that.  “I look horrible.” He saw her words as in invitation and looked over at her clothing again. She wore Khaki shorts and a black tank top with spaghetti straps and a lacy design at the top. He let himself follow her legs down to her black sandals.  “Do you mind?”  “Mind? No, I like, if that’s what you mean.”  “Would you knock it off? I’ve been sitting in a basement for two days. I’m a wreck.” She folded her arms, pouting, and looked out the front window.  Had Keith sent any food down to her? He didn‘t think his uncle was ever sensitive to anyone. “Are you hungry?” He asked, and Cora looked like she had to think about it. “Not sure?”  “I think so.” She rubbed her temples then, and Nick felt bad for not doing something for her sooner. They’d rushed in and out of the Mexican restaurant earlier without eating. He changed directions and found a small hotel behind some other buildings. Cora opened her eyes and gave him an angry and disbelieving look.  “You can take a shower while I get some food.” He gleefully watched her face change, though he hid it. Point for him! He watched her sit in the car from inside the office while he paid for a room. The place wasn’t nice at all, but he didn’t think they’d be bothered here. Once they went inside their room, he said, “I planned on going out for something, but I don’t want to leave you alone.”  “Is ordering in safe?”  “Well, my name’s already on the room, so I don’t think it’ll matter. Besides, they don’t know I helped you. They won’t know to look for me.”  “I hope you’re right. I’m going to take a shower.” She went in the bathroom and locked the door.  Nick kicked back on the bed and folded his hands behind his head. Cora Evans. The woman was hot, and smart, and funny in an odd way. Even though he knew hardly anything about her, he kept getting stirring feelings inside him just by thinking about her, looking at her, smelling her. He vaguely remembered something from college about pheromones and how smell can affect you. Or was it hormones? Or both? Nick wasn’t into science because he studied law. But he felt something physical happen, and it wasn’t just attraction. Though he couldn’t deny that. Holy cow she did something to him.  She smiled a few times. He loved the way she’d tried to hide it. Somehow that made it even sexier.  Was that why he wanted to help her so badly? It didn’t feel like taking on a pro bono case for work. Usually he convinced people, but he didn’t ask for their trust. Yet he wanted Cora to trust him.   Cora stepped under the cool water, hoping to wash off the cigarette stench from Keith’s house. How was she supposed to figure out this mess with Nick out there? Instead of thinking about her money problem, she tried to decide if he was helping his family, or helping her just to get sex, or both, or maybe he really wanted to help her.  He was not relationship material. And she’d never, in her life, considered having sex just for the fun of it. She shouldn’t have thought about that word.  Cora stepped out of the shower without deciding anything and heard Nick answer the door. She smelled food and yanked her clothes back on. Then she slowly opened the door and stepped out, feeling funny with her hair in towel. She pulled it off, deciding wet hair was ok in the summer.  “Chinese ok?”  “Anything edible is good right now.” She usually didn’t stuff her face in front of other people, but Keith hadn’t been a gracious host. She remembered to say thank you several mouthfuls later. Nick tapped his fork in between bites, and for once he wasn’t watching her. Thank Heaven.  “So, how do we get the money back to Keith?”  Oh, she’d forgotten to tell him Jerry’s idea on that. “My dad thought maybe you could, but I thought it’d be better if Keith didn’t know you’re involved.”  Nick didn’t show an opinion about it. “First we need to get it.”  “I can’t walk in and expect it. They’ll probably need time.”  “For a cashiers check?” He suggested. That might work, she thought, because she didn’t know how to handle something like this.  “There’s only one way to find out.” She said, “I guess I’ll go in a branch tomorrow morning and close the account.” She glanced around the room, mainly at the one bed, and back at him. Those hazel eyes of his were bright with laughter again. They weren’t a uniform color, but browns and reddish browns mixed like flames in a fire.  When he licked his lips, she had to say, “I’m not checking you out, I just think you’re eyes are interesting.”  Her words put a sudden wide grin on his face, revealing his white teeth. “You think one part of me is interesting. That’s progress.”  Cora laughed, knowing she shouldn’t, but she couldn’t help it. “Why are you like this?”  “Why don’t you like it?”  “Oh, so women usually eat it up.”  Her comment didn’t slow him down. “Men don’t chase you around?”  “No. I don’t have time for that anyway.”  “Maybe you just didn’t look behind you to see all the guys drooling.”  Cora had to give it to him, he could sweet talk better than any guy she’d ever met. But his sweet talking couldn’t be anything more than that. So why was he helping her when he could obviously get a date with anyone?  Nick stood and picked up the empty boxes, handing her a fortune cookie. Another sweet gesture?  He dumped the boxes in the trash can and said, “I bet yours says, ‘You have a great opportunity tonight, don’t waist it.’”  “Oh brother.”  He paused where he was. “I’m sorry. Old habits break hard.”  Cora had to look away from him to say, “Can’t teach an old dog new tricks?”  “Now that was mean.” He’d taken a step and now stood a few feet from her. She thought about telling him she didn’t take opportunities like that, but knowing he’d practically offered made her tingle. Nick still didn’t move and she turned her head to see what he was doing. Her eyes slid up his body and then hit his eyes looking right back. Fire swept over her and consumed her, like an angry brush fire eating up dry twigs. The look in Nick’s eyes, and that one raised eyebrow, said more than any words he could have spoken. He boldly walked to her and took her hand, lightly holding her fingers. The gentle touch sent a physical reaction pumping though her as if he had pulled her body against him.  Staring up at him, she thought maybe she should pull her lips together and not give him such a come get me look. She couldn’t move, didn’t pull her hand from his grasp either. She didn’t tell him to back off. Instead she let him pull her to her feet, where she still had to look up at him. He leaned closer and kissed her softly on the lips. She searched his warm eyes, wondering if someone could fake that look.  “Cora.” His voice made her name sound like an exotic call. “I knew your name earlier, Cora Evans. I was just teasing.”  “When? Oh.” Right away she threw him on the floor. He brushed his lips across hers again, then stepped closer, applying more pressure. She clutched his shirt, feeling dizzy with delight when his mouth slightly parted.  Push him away, she thought, but instead kissed him back. He made a sound like hmmm when she met his eagerness, and then reached around her, pulling her into him, against his flat stomach. His arms remained loose around her, like he didn’t want her to feel trapped.  Cora suddenly knew what she’d been missing. No one had ever kissed her like this: slow and teasing, enjoying every second. His hands were gentle as they moved over her back.  Cora pressed closer and let herself explore him. Nick turned, twirling her slowly to the bed, where they landed softly.  Ok, what was she doing? He just seduced her with hardly any effort. Nick lifted his head to look at her. “When your body goes slack, does that mean you came to your senses?”  “Is that how you see it?” She barely had a voice. He studied her face, brushing his lips against hers again.  “If you want to slow down, you’ll have to pull your leg out of there.”  Cora flattened her leg to the bed, amazed that she’d been molded to him like that. Her heavy breathing embarrassed her. “Don’t think I suddenly thought I couldn’t do this with you. I just don’t do this with people I just met.”  “What if I promise to keep my hands to myself?” He asked. She loved feeling him touching the length of her, but she didn’t like knowing how she’d feel if she let things go any further.  “What are you asking?”  “I just wanted to kiss you, Cora. I didn’t mean to end up over here like this, but then you . . .”  “What?”  “You seemed to like kissing me more than I expected.”  Her thoughts exactly. “Kissing? And nothing else?”  “Cross my heart.”   Her heart still thudded NASCAR speed the next morning as they walked from the bank to the car. “What a rush.” She kept the folder containing the check against her.  “Want to keep it?” Nick gave her a carefree smile like they were discussing a dollar found on the ground. She didn’t think his question deserved an answer, and told him so with her expression. Then she got to watch his long legs as he quickened his pace to reach the car and open her door. Because he remained by her door, holding it, she slipped by right next to him. And he watched her the entire way. When seated, she looked up at him, at his hazel eyes, and the way he intently watched her.  She’d been wrong to assume she knew him right away. He was egotistic and a smart mouth, but then he was more after that. Like a sweetheart, at least when he wanted to be? Well, she couldn’t say she knew him that well, either, but she knew he’d controlled himself the previous night after she’d gotten him all worked up.  Nick came around, got in, and started the car. Thinking of kissing him the night before got her body revved up. And then he’d asked her all about her life in between kisses, like he wanted to know her as much as he wanted to kiss her. When she looked up and saw the searching look in his glance, Cora knew she’d been thinking too hard and too long. “Shall I call Jerry?”  He handed her the cell phone and she dialed. Jerry wanted to meet right then and get it over with.  “Ok,” she told Nick, “Same meeting place.”  “Looks like our adventure is winding down.”  “Adventure?” She asked. Last night might qualify, but being kidnapped and held for two days wasn’t fun in her book.  “Oh, sorry. You know, what Keith did isn’t right.”  Cora’s eyes about popped out of her head. “Did that just now occur to you?”  “I did say ‘sorry’ with that, didn’t I? But you’re right, that’s illegal. And we let him get away with it.” He stopped at a light and turned to her.  “Because he planned to hurt my father.” “And now we’re giving him back his money.” The light changed and Nick revved up before going.  “It’s his, remember? I don’t break the law.”  “Fine. I’ll hand it over if you’ll go on a date with me.” He grin was back.  “Are you asking for two dates now or is this the same date?”  “That’s a yes, isn’t it?” They arrived and got out together and started toward the door. She touched his arm. “Thank you for helping me. You could have left after getting me out of that house.”  Cora waited for a smirk, smart remark, or a smile. Nick leaned over and kissed her lightly. For a second, she felt dizzy. “Come on, we’ve got business to do.”  Jerry waited at the same table and they followed the same procedure.  “Hey, Dad.” She set the folder on the seat next to her, not wanting it to sit out in the open.  “Where is it?” His gruff voice sounded foreign, and she had a frightening second where she thought they’d been tricked. But, no, her father really did sit across form her with a sweaty face. She nodded down to the seat.  “Give it here and we’ll get out of here.”  “But will everything be ok then?” She asked. Nick glanced over, maybe because he heard her worried tone. Jerry leaned forward with his brow knitted, making parallel lines on his forehead.   Nick tried to keep his attention split between the restaurant and Jerry, who didn’t look or act like Cora. Maybe he’d worked for Keith for too long. Whatever the case, Nick turned to watch him more closely as his voice shook at his daughter. Cora pulled back, flat against the booth, and laid a hand on the folder.  “Hold on, Mr. Evans.” Keeping a level tone, he moved closer. “What’s the problem?”  “She won’t give me the freakin’ check.”  “Hey, keep calm.” He said. Cora’s white face put Nick on edge. They were here to hand it over, but this felt bad. Jerry fisted his hands and looked ready to lunge over the table at Cora. Nick considered telling her to give it to him so they could get out of there.  Then Cora spoke. “I need to know this will be over.”  “How can I guarantee that?”  “Will Keith come after me?” She asked.  “He’ll kill us both now if we don’t hand it over.” Jerry leaned farther and Nick moved in closer. He gave Cora a pointed look, but she held her ground.  “Dad, you stole it once.”  And he’d steal it again? Crap. Nick jumped up and stood by Cora, pulling her up by the arm.  “I’ll take it to Keith so we all feel better.” While he spoke, he saw Jerry’s hand go for his boot.  “Down!” He lunged forward and caught Jerry’s arm. Jerry jerked it straight up and fired the gun he‘d pulled.  A second of silence passed, then screaming. Nick smashed Jerry’s hand back into the wall several times, but it didn’t work like in the movies. The gun stayed put. So Nick did the next thing he thought of. While Jerry punched his side, he reached in and squeezed the trigger till the round was out. Particles fell from the ceiling.  The screams multiplied while people fled. Jerry cursed and threw the gun toward Nick. He rammed his head forward into Jerry’s face.  “Nick!” Cora had his arm, tugging. Jerry stumbled, searching for his dropped gun. Knowing Jerry was out of bullets, Nick threw an arm across Cora’s back and pulled her with him. They bust through the side door and heard sirens. Nick grabbed Cora around the waist and gave her a toss into the car, then jumped in himself. She snatched the seatbelt and pulled it across herself as they took off.  Nick whipped out onto the street and took a fast turn, then slowed to the speed limit, settled back and turned on the radio. They didn’t need to look guilty of anything. He started to pull in a deep breath, but his side felt sore.  Cora, shaking next to him, held her hands over her mouth. The folder set, forgotten, at her feet. Laying his hand on her leg, he said, “Are you alright?”  She nodded, lying, but he needed to keep things controlled as they drove away.  “What just happened?” She whispered. That was not her father back there.  “Money does weird things to people.”  Her father wasn’t the only one who’d shocked her. “Nick, you saved my life.”  His mouth came open, but he didn’t speak. That’s a first. He took a minute before looking at her. And still, he didn’t speak. So he’d shocked himself as well.  Nick kept driving, leaving the highway, and half an hour later they hit a gravel road.  “Do you have a destination?” She asked.  “Out of the city.”  “Then what?”  Nick pulled under a leaning apple tree where the road came to a dusty end. As soon as he turned off the ignition, he turned and took her face with both hands and pulled her close. When his lips met hers, Cora wasn’t ready for the hot sensations. He kissed her with fervor while his hands scorched her neck. A tornado whirl up inside her and she reached for him, too. His lips followed his hands and she couldn’t take it.  Cora cried out and his head jerked up.  “Cora?”  She wondered if her eyes were glazed like his, and if her lips were swollen and red.  “Are you ok?” He asked because she still didn’t speak.  After a deep breath, she whispered, “You . . .”  “Was it good or bad?”  “Good, very good.”  “Want more?”  “Oh, yes.” She closed her eyes, falling again but with eager anticipation.   “Now what do we do?” He held her close, but the noonday sun beat down on the trees above them, heating up the air.  “I hear water.”  Nick laughed. “What? We need to decide what to do about Jerry, Keith, and the money.”  “It sounds like there’s a river close by.”  “Cora?”  She sat up and started to open her door. “I get hot when I’m mad.”  He sat up, too. “Are you mad at me?”  She was outside the car already. “No, my father. Come on.”  He jumped out and followed as she went into the bushes. Pushing aside blackberry briars, scotch broom, and small maples, he wondered how she made her way through them so quickly. They emerged suddenly. Rocks crunched underneath them. Well, she’d found her steam. Before he spoke, she pulled off her shoes and dived in, fully clothed.  Cora surface and pushed her long blond hair back from her face. Talk about hot. Nick stood transfixed on her.  “Come in with me.”  Her shorts and tank top would dry quickly, but he wore thick shorts and a T shirt. He pulled off his shirt and thought about the shorts. Well, what’s the point of boxes if you can’t swim in them? Nick heard her laughter as he dropped his drawers and jumped in after her.  The water wasn’t freezing cold as he’d expected. “This does feel nice.”  She swam against the current where the water grew deep in the middle. “I want to stay here all day.”  With the serine forest on both sides and the clear sky above, the stream felt secluded from the world and its problems. “Why can’t we?” He asked, swimming closer to her, wanting to hold her in the water.  Kicking harder, she moved ten more feet away from him. Her eyes had been flirtatious as evaded him, but then she grew serious. “Nick, Jerry’s going to tell Keith about us, isn’t he? And now we stole the money.”  “But not on purpose.” He clarified, “Doesn’t that make all the difference?”  She didn’t swam away as he slowly came to her. “Do you think Keith cares?”  That sobered him up a bit. He threw his own hair back and rubbed his face. “Come here.” Cora looked curious as she swam over. He lifted her up against him and wrapped his arms around her. He’d never felt a need to hold someone before, but he wanted her right next to him. She reached around his neck, holding onto him while he held her. His eyes glistened above the water’s reflecting light as her looked at her. Their lips met in urgency and her fingers snagged handfuls of his hair, pulling him closer as they picked up where they had left off before. He wanted to kiss her until they both couldn’t breathe, but she pulled back a little, teasing, and made him go slow. Was she trying to torture him? Her full lips . . so soft . . . he couldn’t think. Her own game beat her and she couldn’t hold back one more millisecond. She felt lost, and there wasn’t anything but Nick, his arms around her, his kiss.  “Oh, Nick, we can’t stay out here all day.”  “I know, but can we play dumb for a while?”  “Kiss me again, and then let’s get out of here.”  He seemed to agree, but his one kiss was a very long one.  “Nick . . .”  “Yes, Cora?” She felt his lips smile against hers. “Alright, you’re right this time.”  They dried their clothes while sitting on a fallen log in the shade, where the breeze kept them cool, and then went back to the car so Nick could call Keith.  Keith got it on the second ring.  “Has Jerry Evans talked to you?”  After a pause, Keith asked, “What do you know about Jerry Evans?”  “He tried to shoot me today. And I’ve got your money.” Nick didn’t want to drag this out, but just hand over the check so Cora would be safe.  “Can you bring it here?”  “How about I leave it for you somewhere?” He was glad Keith didn’t ask why. So they set up a place and ended the call. Cora’s arms were crossed nervously. He took her hand and said, “This is it. We’ll drop the check off for him and be done with it.”  But Nick knew that wouldn’t be the end of things.  Two hours later they were back in town, parked above the park where they planned to drop off the money. They’d left Nick’s car at a parking ramp and rented out a Ford Taurus, a common car that hopefully wouldn’t stand out. Nick wore a baseball cap and held a newspaper up in front of him. Cora liked the look. Though he’d probably look great in anything.  She was reclined in the seat next to him so hopefully people wouldn’t see her. With his face still in the paper, Nick asked, “You’re enjoying the view, aren’t you?”  “What about your view? See anything?”  “A lot of cars are coming and leaving again. I’ve seen a few men stay. One’s on a bench with a newspaper. Guess it’s not the most original idea. The other’s walking a dog.”  “Do you recognize them?”  “The one with the paper, I think.”  She wanted to sneak a peek, but knew better. “But that doesn’t mean they plan to do anything, does it?” Scouting the area might be a smart idea considering the amount of money involved. And they were doing it, too.  “No . . . Keith wants his money back. But I’m sure he’s wondering why I have it and where Jerry is.”  Cora couldn’t think about her father right now. “Time?”  “We’ve got thirty minutes till we’re supposed to drop it.”  She didn’t like it, even though Nick set the plan up with Keith. So she asked, “What if we go now?”  “Leave?”  “And drop it somewhere else, and then call him. Wouldn’t that be safer for us?”  He waited a minute to answer. “It might not go over well, but I agree with you. I’ll start driving and you think of a place.”  Once out of the park, she climbed up into the seat. “The closed grocery store down this street should work.”  Nick nodded and called. Keith didn’t like it one bit, but Nick had the money and insisted. He didn’t want Cora anywhere near Keith.  “Wait a minute,” Keith’s voice rose, “You’re giving me a check?”  “Take it or leave it.” Nick hung up and started thumping on the wheel. He tried to stop when he saw Cora watching. She didn’t need to think he was nervous. The phone rang.  “Listen, Nick, I figured out why you’re doing this.” Keith started. “But if you don’t bring it to the park right now, Cora won’t get to say goodbye to her father.”  “Why would I care about that?” He hung up and turned to Cora. “Would Jerry be dumb enough to go to Keith?”  “Would anyone? He’d just lost all that money.”  Exactly. Nick didn’t believe Keith had Jerry, but he explained the situation to Cora. “He’s threatening to kill Jerry.”  “What?”  “But there’s no way Keith has him.”  “What if he does?” She asked.  “Cora, I don’t want you to risk your life to help him. Especially when it’s unlikely he’s anywhere around Keith.”  She leaned back, rubbing her temples. “Is Keith capable of killing people?”  “I sure don’t want to find out the hard way.”  “Why did Dad get us into all this?” She covered her face, and he reached over to her shoulder.  The closed grocery store lay up ahead.  “Want my opinion?” He asked. When she’d first met him, she wouldn’t have. But now she did.  “You’ve got a great looking guy and a lot of money.”  “You know what keeping the money would mean?”  “You and me and somewhere far away.”  Well, he had saved her life. And he was hot. “You know, I don’t like you for your looks. Just your looks, anyway.”  Nick tilted his head and rolled his gaze down her. “We make a great team, don’t you think?”  The car rolled beside the store’s parking lot then. Nick and Cora both turned their heads to look that way.  “Keep going.” She said.  

						
</post>
</Blog>