<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>27,May,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      What a weekend. We drove around the city looking for houses for sale. There is precious little out there.  Saturday our agent sent a short list of homes for sale, 1/2 of them not even built yet. We looked at four properties on Sunday, and are poised to make an offer on a 1/2 built home. There are several more houses on our 'must see' list, but I have the feeling that we will buy NEW. What that means for ME is thet I'll be able to install CAT 5 (ethernet) cable throughout the house before the walls go in. Tonight we'll see that last few houses and make a choice ... if all goes to plan...
    
</post>
<date>23,May,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Good news. If I sounded a bit depressed yesterday it was because our selling price was too low. Well, it turns out that I didn't take into account how much he had paid off on our present mortgage since the beginning of this adventure. The big advantage to taking a whole year to sell your house is that in the meantime you've made a whole year of payments on your present house. Our initial goals are still on track because of this. yabba dabba doo!    
    
</post>
<date>22,May,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I'm sitting here celebrating with a Corona and a bowl full of nuts. The cause for celebration is that we sold our house ... finally. We first put it on the market, let's see ... about 12 months ago? Where is this sellers market we heard about? Seems to me that the housing maket is not nearly as desperate as we were led to believe. Anyways, the condition on the offer was met, and the buyer's financial institution's assessor is coming tomorrow.  Then the deal is done. I am not totally happy with the offer, but what can I do now? Cut corners, compromise, eat KD for a few months. The fun part is that we get to start house hunting in earnest tomorrow. I'm just looking forward to getting into a bigger house and the opportunity to unpack boxes that have been stacked in the basement for the last eight years. Cheers.
    
</post>
<date>21,May,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, yesterday was the Big Smokeout with the Big Honey. We changed the spelling of Honey to distance ourselves from the origin of the word : Winnie-the-Pooh. In tribute to the original use of the barrels, we re-dubbed it the Big Honey. Anyways, there is a new blog dedicated to the Big Honey and those that will use it. It will be at  urlLink bighoney blog . The original webspace  and storage for the pictures is in  urlLink my webfolder .
    
</post>
<date>20,May,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday was the assembly date (over beer and pizza) for our new smoker barbeque dubbed the Big  Hunny  Honey ... named after the two BeeMaid Honey barrels it is made of. Thanks again to the  urlLink Peters Honey Farm  for supplying the old barrels. Today is the inaugural "smoke" with dry-rubbed 6-inch back ribs. Once the  urlLink Big  Hunny  Honey  has a chance to cool down, we will empty 6 cans of black high-heat stove paint on it.
    
</post>
<date>17,May,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, the house sold AGAIN ... this time for much lower than I wanted, but (if you want to look at it this way) we will get $2000 less than the last offer we accepted, which, in the Grand Scheme of things, is not a whole lot of money. I could spend more than that on a suite of ADOBE products... at least I wish I could.  Anyways, some background: We have been trying to sell our house since Fall 2001. Various factors kept buyers at bay ... namely our high price because we were not serious about selling at first, the condition of the foundation in our 1911 2-story house, and the fact that we are located right next to a big-ass apartment block. Then we changed the factors that we could to generate interest: We lowered our asking price by $8000 and we started fixing up the joint.  We got a conditional offer in March or April, subject to the appraisal of a building inspector. He could not recommend the house, so the buyers backed out. We fixed up the house some more by replacing the worst shingled areas on the roof, and overnight the showings seened to pick up. Within a week (today in fact) we got our second offer. Lower than we expected anyone would even dare offer. We countered with $2000 more, and they accepted within several hours. Now their only contract OUT is if the furnace is in such bad shape it needs replacing. Stay posted to find out how our house-selling saga ends.    back view   
    
</post>
<date>16,May,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      This  urlLink Calendar    and  urlLink Web Color pre-Visualizer  are  contest entries for web pages  under 5 Kbytes ... my title jpg alone is over 19 kb! Check out other entries at  urlLink www.the5k.org/  
    
</post>
<date>15,May,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Everything you ever wanted to know about Canadian Grain from my current employer: The  urlLink  Canadian Grain Commission  
    
</post>
<date>15,May,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Some of my geek friends and I have decided to get into the shop and get our hands dirty. We concluded that if our wives could have countless 'girls night out' 's, then the men were entitled to a weekend to ourselves. We decided that a fitting venture would be a 'weekend welding workshop' ( or WWW for those of you that didn't notice the clever pun), in which we would build the ultimate smoker barbeque. For a glimpse of what we are attempting to build, see:  urlLink  The Big Baby . So far we've cut one barrel in half (noisy), ground some rust off (messy) and drawn some pretty lines where the wood-stoking door will be. The WWW is a bust though as the wives made their own plans again and left us men with the kids. We'll have to do it after bed-time.
    
</post>
<date>13,May,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Another issue I have came to light today while I was examining the contents of my pockets. Among the bits of paper, post-it reminders and receipts, were some brand new yet crumpled up $5 and $10 bills. Now what is keeping me from storing these things in my wallet, where they belong? The answer, of course, is because that my wallet no longer  fits  in my pocket. I have gone through my wallet so many times, trying to cull the crap that gathers there, but no matter how much I throw out, what's left is still too much for my back pocket. What gets me is that with the technology we enjoy today, it still takes 1/16 of an inch x 2-1/8" x 3-1/4" of plastic to store a name, a number an expiry date and a signature. If you have 16 credit cards/debit cards/bank cards/club member cards/air miles(tm)/phone cards/blood donor cards ... you already have 1 inch of your wallet thickness. On top of that I have the (much smarter) thin plastic coated public library card/insurance plan cards (at least 3 or 4 of them)/wallet calendar/BlockBuster/a few pictures of the girlies (my own, not the GUESS girls ... well maybe them too ...) My wife health insurance plan cards (for dual coverage)/ several business cards I use all the time, Subway coupons, Public Transit tickets, Driver's Licence, postage stamps, 1 free with 10 whatever ... CD's, Popcorn, Power Juice, Coffee, Haircut, car wash, film developing ... etc. In the end I have room for everything  except  money. I might as well carry a purse. I don't see  why   companies couldn't offer barcode stickers instead of full sized credit cards for discounts and '1 free with 10' offers. Air Miles, the Library, Chapters, and my health plan could all be stuck on the same card. Those forward thinking companies (like Safeway) that accept my phone number instead of a barcode are even better. Those cards I can leave at home or in my wife's purse. Who can I call? Where can I take my beef? Do you think that VISA(tm of course) and MasterCard(ditto) are aware of this problem?
    
</post>
<date>13,May,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Whoa, I just ran 200 miles [+/-198]. Waiting for the rumored endorphins to kick in. Maybe they can be coaxed out with a hot shower. Last week I thought I'd die after 1 mile. This week I ran 2. It ain't much, but   am  improving. Gotta go now and log my progress at  Runner's World's   urlLink  free   Training Log.
    
</post>
<date>10,May,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      OK, I admit it. I'm out of shape. I was supposed to go running Friday and Sunday, but I was not able to get out. Instead, I decided to reroof part of my house. My brother came over Saturday and helped me out (with his carpentry expertise) and we got half of the job done. Now my hands feel like sandpaper, and every muscle in my body is screaming for A-535. I didn't run, but I feel like I got a workout. After a few finishing touches, I'll be ready to do the back roof next Saturday. All this just so we can sell the house.
    
</post>
<date>10,May,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      HAHA ... HUGE water-main break at Pioneer and Water today (that's close to Provencher Bridge). Cars of all sizes are pushing through water up to 2.5 feet deep. The ONLY stall was a businessman in his fancy BMW. I was going to comment as I drove by on my bike, but the look on his face told me I'd be better off keeping my thoughts to myself. 
    
</post>
<date>08,May,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink  What IS it with some people? If this blog had a theme it would have to be that. There will be a good long rant coming about the quality of service in the retail and so-called  service  industries, but first lets talk about today.   The date is May 9. The weather is damp and cold. Tons of wet snow has been falling since late last night and the city is dripping. Transformers are shorting out because they're filling with slush, and traffic is crawling because, between today and three weeks ago, people have forgotten how to drive in the snow. This morning, as each of my coworkers arrived at work, they took their turns describing the fights they had with their significant other. Throughout the day these normally good natured people proved  how scrappy they can get. Somehow the snow had completely demoralized them. What's up with that? Granted, we are not supposed to have blizzards in the month before June ... but it  happens . I can remember many ice storm in May. This one is just a little warmer and wetter. It's no reason to stomp around and pout. We work in an  office  building. We don't even  go  outside for heaven's sake. Weather is weather. It is unpredictable and uncontrollable. Don't let it ruin your life.
    
</post>
<date>08,May,2002</date>
<post>

	 
          Daryl's Blog is active   May 8, 2002  
    
</post>
<date>28,June,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      The inlaws wanted to see the inside of the house yesterday, so they called us up. We met them there last night, got a key from the show home, and took a peek. All the wood trim and oak pantry door is installed. The top coat of paint was also finished - but it is the wrong color!. I suspect that the paint supplier forgot to add the tint, since it was just a flat white. It was supposed to be the same as all the other Hilton homes ... a darker cream color. We told the builder and they are looking into it. While we had the builders key, we stole a look at the neighbors house across the street. It is identical to ours but a little further along.  Their basement is poured and their cabinets, lights, some flooring is installed, and their paint is the right color. I outlined my plans for the basement, and Janet and her mother agreed with them. All systems are 'go' and the hi-tec basement planning pushes forward.     right color (in the neighbors house):     wrong color:      
    
</post>
<date>25,June,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Sunday was a day of fun for the kids. The Red River Ex -- a 10 day fair and amusement park -- is in town.       
    
</post>
<date>15,June,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      We borrowed a key and took a peek at our house again on Saturday (June 22). As was on an earlier pass in the rain (Wednesday), the tar paper and wire mesh has been added to the outside walls in preparation for the stucco. Now the inside plastering is completely finished and primed, ready for painting. The front concrete steps were poured yesterday and the interior woodwork ... door and window trim, wall caps, sills, were brought in for installation.        Last Sunday was the Manitoba Marathon. I ran the shortest run available - the 2.6 MILE SuperRun - 1/10 of a Marathon. The guys are gearing up for another Marathon in Walker North Dakota in Fall. I have agreed [in principle] to join a relay team and run 13 miles. Time will tell if I can adequately recover from my 2.6 mile ordeal. My official time was 29:51, but that was from when the gun went off. I spent several minutes folowing the crowd to the start line after the gun fired. MY watch time from startline to finish was 27:17. After the Marathon we had a little birthday party for:   Janet told him that we were singing HAPPY BIRTHDAY for him. He nodded and smiled. A few moments into the song he asked her who we were singing Happy Birthday for... It's not his memory, it's his hearing. I don't believe he has any batteries in that hearing aid.
    
</post>
<date>15,June,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      On Thursday the inside walls of the new house were covered. Our new home is beginning to take shape.       On Friday the wall guys started taping and plastering and added the rounded corners. Also on Thursday, we picked the lighting fixtures that will go into the house. All of the interior lights will be of [faux] Italian (marbled) glass with pewter hardware. Tomorrow is the Manitoba Marathon, and then a picnic/barbeque for Father's Day and my Grandpa's birthday. Don't ask me how old he is ... I've lost track.
    
</post>
<date>10,June,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      In case you are curious, I have heard from area residents, that the street name "Braswell" Rhymes more with "Maxwell" than with "Roswell" ... if you can imagine the 'x' being a hard 'z' sound. Maybe "Braz-well" would be a better way to put it.
    
</post>
<date>03,June,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      This past week was a busy one. We choose carpet and vinyl flooring colours for the new house. I drilled the cable holes for my future Leviton Integrated Network [I found out that 1 14-volt drill battery lasts for 2-1/2  1" holes through a 2x4, and 2 layers of subfloor]. I found plans for the house in the house, that some contractor left behind when he was done ... so I scanned them into my computer. I can now plan our basement layout with more precision.        The house now has fascia, soffits and brick installed. The rough plumbing electrical and framing has been inspected and the walls are ready to be covered. The Doors and Windows are installed and the garage floor is poured. 
    
</post>
<date>03,June,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      What a rush! The last time I posted was a week ago. It seems like yesterday. What has happend in the intervening days might qualify as the biggest rush in recent memory.         As I expected, we decided to buy a brand new house. After scouting around to see what was available in the used houseing market, we decided that for about $15,000 more, we could have a  brand new  house. We found the biggest lot (longest dimension, 210 feet) with an adequate sized house (1188 ft/sq with a full basement) in our price range ($130,000 give or take $20,000), and put in an offer. We offered a little more, and added a lot more 'built-ins' than the original price offered. For example, we asked for all appliances to be included in the asking price, as well as air conditioning and some landscaping. The builder counter offered $1100 more, and we countered again ... to meet him half way. The deal was then accepted and signed.        Since then we have been choosing colors for the house, planning how and when we will move, planning my  urlLink Leviton Integrated Network Structured Media System , and driving by the house every day to video tape the progress. My dad, a builder for many years, came and looked at it, and gave me a few points to complain about. We are happy because even though it is a small house, it has 3 to 4 times more space than we have now, it's in a low traffic neighborhood with lots of young kids, and it will be  new, brand new !
    
</post>
<date>29,July,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      It took a while but I'm back online. Our Internet service was installed into our new house on Saturday, but I JUST got the wiring to the computer hooked up now. The installer was not interested in doing that for me since he had never seen a Leviton BHN* box before.  Neither have I, which is why it took me till now.      This is a picture of my Cat5e Ethernet jack wiring (before trimming):            The move 8 Kms south went amazingly smoothly. I got an early start by loading all of my books magazines, collections, etc. early in the morning. As soon as the sun hit us the temperature soared to 30 C, so the early start saved my life. I'm sure I would have had heat stroke if we started later. Our U-Haul with Arizona plates had to be boosted twice. The U-haul guy later told me the battery was brand new, so the charging system must be faulty. No problem though ... we all know how to boost cars in the Great White North. We had just the right amoount of ppeople over to help us. Not so many we tripped over ourselves, but not so few we had to do it alone. at noon there was a turnover of people, so we got fresh muscles to do the heavy lifting. I must have drank (drunk?drinkin?) a couple gallons of water that day, but I made not one trip to the toilet. It all came out as sweat.  We unloaded all of the basement boxes into our new garage. There they still sit. It will be a while till we can afford shelving to unpack it all.  It  seems that every task I set out to accomplish now is an excercise in circular reasoning: I need to unpack boxes to get to the items I need. But I need shelf space to dig through the boxes, but I need to move the boxes to build the shelves, but I need room to move them too ... When it gets too frustrating I just go and sit on the couch in my new living room, and smile. We love the new neighborhood so far. Our neighbors are great, the train is much less intrusive then we imagined ... much less than living in an airport air lane, next to zero traffic, NO noise at night.       Everybody workin', no one  to take pictures... this is all we have for  moving day pictures ...               Break time               *see previous posts
    
</post>
<date>24,July,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      I guess it is now officially Wednesday July 24. This afternoon we see the bank to sign mortgage papers. Then tomorrow we get an 'official' walkthrough at the new house. I believe it is to voice any concerns we may have missed to date, and for receiving special instructions on how to care for a new house ... yard regulations, new concrete care, telepost adjustment, etc... Then we see the lawyer's assistant to sign papers. Next morning, Friday, we see the lawyer again to collect the front door key. Then the real work begins!
    
</post>
<date>23,July,2002</date>
<post>

	 
         The house as of July 23 ...  3 days before  possession day:                             Our current basement:      
    
</post>
<date>19,July,2002</date>
<post>

	 
         Vacation instructions:           
    
</post>
<date>18,July,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      One working day until vacation time! Today I felt MUCH better. My recovery is well over the hump. Now since Janet is at work all day, and the kids are at the grandparents, I just might go shopping. Did I hear Home Depot is having a 70% off sale? Mac users might find this of interest: urlLink dotMac 
    
</post>
<date>17,July,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Three working days till vacation!  6 days after wisdom-tooth surgery, and my face is still swollen. My antibiotics run out today. I have 3 doses of painkillers (mood-improving) drugs left. The stitch-holes feel inflamed and sore ... like I bit both cheeks really hard. I cannot eat fast enough to get full so I have a perpetual hunger-headache.  
    
</post>
<date>14,July,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      The weekend of pain is officially over. The discomfort is not, however. The 'pain' was really far from it. I tasted no blood. I felt no real 'pain' from the missing teeth. I stopped taking painkillers after 14 hours. The real inconvience is the swelling around the jawbone and the burning around the stitches when I try to eat. I have nothing to complain about and I think the procedure went remarkably well. Now I am waiting for the stitches to dissolve so the holes can heal over. I tried to eat steak yesterday. Ha Ha. Without functional cheeks to position food between my molars, I ended up swallowing most of the pieces whole.  New in the house today: bathroom sinks, Leviton Basic Home Network media panel.    Kitchen sink:               Bathroom sinks:     Leviton BHN panel:      
    
</post>
<date>11,July,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      2 news items: The incredible progress made in the new house earlier this week; and my wisdom tooth removal this afternoon.    Vinyl and Carpet:     Measuring for Window Coverings:       1) We visited the house on Wednesday. Last time we looked (on Saturday), they had just poured the basement floor and moved some wall materials into the basement. They had mistakenly installed the kitchen vinyl flooring in the bathrooms, and had correctly installed the underlay for the carpet.  Monday and Tuesday saw all the vinyl properly installed, all of the carpet installed all the way to the bottom of the basement stairs, all of the ductwork, A/C, and furnace componants, sump pump and pit installed, and basement walls (perimeter only) framed and insulated. There must have been three different sub-contractors at the house during those two days. We measured for window coverings. On the way out we also noticed that the garage door was installed.    My Bottom Molars:            2)Wisdom Tooth (x4) removal... This happened today. I was scheduled for 12:45 pm, but the queue was pushed back for a few hours. i got out of surgery at 3:30, and Janet picked me up at 4:00. The drugs they gave me put me to sleep (or rather, I just fell asleep, since I stayed up till 2 am last night ... I wanted to fall asleep on the table), but I did wake up in the middle of the third tooth. I tried to yell "you got the wrong tooth" ... twice, but both times they told me to try not to  talk : ) ... I honestly thought they were drilling on my second molar, not the third.  After the surgery -- I felt great at first: no effects felt from the drugs, I was walking right away with no dizzyness; my lips and chin were numb and felt like they doubled in size -- a mirror proved otherwise; I took an ice pack and painkillers right off the bat, but when they wore off after 3.5 hours, I took some more. In the 4th to 5th hours, the freezing wore off, and the new dose of painkillers hadn't kicked in yet the pain was... exquisite... I suppose 8 years of treating migraines with Tylenol with codeine (T1's) has made me a little tolerant of the drug.  I'm taking T3's now and they're not having the desired effect. I'll have to increase the dose, or put them closer together. I also received drugs to decrease swelling (Dexamethasone 2mg 2x/day for 4 days), and antibiotics for 6 days; so far, 5 hours later, swelling is minimal. All in all, I am pleased that the surgery went quickly, and that there was no nerve damage of any kind.
    
</post>
<date>10,July,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       Dilbert for Wednesday, July 10 2002  ^^                               ~~ () ~meet with our vendor         () ||  and come up with a plan.     J|     I�ll do the same with      their executives  ^^       ~~ ()       () ~Can you see any reason ||       J|  why MY meeting might be               a complete waste of time?  ^^                           ~~ () ~Sure, lots of them,      () ||  but I�m planning to      J|     spring them on you      during your performance     review.  
    
</post>
<date>08,July,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      We spent the weekend packing. Although the official possession date for the new house is July 26 (3 weeks minus 3 days), an they may let us in a week early... Next weekend is my  urlLink Weekend Of Pain , so I'm not expecting to do much more than lie on the sofa and watch TV. That would leave a week or two before the big day. Packing is going well, but I feel like I'm living in a warehouse.   The basement is poured!. We looked on Wednesday, and there was that pile of gravel that was being used to support the underfloor plumbing and weeping tiles. They must have brought the crushed rock on Thursday, packed it down, and then poured the floor on Friday. Now it is ready to walk on and the furnace and duct work can be installed.  We had been talking to the builder about installing the deck-header at the back of the house. The chemically treated rot-resistant 2x10 is bolted to the outside wall, and is used to secure the deck to the house. This board does not come standard with the house, so we were going to have to pay for it. Alternatively we could install it ourselves after the stucco is on the house. This would involve a lot of stucco removal, or an unstable header bolted to the outside of the stucco. The price was $140 for a 20 foot deck-header. We were going to pay it, but then remembered that the framers forgot to install a small 4 foot wall between the living room and the front entrance. Although we like the omission, we used it to trade for a deck-header.  
    
</post>
<date>04,July,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Performance Review. Phew.
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      We visited the house and insepcted the new changes. The tile guy was there so the doors were open. We found a roll of carpet underlay on the floor -- it seemed to be too soft for 'upgraded' underlay, so we took a sample to the carpet store to make sure. All is OK. We just got a soft sample. The rest should be fine. They found it strange that there would be a half-roll in the house at all, since the underlay and carpet are usually delivered on the install date... next Monday. We are pleased with the new kitchen colors and the paint job. Possession date is in 3 weeks and 1 day, so we are starting to pack up at the old place.Have a Safe and happy July 4 those of you south of the [cdn] border.     New Kitchen:            new paint job right color:     Becky in the Big House:        
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night was the last fireworks display we will get to enjoy from the comfort of home. Yesterday was Canada Day and the evening fireworks take place in the middle of town, six blocks away and across the river. This year was more extravagent than ever, with two displays taking place on either side of 'The Forks' where the Assiniboine meets the Red River. Becky says "Happy Birthday Canada", and Jenny says "Thanks, Canada for the beautiful fireworks".    Fireworks Canada Day, 2002     From the kids Bedroom Window       Today the painters are fixing the mistake made last week in our new house. I don't know who made the goof, nor do I care to know. The important thing is that it is fixed. Our cabinets were also installed today, and they are prepping the basement for the pouring of the concrete.
    
</post>
<date>30,August,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       Who-hoo!  We are finally able to park in the garage. I have officially finished moving everything  into the house that belongs in the house. The only junk left in the garage is future shed and yard stuff  and garage/workshop stuff. The basement is now a little crowded and disorganized, but that will change  as we unpack. This A.M. as I walked to the bus-stop in the dark, I heard a blood curdling screeech. I looked in the  direction of the scream, but saw nothing. The second screech came from behind me so I knew that  what I had heard the first time was an echo off of a house in front of me. I looked back toward my  house, and sitting on our neighbors roof was an owl sitting  at least  two feet tall. For my benefit  the owl stretched his wings, and jumped off of the roof and landed on a roof closer to my position.  I took out my camera with the intention of shooting the owl if it flew over me, but I didn't get the chance.  This would be the second wildlife I have seen since moving to this area, the first being a deer on the  railroad tracks.
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       Finally! The day has come  ... After returning from Grandpa's lovely funeral, we discovered that our driveway had been poured. This marks an end to the muddy feet that come from little feet slipping into the gaps between construction site sidewalk blocks.     Driveway form, Tuesday August 20:           Poured Driveway, August 21  (color cast due to evening light)         
    
</post>
<date>18,August,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday at 4:15 am Grandpa went to his reward and rejoined Grandma. We grandkids have 'missed'  grandpa (Henry F Siemens of Altona) ever since his hearing went, and will miss him even more now.  Grandpa will be remembered for his 'sermon-in-a-prayer' style grace before family meals, His unending  string of new cars every two years, so he didn't have to worry about repair costs and family safety, his  strong opinions about local matters -- and his arguments with grandma over the details, all of the practical  furniture that came out of his basement woodshop, his Hammond organ playing at Christmas, his sense  of humor and his smile.     At the age of 91, Grandpa (at his birthday party above) suffered a 'silent' heart attack,  a condition only diagnosed after blood tests. After a brief recovery, he developed  pneunomia and died peacefully August 17 4:15 am.  
    
</post>
<date>17,August,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       Phew... I made it home ...  I drove home from Steinbach with one eye closed, listening to  Boom, chucka luckalucka, chuckaluckalucka boom boom ... waiting for the dinosaurs We rented a movie, and had some pizza with these great sprinkle-on toppings that added extra flavor. One was a mild Italiano, and the other was blazing hot Chili Peppers. All was fine and dandy until, on the drive home, I absent mindedly rubbed my left eye. Youch! I'm glad the deer decided to stay in the fields tonight. I would not have seen them on the road. BTW, thanks D for letting me use your only cup, and sit in the captains chair.
    
</post>
<date>14,August,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       wow, what an eventful week so far ...  Jenny turned five and got her new bike on Sunday. I immediately put training wheels on the new bike and took the training wheels off of the old small bike. Two days later -- Jenny is driving the old small bike [without training wheels] unassisted. We had no part in teaching her how to drive a bike. Like Becky, she just did it. Nike would be proud. The next day [sorry Paul, you're too late ...] Becky lost her second front tooth in a week. Guess what's all she wants for Christmas now? Today we left the old house for good. Everything we want to keep is moved out, the final meter readings were made, lawn mowed for the last time, and the keys left behind. Good luck to the Anders, the new owners as of tomorrow morning.
    
</post>
<date>11,August,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       Everybody welcome Jenny to the Five Year Old Club. And the Big Girls Bike Club. Both achieved the same day, August 11, 2002! 
    
</post>
<date>06,August,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Paul bought a house, Paul bought a house...   (sing to the tune of nya, nya nya, nya, nya) 
    
</post>
<date>06,August,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      We've been in the house for a week now. So far there have been a few surprises.  For starters, and to our complete surprise, a garage door  opener  was  not  included in the price of the house. I suppose it's because everyone has their own idea of what a garage door opener should do, so it's left up to them to go out and purchase them ... but I think it should have been handled the same way as the lights and carpet and appliances: you get a base model unless you go to the store early and upgrade. As it happened, we went to the Sears website and got their top-of-the-line model for a cut-price. At least $100 less then the competition name brand [that probably MADE the Sears model]. It came with 2 remotes, a wall switch, infrared beam safety feature, and an external keypad entry system. Next, a hand rail for the basement stairs  fell off  the wall at a moment when I was depending on it greatly. It was glued to the paint, and fastened with screws  so short  that the tips only just barely penetrated the underlying wood 2x4. I replaced those screws with ones 1 inch longer. THEN ... someone brought us red wine for a h/w gift ... then proceeded to spill some on the carpet (see our carpet color in the archives). The  ladies  poured their own white wine on the red spill, and diluted it enough to remove the marks with detergent and water. I think there is now a  light  spot on the floor. Then I was BBQing beef back-ribs, salmon and steak, and I  dropped some back-rib grease on the garage steps and garage-entry door... (and  then  I burned the steak while showing the guys the rest of the house (namely the basement). There was only one steak, so it wasn't missed). At this rate the house will look totally lived-in in a few weeks, then we won't have to worry about it any more.     new dining room     Jenny and Vinnie     new front yard        up the street     new garage door opener     temporary storage        Jenny's new friend     our new friend     Becky losing her first front tooth         
    
</post>
<date>26,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
              I am Marvin the Martian!  
</post>
<date>25,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       The time is Eight, Thirty-one a.m. -- The temperature is minus one degree centigrade.   This morning is the first time this season I've seen the temp drop to below freezing. We're still waiting for the stucco guys to do our house ... and the three neighbors around us.  Yesterday we installed a few curtains and a basement doorbell chime. With any luck I'll get a  urlLink 150" target=king&gt;   before winter storms in. We have a lot of furniture and shelving to build to make our new house a  home! 
    
</post>
<date>23,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       B ig headache at work the last few days. last minute changes leading to cascade failure throughout all of our systems. Comedy of errors, whatever you want to call it. After 3 days of overtime and forfeited days off we have finally caught the tiger by the tail. To remain positive, we have hijacked the theme song from the kids show 'Bob The Builder' ... "Can we fix it?  YES WE CAN!"  
    
</post>
<date>19,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      I added two moving day pictures to the post of 7.28.2002. I could not believe how hot and tired I got that day. I do not want to do that again in the near future. 
    
</post>
<date>18,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      I just changed to a more space-efficient blogger template. Sorry to you who need reading glasses to see the new text size, but I was always bothered by the humongous proportions of the other template. If you feel nostalgic, you can always review the archives, which I will leave alone. Now I'll have to re-do my customizations...
    
</post>
<date>16,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       Update for September 16, 2002:  Todays news is that there is no news.  Nothing worth sharing happened last week. Our house was not stuccoed.  Our yard was not levelled and landscaped. I did not fill up the film containing  the photo of BBB (see the Sept. 9 entry -  man, that was fun).  We  did  get the money from our old house ... but that wasn't too exciting  as we ended up about $1000 short ... so we will be staggering for a few paydays. I  did  also find a quick easy way to index my new photos to make them  available (for viewing only) online. If you're interested, check out my  webserver (if it is turned on) at    urlLink  http://webfolder.sawatzky.info/   sawatzky.info no longer active   I will be distilling, renaming, and moving the files available to the general public,  so you may have trouble with bookmarks of a specific item. Any movies you  find require the Apple Quicktime plugin. 
    
</post>
<date>10,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Dang it, just when I thought I licked this racist thing, some nigger come along and prove me wrong ...  urlLink take a looka dis ...   How did I find this you ask? Well I ... welll ... I was searching for lyrics to a song I was listening to  ...  
    
</post>
<date>09,September,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       After a fairly uneventful week, came BBB day.   Boys Being Boys is what we dubbed the events of Saturday September 7.  In the evening we changed our acronym to GONADs, for Going Out Night for All Dads.  This of course is in response to (and some would say 'revenge for') all of the GNO's  we've been seeing recently. Girls Night Out is of course at least a monthly occurance,  so we have to make the most of our BBB's and GONADs.      Saturday started at 6 am Saturday A.M. when we all had to drag ourselfs out of bed, despite it being a weekend.       We all (7 of us) met at (get this) 'Bacon and Eggs' Restaurant for breakfast downtown. B is a small one-man operation downtown with super-cheap  big breakfasts, as the name suggests.      After breakfast we strolled through a China-Town grocery where a few of us picked up food and snacks for later in the day.       One of the seven departed for the rest of the day, to rejoin us later for supper. The other  six of us spent the next hour or so at the S.I.R. outdoor store, and then the Lee Valley  Woodworking store.      After a stop at Tim Hortons for another coffee, we headed for St Laurent's 'Paintball Paradise', an hour and a half north-west.     At PbP we shot at our opponants with 280 ft/sec paintballs for about 5.5 hours in the great  outdoors. A great time was had by all and no lost eyeballs. Our games were played in the forest with dense underbrush and a light drizzle coming down from above.       After changing our of our thoroughly drenched clothing into something respectable, we headed  for Muddy Waters smokehouse at The Forks. This is where the GONAD part of the day began.  We called a few others to join us, but only the one who left us at breakfast rejoined us for an  amazing dinner of: Pork Ribs, Beef Ribs, Pulled Pork, Roast Chicken, Baked Beans, fries,  veggies, bread and butter, beer, coffee, cheesecake, apple-crisp, and pecan pie.      After dinner six of us went to the Cheap Theater and saw  Minority Report  for $2.95 each. On Sunday we each nursed our aches and pains, and today the pain is a reminder of the great time we had during the BBB weekend. [Come back next week for Pictures]
    
</post>
<date>31,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      The kids are out now... augmenting their candy supply for the long winter ahead.   urlLink      TRICK OR TREAT!!!  
    
</post>
<date>23,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink     Happy Halloween!  Congratulations for surviving the coldest October in HISTORY!  Play safe this Halloween.
    
</post>
<date>23,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       PayDay!    Let's see if we can't crawl out of our hole this time...
    
</post>
<date>21,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Janet has a new (additional) job! There is no way to put this delicately so I just tell it like it is...     She will now be collecting and processing your bodily fluids for new life insurance applications. If you are in the market, there is a small but not impossible chance that you will run into Nurse Janet.
    
</post>
<date>18,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       Oops, we did it again ...  In a bungled WindowsXP ad  urlLink Microsoft  throws pie in its own face ...
    
</post>
<date>16,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      -11c this morning ... Brrrrrr.    I will be on a 3 day course starting today, at the CanadInn on Pembina. That means I won't be back at work till next monday. WooHoo! 
    
</post>
<date>15,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       Good day all you canadians eh?  Have a nice Thanksgiving weekend? All stuffed full of turkey?    I wrote this as a comment in PABLO's blog, but it bears repeating here: I would boycott Tim Hortons if I could find a better [and more convienient] cup of coffee somewhere else. Their whole rational for not having debit machines is SPEED. However, the only place you see speed is through the drive-thru. Why not then offer debit card service INSIDE where service is already turtle's pace, and leave the drive-thru cash only? (some Robin's Donuts do this already). If I don't have cash, I refuse to go to the bank machine to get money just for Tim Hortons. I'll drive out of my way instead and get a good cup of java at Starbucks (who DO take Interac).
    
</post>
<date>09,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
        EXTRA  THIS JUST IN!   The photo evidence is all here  ...  urlLink    The five mennonites and one sympathizer who escaped their accountability peers for a day of secret carnage in the outback have been identified, thanks to a photo leaked to the press by an unknown informant. The names of the alledged anarchists are as follows, from left to right: Myron K, Martin P, John W, Kevin S, David S, Daryl S.   Click on the small photo for a larger one. 
    
</post>
<date>08,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       Will the real Slim Shady PLEASE SHUT UP?!?  This may be old but I still find it funny:   urlLink   Will the real Slim Shady PLEASE  SHUT UP ?!?   
    
</post>
<date>05,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       Snow      
    
</post>
<date>04,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       A few house blues  ...  the builder is sticking us with the cost of a permit we thought he took care of long ago ... the animal services branch is cruising new neighborhoods ( such as ours) and forcing all dogs to be licenced (we got away with no tags for 8 years, and the dog is already 12 years old) ... the same dog had an 'accident' on the new carpet, not totally his fault ... and although I have the new saw, I have no money for wood, and the weather is turning very cold.
    
</post>
<date>01,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
       I bought the saw!  Sunday afternoon I finally got the table saw. There was no picture available on the Delta site, so I took this one which is almost the same. [update: this is now the right picture]. I could not be happier with it. So far I have not cut any wood with it. I spent one night assembling it, another adjusting it, and listening to the whirr when I turn it on. Every time my hand brushes that razor sharp cross-cut blade, I lose some blood.  Hopefully tonight I will be able to make a few cuts on wood.    urlLink     Congrats to Pablo on his first day of  HOME OWNERSHIP !!!
    
</post>
<date>19,November,2002</date>
<post>
</post>
<date>18,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
         If I was a U.S. city I'd be Seattle, the Emerald City.  What US city are you?  urlLink Take the quiz  by  urlLink Girlwithagun .
    
</post>
<date>13,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Halloween is a distant memory, the snow has arrived and Christmas is in the air. The kids are putting together 'Operation Christmas Child' packages, and Christmas concert practices dominate our calendar. This season induces in me the kind of feeling I get when I see my VISA bill ... that sinking feeling in the pit of my stomach. Maybe the two causes are in reality the same thing. I'm fine by summertime.   
    
</post>
<date>04,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Its four days past Halloween. There were no incidents in our new neighborhood that I have heard of. Last night though, I had to put on my candy cop hat. One of the girls decided that she didn't need real food anymore. She was happy with her new diet of  flavored sugar. I had to tell her that, just like at McD's, BK, and Wendy's -- if she didn't eat her real food, the prizes were mine. Once she realized I was serious about placing the candy on the top shelf, her appetite suddenly returned.    
    
</post>
<date>30,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
          Today was my first day back to work after a wonderful Christmas week off. Ugh! I seem to have picked up a cold during the Christmas break, something I was resistant to for the previous two months, while everyone else in our house was sick. On the bright side, Tomorrow, New Year's Eve, is a 5 hour workday for us Gov't types. Can't complain about THAT.  Santa was kind this year. Mostly $$$ and shop tools. Janet got a FREE **1/3** Megapixel Vivitar Emage 100V digital  camera with her recent cell phone purchase. With 8 MBs of RAM, it can store up to 26 full screen* photos at reasonable Quality. With compression on that number rises to almost 100 photos! The photo of my messy cubicle (above) was from that camera, but I scaled it down by 75%. Of course nothing is truely free, and the price I paid was the camera's software now causes Photoshop 7 to crash on startup. Doh! Well, we have an evening of  food and bowling planned for our New Years Party. Take care, and remember ... when you drink and drive, you lose! ; )   *if you have a VGA monitor!
    
</post>
<date>21,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink        Merry Christmas everybody!  (or all  one  of you that reads this with any regularity!)  With only 4 days to go I wanted to get this note in before it was too late. All four of us have at least the next 12 days off. We will visit family, play with our new toys, and continue the cleaning up process we have been involved in since we've moved into this house.  MOST of our Christmas shopping is done. If anything, I want to go look for alternive grab-box gifts so I can keep the ones I bought -- they're too nice to give away. Or maybe I'll but a few more of the same to keep!  As a Christmas present, my boss let me know [early] that my work term was extended another 3 months from the end of January. Yay. I know it's not his fault, but our terms at work have been short, and we usually only hear the day before they expire, that they have been extended. 
    
</post>
<date>13,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Happy Birthday Janet. Janet gets 35 bumps this morning. She can count them on her newest business tool from Palm Inc while playing Giraffe, the Grafitti learning tool.  urlLink      
    
</post>
<date>10,December,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      The Geniuses in Apple's marketing dept. have done it again... you can now buy a classic G3 iMac, snow white in color, under the moniker of 'Classic' for a mere $1249 [Canadian dollars]. This iMac is identical to mine in all ways but one ... it does not include a CD burner. Yes, now you can Rip and Mix, ... but you can no longer BURN.    urlLink     What confuses ME is that I bought mine a year ago as a 'Special Edition' for </post></Blog>