<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>10,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      there, i hope you are all real happy cause i updated my mother fucking blog.  i'm not happy but how is that different from any other day.  great great now my fuckin music won't play. this has to be the shittiest day of all time.  go to the curling rink cause amanda says that we are supposed to curl tonight and we aren't and she doesn't show up.  i have shit loads of home work, like it will ever get done.  the guys lost at pictonary in bio i have 2 tests tomorrow, and i think i should be working this weekend.  i really hate this.  although the pictonary was so rigged, the girls had the damn teacher, how could they lose.  especially when one of the carogories is biological or chemicle structures.  i hate school, i think i should quit, but then i can't even get a job a mcdicks. 
    
</post>
<date>09,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      now i put links, this is high tech shit
    
</post>
<date>07,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      this better damn well have worked 
    
</post>
<date>07,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      this damn template won't change 
    
</post>
<date>07,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      in 1776 thomas jefferson signed his name on a leaf of marijuna.  betcha didn't now that, and that leaf gave birth to the stupidest country in the world. a place where people can carry guns where ever they want but if they use it they get arrested.  if you can't use it what is the point of having it.  there isn't one.  kurt says that he wasn't dying yestarday but i really think he was, or maybe on crack, but he says hes not that either, not like that big crack head lance.  
    
</post>
<date>07,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      well shit, again its not working how come tech nology hates me, first the pepsi machine wont take my money, so i give it to nolan to try and he gets it first thing then the can wont open now this good damn thing wont do the thing.
    
</post>
<date>07,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      i had to start a brand new blog all because my other one, well no its not because it sucked but because i acually forgot my username and password, but hell now i have this new pretty blog, that really sucks, i had put all of my effort into that blog and now its dead.  but hell now i can start again, this one better not suck or i tells ya there is gonna be hell to pay, for me of coarse.  so really it doesn't effect anyone else.
    
</post>
<date>17,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      god damn tests...well not all of them, i mean i am Metatron king of angles, thats kinda sweet. but i am also a see no evil monkey a fuckin civic and a hufflepuff, what the fuck is a hufflepuff, is that like a brand of marshmallow?  
    
</post>
<date>17,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      old king cole was a marry old soul a marry old soul was he, he called for his pipe and he called for his bolw...i wonder what they were talking about.  why can't everyone be like old king cole, happy.  everyones mad at everyone, cause hats and cds and kelseys and screaming and its not fun. kurt and kayla and sarah and why cant you be fucking friends.  mary had a little gram, but all grams are little, i can't spell, maybe i should get hooked on phonics, it worked for all the other idiots, even some in the states and they are the stupidest kind of idiots.why don't the states use the metric system it makes so much sense.  its so easy.  you can get 240 hectares on a single tank of carosene, which is the same as getting 40 rods to the hogs head.  Oh and the plant is fine...don't be chilly cause chilly ain't never been cool.
    
</post>
<date>26,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      "Congratulations, you are George Christ, brother of Jesus. Although a little on the bitter side, you still love your mom and take care of your environment. You are also notorious for running around wearing only socks on the weekends."  i thought jesus' brother name was al.  
    
</post>
<date>25,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      apperantly i am a vancoverite, how the hell does that work.  i am the almost appidimy of a prarie boy. except i don't chuck hay bales and shit, cause i ain't none hick.  "i think i'll go out to alberta, weathers good there in the fall"
    
</post>
<date>25,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      "You get the FELL-IN-THE-DEEP-FRYER BARBIE!!  You PYROMANIAC!!!!!!   You love love love love fire. You like setting things on fire, including  people. You enjoy mass destruction and chaos within our world, and are not  happy with today's society. You seek friendship with those like yourself,  and you're generally mean to people."  pyromaniac barbie mother fucker.  now has this thig got my number or what.  and i an the classic BIG MAC. 
    
</post>
<date>25,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Laney man, had the cops seen you walking around all crazy acting suspisious at 3 in the morning, i garundamntee you they would have come after you.  Then you would have had the scary side walking cops after you, and then i would laugh.  no more drugs for laney. they seem to be affecting his brain.
    
</post>
<date>25,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      one more little tiny note, sarah i will still be satan, cause its fun people, try it. Evil is good. 
    
</post>
<date>24,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Ladies and gentlemen i Scott "Satan" Mitchell have a new out look on life. I have realized that its not the simalarities between my friends and i that make me like them, i like them for there difference, and who they are. Kurt and his crazy phsycotic unexplanable behaviour, kelsey cause she is ever so screwed up, its funny, laney cause well hes laney, he always nows what i'm thinkin, not like the fat free yogurt thing (only kurt and i will understand that). Vance is one crazy ass son bitch, and i am glad that he is there, b-rock is the most super passive smart person i know. he knows everything. it like " hey b-rock whats the capital of nevada?" and hes all like "its carson city you dumb shit" although i have never heard him say shit, its kinda wierd. And if i went on i would never ever get to sleep. but there is one more that i need to mention, Tara. I was reading her blog and i realized that for years i have been so wrong. so in closing i say this, to any one i have ever hurt in any way, i'm sorry.   and i don't often apoligize for anything so this is a big step for me:)   oh and this entire being mad thing has to stop, its really quite stupid. and if there be any way i can help at any time, i'll probably be home, i lead a very boring life.
    
</post>
<date>24,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      BBBBBBBBBBBAAAAAAAAAAAAHHHHHHHHHHHHHH  now that thats over with, this was a fucky day, laney wasn't there in the morning but he was at noon, i felt like death first peiod then by second i didn't, armestead screwed my dodge ball team over, that short bastard, he pushes the end ball, the only one we ever get off the start, lets his team cheat.  And then bucyk told me that if i bought a cookie she wouldn't give us home work, but she wasn't going to any ways.  She screwed me.  Long and hard.  how come you never see pictures of hell. and all angles are tall and blond...where is everybody else?  It doesn't make sense.  And now George Carlin is coming, so if i have money i will so be going cause he rules.  all my news is bull plop, BULL PLOP  
    
</post>
<date>24,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      damn computers. everytime i get something done they find a way to fuck me over.  i had just finished updating and when i told it to "post  publish", it decided to have an error. and it wouldn't let me reload the damn page, and now i don't remember what i was talking about...except (dream sequence)  something about chuchs getting hit by tornados and race car drivers punching them selves in the head...oh and of coarse the part about tara being wrong and kurts story being right.  and it makes sense cause it has midgets, midgets.  and flying fire breathing monkies.  and bishnu.    kpasa...k watcha call your pasa.  I have the only weather forcast you will ever need... tonight DARK, and continuing dark through the morning,  but thats not all oh no, the weather will keep on changing on and off for a long time.  i have a plan for kurts birthday, we all go to his family liqour store, also known as the pantry, and take it all to the basement, what a night that would be.
    
</post>
<date>02,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Oh and kurt its not used to like you she still does
    
</post>
<date>28,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok well kelsey said just about everything i wanted to but her starting wasn't what min was going to be so... START  FUCK OFF YOU BITCH.  what is up you ass, or is it what do you want up your ass that you can't have.  Sure at one point i was mad, but lets face it people i have anger problems, and up until just recently i was always mad, but now i except things (thanks to my number roughly 7 hero Tara).  You are so jelous, face it you want him but you aren't going to be getting him, EVER.  Oh and as for her spelling, atleast its better than you slbo like grammar, "IS THAT REALLY THAT HARD TO SPELL 'HYENA'".  it should read is IT that hard to spell hyena. and up until tonight i couldn't spell it either, by tomorrow i won't be able to, and i don't give a flying fuck.  Kurt is not going to get hurt, and if he does, there are many people that he could go to for help.  he knows that.  But it won't happen.  In the wise words of the great british band The Who "who the fuck are you".  What kind of friend are you if you can't even be happy for your friends when there happy.  Kelsey is a good person, and she knows that hell you know what Kelsey you are a great person, better than melisa as a matter of fact.  Kelsey does have the right to get mad at you, because YOU ARE BEING A BITCH. you want kurt she got hime.  be happy for him, he's happy now.  And that makes me happy.  Kurt you better stay fuckin happy to cause i need someone to make me happy.  Sure she may not be able to stop you from "representing your feelings", and what the fuck does that mean anyway, but maybe if you stopped being a stupid naggy jelous bitch she wouldn't have to stop you, you would do it yourself.  sure kurt is a mutual friend, but face it melisa there are certain people that you like better than others and kelsey is that person (hopefully i'm still high on that list) and you will never be there.    And the part that pissed me off even more "CALGARY STAMPEADERS KICK ASS!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! " FUCK YOU BITCH Eskies all the way, the cup comes home, to Edmonton not calgaary, oh wait Calgary doesn't even have a chance. Hopefully tomorrow i will be in a good enough mode to post the good news i had.  I was going to do it tonight but because of you now i'm pissed.  I NEED BOOZE OR DRUGS.  Or something that will give me that same feeling. END  thats it g'night 
    
</post>
<date>28,October,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      Like a dog with out a bone.  The doors totally rule, although there is speculation that jim morrison was gay, but i don't think he was.  95 hours until the hockey game, thats 5700 minutes, or 342000 seconds. That really doesn't seem like much, but i am really excited.  Some times ya feel like a nut.  I don't know why i said that. its odd how when your typing things just come out.  oh and i found out that jesus' brothers name was Bob, which makes sense cause the song is called jesus' brother bob.  its really cold, i don't like it.  why isn't it summer, then it could be my birthday, and warm.    Keep on rockin in the free world people.  it can only help 
    
</post>
<date>09,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      No one knows what its like to be the bad man...to be the sad man, behind blue eyes what a great song, it totally expreces how people can see one a person as one thing when the person is the exact oppisite.  i think i have finally compiled my list of heros 1. Steve Austin - meanest sob that ever lived 2. Steve Erwin - dumbest man a live but intilled of love of reptiles in me 3. Kurt - CRAZY 4. laney and vance - no real reason but they have to be there   thats as far as i've gotten for now, but eventualy i will complete it. Damn you, Damn you all i dunno why but your all damned.  DONT YOU WANNA RAIN DANCE  if vance tells you something is good always beleive him, he's never wrong, like with the coral, he also says the doors rule.  Vance is no chumpsain not like that damn cole, what a rekazoid. i think thats it for now, but i'm not sure so it will be  bye all
    
</post>
<date>04,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      oh life is good for once. i am in the absolute best mood of my life. i have never been happpier.  My entire day was good.  especially the end.  Kelsey and Kurt know what the hell i'm talking about, but thats it, no one else.  All my troubles have seemed to melt away it the last little while, i am completly relaxed (finally no risk of a heart attack).  WOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO  
    
</post>
<date>03,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      ok melissa we all know that it was you that was concerned.  And now you are trying to cover it up.  Well guess what its not working.  If you didn't give a shit YOU wouldn't have posted it in YOUR blog.  And i don't care if the football thing, football is all this city has, look at the hockey team, they suck.  so you chose to hangout with other people, no one cares.  and being a stuck up bitch isn't a good thing, it makes people dis like you, i would even go as far as to say hate you.  You do like kurt, you told me and i qoute "I am jelous", this being your response to the question why don't you like kelsey.  alright thats it bye
    
</post>
<date>03,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      i hate my life. finally i find someone that i want to ask out, but no. i'm to fucking stupid to do it.  god damn mother fucking me.  i hate it cause shes perfect, but i'm and idiot. a fucking retard.  is that spelt right, knowing me probably not.   FFFFFFFFFFFFFUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUUCCCCCCCCCCCCCCKKKKKKKKKKKK  wow i really feel better now
    
</post>
<date>23,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      i had a fan fuckin tabulus night last night.  And i want everyone to know that.  And now i am in the best mood ever, and it won't go away, cause i have cinamon gum, and altoids.  I now have a favorite night of the week, FRIDAY.  fridays rule.  lanny you doubted me, and i did that thing and then when i went to send it, it said it didn't recognize and email adress, so i went to look at them and i hit the wrong button and it closed, but i did it.  and you thought i wouldn't.    Peace outside  ASSCRACKER
    
</post>
<date>17,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      damn its been a long time since i did this.  But i figured i should cause...well i dunno, i really have no reason, or anything to talk about.  HAPPY BIRTHDAY JERKASS.  you know who i'm talkin about.  your finally 16, took ya friggin well long enough.  Jesus.  i have no idea what to say, so i'm leaving and cartoons are starting soon, YAY cartoons.
    
</post>
<date>27,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      life never seems so bleak until you realize, youve lost it all. one day your the king of the world. the next you just another nobody, trapped for eternity lost in space. thats the day when you wake up and realize, that it was all a dream there was never anything you always were and always will be a nobody
    
</post>
<date>26,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      i wish i were dead. simple post.  i wish i were dead
    
</post>
<date>26,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      i am so bored right now.  i really could use something to do.  sigh.  i haven't been this bored in a long time.  "i have hours only lonley".  singin the song of my life.  Behind Blue Eyes, the Who.  great song.  i could clean my room it needs to be done, but that sounds even more boring.  I NEED SOMETHING TO DO!!!!  ASSCRACKER
    
</post>
<date>25,November,2002</date>
<post>

	 
      "Life is a game that no one wins" well i'm winning.  Life is acually going my way for once.  things are great, and i know that i'm not dreaming it all.  although it felt like  i was for a while, but tara told me that it was real.  According to driver training guy i have a speeding problem, but who doesn't go 20 over.  and residential areas, who cares.  its more fun in there.  thats about it, just had to say i had another great day, thats a new record, 4 in a row.    ASSCRACKER
    
</post>
<date>08,March,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      november 27th, that was a hell of a long time ago, so, lets play hardball. what the hell is wrong with you people.  its like you want to go throught this "lets pick sides" thing again.  Its fuckin stupid.  if you don't want to be near somebody, don't.  If you don't want to talk to them, don't.  its not that hard of a thing to figure out.  lance is the only one acually doing it the right way.  maybe people should take some fucking lessons.  but this can't all be blammed on us.  Kurt, its not that like people are trying to lose you as a friend, thats the last thing I would want, but you spend all your time with her, you follow her every where, you do everything she tells you to do.  its not that people don't want you as a friend, people just don't want the two of you to come as a package, your friend but not hers.  and thats how it is.  lance is the onl smart one out of all of us, and brock.  cause brock is like, super smart.  
    
</post>
<date>12,March,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      :. Punk is also a young, untrained circus elephant.  :.greatest definition of all time.   :. </post></Blog>