<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hello guys! This blog was created so that we could keep in touch until the day of The Reunion. Also, mucho thanks to Mr Lee's suggestion to place the count-down-meter online! There's a count-down script, photo gallery and a tag-board at the right hand side of the page. (More to come) Til' then, take care and all the best for your prelims.  " Dream the dreams that have never been dreamt. " -- David Bower     The Six Mistakes of Man  1. The delusion that personal gain is made by crushing others. 2. The tendency to worry about things that cannot be changed or corrected. 3. Insisting that a thing is impossible because we cannot accomplish it. 4. Refusal to set aside trivial preferences. 5. Neglecting development and refinement of the mind, and not acquiring the habit of reading or studying. 6. Attempting to compel others to believe and live as we do.     Credits:   urlLink  http://asc.iwarp.com/attitude.html   urlLink    
    
    
</post>
<date>30,June,2003</date>
<post>

     
      I'm drinking pineaple juice. yummers.
     
    
</post>
<date>29,June,2003</date>
<post>

     
      First days are so  exhausting  i tell ya.. fortunately  mr lee  was absent today and we had 2 periods of free time. the other 2 math periods were spent on congruency by 2 relief teachers  mr wong  (i think) and  miss ng . mr wong resembles  clay aiken  so yeah, that was actually pretty cool. the guys and  jiax  actually thought i had a crush on him. * tsssk ..which is so not true haha. anyways, ms ng came in 1 period later.. and  nic  and her had a loong chat. she was from rgs! cool. she went around then came to MY desk. played with mah  mr bean  teddy keychain and childishly said to herself  "ayee so cute!!"  then she suddenly turned to me and asked curiously,  "are you a eurasian?"  then i gave her this  -.-"""  look.  Hmmm.. i hate to be rude but i honestly don't quite like her.. =\  i dislike people who purchase tinted contacts. she has grey ones. yuk.    Mr hang  came and spoke to us today as well. although he didn't quite emphasize on what he actually wanted to as he kept cutting in with all kinds of diff experience.. the msg he actually wanted to bring across to us is to not look down on ourselves..must be confident..etc =) yeah. to find out more, read  nic 's (amelia) blog. he's a gd principal i know.  After assembly, we had a spot check. hahaaa we pretty much humiliated myself in front of my classmates and teachers.  mrs abdul  wanted our blouses tucked into our skirts/pants all the way. aah. like  lin yi qin . *tsk tsk. damn funny though. lols. we looked so much like geeks! i had a tummyache after laughing too much.  Anyways,  nic  eats too much whip potatoes..  =\ nic, cut down on that will ya? you don't wanna turn into a potato do ya? hahaaa =P  
     
    
</post>
<date>29,June,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Yo yo wassup wassup. hmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmmm. bored =)  zuhayr  hasn't started his homework yet. i'm gonna work on the chinese essays and ss workbk soon. chinese 1st priority though.. cos there would be chinese tomorrow, according to  chongyan 's sms for  monday's new timetable . (eng, MT, math, PE).  tres b uno , rmbr to bring ur books and assignments! and also..  miss koh  wants us to bring  TYS  tmrw. *sighs. it's gonna be a boring monday.   Ciao sexy pple. take care. don't pon school tomorrow (zu) =P rmbr to watch  star search  tonight. i've been anticipating it for quite some time now. *hug hug!*
     
    
</post>
<date>28,June,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Valerene  and i have decided not to go for our kayaking course today. instead, we would be attending the 2 day course on the 6th and 13th of July.  Hopefully  nothing crops up at the very last moment. just 2 days back, we were informed that the  Police knowledge  course would last for 3 days, instead of 2. the test was held at  Training command  (Tracom in short, also known as the Police academy) today.  Everything went smoothly.. in the beginning, we had to march a longass distance to the lecture theatre. then we were brought to air-conditioned classrooms =) we combined classes with  queenstown sec  for the test.. they were pretty.. crazy like us. our PCIs were  really  nice. he allowed us to cheer and stuff while the other classes had to shut their mouths up for the entire 3 hours +..  =P After the test we wenta' change into our quarter Us and this group of annoying fucktards (PCIs) totally abused their authority!  i hate them . i know i once said,  it takes a lot of energy to hate someone . however in this case, they are SO worth to be despised and blacklisted. i hope one of them accidentally comes across my site and reads this. yay. i hate you.   Lunch was  okkaaay . i had carrot cake with  ma'am  jess ,  fungi kor , val,  jeff  and the other CIs. then got home while the rest wenta' catch  charlies angels  full throtle. aaah. tired.. ahaa. anyways!  today  is a special day. so i shall take some time to think about things. take care lovers =D *teehee.
     
    
</post>
<date>27,June,2003</date>
<post>

     
      I'm moodswinging now, and i'm feeling really giddy... 
     
    
</post>
<date>26,June,2003</date>
<post>

     
      On   wednesday  ... The  tres B uno  BBQ finally! while we were on our way to west coast park, it started pouring. so we walked under the rain slowly and drenched ourselves totally. took my towel out to shelter  amily ,  kalyn  and myself then we hid under a tree. haha. so weird. then  jason (weihoong) had a  brilliant  idea to go to the beach cos' it was windy. we stayed there and wet ourselves further while  jess ,  ruth  and  siti  wenta' ginza plaza to get some stuff from shop and save.  georgia  and  hafiz  came a coupla' minutes after.. under the rain as well. haha. this family left the lil' hut/shelter so we took the entire thing to ourselves. like  yay  finally someplace dry. =)  while it was still raining cats and dogs.. the hut started to flood! teehee. we lay garbage bags (clean ones) on the ground and all sat around and played  DARE . before you do the dare.. each of us would hafta' eat a nut with  wasabi !  yukk!  mine turn came then it was quite gross lar.. and my dare was by stoopid  jason  haha. i hadta' sit on  jeremy's  lap and do some hug hug thing while they took a picture. some other really fun 'dares' was siti's when she had to unzip  lucas's  shirt and hugged him from behind?? and ruth's boogie dance! later we had lunch at KFC... then flew kite.. climbed pyramid.. took pics ;) teehee.. walk a lot too..  jeremy , amily,  simon  and i wenta' pick  miss koh  up from the bus stop. wooh. couldn't recognise her from far. then jeremy walked  barefooted  from the park to the bus stop cos his socks were soaked. lols. stinky feet! =P when we got back the guys were already producing some work! very impressed. you should've seen jason fanning the fire and all that. haha. so zai!  kenneth  and the other dudes also helped.. then the girls (ruth, amily, karen, geraldine, eileen, jess, siti, myself, kalyn) all helped out to prepare the food :) most of us were helping to thaw the 1/4 frozen chicken with our hands (wore plastic gloves) teehee then ruth the no.1 chicken poker taught all of us how to use the " zhu zhen " (according the gerald! it's the long satay stick) to pierce the chicken really nicely. it was something like the  fang tai  cooking show ahha. all the house wives learning how to cook! lols.. then we started speaking in mandarin cos' we wanted to help gerald, eileen and ruth to revise for their chinese orals.. lols!  karen  made me laugh so much =P after dinner with the teachers ( ms halizah  came later too), games.. i wenta' play soccer with the guys!! ;) was hilarious.. cos'  zuhayr  let me kick in 2 goals teehee =P  siti  told us ghost stories and freaked miss koh out.. then we wenta' the mush track thingy? i duno what is it called.. each had to find a partner and walk in the dark.. pretty scary.. then we all started screaming and freaking each other out!! did lotsa' stuff then cleaned up the place.. by then it was already 9pm++.. took a pic altogether then left.. really sleepy and happy =)     Today  ..  had  police knowledge  course at school. since we were the host, there were a lot of things to be done by us.. it was pretty tiring but it got better later. we got to serve them food in a buffet style. =) anyways the course was from 8am-5pm and i'm really beat now.. still gotta polish boots for tmrw.  I was really upset when i found out that there was a 3rd day for the course.  the test . honestly, i would rather go to the kayaking course. * tsssssk . really extremely confused cos i don't know what to do.. until  fungi kor  suggested something.. felt relieved afterwhich.  however ,  mr lau  later sms-ed and said that the test would end at 10am, when my kayaking course starts at 10am too. and it takes like 1 hour to get there by taxi i think. * sighs . geeeshhh okay wanna go polish my boots oredi. ciao friends! =) *huggles*  And  welcome back joanne!  haha. =)
     
    
</post>
<date>24,June,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Yongjie  makes a great study partner. he shuts up when we're doing work and yaks non-stop while we were having lunch. anyways, i have completed my 3 english essays and humanities source-base assignment. goodie. i know that is not a lot but hey, that's better than staying at home for 24/7 and not doing a single shit rite? teehee.  Now it's time to partehhh at tomorrow's class BBQ!  yeehaw .
     
    
</post>
<date>23,June,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Puppies for sale    A farmer had some puppies he needed to sell. He painted a sign advertising the pups and set about nailing it to a post on the edge of his yard. As he was driving the last nail into the post, he felt a tug on his overalls. He looked down into the eyes of a little boy.   Mister," he said, "I want to buy one of your puppies."   "Well," said the farmer, as he rubbed the sweat off the back of his neck, "these puppies come from fine parents and cost a good deal of money."   The boy dropped his head for a moment. Then reaching deep into his pocket, he pulled out a handful of change and held it up to the farmer. "I've got thirty-nine cents. Is that enough to take a look?"  "Sure," said the farmer.   And with that he let out a whistle,"Here, Dolly!" he called.  Out from the doghouse and down the ramp ran Dolly followed by four little balls of fur. The little boy pressed his face against the chain link fence. His eyes danced with delight.   As the dogs made their way to the fence, the little boy noticed something else stirring inside the doghouse. Slowly another little ball appeared; this One noticeably smaller. Down the ramp it slid. Then in a somewhat awkward manner the little pup began hobbling toward the others, doing its best to catch up....  "I want that one," the little boy said, pointing to the runt.   The farmer knelt down at the boy's side and said, "Son, you don't want that puppy. He will never be able to run and play with you like these other dogs would."  With that the little boy stepped back from the fence, reached down, and began rolling up one leg of his trousers. In doing so he revealed a steel brace running down both sides of his leg attaching itself to a specially made shoe. Looking back up at the farmer, he said, "You see sir, I don't run too well myself, and he will need someone who understands."    
     
    
</post>
<date>23,June,2003</date>
<post>

     
      The Japanese buffet dinner was wonderful. i'm bloated. i  looove  tempuras. it has been quite some time since i've consumed really really  really  fresh prawns. the chefs prolly deep fried them while those pathetic creatures were still struggling for help =\ haha. i really don't know. i had quite a lot of fun with my god-mother, lil cousin and my grandma. it wasn't that bad afterall. i actually felt quite comfortable around them. i would appreciate it though, if they'd speak up more often and crack some corny jokes! because that is what  my  family usually does. i adore fun people. =D  Anyways, i had  better  wake up by 9.30am tomorrow.  Yongjie  and i might be workin on our homework together. hopefully he is able to make it. besides, i need to write a compo of characterisation all about him! so i should really get to know him better. i would then be killing two birds with one stone.   Yongjie unable to make it = no motivation = zilch productivity!!   * Tsk!!  at least if someone goes, i'll be able to force mahself to do something. 
     
    
</post>
<date>22,June,2003</date>
<post>

     
      I don't know if  urlLink this  can help any of you but i sure did learn a lil' about guitars  urlLink here . just some facts.   Anyways, i'm gonna get changed now. my parents are taking my sissas, cousins, a coupla' relatives and i out to this japanese restaurant at circular road. somehow or rather, i ain't excited about it at all. maybe cos' i don't really feel comfortable eating out with my relatives. it's just  weird . til' then, keep groovin guys.
     
    
</post>
<date>22,June,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Each morning i awake to the euphonious guitar chords played by my lil' sissa  Serene , which is supposed to be a mimic of an alarm as i do not have a sound proof bedroom door. however, it seems more like a lullaby than an alarm as i am simply reluctant to get out of bed. i have absolutely no life at all. the following is my daily dosage:  - brunch, alone in front of the telly - bath time babeh - computer!  yeehaw!  (im a net geek) - telly time - dinner -  more  telly  - slack and unwind - read (magazines  only !) - nitey mates   Yesterday was mucho productive though. i went ta daddy's club for a swim. not forgetting, i caught  the hulk  with a coupla' seniors. it was an average movie.  I seriously gotta do something about this. sucks big time yo. this will prolly be my last entry ever cos' i will no longer be alive after this night. my parents are going to chop off my head and eat it for supper because i have yet to complete my holiday assignments and i am addicted to the frickin web design programme on my puter.  fuckkkkkkkk . Oh well life wasnt that fun anyways.. everyone who reads this is invited to my funeral. i hope you miss me. TOODLES!! 
     
    
</post>
<date>22,June,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Ever miss getting some old fashioned love letters? you know on paper and with ink.. with postage stamps. considering the rampant spread of e-mail, the chances of actually receiving a real flesh and blood letter are so slim as to be laughable.. but never fear, the internet solves all problems. Since the next best thing to a real love letter is a scanned one,  urlLink here is a site  that has exactly that: scanned love letters. 300 of them!
     
    
</post>
<date>21,June,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Zuhayr  wants me to teach him how to play the guitar once i have  mastered  it.   Buttttt... since i'm learning it  on my own  (yes without anyone's help! tssk), it'll prolly take me a coupla years -.-" Who knows, i might even give up in just a coupla' days. HA!  It's kinda fun though.. as i was chatting with zuhayr and  jeremy  online last night, i printed out the guitar chords and strummed 2 songs by  avril lavigne , i felt so satisfied. ;) it's very very difficult hey.. fingers pain le. I think i should get some tips from  bingrui  and  huizhen (whitney) then go to  phoebe's  place to do some major jammin with her drumset. that would be cool.
     
    
</post>
<date>20,June,2003</date>
<post>

     
      I'm piggin out on popcorns now.  Mmmmm.
     
    
</post>
<date>20,June,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Just as i thought i was at my lowest..   he called  :) :) :) :) :) :) :) :) :) :) :) :) :) :) :) :) :) :) :) :)
     
    
</post>
<date>17,June,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Remember, don't waste time comparing your life to others who seem more fortunate. being fortunate is based on how much peace you have, not how many luxuries or conveniences you have. practice from the heart to make peace with what is, then life gives you more help to change things for the better.  -  Doc Childre  
     
    
</post>
<date>17,June,2003</date>
<post>

     
        YAY  orz! I'm back from a 3 day 2 night Adventure Training Camp (NPCC) at Pulau Ubin. it was so incredibly enthralling and memorable.  natalie ,  valerene ,  hafiz ,  jeff ,  chihwei  and I were selected among our other squadmates to assist the sirs and ma'ams at the camp. we were considered as NCOs there. =D those secondary 2 kids were so adorable. they could not quit addressing me as "ma'am". same goes for nat and all. that was the very first time i felt.. "BIG".      Day 1   Left school for the jetty at Changi then took a ferry to PU. hiked a long ass distance to the campsite with all the heavy 'barang barang'. the 6 of us were the first to arrive with a coupla' sirs cos we had to unpack all the food rations, tent-pitching equipment and stuff. we had to do most of the 'dirty work'.  The secondary 2 cadets took quite awhile to settle down. they took almost up to 2 hours to pitch their tents (4 to each) when a team of 8 can actually do it in 15 minutes. afterwhich, own activities.. while the NCOs had to take care of a lot of other stuff. so tiring k. dinner was quite fun.. outdoor cooking. had instant noodles and some can food. i looove pineapples! the weird thing is that, everyone at the camp seems to have a fetish for pineapples.  Activities til' damn late. mock campfire was hilarious. the NCOs helped out a lil' in the cheering part then  sir yongfa  did some silly dances.. =D got to know some cute ACS(I) guys cos' i sat beside them during the mock campfire. haha. NCOs took our bath at 11 plus. i slept at.. hmm.. 1am ++? cos this annoying freak sir SO had to wake val, nat and i up in the girls dorm to switch dorms.. *tsk tsk.   But before that.. we were enjoyin ourselves bathing.. while the sec 2s all had to knock it down duno how many? stay in pumpin position.. under sir kiwi.. so don't expect him to be merciful.. cos truthfully, a bunch of em' were blatently rude and rowdy.  very  disappointing.      Day 2   Woke up to the bellowing of  sir benghui  and that  dragonball dude  at 6am ++ during the sec 2's physical training. so many casualties! heard they kana pumping lotsa times. Jeff cooked noodles for nat and i then we became nurses of the day. heh. gotta take care of those poor lil' souls. some were faking. their acting skills seriously suck big time. *sigh*  All left for  the amazing race  around pulau ubin from 9am-4pm.  sir kiwi  made the NCOs in charge of the casualties and we had to stay indoors. they had to do area cleaning! at first i thought sir kiwi was being really mean to get the sick ppl to wash the toilets and stuff. however, sir kiwi has done all those first aid crapola shitznitzz before and he could tell who were really sick and who weren't. power rite. the cadets i was in charge of were really obedient. on the other hand, val's group of boys were a disaster. they tried to lock her in the campers toilet.. sprayed water at her..point middle finger.. blah blah. val complained to  sir alan . all knock it down. sir alan so zai!!!  This new town boy kept asking nat what my name was  then when i walked down the slope to check on them scrubbin the messtins at the campers toilet, he began following me everywhere i went and wanted me to tell him my telephone number, address and 'if i gotta boyfriend or not?' or else he would not stop followin.. he's quite funny larh.. but must maintain NCO standard sia.. haha.. so me just smile at him talk abit and made sure that he wasn't 'eating snake'. then.. hmm.. cleaned somemore.. slacked big time.. let them rest.. very soon it was 4pm plus and the teams from the amazing race returned all bushed. sec 2s kana pumping  again ... this buncha' campers are so nonchalent. Dinner was provided by Mr Lau. (yay!) he treated the NCOs to friedrice. glad he knew we were sick of the instant noodles. campfire til' 10 plus.. er it was quite alright lar. kinda' boring but erm quite funny? once again, they kana pump. *sigh* NCOs took our baths at 11 plus then nat, val and i decided to sleep in the canteen with some of the sirs and ma'ams. sir kiwi spoke to us.. wow.. raised mah confidence level and i really appreciated what he had told us. me was so effin' cold.. practically freezing! could not sleep cos the benches were er, hard? -.-"     Day 3   Woke up early. had lotsa' things to settle cos it's the final day. PT as usual. shared noodles with jeff then packed our bags.. packed rations into boxes.. we were treated like servants and dogs.. did dirty work told by sirs. those mean mean ones from new town especially. i don't quite like em. even had to take out all the 34 sets of bed sheets and pillow covers all those crapola shitznitzz then fold them and all tt... val say next time no job we shld work at ritz carlton hotel clean hotel rooms. -.-" later.. packed those tent equipment.. etc etc from 7am plus to 10 plus just kept being told to do all the work loh. today  sir OJ  allowed us to PUMP THE CADETS! wow. but none of us did.. took group pix then left the campsite.. hiked back to jetty then back to where i belong hehe.   OKie gonna sleep now... toodles.
     
    
</post>
<date>17,June,2003</date>
<post>

     
      I'm outta' this island for the next 3 days.  Til' then, keep groovin honehs. ^_~
     
    
</post>
<date>16,June,2003</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink This  is interesting. I scored a 6. =\
     
    
</post>
<date>14,June,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Morning good people. the weather right now is suprisingly cool. an estimation of 28 degree celsius. bloody awesome hey! I wish some things would stay the way it is. unfortunately,  nic  is right. things do change, people do change. but we can't just put the blame on people/objects. that isn't what life is all about. we have to accommodate ourselves to the new requirements from time to time, which I admit, can suck at times. life is all about challenging ourselves. without obstacles, life would be effin' uninteresting wouldn't it?  That is why I believe everything that we are put to go through in life happens for a cause. we just have to sit back, and think calmly of what we ought to learn from it. 
     
    
</post>
<date>14,June,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Did I mention?  Sir Faizal  got posted to  OCS!  (officer cadet school)  yay!  that's the best mmkay. =D  he wanted to give me a suprise the other day at the campfire but  Bernard  had to ruin everything by leakin it out to me before he could say anything. that butthead.  -.-""""   Sir Faizal rocks me and mah socks. (:
     
    
</post>
<date>14,June,2003</date>
<post>

     
       The Campfire    urlLink Entrance  Entrance of the campfire at the dungeon gate.  urlLink The sirs and I  Taken with  Sir Faizal  and  Sir BengHui .  urlLink Yati, me, Xiupin  Don't ask me why I always look blurry.  urlLink Nana and I!  I love nasuha. (:   urlLink Chaos  Some dancing game thing.  urlLink Bernard and Yati  They were forced to.  urlLink Me and Jess  In the midst of the campfire.    At the funeral    urlLink Serene  Lil' sissa lying in the tent.  urlLink Cousins and I  Slackin in the tent.  urlLink Ketchup  Coussie's dog
     
    
</post>
<date>14,June,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Avril Lavigne  Why    Everytime I hear this song it just makes me wanna cry. I guess why I love it so much is because I can relate to it heaps.
     
    
</post>
<date>13,June,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Avril Lavigne  Chop suey (system of a down cover)    This just had to make me laugh so badly.
     
    
</post>
<date>13,June,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Nobody gets too much heaven no more It's much harder to come by I'm waiting in line Nobody gets too much love anymore It's as high as a mountain And harder to climb. 
     
    
</post>
<date>13,June,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Remember my  grandfather  who was been admitted into the hospital during the SARS outbreak in april?   He passed away at  8.15  this morning...
     
    
</post>
<date>13,June,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Thanks for the reminder from  michelle  that today is  Friday the 13th .  Actually.. whether you're gonna make today fulfilling and fun.. or depressing and unproductive, it's all in one's state of mind.   Good luck to  Sir Faizal  for his posting tomorrow! oh yes, i have decided to go to the guide's campfire. initially i didn't feel like attending cos' i would be the only girl. however, i managed to get  nana ,  jo ,  ros  and  kasinah  to come along. now i wouldn't feel alone! =D  yipee!  and about tmrw's shooting competition, i'm feeling really psyched. i can't wait.  Girls just wanna have fun..
     
    
</post>
<date>12,June,2003</date>
<post>

     
       The positive side of life   Living on Earth is expensive, but it does include a free trip around the sun every year.      How long a minute is depends on what side of the bathroom door you're on.   Birthdays are good for you; the more you have, the longer you live.   Happiness comes through doors you didn't even know you left open.   Ever notice that the people who are late are often much jollier than the people who have to wait for them?   You may be only one person in the world, but you may also be the world to one person.   Some mistakes are too much fun to only make once.   Don't cry because it's over; smile because it happened.   A truly happy person is one who can enjoy the scenery on a detour.   Have an awesome day, and know that someone who thinks you're great has thought about you today!..   "And that person was me."..... Please don't keep this message to yourself.....send it to those who mean so much to you.... "NOW"....    urlLink Sticker   urlLink print .
     
    
</post>
<date>12,June,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Holy cow!! everyone go download this song " Should i stay " by  Dreamz FM !!!!  The guys from  the bachelorette  were soo hawtt. i was in awe when i realised how many professionals there were among the 25 bachelors! geezes christ! there was even a breast implant sales man.   Alrighty gotta rush to meet  amily  at the mall! that gurl ahh.. haha. last min called and asked if i could get some token of appreciation for the campfire tmrw. oh ya, should i go? i will prolly be the only girl from the npcc going...
     
    
</post>
<date>12,June,2003</date>
<post>

     
      The chinese oral was a disaster! * screams into pillow * i swear what i said during the convo was a direct translation of english to mandarin. to make things worse, my examiner is the HOD of mother tongue. geez, looks like i shouldn't even think about passing this time. i bet even  sir faizal's  mandarin is better than mine. what idiom..  "bu dao huang he....." ?? i honestly do not know what it means and neither have i heard of it. =X this reminds me, i should set a new target for chinese. =)  B3 . kkies yaa.. settled!   While waiting for my turn durin oral i sms-ed  gabriel  (fengrui) ask whether he wanna watch movie then he str8 away replied and said ok and asked for the venue and all tt. but after oral he totally became sooper wishy washy.. * tsk tsk  he couldn't make up his mind where to go. but in the end we went.  jiax , him and i took bus no. 7 to town. we decided to go to PS to catch the 12.35pm show. (i was forced to watch  JU-ON  by jiax!) but gab left we 2 poor girls to watch the horror flick after he received a phone call from his friends. he's sucha meanie k. so jiax and i caught the 12.10pm show. i think lotsa' ppl mistook us for  lesbos  cos' we were practically hugging each other in the theatre! =\ if u see us from behind you might think tt we were making out and humping each other! haaha.. then we took the popcorn box and chips wrapper to cover our faces (eyes to be exact) and were the only ones screaming. so not fun k! the movie was quite alright lar.. scary as in.. a lot of scenes where the ghost (whatever) suddenly appear tt type.. typical jap horror flick. it's not a 'must watch' though. if you have lotsa' cash in your pocket and ure bored on a hot afternoon then you might wanna see it..   Rushed back to clementi for shooting practice.. * phew *  sadiq  and i were late together haha so we walked to skl to meet them. =) poor  pinky  she waited for about 45 mins for us! =\ and she was soo beat from all the drills. heard from her tt some timings change oredi... after the prac,  mashafiz ,  nat  and i wenta' the mall to walk walk. we went to harvey norman then being the dork tt i am, i began playing on the electronic organ (damn cool) then mas was soooper funny make us laugh until stomache! =X they had more than 100 songs installed in the organ loh. so cool.. we bluffed this cute little girl.. we just anyhow banged on the organ and she actually tot we were playing the actual thing. it was so easy for us. hahaaa so mega lame i tell ya! =b   Kkies gotta eat dinner now.. i'm expecting a visitor later. btw, i saw  jingping  on telly! channel news asia. this afternoon at the hee-uge screen in the mall. coooolies. haha. called her lil' bro and told him.. then he was like " huh she on tv!!!? really? " haha so cute. ciao and tc!
     
    
</post>
<date>11,June,2003</date>
<post>

     
        Singapore Chinese Girls' school    urlLink   wat school in singapore are u suitable to go?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
     
    
</post>
<date>11,June,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Ahoy there. kkies..  shan ,  jo  and i wenta' siloso beach. mother nature was so nice to us ok. first it was effin' sunny. * does the happy dance * tanned a lil'. looked at the hotties a lil (none as hot as him though). then after about 30 mins, mr sunshine disappeared then down came the rain. =\ perfect weather hey. especially when the purpose of our trip to sentosa was to bake ourselves.  *Yawnss* tmrw would be scary. =) chinese oral exam. haha. last year during the convo with the teacher i was practically mumbling.. nothing came out. absolutely nothing. but the teacher was nice! not only did she prompt and help me with words that i wanted to use but didn't know how to.. she gave me a passing mark.  Mmkays i'm gonna fill up the form for my kayakin course.. hopefully there are still vacancies!! i will self mutilate if there ain't any left. =( i'm crazy about this course.  Sleep tight sweethearts. don't let the bed bugs bite.
     
    
</post>
<date>28,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      hi peeps! my net broke dowm somehow and i'm desperate to blog... so!! i got mah hamsty-gal-buddy to update for me. thanks eileen.  life has been a struggle. ahaha. ok maybe not that bad hey, but 5 tests per week is a  killer ! =x very tired. the class is getting cranky too. they brought hamsters today and it was rambling all over the classroom. lol. ok, short blog...  miss everyone out there! take care!! *smucks*!  - invaded by eileen! :))
     
    
</post>
<date>22,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      I do not know how to explain this.. but right now, there seems to be a turning point in my life. something.. positive =) 
     
    
</post>
<date>21,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      It was fun today. played basketball with  jeremy ,  simon ,  rongmin ,  jess ,  sheena ,  amily ,  jason (hoongy) and a coupla' others.. haha. we beat the  ex-2D1  team. we rock! *hugs team members* haha.. the match was soo crazy.. kept screaming.. had lessons which were very lifeless.. after skl, wenta' meet  faizal  (not bin noordin haha) from  tanglin sec  with  val .. he's workin at watsons.. yupps. anyways, we had lunch and talked a bit before he walked the both of us to the mrt and bus stop.   Heard a distinctive voice from behind me.  jason  :D and his friends -.-"""  timothy  and the other guy + i pretended we didn't know jason. he was SO embarassing us! *tsk. kept laughing for no reason.. haha. but i see him also wanna laugh.. so yeah, was pretty hilarious.   I made a blog this afternoon. dedicated to  HIM . i'll feel better after getting stuff outta' mah chest then =) i will  blog my writings in there from now onwards..
     
    
</post>
<date>20,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Haha! i just found these 2 pics from an old diskette, which were taken a year back. i am still in shock...            So cute right? lols! if you're wondering who those guys are.. the first pic features the ever so popular  medwin  teng tw on the right and  shaun , who now looks entirely different with his copper red, spiky hair. in the 2nd pic.. again, shaun standing up, and  kenneth .   I had no idea how boys can change so much in sucha' short period of time. now i do.
     
    
</post>
<date>19,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
        "sometimes goodbye though it hurts in your heart is the only way for destiny. sometimes goodbye though it hurts is the only way now for you and me."     Buenos dias ! (good morning in spanish) approximately an hour to  boot camp !! * wacka wacka! * :D  Anyways, i was so pooped last night that as i was smsing TS  faizal , i totally zonked out. i dreamt that daddy gave me money to buy the  ripcurl  slingbag. haha. this morning when i awoke to my lil' sister's rants.. (=X) i was smiling to myself. i checked my wallet. but i only saw a few pathetic pieces of paper in it. * sigh... * 
     
    
</post>
<date>19,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
       "Meet me tonight in the moonlight.. meet me tonight all alone.. i've got something to show you.. something that's yellow and looooong!"     Vanakam  , my lovelies! yesterday was the 2.4km run.. i was honestly very pessimistic about it. on the other hand.. i felt so touched when i heard and saw  all  my friends cheering for me.. all my  2c1  ol' buddies..  valerene ,  zara ,  jo ,  shan ,  nat ,  esther ,  mich ,  shuyi ,  LAIKIU ...even the guys! whom i'm not close with..  shaun  especially? could hear him shouting my name.. then someone was sayin "pearlyn your face is very red!" ... also heard jo shouting that i can't give up since i've come this far.. then i heard a lot of "go pearlyn! you can do it!! c'mon!!" hahaa..  thank you...  everyone =) after i ran non-stop for 7 rounds.. i sprinted during the last round cos i tot time was going to be up.. then zara was jumping up and down hahaa.. then sprant.. to mr loh.. then he clocked my timing and said i did well. but...when me sprint finish.. i couldn't breathe.. then my inhaler was with  amelia  darling.. and i was struggling to say out her name.. luckily  lucas  was behind me and asked if i was ok.. i kept pointing towards amelia then he was all blur blur.. then like kept doing hand signals then the pple around kept shouting for amelia.. then she was like my "missy" (nurse).. took out my inhaler from her pouch where we put all our stuffs and passed it to me.    Val  cried cos she missed 2 secs to get 'A'.. then she say mr ng talkin to someone else then give her timing late. sigh. so she very angry loh.. kept swearing  IN FRONT OF ME . she knows that detest vulgarities. sigh. but ... it's okay lah.. she kinda apologised.. but i understand.. that's her, when she's furious. the day didn't get any better later though. unfortunately, jo lost her wallet. we searched high and low for it. nopes. so she went home depressed. our outing to celebrate ame's birthday in town was cancelled.  dad  called me. wanted me to go home right away, get changed and all. cos' couzie's havin house-warming. so like, i reluctantly went home and had to leave ames, val and shan.. saw  yongfa  at clementi interchange.  Couzie's house is really pretty =) a condo.. at sengkang.. like resort =D =D =D the pool is soo beautiful. i was telling my sister  cherryn ... if this is considered really cool, then i think i would've probably fainted if i were to join the  the bachelor  and stay in that kick butt bungalow loh. can die i tell you!! so zai! had bbq.. then did lotsa' stuff with my couzies too.. we caught an insect from the water at the fountain and left it in the cup =\ oh man.. the good ol' days! i don't know if many of you girls out there used to do this lah.. but last time when i stayed in my old place.. i had very fun neighbours who were mostly around my age. mostly boys. and this 1 girl from nanyang i rmbr clearly. we would go to the playground and behind it there's a huge drain where there were heaps of tadpoles. then once i took the net from my home cos' i had a fish pond with lotsa' kois.. then my grandmother found out that i took the net.. she scolded me! she didn't allow me to. so we had to make use of our brains and resources to make nets and all. used all sorts of methods.. hehee.. sticks.. pails..leaves.. etc.. it was SO FUN!! =) i loved those days when i had no homework and could catch tadpoles everyday. heheee. but everytime when i catch em' and put them in pails or bottles, my grandmother would persuade us to let them go. so eventually, my sisters and i had to let them go . =)   Okay anyways. today had  npcc  trng. celebrate ame's birthday with choc cake. yum. with 1 candle. played basketball and  berd  was sliding on the bball court as tho he was ice skating..cos it just poured. yea. quite funny. berd so rough tho! hit  jeff  until his lips bled. now around the cut got blue black oso. actually, it was purple when i saw jeff after trng. eeeks. we had light PT. then did drills from 9am-1pm. wowwee. at first we combined with sec 2s. was so disappointing. our morale and confidence level went low... very very low. promised ma'am  yeewen  to do gd job. but we let her down. she scolded us until her voice 'zao sia'. on the other hand.. mmm, i would say  we deserved it , undoubtedly. later we split. did a better job. confidence level and spirit shot up. then  sir faizal  came back to visit! homad him. haha. then  mrs abdul  eat vinegar (jealous)! teehee. so cute. =) the  bernard ma`am  never come today.. lols.. learnt new drills. so glad.. but I MISS FANCY DRILLS oredi.. =P after trng wendi fainted. poor boy.. =X i'm oso not very sure what happened.. hai..  Oh okkkk fun part =P wenta' lunch then IMM. actually i was feeling tired and didn't wannt go IMM but val persuaded me too.. duno why she so deperate one sia.. keep saying want to go.. don't tell me she likes  *tweet! tweeeet tweet!*  hahaaa.. kk. *shuts up* better not say or she'll kill me. anyways, i was just kidding. played truth or dare (without e dare) and revealed our inner most secrets. afterwhich we wenta walk walk.. then gonna go home le.. saw  tanglin ,  nanhua  and one more malay ma'am duno from newton or what? yups.. spoke to tanglin faizal when he struck up a convo with me. he said he was short.  -.-""  hahaa. quite funny guy lah.. gave me sweet too. *yum. then went home cos mama called my hp le.. haha.. wait for beng, faizal they all so long loh.. heheee =) but it was worth the wait :D   Alrighty.. very very long blog.. oso duno why guess im quite 'high' now tts why. take care. *huggles* lotsa love and friedrice.    urlLink CLICK HERE  for photos taken yesterday! =)
     
    
</post>
<date>17,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      In 1883, a creative engineer named John Roebling was inspired by an idea to build a spectacular bridge connecting New York with the Long Island. However bridge building experts throughout the world thought that this was an impossible feat and told Roebling to forget the idea. It just could not be done. It was not practical. It had never been done before.   Roebling could not ignore the vision he had in his mind of this bridge. He thought about it all the time and he knew deep in his heart that it could be done. He just had to share the dream with someone else. After much discussion and persuasion he managed to convince his son Washington, an up and coming engineer, that the bridge in fact could be built.   Working together for the first time, the father and son developed concepts of how it could be accomplished and how the obstacles could be overcome. With great excitement and inspiration, and the headiness of a wild challenge before them, they hired their crew and began to build their dream bridge.  The project started well, but when it was only a few months underway a tragic accident on the site took the life of John Roebling. Washington was injured and left with a certain amount of brain damage, which resulted in him not being able to walk or talk or even move.    "We told them so." "Crazy men and their crazy dreams." "It`s foolish to chase wild visions."  Everyone had a negative comment to make and felt that the project should be scrapped since the Roeblings were the only ones who knew how the bridge could be built. In spite of his handicap Washington was never discouraged and still had a burning desire to complete the bridge and his mind was still as sharp as ever.   He tried to inspire and pass on his enthusiasm to some of his friends, but they were too daunted by the task. As he lay on his bed in his hospital room, with the sunlight streaming through the windows, a gentle breeze blew the flimsy white curtains apart and he was able to see the sky and the tops of the trees outside for just a moment.   It seemed that there was a message for him not to give up. Suddenly an idea hit him. All he could do was move one finger and he decided to make the best use of it. By moving this, he slowly developed a code of communication with his wife.   He touched his wife's arm with that finger, indicating to her that he wanted her to call the engineers again. Then he used the same method of tapping her arm to tell the engineers what to do. It seemed foolish but the project was under way again.  For 13 years Washington tapped out his instructions with his finger on his wife's arm, until the bridge was finally completed. Today the spectacular Brooklyn Bridge stands in all its glory as a tribute to the triumph of one man's indomitable spirit and his determination not to be defeated by circumstances. It is also a tribute to the engineers and their team work, and to their faith in a man who was considered mad by half the world. It stands too as a tangible monument to the love and devotion of his wife who for 13 long years patiently decoded the messages of her husband and told the engineers what to do.  Perhaps this is one of the best examples of a never-say-die attitude that overcomes a terrible physical handicap and achieves an impossible goal.    + + +  Often when we face obstacles in our day-to-day life, our hurdles seem very small in comparison to what many others have to face... however, The Brooklyn Bridge shows us that dreams that seem impossible can be realised with determination and persistence, no matter what the odds are.  Even the most distant dream, can be realized with determination and persistence.
     
    
</post>
<date>16,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      There you go. how's the new layout? aiight, i'm gonna go revise tomorrow's math test. ciao lovers! lotsa' love and friedrice.   P.S  there's a hee-uge storm at my place and i'm scared. i hate storms.
     
    
</post>
<date>14,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Ello ello people! =) how's everyone? thanks for all the geustbook entries btw. i read through every single one and i felt so motivated. especially * clears throat * his. i seem so affected by everyone's moods. when i'm with different people, my mood differs. take for example today.  nic  has been feeling really down due to certain problems. when i was with her i felt depressed too. i was worried. and i scolded her for doing something really foolish. as her friend, i guess all i can do is to advice that poor lil' soul and state my opinions. whether she wants to follow her heart, or take my advice, it's totally up to her. she has the right to decide anyways. then there's  jason ,  jeremy  and  eileen . when i'm with them, i feel as though i am on cloud nine. when eileen and i look at each other. the first thing we do is to laugh out loud. when jeremy and i meet, we sing our favourite songs, he whines, and i talk. when  jason  and i sit beside one another, everything seems to be flowing so naturally. we can simply talk about any thing. his  incredibly  corny jokes make me laugh my ass off.  amily ,  ruth ,  nana  and  jessica  are such cheerful sweethearts, to just look at them in the eye would make my day.  jiax ,  martin  and  fengrui  are the 3  crazy  peeps who are basically the funniest people.. but they can be very very corny too. fengrui likes to challenge me by   suaning   me. so i guess being around him would perfect my suaning skills too. i can remember extremely clearly when i was in secondary 1. haha. it was horrifying. when people  suan-ed  me, i would just smile or giggle. i mean, it wasn't fun at all! i truthfully haven't encountered anything like that when i was in pri skl. because such things don't happen often in an all girls skl. no wonder i didn't have any guy friends besides those 2 sissified guys when i was in sec 1. i've learnt so much during my 2 and a half years here in CTSS. can you imagine how much more we would have to learn in the near future? like SO SO SO SO SO ever SO mucho. and if i do show interest in those stuff, i can gurantee myself that i would be quite a smartie hey? haha. okay.. enough already. but honestly speaking hey, even  samuel  was surprised when he experienced me suaning him back... *teehee.  I am feeling much better so ignore the previous post. i was basically typing out how i felt at that moment. i didn't mean it. on a brighter note, my lil' sister and i have reconciled. haha okok it wasn't that serious but we ignored each other for a night. she designed a postcard and apologised to me. that was before i went for my  kayaking 1 star course  on sunday. *sigh. like, she stayed up til' mid night to do that for me... i said sorry to her too.. because i also made her cry and i wouldn't say i wasn't in the wrong because  i was . as an older sister, i really should've handled the situation by giving in to her. my dad reprimanded me for that. anyway!! now that we've made up, i would so love to squeeze her cheeks =D i want to be a better older sister. i wonder if i am a good one.. people say i am like a mother to them. but at home, it's tough for my lil' sister to respect me and treat me as a role model as much as i wish her to, because i  do not  set a good example! remember i have a list of accomplishments which i want to achieve? i have added that in.. in fact, i have longed to be a good older sister since i was younger.   After assembly today, i went for a lil' shopping spree and spent quite a bit. i felt good letting go some money. anyways, i am off to fill my stomach. so take care ya'll =) lotsa' love and friedrice 
    
</post>
<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      "Why is everything so confusing?? maybe i'm just out of my mind."  Why i am crying over stupid things and wasting time on stupid things. because im a stupid fool. people take me for granted. people don't care about how i feel. people say this, people say that. since nobody likes the current pearlyn then let's see how it would be like if i were to be stricter, firmer, much much more hard-hearted, bitchier, more selfish, insensitive, inconsiderate and loud.   I currently really hate my life. things are messy. and i just quarelled with my little sister and  i am crying . this is what i get after a tirin day at school. i am already  so drained  from every fucking thing. school. tests. [him]. npcc. homework. friends. annoying sisters. kayaking tests. tuitions. myself. like wow i'm already almost 15 and i am  actually  crying because i think my life sucks. i was SO born a loser hey.  God must hate me, cursed me for eternity.
     
    
</post>
<date>11,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      My day was pretty much like  urlLink this...  x)  Anyways, i'm really beat. i'm gonna iron mah uniform, polish mah boots and get ready for tomorrow's np training. there will be changes, and i need to be mentally prepared. do take care friends.
     
    
</post>
<date>10,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      First, let me say one thing. i never thought i'd say this, but poor  Britney Spears .  urlLink she seriously sounds like she needs some lovin.  err, wait. i've got something she doesn't! i'm better than you, Britney Spears! feed my ego!   I didn't update on what has been happening at school yesterday. it was helluva' amusing because my  spare tyre ,   jason   (weihoong) is right beside mah.  ms halizah  probably decided to put him and i together because she thinks that i am the only person who can tolerate his wackiness! i love sitting with  karen ,  jeremy ,  jason  and  eileen ! our mouths never get to rest. dang, i love to talk! don't you??! hmm. no wonder  amily  and i got reprimanded by potato head  mrs chen  after bio lessons. * tssk.  anyways, we deserved it, we weren't even cooperating with that poor lil' soul when she was trying to make us focus and understand the chapter. anyhow, we apologised. that made me feel  really guilty . on a brighter note..  (:   HAPPY BIRTHDAY EILEEN!!!   :)   P.S:  he called!! haha. like  OMIGAWSH!!  * faints * lmao..  P.P.S:  i can't wait fer' tmrw! yeehaw!
     
    
</post>
<date>09,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
         The blow was almost too painful to bear. this was because hopes that conjoined  Iranian twins  Laden and Laleh Bijani would pull through the risky surgery to separate them had soared SO high. even at 1.30pm yesterday after they had been separated, optimism remained high.  Suddenly, within hours, they were both  DEAD .  The team of 6 surgeons and their 100 supporting staff had tried to stem the profuse bleeding. they failed. but we should not allow this tragic setback to douse the fire of our passion to push the frontiers of medical science or have our nerves frayed in the facing similar challenges in future. they are bound to come our way again.  What led to the deaths will be examined and analysed in weeks ahead and something positive would have been learnt, to be shared with the international medical community. the surgeons involved in this operation should be proud that they had the courage to take this calculated risk in trying to help Laden and Laleh when no others in the world wanted to. even the Germans declined to help when they were approached by the sisters in 1996.  the surgeons here knew the outcome could go either way. but more importantly,  the twins knew, too.   the worst has come to pass and this was something the Raffles Hospital team was aware it had to face.  When they were as young as eight, a family friend remembers seeing the pair trying to walk in opposite directions to break free from each other. public hopes that they would survive the surgery, which began on sunday, had taken to the sky partly because of Dr Gog and his team team's success with the Nepalese twins.   Laden and Laleh knew that the operation was highly risky, yet they wanted to go through with it in order to fulfil their hope of being separated.  they faced the challenge with  remarkable  fortitude, optimism and cheerfulness.    -  Extracted from Streats and The Straits Times  -   I was deeply saddened by the news when i was told by my mom yesterday. Laden and Laleh were such adorable common laymen.. they absolutely did not deserve this. what wrong have they done? to choose to lead separate lives? on the other hand, i hope all of us have learnt something from this. we should all appreciate and cherish the people around us. the lives we lead. the things we own. and who we are.  we are undeniably, very lucky . i would like to extend my heartfelt condolences to the Iranian people and the family of Laden and Laleh.   To everyone who reads this, do take care.   "Ladan and Laleh, like two butterflies have burnt in the candle of destiny, but it is the light of this candle which gives us the hope to continue the endeavour for the betterment of human life."  
     
    
</post>
<date>08,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Yay got this off amanda. its actually part of this whole long survey. but oh well i'm only interested in THIS part.   This name makes you think of   RYAN:   JOCK boy. the jerk type who makes out with random cheerleaders by his locker EVERYDAY and occasionally with the not-so-gorgeous nerds, just to torment them. he gets away with EVERYTHING though, just because he looks like OHMYGOSH!! HAYDEN CHRISTIANSEN.   ALEX:  sporty guy with a goofy grin. he is tall and lanky and most definitely a redhead. his skin is permanently pink. he's really good at running, although he flaps his arms too much and looks like a chicken when he does.   TIFFANY:   exotic girl with her hair in cornrows. she's the funky hiphop type, she's into breakdancing, dj-ing and grafitti art and she beats the boys at it all. she LOVES bar top dances.   PAUL:   the boy in the corner, gazing out of the window during class, he stands up occasionally to make inspirational speeches which are mostly irrelevant to anything that is being discussed, but he gets away with it.    ABBY:  goth-ish grunge girl, dressed in vintage black. she loves drama with a passion. she is often seen with a camera and she goes around filming people in the hallways. she tints all her short-films purple though, because it's prettier that way.    PHIL:  guy in a tight t-shirt and feminine cut jeans, and that versace bag. he is not gay, he just has a horrible sense of fashion and tries to be everything, punk rock, emo, vintage all at once. he waves his hands about too much and oh yeah, and he just LOVES giving girls fashion tips.    SALLY:  surfer chick! long, straight, silky dark brown hair accompanied by streaks of light brown. she does 100 sit-ups a day and has very nice, firm abs.   DERRICK:   boy in too-big-pants and a backward baseball cap who watches MTV too much for his own good ("i'm just chilling, man!"). he never hears what you say because he's always plugged into his CD player, grooving to ludacris or missy elliot. he starts every single sentence with "y'all" and ends it with "dude" or "man".   ALLEN:  androgynous pretty boy. he looks like a fairy, and has dark haunted smoky eyes and full girly lips. the girls adore him, and he could pass off as a model. but he never really belongs anywhere.   JODIE:  5 foot 11. gorgeous. black hair and green eyes. model type. totally.   SAM:  loud nihilistic girl who is pro-anarchy. she's a rebel and a non-conformist, and sometimes tries to hard in the process.    MICHELLE:  preppy, AVRIL LAVIGNE worshipper.   JESSICA:   blonde cheerleader captain with that jock boyfriend and that huge clique of admiring girl pals. she ALWAYS needs a manicure, or a pedicure (they are like therapeutic!). she is the miss popular type, everyone can't help but loveeee. her  dream is to be on the cover of Seventeen and get voted prom queen.    LEAH:  child-like girl with her blonde hair tied in plaits. you can almost see her mind wandering off to make believe land.    ERIK:  hippie boy. he wears tie dye (homemade) and has long straggly hair, pulled back from his face by a sweaty headband. he kisses trees and holds candlelight vigils in times square. the boy believes in peace, love, hope, joy.   BILLY:  the type of guy who is ALWAYS sweating from his armpits. he's a little momma's boy and dresses in white collared shirts and Sesame Street ties. his socks are nearly knee high, his shirt is tucked all the way in, and his pant's are pulled up to his bellybutton by suspenders. he's not very bright either, and doesn't get any of the jokes people say. he's quite a sad little thing. his parents own a farm.   JOSHUA:  typical slacker boy (i would have said JOCK. if his name was josh. but well joshua is a different thing all together). he doesn't care what people think of him REALLY. he just hangs in the garage and plays the electric guitar. he wears whatever comes out of the laundry (if he bothers to even change) usually its the same nirvana shirt, torn up jeans, grunge sneakers assemble. even his hair is naturally messed up. of course, he begins every sentence with "like", and EVERYTHING he says even the most direct statements , sounds like a question. ("like, he was here today? and like, i saw him?")   BRITNEY:   annoying little sister of a head cheerleader (see JESSICA). probably a ten year old, who is as blonde as her sister. she wears her hair in pigtails and lovessss picking up the extension to whine while big sis jess is on the phone mushytalking with her boyfriend. an aspiring teenybopper star, who just adoresadoresADORES dreamstreet.   CHRIS:  spiky hair and sunglasses, he has barbie doll eyes and plucked eyebrows. he lounges about in his convertible in too-tight sleeveless tops and leopard print leather pants. he's perfectly straight though, in fact he's a playboy and he changes girls like he switches rhinestone earings.   MARIO:  three words: Gay Italian Fashionista   BRANDON:   a poet, a writer, an artist, a singer...and very pretty on top of that.   Hahaha i guess i got REALLY carried away describing people. but its fun! and it boosts your creativity :D * beams *  
     
    
</post>
<date>08,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Today was incredibly terrible and stinkin.  i was suicidal this morning.  i felt so depressed and low-spirited. i felt like crying the whole day.. i guess most of my close friends know why :(  Things changed for the better during the last period though.  ms halizah  switched places for a coupla' us during the last period. now i am sitting with  jason (weihoong). * beams *  jeremy  sits in front of me and  karen  sits behind me.   However, the day became really depressing again after i got home. man, my mood sure does fluctuate hey. i received news from  mummy  that the  Iranian twins  have passed away. i turned on the telly to channel news asia and read, " Latest news: Second Iranian twin dies  at the bottom of the screen. * sobs * i feel for them. i sms-ed  amily ,  jess  and  kalyn (dingling) about it..   Anyways, i hope tomorrow would be a better day.
     
    
</post>
<date>07,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Yesterday was really fun :) i woke up at 5.30am and got ready to leave the house at 7am. do you think taking 1 and a half hours to get ready is too effin' long? haha. some people think so.. oh well. anyways, i reached clementi MRT at about 7.30am so i was the earliest! and saw  kenneth  and his friends who were on their way to kallang for the NDP full dress rehearsal.  valerene  came a lil' later and  jess  (ma'am yeewen) arrived late. we took the train to  tampines  and met up with  bernard ,  fungi kor ,  edywn  and  weix kor . afterwhich, we hopped onto bus  19  and it brought us to  CSSC ! (changi sea sports club)  I guess you already have an idea of what i did yesterday hey? haha. yup, you're right. i went  kayaking ! val and i signed up for the  1 star course  which consists of two lessons, both from 10am-5pm.  Our instructors were  serene  and  charles . serene is a NPCC ma'am and i think she's in her twenties. she's very good looking. charles was from NCC and he's quite corny. we changed into our wet attire and intro-ed ourselves to our group memebers! there were 10 of us altogether. val and i were the youngest. most of them were in their twenties.. from poly.. uni..  :) we had a lesson and introduction on the parts of a kayak. then tried to paddle. all the different strokes. we learnt lotsa' stuff yesterday. mainly:  - embarking - disembarking - forward stroke - backward stroke - sweep stroke (360 degrees) - J-draw - capsizing - T/X rescue  I don't have any problems with all the strokes. capsizing is scary but the more i try it, the more exciting it becomes. however, you wouldn't like it when all the salt water gets into your nose. very annoying =\ i personally find T/X rescue the most difficult =( it has to be done in pairs. one person has to rescue, while the other has to capsize on purpose. then the rescuer has to paddle to the capsized kayak, somehow lift the damn heavy thing up onto his/her own kayak with the haul facing upwards to allow all the water to flow out. then your partner (the person who capsized with the kayak) has to hook both legs and arms on one side of the kayak so it appears to be a  see-saw . (both kayaks are in a  t  shape) then you hold on to the deck line and swim to the other side and do the koala-bear hug again. it the kayak tilts and all the water flows out again. later, flip the kayak back with the haul under water then you gotta climb up the kayak with the help of the rescuer, which is damn tough for me.. * sigh * especially when we did it in the deep sea because the waves were so huge =X plus, i'm so heavy! so i need lotsa' arm muscles. haha. i should train up. one time, i kept trying to jump outta the water and flip my body onto the kayak until i had a cramp on my calf. so pain sia! * tsk * i had to do it 3 times altogether yesterday, 2 times compulsory while the other was volunteerily. and all 3 times i got up with the help of my friend. * phew * :)  At about 5pm.. we ended and had to wash our kayaks and trolleys. it was quite fun, i love to play with water hoses. haha. i also spoke to one of my group member...er.. i forgot her name.. i asked if she was a  butch  =\ do you think i was being rude? i hope not.. cos she said she wasn't offended :) she also said that she wouldn't classify herself as a butch. so i just smiled at her and asked if she was ready to carry the kayak over to the shelf. teehee. she's soooo very nice.. she helped out in our rescue by anchoring our kayaks when we were nearer the shore. and she has such huge arm muscles! i learnt that she was a dragon-boater from her partner :) val,  charlene ,  joyce  and i washed our hair in public at the showers and pipes where everyone goes to to wash their kayaks, cos' the shower room was bombarded with peeps. then dried our bodies and got changed. debrief after everything.. and left for dinner with my seniors at changi village :)    WOW , what a day! and i got sun burnt too. but last night i put like duno how many donkey layers of mosturizer cos i don't want my skin to peel. it looks okay now.. gonna return to the usual colour soon. hopefully by tomorrow :)
     
    
</post>
<date>05,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Boney M  *  Rasputin       Ra, ra,  Rasputin , Russia's greatest love machine!  my personal pick of the week, this mp3 is not only a historical song (although not exactly accurate) which we (3B1) have learnt just last week (the Russian revolution), but also comic relief. we love Russia, yes we do. listen to it or else your fate will be similar to Rasputin's.      ((LYRICS))  There lived a certain man in Russia long ago He was big and strong, in his eyes a flaming glow Most people looked at him with terror and with fear But to Moscow chicks he was such a lovely dear He could preach the bible like a preacher Full of ecstacy and fire But he also was the kind of teacher Women would desire  RA RA RASPUTIN Lover of the Russian queen There was a cat that really was gone RA RA RASPUTIN Russia's greatest love machine It was a shame how he carried on  He ruled the Russian land and never mind the czar But the kasachok he danced really wunderbar In all affairs of state he was the man to please But he was real great when he had a girl to squeeze For the queen he was no wheeler dealer Though she'd heard the things he'd done She believed he was a holy healer Who would heal her son  But when his drinking and lusting and his hunger for power became known to more and more people, the demands to do something about this outrageous man became louder and louder.  "This man's just got to go!" declared his enemies But the ladies begged "Don't you try to do it, please" No doubt this Rasputin had lots of hidden charms Though he was a brute they just fell into his arms Then one night some men of higher standing Set a trap, they're not to blame "Come to visit us" they kept demanding And he really came  RA RA RASPUTIN Lover of the Russian queen They put some poison into his wine RA RA RASPUTIN Russia's greatest love machine He drank it all and he said "I feel fine"  RA RA RASPUTIN Lover of the Russian queen They didn't quit, they wanted his head RA RA RASPUTIN Russia's greatest love machine And so they shot him till he was dead  Oh, those Russians...     
     
    
</post>
<date>05,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Most of my best friends would probably know how reluctant i am when it comes to getting married and having babies, although i adore lil' kids to pieces. however, right now, i have completely changed my thoughts about that. i repeat, i wanna make love and have a baby like this!!!         I can imagine myself breast-feeding this adorable baby already :D :D :D * aww *  Credits:  urlLink ash's photolog 
     
    
</post>
<date>04,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Hi ladybugs!  I needed to let go of myself  really  badly from all the stress. i shan't elaborate since it isn't necessary, hence, last night when i met  nora sweetheart  online, we decided to hang out today and have some gurly fun.  I took a cab to town then met her at 10.15am. we took stickers prints from 2 different machines at the annexe. 8 beam and this other new hee-uge machine. it's so model-like and seemed sophisticated. and in one of the snapshots i carried her! and she was really amazed by my sheer strength. anyhow, we bought tix to catch  charlies angels: full throttle  at 11am in cineleisure.. =P  it was soooo awesome ya!!  it  really  kicked butt. we were yakking all about it while we were on our way back to the heeren shops. afterwhich, we took prince machine sticker prints (which is the bessstt haha.) and went window shopping.. cause at that point i have already spent  $50 .. so yeah.. broke  again . waiting for nicco to return me $$ =\\ looked fer' necklaces.. adidas sweaters and a  urlLink ripcurl  sling bag.  nora  and i are gonna buy that sling bag together! hopefully by the time we save up...it's still being sold =D  dang.. we fell madly in love with it upon setting our eyes on it. nora and i have minds that are so alike. we keep sayin the same things at the exact same time. haha.   After everything, we proceeded to some mandarin hotel for a seminar.. then we saw  urlLink imran ! haha. it was sooo funny i tell ya. we went in and were strolling around the lobby when nora saw this malay boy in the  SJI  uniform. then she was all "oh my god, is that imran?" and we began freaking out. hahaa.. later she and i hugged each other goodbye.. =) we would be meeting in a month's time. teehee. oh yup, if you're wondering who nora is, well, we met through the help of  BARDOT ! haha. erm, cos we were once crazeee over bardot. then somehow we began chatting over the internet (and she had a website too) and decided to meet up one day. she's one of the many internet peeps i've met up with.. =) and i lub her. she lubs me too! *huggles*   Click below for sticker prints!  urlLink Sticker print 1   urlLink Sticker print 2 
     
    
</post>
<date>04,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink Photos  of the BBQ at west coast =)   (V)  (&gt;'-') o(")(") 
     
    
</post>
<date>03,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Everything is going to be all right, why should I not be glad? to contemplate the clouds clearing beyond the dormer window and a high tide reflecting on the ceiling.  There will be dying, there will be crying,  but there is no need to go into that. The poems will flow from the heart unbidden and the hidden source is the watchful heart. The sun will rise despite everything and the far cities are beautiful and bright. I lie here in a riot of sunlight watching the daybreak and the clouds flying, everything is going to be all right      
     
    
</post>
<date>03,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      I was devastated!! all I could think about was,  "why me" ? i just couldn't believe what was happening.. it was so unjustified. i plucked up my courage, spun around, and cleared my desk. i held my books on one arm and my bag in the other. i ambled across the classroom and settled down at the other side of the class. my new seating partner?  Joshua .  I have to  thank   yulun . for the past coupla' days, he has been teasing me about  "si-car-lly"  sitting with joshua. especially when we wenta' the mall that day. he was all, "  WHAT IF  you were to sit with joshua? what would you do?  i casually replied while laughing out loud,  "haha that is impossible! it can't be that coincidental right?"    Then this morning when i saw the new class seating plan, i nearly passed out. i was scanning the piece of paper. i finally saw my name. i was anxious to read the name of the person who would be sitting beside moi. very very nervous. everything seemed so...  slow motion-ed , and so dramatic.   Indeed , it turned out to be J-O-S-H-U-A.     Wow , life is overwhelmed with  irony , ain't it??   My life rocks .   Jiax  and i gave  ms halizah  the cold shoulder today. gave her attitude prob during her 5 lessons with us too. cos' basically, jiax can't sit with  jason (weihoong). they quarrel 24/7 and just can't get along. as for me, it is a fact that josh really is pretty dirty when it comes to personal hygiene =\ and i can't quite get along with him either. don't say i ain't trying, i have. we are okay together.. but, i can't open up to him like i do to  yulun . we don't joke, we don't talk, we don't laugh, we don't sing, we don't do anything together! and it really sucks if i have to sit with the same person for the entire day when we don't even communicate.  i miss yulun....  * bleahx*  well, not only did ms halizah put jiax and i with somebody whom we don't feel comfy around with, she put jiax,  fengrui (gabriel kor),  yulun (martin kor) and i each at a different corner. and  nic  is right at the centre.  kalyn (dingling) got to sit with fengrui. sighs. at least they can still talk..  amily  is sitting with  jeremy  kor. =( *sobs* how cool.  jess  sitting with  hafiz ,  ruth  and  simon . aaahhh.. my best friends are all so far away.. so so far away.  During the peer leaders and prefects' meeting after skl, jason told me that he has informed ms halizah about wanting to change his seats. he told her that he wouldn't mind sitting with me. so hopefully, ms halizah would put us together. i am praying SO hard that this would happen. 
     
    
</post>
<date>03,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      I bet there were more than 150 of us who were late today. i was one of them. the gate was closed sooo early..  eileen  and i ran for it and mdm reenuka(sp?) shut it right in front of our noses. * tsk tsk . had bio lessons..  mrs chen  was quite alright. better than i had expected. i preferred her style of teaching. physics were really funn ;) i lub  mr chin . haha. he talks to us a lot.. after recess had english..  yulun  said he wouldn't get called but he finally did.. after i shouted his index no soooo many times,  ms koh  finally wrote it on the board and he had to go up to write down the movie review stuff. serves him right. lol. he was sitting there shaking his leg all along.  and if you're wondering why i sometimes shift my desk away from him, it's because he always annoys me with all the nonsensical critisisms bt' ms koh whenever it's her lesson. and i can't stand it. i like ms koh. then he talks about all these really silly stuff and fantasizes about his girl TO ME. -.-"""" ms koh hadta' talk to him privately cos' he wrote " steamy scenes " on the whiteboard. ttaaaahaa. anyways, today is prolly my last day sitting with him..so.. yeah.  saaddd . gonna miss my best budd yo. * sigh . i really hope ms halizah wouldn't change my seat tmrw..   After skl.. wenta'  JP  with  jess  and  amily  meis.. :)) hahaa.. walked and walked..silly amily spent like $40 on pressies.. lol.. then she kept complaining and askin herself why she ended up spending so much.. lol.. then i saw my nokia 2100 cover.. i asked about 5 ppl oredi.. all 5 said  pink  suits me best.. so i'm prolly gonna save up and buy the pink cover.. then ate the snow ice thingy with hersheys chocolate syrup  YUUUUMMmmmm .. hahaa. kkies ;) betta' go find my physics file now.. i lost it =\ .. tc lovers (:
     
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      This morning was pretty much lifeless cos' the first 2 periods were occupied by humanities. i enjoy history. yet i feel that it is boring. math was a total disaster. mr lee was absent. i hope he's ok.. heard that he's real sick. =\ the relief teachers seem to be tryin their best to teach and convey their msg to us.. however, it wouldn't work cos they have insufficient experience. they have absolutely  no idea  how to handle  young adults  (according to jiax) like us. scholars are smart. but so what if they're smart? some of them do not know how to apply the practical skills. this shows that  being intelligent isn't all . in this case, i'm talking about the new trainee teachers who are scholars. hopefully they'll be able to adjust themselves in this totally new environment. =) soon.  P.E was okaayy.. did conditioning once again cos' our physical fitness test is just around the corner! *eeks. 5 rounds.. and total 25 push ups and sit ups. then hadta' run another 7 rounds.. but penny ang said 2 can le. =) *hug hug* so nice. discount until so much. =P later.. english lessons.. quite boring =\\ physics was quite fun.  mr chin  likes to play with us. chinese was monsterous, since  liu jian  is always here to condemn and lecture us.   Bio was damn slack. we have a new teacher.  mrs chen . it was like a TPI lesson. she intro herself. made us intro ourselves. do some worksheet about ourselves. then write a list of friends + a word to describe them. asked her quesn. took up 2 periods.  viola , skl ended at 3pm. yay =)  Went home with  kalyn ,  ruth  and  yulun . he wanted me to go to westmall with him to buy puter parts. said tt if he didn't have enough $$, i can be his ATM machine. * tsk . couldn't find his stuff. boo. hmm. forced me to wait for the 173 bus with him. wait for sooo effin long. that yulun ah... he knows me too well. he knows tt i won't get angry with him, will always forgive him and can put up with his nonsense. he's like.. the one who can really make my day.. even when i'm damn depressed.. his  clone  conversation (inside joke) really cracks me up. oh wells, enough about the maniac. very tired.. gonna eat dinner (: tc guys!
     
    
</post>
<date>01,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Friends matter the most to me. so if one of them would have to go away some day, i would happily let him/her go, although i'm going to be undeniably reluctant to. if letting them go makes them happy, i would be contented. the same goes for the special someone whom you love. i'm sure you'd want the best for him/her, wouldn't you? =)   i would. 
     
    
</post>
<date>28,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Note to  debre  and ex rgps peeps, i'm going back tmrw..those who're reading this from rg and know me wanna meet in skl or smth? anyways,  happy teachers day ! teehee. tmrw im pulling curtains - stage coordinator. must clap for me sia. very tiring pull curtain one leh. haha. keke ciao people. missing ya. :)
     
    
</post>
<date>26,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Ahola :) how's everyone? me is... fine :) i miss blogging. life without the internet connection is honestly incredibly boring. i have like, absolutely no life at all. anyways, we're supposd to have history lesson under mrs raja now. but she's not here, gotta do source based qns but didn't bring moi hist book. *sigh*. mr woon is here. he's like SO nice. let me use the comp. teehee. =P oh yupp, just a random thought, mr lee is sucha' hip hop teacher. keke. he's just really caring..he is an epitome of a loving father. *hugs hugs*   This morning something pretty unpleasant happened. if  YOU  are reading this, i REALLY hope you realise that you're being extremely foolish and incredibly immature. you made me change my mind about how i felt about you. don't think that just cos' you have a powerful back up you can bully your fellow mates aiight. remember, you will lose that back up some day. and on that very day you lose that back up, people are going to  get back at you for what you have done to them . it won't be very nice then hey.   Well!! to everyone out there, keep on groovin hey. and in case i don't get to blog for the next coupla' weeks..happy teachers day + happy be yourself day. good luck mates. peace out. xox.
     
    
</post>
<date>13,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Yeehaw!! hehe keke.. err, i'm in school right now. ames behind me trying to get me off asap plus i gotta collect stuff from jason hoongy. tsk tsk. let's see how's life. quite boring? except can see *tsk tsk* la hey? he bery nice so erm.. okok shall not elaborate right now. in school, as usual, quite havoc-ish. the other day mr lee called my home. me was suuuppper shocked. ok not shocked but surprised!! :) yipee. then like, he asked me about the class and all. he also called fiona yesterday. haha. i bet fiona was over the moon. *yeehaw* i can't wait for friday. firstly, mr lee will be back alive and kickin some major butt in class! secondly, i will be departing this island... so pulau ubin! yeehaw. yuppers. gonna have a camp. adventure training camp to be exact. i hope it's not gonna be 'xiong' or else i die. ok la.. amelia wanna blog now. ciao you sexy people! and hello to maizura! i didn't know you read me blog. haha. *toodles* :)
     
    
</post>
<date>11,September,2003</date>
<post>

     
      today was pretty much productive. i had chemistry lessons from 11am-1pm then lunched with geetha, narin, karen, fiona, eileen, gerald and a whole buncha' girls. jason hoongy and zuhayr-ra were sitting at the table next to us. after which, geetha, gerald, eileen, karen and i hit the gym. geetha, exhilarated, went in  first  cos' she was in a hurry to meet  bala , the gym instructor. haha. he was incredibly friendly. i got to know him after a while. we worked out for 2 hours then left...  soap asked me to go to guilin to celebrate mooncake/lantern festival, but i couldn't..cos mom's cooking "mian xian". it's my chinese birthday today :D ya'll have fun viewing the moon and eating mooncakes..haha. aiight, lil' sis keeps bugging me for the net. ciao! 
     
    
</post>
<date>08,September,2003</date>
<post>

     
      hola there! hehe. at nat's house right now =) reaaaaally fun. esther, christina and i came over and must've shed a coupla' calories after dancing for 2 hours. i'm supper excited about the ROD. hope it becomes a sucess hey. anyways, how's everyone? oh yupp, like the new layout? hehe.   over the past coupla' weeks i learnt like SO much. the  electric guitar . i guess i've mentioned to a few of you that my dad bought an electric guitar rite? during july, i practiced on the acoustic guitar on my own after being inspired by sir kevin from tanglin sec. so yesss..now i can handle the chords pretty well. i always fantasize myself on stage playing in a band whenever i listen to music that i like. hopefully that will come true some day. me. performing. on stage. in a band.  ohkays, enjoy your holidays people. peace out. xox =)
     
    
</post>
<date>30,November,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Dear Sonority,  I stole this from aaronn.  A- Age: 15. B- Boyfriend: haha no. C- Chore you hate: washing the dishes! D- Dads name: michael. E- essential make up item: lip gloss. YUMMY!!  F- favourite actor: johnny depp. ooOohs hawtt. G- gold or silver: silver. H- hometown: singapore (doh!) I- instruments you play: piano, recorder, electric/acoustic guitar, harmonica. J- job title: student.  K- Kids: kids are fun! and innocent. L- Living arrangements: organised? M- Mom's name: irene N- number of people u've slept with: none. O- overnight hospital stays: i can't remember. but i was admitted into hospital twice. once for asthma and another cos' i stuffed tissue up my nose and it got stuck. so i had to have an op. dumb me rite?  P- Phobia: altophobia (heights). Q- quote you like: "dreams do come true, and it's up to you to make them into a reality."  R- regular drink: water S- secret crush: it wouldn't be a secret anymore if i were to post it on the world wide web. T- time you wake up: nowadays 5.30-6am. i still have school! eek. and i'll be working next week :) U- unique habit: erh.. staring out of windows?  V- vegetable you refuse to eat: celery. W- worst habit: biting my nails. X- X-rays uve had: i can't remember. Y- yummy food you make: pasta! Z- zodiac sign: dragon.  last kiss: like everynight i kiss my parents? haa. last good cry: quite some time ago. 2 months back? last library book checked out: it's a book on outdoor leadership. last crush: haha. :) last phone call: bernard. last tv show watched: MTV. last time showered: this morning. last shoes worn: adidas. last cd played: the all american rejects!!! last item bought: a skirt from jennyfer. last downloaded: some song by green day. last annoyance: the puter. last thing written: this. last sleep: last night. last chatted with: nic(amelia) last sexual fantasy: haha. that was quite some time ago.. last weird encounter: this person keeps sms-ing me friendship/miss u/love msgs. when i ask who is it he/she replies with ANOTHER msg on friendship blah blah. last ice cream eaten: napoleon. last time amused: 30 secs ago. the television. last time wanting to die: i love my life. i love my family. i love my friends. i love what i'm doing. last time in love: hmmm. i would like to keep this private. last time hugged: mommy! in the swimming pool this morning.  last chair sat in: the chair in front of the computer table. last shirt worn: green OP long board classic tee. last poster looked at: BARDOT!!!! last show attended: rugrats go wild!
     
    
</post>
<date>29,November,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Dear Sonority,  Guess what!? i have just accomplished climbing the monkey bar!! hehee *Weeeeee!!* okay alright, ya know, since i was in primary school, i've never been able to complete the course. i would always fall on the like, 3rd bar? yes!! see how bad i am at it! yet today, we had to do it during NPCC trng for some campcraft thingy. my squadmates were cheering me on and i just looked front, persevered and told myself that "I CAN DO IT!" instead of thinking "OH NO I'M GONNA FALL NOW!!" my determination level was at its highest! * does the happy dance * after more than 12 bars, i hung onto the last and proceeded onto pegging! * beams * =D  We had a changing parade as well. from PT kit to full U, full U to PT kit, and PT kit to full U again! feeling quite shiok cos it has been quite some time since we've done it. fatest girl timing is 3 mins and 35 secs i think. in future we shall aim for 3m30s, the 3m, then 2m30s, then 2m. wooo! aiight, i was only kidding, i don't think it is possible to finish changing in 2m. hurhur.   Alrighty, i'm rather exhausted now. ooohs, my sis is back from prom! she stayed over at The Oriental. i missed that girl sooo mucho!!!   P.S:  Click  urlLink HERE  to view the photos taken at Geetha's house :)
     
    
</post>
<date>28,November,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Dear Sonority,  The poem below was taken from this book by Sean Sheehan, "The Holocaust: The Death Camps". i borrowed it from the library today and began reading it as soon as i got home because it is  unbelievably  interesting. it is certainly depressing to know the harsh conditions people were living in though. not forgetting the macabre process of mass murder. * ewww .  I met up with Jeremy and Jason(weihoong) at school this morning to ask Miss Halizah questions on the holiday homework. she re-taught the entire chapter on moles and it helped us quite a bit. the problem with jeremy and i is that, we are  able  to memorise the fomula, BUT, we're not sure how to apply them to the questions. =\ so sucky right? hehe. ah well. anyhow! she went really slow and i managed to catch what she was explaining. not many people know the patient and soft side of Miss Halizah i guess. i myself was surprised! =)  After attempting the questions, we just sat there and chilled with her. talked crap and also watched the graduates strutting their stuffs hahaa! many of them dressed up really elegantly and formally. but like what miss halizah had mentioned, Singapore's proms can't be compared to the ones in the states/west where guys pick the girls up in their dad's car! haha! which is so true. anyways, they're still underage, and that kinda' stinks. my sister from crescent girls will be attending her prom night in several hours time. she bought this beautiful tube gown, dyed her hair, permed it and i don't know what else is she gonna do to herself, but i believe she'll look awesome tonight!! i'm so happy for her! she'll be staying over at The Oriental with her NCC mates too. all squeeze into 1 room. i bet it's gonna be one helluva' slumber party! teehee. i wouldn't mind getting drunk with my mates there if i were her.  I pity our graduates though. i pity myself too! graduation in school is rather..pathetic! yes, that's zee perfect word to describe the occasion and venue. hmm. we were discussing about how their make-up's gonna melt due to the uber hot weather. i saw almost everyone ambling into the school gate. mr hang dressed up for the occasion. mss koh too. miss shelley low especially! woah! she was, "radiant"! hehe. here is my pick for the best dressed! (dress+make up+attitude)   BEST DRESSED MALE:   Melvin Tan    BEST DRESSED FEMALE:  The tanned, slim, tall netballer with straight long hair. a pity i don't know her name!  It was so cool. huishan was standing near the gate with a camera crew (MRL). somewhat like the Star Awards!
     
    
</post>
<date>27,November,2003</date>
<post>

     
       I keep forgetting   I keep forgetting the facts and statistics and each time i need to know them.  I look up books these books line twelve shelves in my room.  I know where to go to confirm the fact that in the Warsaw ghetto there were 7.2 people per room.  and how many bodies they crammed in Auschwitz at the peak of production.  twelve thousand a day i have to check and re-check...  and did i dream that at 4pm on the 19th January 58,000 emaciated inmates were marched out of Auschwitz.  ... i can remember people's conversations and what someone's wife said to someone else's husband.  what a good memory you have people tell me.  ( I keep forgetting by Lily Brett, quoted from Hilda Schiff  Holocaust Poetry  )
     
    
</post>
<date>27,November,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Dear Sonority,  On  tuesday , Geetha invited Kalyn(dingling) and i over to her place to bake cookies. her aunt's secret cookie recipe is unbelievably enticing. YUMMY! we also had a manicure and peticure session. kalyn is like the expert in this area, she brought an entire set of buffer, nail cutter, etc! i was rather amused when i saw what she had brought along. haha. she taught me how to go about doing this and that and it was really interesting! i painted my toe nails black and coated them with layers of glittery sparkles, bearing in mind what my lil' sis had mentioned earlier, that i don't look too good in black varnish. "too gothic." but she said that by adding the glitter, it appears much more rad. geetha and kalyn looked wicked too! ;)    Yesterday  was special. i didn't have to go to school whatsoever, hence i just watched telly and chilled at home. i saw the "ice cream show" on the discovery travel and adventure channel and i'm  amazed  by the amount of ice cream the Americans consume! it's  scary    Today  was extemely productive. the dance practice went smoothly, although the beginning of the prac was uber lame! we couldn't find a suitable spot for the dance as the juniors were using the NP room. so val decided to proceed to the FIELD! so we danced in front of the express way and the HDB flats to be ridiculed at. how corny! we practiced for a lil' while before using the NP room cos' the juniors weren't quite ready yet. you know, always make use of your time wisely, don't waste precious moments. =) we danced like dunno how many donkey times and finally ended at about 10.30am. teehee. wenta' ask mr lee math questions and offered friends and teachers the cookies which geetha, kalyn and i had baked! mr azmi thought i was going to poison him. oooh, do i look like that type of person? sigh. haha! he was pretty comical. qingrui ate it. gerry too. all my squadmates and a coupla juniors did. (they commented on how yummy it was!) mr lee was the only teacher who happily munched on it. mr azmi ah...sigh X 10000!  Afterwhich, val, sir alan and i wenta' JP to watch " Rugrats go wild! " it's sucha kick-butt movie!! i noticed that i was one of the many who laughed away throughout the entire movie cos i'm a fan of The Wild Thornberrys and i think Debby ROCKS! (although seemingly bossy) while val and alan were like stoning while i'm laughing away...haha. but overall yes, it's smashing! (hehe again, inside joke by Nigel Thornberry!) i would give it a  4/5 . =)
     
    
</post>
<date>26,November,2003</date>
<post>

     
       5 Easy Steps to Suicide Enlightenment   Did your boyfriend/girlfriend just break up with you, parents getting a divorce, have no friends, just got an f, these are all perfect reasons to end your life and all the suffering such things bring. Without further ado let's get the gun loaded and ready:   STEP 1: The first step to having a successful suicide attempt is to give off signals that you are becoming suicidal. That way when you pull the trigger, people feel more blame for having ignored your hints and then you affect even more people then just yourself. This is key to ending your worthless, hard life. The first thing you need to due is become anti-social. Friends going to the movies and then some ice cream? Not you, you are going to sit at home in the dark and listen to Dashboard Confessional, and when someone asks you what is wrong you will say "Nothing, I'm just tired", but when you say this, it is key that you give off the "I'm full of shit and want to kill myself look". Seclude yourself. Be pessimistic.   STEP 2: After giving off hints, it is time to confide in a friend or write letters and let your friends find them. When your friends address you and offer their help, make sure you deny it and again say "Nothing is wrong", be convincing this time, I don't want them to stop you from ending your life. When your parents get worried and start to pry into your personal life, give them the guilt trip and then go upstairs, lock yourself in your room, and make slits in your arm but make sure they are not noticeable and will only be seen by your friends. If your parents see this your attempt at riding the world of a dipshi....depressed person with a meaningless life will be ruined. RUINED, I TELL YOU. First 2 steps are easy enough, now comes the time to write your suicide note and pick your weapon of choice.  STEP 3: Make sure that you become such an outcast that people at school start to make fun of you. So when you finally end your life they feel the repercussions as well. Be sure a day or two before you do it that when someone blurts out "Hey fatty" you counter with "You know you could make someone kill themself with comments like that" and hope they say "Please kill yourself." If they say the that, it will be a great feeling you give them when they find out you did what they wanted. Also be sure to hit yourself or create some kind of pain when they call you names, so they think you are a freak. It is important that you create this loner image-- be sure to sell it.  STEP 4: Writing the suicide note is the most important thing. This are the last words people will remember you by. Since this is crucial I will give you a template suicide note and you can fill in the blanks where you see fit.     Dear insert name here,  I can't live with this sadness no longer. I needed to end the suffering before I affected others, it was the only way out of the pain. For "insert your age years" I have lived with this pain. Now it has come to a close and will no longer eat away at me.  Mom and Dad - it is not your fault, you guys were great even though I didn't get that $40,000 pony when I was 7, it wasn't that or the time you were 10 minutes late to pick me up from "insert best friend name". I love you guys and want you to know that it isn't your fault.  Boyfriends/ girlfriend's name - I love you, but how could you cheat on me with that stupid slut. After you told me we were going to get married. We had been going out 2 months and you just did that to me, but it isn't all because of you. We were gonna run away and live by the ocean and have a baby each day of our healthy lives. I knew I couldn't make anyone happy or even myself. Remember me forever and don't forget the precious times we had together.  Mom and Dad please don't cry over me, and I am sorry my "insert comment of how your body or guts will be found" the last thing I wanted to due was hurt anyone. However there was no other choice.   insert partial poem or quote about life  your name here     STEP 5: Copy that word for word and you will be sure to give your family members and loved ones the greatest gift of life. Now on to following through with your stu...suicide. I would suggest taking a gun to your temple or in the mouth it is the least painful and you will have a closed casket so no one has to see your "ugly ass" one last time. Also the walls will be stained with your blood which is the perfect everlasting memory to give to your parents. Be sure to have a picture of your parents and you near the scene of the suicide to add to the effect. If you find that too gruesome or do not have a handgun readily available, then I suggest hanging yourself when your parents leave and do it right in front of the front door, so when they get back from "ignoring their picture perfect child" they will see your body swaying side to side. This will make them feel even more responsible because they left you alone. We all know that you should never leave your kid alone at home. If you do not feel like doing this then swallow some kind of poison or pills or slit your wrist, however I highly recommend one of the first two options; the others are not as gruesome and do not have as much lasting affect.  If you are considering committing suicide or you know someone who wants to, please let them read this so they can get through it and end their life. The easy way out is not to be a reasonable person and realize that shit happens and move on, but to kill yourself. Realize there are no other options and get on with the show. Also if you could record it and have the tape sent to me that would be awesome. If you have problems pulling the trigger remember Nike...Just do it. So what are you waiting for...CLICK CLICK BOOM.  (Credit upon the idea goes to Bad-lands.com)
     
    
</post>
<date>24,November,2003</date>
<post>

     
       "The Artist In The Ambulance"   Late night, brakes lock, hear the tires squeal red light, can't stop so i spin the wheel my world goes black before i feel an angel lift me up and i open bloodshot eyes into fluorescent white they flip the siren, hit the lights, close the doors and i am gone now i lay here owing my life to a stranger and i realize that empty words are not enough i'm left here with the question of just what have i to show except the promises i never kept? i lie here shaking on this bed, under the weight of my regrets i hope that i will never let you down i know that this can be more than just flashing lights and sound look around and you'll see that at times it feels like no one really cares it gets me down but i'm still gonna try to do what's right, i know that there's a difference between sleight of hand, and giving everything you have there's a line drawn in the sand, i'm working up the will to cross it rhetoric can't raise the dead i'm sick of always talking when there's no change i'm sick of empty words, let's lead and not follow late night, brakes lock, hear the tires squeal red light, can't stop so i spin the wheel my world goes black before i feel an angel steal me from the greedy jaws of death and chance, and pull me in with steady hands they've given me a second chance, the artist in the ambulance can we pick you off the ground, more than flashing lights and sound   Brilliant!
     
    
</post>
<date>23,November,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Dear Sonority,  Oh my goodness. can someone  please  tell me what plans i have on wednesday? (if you happen to know) i can't remember and i'm SO freaking out!  alamak ...
     
    
</post>
<date>23,November,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Dear Sonority,  Wow. read  urlLink this  article. my mom showed me one similar to it. how dumb is that? i wonder who were the "mature" little snots who thought they were so cool thinking up that kind of crap..c'mon! they're just meaningless little bracelets that have absolutely no purpose or point. honestly, the bracelets aren't the issue..it's the lack of parenting and all the sexin' going on these days by kids so young.   By the way, they aren't called "Sex bracelets" in Singapore if i'm not wrong? from what nic and eileen had mentioned to me earlier, they're called "F*** bracelets". ahaha! nice one.
     
    
</post>
<date>23,November,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Dear Sonority,  How's it going? i went bowling and chilled at west bowl yesterday after training, before returning home to watch the match of this season! hehs, if you have no idea what am i blabbering about, it's the rugby world cup finals between aussie and england! england won  20 - 17 . i wish i was in sydney among the thousands of spectators cos the vibe was sooo awesome!!  Anyways, Sir Faizal kept doing silly stunts while bowling yesterday. mind if ya break ya finger dude!! haha..some crazy spins, but some worked out well. hyper-active as usual..hehe. as fer' me..i can't bowl for nuts!! i'm not good at it. it's really weird though..when i'm playing for someone else, in this case for pinky, i strike sia(by luck)!!   Daddy brought mommy and i to the club for a swim after breakfast. i got sick of swimming after swimming for several laps, so i went tanning and fell asleep. fortunately, it wasn't very sunny. i would've gone kayaking today with sis cherryn if she allowed me to tagged along..but she and her junior were gonna practice their 3 star skills, i guess for another expedition? yes, so some other day, she says. serene has gone to the movies with her mates... and mika, exams! geeesh, that poor girl!  but  we're gonna have dinner outside tonight to celebrate her 20th birthday..hopefully she'll just let loose and have fun with us! *muakz!* i love you sissa!
     
    
</post>
<date>22,November,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Dear Sonority,   A  Jonny Wilkinson  drop-goal in the final minute of extra time secured the first ever Rugby World Cup win for England  20-17  over the Wallabies, in a pulsating Final at  Telstra Stadium in Sydney  last night. After being the focus of attention for practically the entire tournament, Wilkinson  under extreme pressure -- slotted the decider to secure the Webb-Ellis Cup for the Martin Johnson-led English. It followed a titanic fight-back from the Wallabies who went close to becoming the first team to defend a Rugby World Cup title and the first to come back after trailing at the half in a Final. England led 14-5 at the break after tries to Lote Tuquiri for Australia and Jason Robinson for England. The scores had been locked at  14-14 at full-time , after  Elton Flatley  kicked a dramatic last-minute penalty to draw Australia level. Flatley had earlier kicked two second-half penalties to close gap to three points. England led 17-14 after Wilkinson's fourth penalty early in the first period of extra time. But Flatley replied with another last-gasp penalty to level the scores again at 20-20 before Wilkinson clinched the decider in the last minute of extra-time. It was only the second time a RWC Final had gone to extra-time, securing  England's first every championship , and the first for northern hemisphere teams in Rugby World Cups. Australia's epic performance was also widely acknowledged, despite being the Wallabies' first ever loss in a Final.   ENGLAND AUSTRALIA   20  (14) Score  17  (14) Jason Robinson Tries Lote Tuquiri Cons  Jonny Wilkinson 4 Pens Elton Flatley 4  Jonny Wilkinson Drop-Goals     The match was incredibly exciting, although i was rather disappointed that the Wallabies (Australia) were defeated. i felt as though i was a part of England because when they were on stage victorious, tears welled up in my eyes, and i thought i was about to cry. i was touched, and felt elated for the English. to those who have missed the  urlLink Rugby World Cup  finals between England and Australia, be sure to catch the encore telecast if there is one. 
     
    
</post>
<date>21,November,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Dear Sonority,  Time for the  urlLink friday five !   1. List five things you'd like to accomplish by the end of the year.  * to finish my holiday assignments * have a sparkling clean bedroom and clean it regularly * learn to cook a decent meal * be a disciplined and well-respected NCO * lose 5 kg   2. List five people you've lost contact with that you'd like to hear from again.  * distant relatives * sally polihronas (ex-Bardette) * all kindergarten mates * all pri school mates * my grandmother who passed away..   3. List five things you'd like to learn how to do.  * 2 star kayaking  * guitar lessons instead of learning it on my own cos it's tough! * vocal lessons * photography * surfing   4. List five things you'd do if you won the lottery (no limit).  * donate to charity * buy a landed property for my family * treat everyone i know to an expensive 10-course dinner * build schools, houses and bomb shelters in countries like Iraq and Afghanistan * travel all over the world   5. List five things you do that help you relax.  * pray * listen to music * play the electric guitar * reading * day dream
     
    
</post>
<date>20,November,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Dear Sonority,  Hit the gym today with karen, ruth and liuming. woohoo! feeling refreshed and all. right now i'm just chilling at home after a rather tiring week. yesterday's rifle drill was incredibly fun though exhausting! the rifle is like, really heavy and imagine holding it in the "homad" position for an uber long time! unlike the NCC's unreal rifle which is made of wood, ours is the real thang dude. teeheee.  Today is sorta' the last day of school and i am gonna miss everyone. * sniffles * it is gonna be weird not attending school for the next 1 month or so. geesh.  Alrighty, for all those with  urlLink Friendster , do add me mmkays? keep grooving lovers! *huggles*
     
    
</post>
<date>18,November,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Dear Sonority,  I am still enjoying the after effects of all the fun I had at  Mr Lee's BBQ  party last night. i was physically drained, but mentally awake although i was in bed at 12 midnight..haha. i had to force myself to sleep. =\   Anyways, Mr Lee met up with Wenxing, nic(amelia), simon, jeremy and i at IMM in the afternoon and bought our BBQ essentials. he drove us to his place and the guys ganged up against me. made me sit in front with Mr Lee. it was kinda' embarrasing cos' they wouldn't stop teasing me..especially simon and wenxing! *grrrr!!!* how annoying can those silly fellas get? at one point when it was really sunny, mr lee helped me put down the shade above me, then wenxing was all " did you all see that? " that freaking a**h*** said it so loudly and they were all cracking up then mr lee was like " see what? " all blur. my gosh, i swear i could've kicked wenxings balls then. *grr!* so paiseh..  The entire BBQ went really well. the weather was awesome and everything went on smoothly although there was an excess in food. wenxing was so frustrated cos' he couldn't cut the stingray! haha! cut until the knife BENT! another hilarious scene was while preparing food before the rest arrived, mr lee tried to cut the corn using the knife and the corn was flying all over the place! he didn't succeed in cutting them so i was like, "you don't help out in the kitchen at home do ya?" and he was like "yaa!" with a grin flashed across his cheeks. haha!  We had a "moon-tan" and caught up with one another. geetha, karen, eileen, peiwen, dingling, gerry and i tried to push our girlfriends down * eh hem * while strolling at the edge of the pool. haha! mission unaccomplished though, and gerry and geetha slipped and fell on their butts!  oouuccch!!  we all broke out in laughter. tehee. those poor lil' souls who fell on their butts.  Mr Lee had chats with all of us and we kept asking him about his sons. so we finally went upstairs and i think he asked his son to come out...but he was all shy, and so were we. so never talk to him. * aww ..* but he is   really  good-looking . he has the  ACS(I)+outdoor sporty+smart+skater  look. very cheeky face too. (btw, he skates! so hip hop rite?) and according to ruth, he is in ACS(I). so like, wow, ellidegable bachelor huh? but seriously jess, he's much cuter than your  tuna ! keke..just kidding. don slaughter me.   After a looooong day, daddy picked ruth, dingling, yulun and i up at about 10pm..sooo exhausted! keke, if you're interested to see some of zee photos, click  urlLink HERE ! haha. had heaps of fun and we have to thank Mr and Mrs Lee for this awesome party. =D  So long mates! tata!
     
    
</post>
<date>17,November,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Dear Sonority,  I shall gladly admit that  today  is one of the  *BEST DAY OF MY LIFE!*  I had just taken a bath after returning home from  Mr Lee's BBQ  at his condo. it was   amazing  . so wild, so fun, so crazy, so happy, so delicious, so  shuai (his sons) and so WET that i will always remember this day.      17th November 2003     Mr Lee and 3B1'03 rocks me and my socks!      Always ... (Shall blog more tomorrow) Good night for now. 
     
    
</post>
<date>16,November,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Dear Sonority,  New layout up! i had just unknowingly given away several millions (or billions?) of NP to Zuhayr. *sniffle sniffle* that lucky boy...i honestly didn't realise that i had mansions worth of money in my account which i haven't touched for donkey years. grieve, i shall not, because if i ever play neopets again i would SO get hooked.  Anyways! Mr Lee's BBQ is tomorrow and i'm exhilarated. keep loving sweethearts. peace out. xox.
     
    
</post>
<date>14,November,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Dear Sonority,  I had a haircut! actually, i had it trimmed and layered. however, according to my sis(cherryn), it looks the same. i also bought black nail varnish and it looks really gothic. then serene says it doesn't suit me. i tried to remove it, but the varnish seems to have gone under my nail!? arrrgh! i think i need some help here..  Anyways, i'm really anxious about tomorrow's campcraft selection. i'm not afraid of  not  getting into the team, i'm just, nervous that it might be too tough to handle. another cause of worry would be the attendance of my squad and my juniors. we are expected to pump 10 times for every NCO who doesn't turn up. and 8 of them didn't turn up during the previous training. *gulps*  I did  urlLink this  cos' i felt like i didn't have a life. * boredom envelops pearls *
     
    
</post>
<date>12,November,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Spare a thought for Mrs Lee:   Senior Minister Lee continues to worry for Singapore, at the ripe age of 80, when many of his peers have retired and are enjoying life. We continue to benefit from his views, so if his wife is not all right, he is not going to be able to focus. From what i read, Mrs Lee took care of the family while Mr Lee took care of the nation. any married man will tell you that that takes a lot of sacrifice. cost of medical treatment for Mrs Lee? At this time we should be asking, "Mrs Lee, are you feeling better?"  --  The Straits Times   It is ironical that some Singaporeans should question the integrity of SM Lee. it is indeed very sad. sigh. hopefully both SM and Mrs Lee recovers speedily. 
     
    
</post>
<date>11,November,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Wednesday, and i love you still.  Days pass, boys and men talk to and at me, of love or the feelings that they imagine to be sweet, and it's all very nice, and i take comfort where i may, but my brain and body ache after you.
     
    
</post>
<date>11,November,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Dear Sonority,   Geetha, Jessica, Ruth and i hit the gym this late morning to shed off some calories after history lessons. we met up with Amelia in the noon to check out the prices of the BBQ essentials and cracked up at every lilttle thing we talked about. it was difficult to make a choice between the two bottles of wine we saw, which we thought would make an excellent gift for Mr Lee. both wine bottles looked incredibly exquisite. Geetha mentioned that yam biscuits would be suitable for him whereas Jess felt that Yun Nam haircare vouchers were more benifitting. i thought it would be a GREAT idea to leave   our   mobile phone numbers in a box of ferrero rocher for his 3 sons.  Regarding my previous post, difficult times have helped me to understand better than before, how infinitely rich and beautiful life is in every way.    urlLink Chuang Tzu  quotes, "Flow with whatever is happening and let your mind be free. stay centered by accepting whatever you are doing. this is the ultimate."   
     
    
</post>
<date>10,November,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Dear Sonority,   Life at this stage of my life is pretty different...  Have you ever encountered a specific point in life whereby this huge change occurs in yourself you don't even realise what you're doing, whether or not it hurts your friends, family members or even yourself? sometimes, you're doing it because it provides support for your ego and sometimes you stay in that position out of sheer inertia because others expect it of you.   I hope that no one hates or holds a grudge against me. cos nobody is truly perfect. ultimately humans will never be perfect, maybe 99% but not 100%.  Just like a diamond, i hope i will be polished into a better person...
     
    
</post>
<date>09,November,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Dear Sonority,   I WAS drunk last night at my cousin's only after drinking a teeny weeny bit of alcohol while enjoying the rugby match. and i'm suprised there was no typo in that post or should i say 'short statement.' ignore the previous entry, it doesn't seem to make sense. "heart-poundingly"? what was i thinking? and also when i think sober, i talked a lot, to a lot of people and now i 'kinda' regret it.  The regret that makes u go "i ain't drinking and talking after it no more!"   Did you guys watch the  urlLink rugby world cup  match last night when England played against Wales? friggin' awesome wasn't it!?  prince Harry  was present too... * awwwwsh *  
     
    
</post>
<date>09,November,2003</date>
<post>

     
      "You sound like an orgastic trumpet." "You can say that again." --My sisters, apparently trying to tell me how i sound like while blowing my nose.   Oh alcohol..sweet heavenly alcohol.  Thank you for being so accepting and for everything you do to my body.   Gotta go and catch some sleep..a few hours left. Heart-poundingly.. is there even such a word?!..  
     
    
</post>
<date>08,November,2003</date>
<post>

     
       The Sound of Silence    Hello darkness, my old friend,  I've come to talk with you again,  Because a vision softly creeping,  Left its seeds while I was sleeping,  And the vision that was planted in my brain  Still remains  Within the sound of silence.  In restless dreams I walked alone  Narrow streets of cobblestone,  'Neath the halo of a street lamp,  I turned my collar to the cold and damp  When my eyes were stabbed by the flash of a neon light  That split the night  And touched the sound of silence.   And in the naked light I saw  Ten thousand people, maybe more.  People talking without speaking,  People hearing without listening,  People writing songs that voices never share  And no one dare  Disturb the sound of silence.   "Fools" said I, "You do not know  Silence like a cancer grows.  Hear my words that I might teach you,  Take my arms that I might reach you."  But my words like silent raindrops fell,  And echoed  In the wells of silence   And the people bowed and prayed  To the neon god they made.  And the sign flashed out its warning,  In the words that it was forming.  And the sign said, "The words of the prophets  are written on the subway walls  And tenement halls."  And whisper'd in the sounds of silence.    The Sound of Silence  -- Simon  Garfunkel   
     
    
</post>
<date>08,November,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Dearest Sonority,   I'm red and hot all over. the weather today is  aggravating . first it was all uuubber hot in the early part of the day i swear i could've walked around the house naked (but i didn't cos i wasn't alone at home). then it rained cats and dogs abruptly like nobody's business in the evening. (o'_'o) gee.  Anyways, i seriously think there is something wrong with my skin. one reason why i turn red, or in simpler words,  blush  easily, could be due to the dilation of my arterioles located near the surface of my skin. on the other hand, my blood capillaries and arterioles could be just a hair's breadth from my skin! (although it may sound rather ridiculous)  yet if that isn't the case, then why is it that i get red and tanned easily?   While we were training for the campcraft competition under the scorching hot sun this morning/noon, we had to carry our metal pegs and run around the tracks on the field at the same time. i was holding one peg and a mallot on the other so that slowed me down and i got pretty exahausted before my face became bright  red . once again,  sir benghui   had  to make fun of me in hokkien.. but it's not like i have total control over what my body does right? aiii. in addition, during one particular npcc meeting that was held in the np room,  mr lau  came in and spoke to us and asked why my face was red. he  actually   thought  that i had make up on.  Another time when ruth, jessica and i wento sentosa beach during one of the marking days, ruth and i got so badly burnt that when i went to school a few days later, taufiq and the guys called me "lobster" and all kinds of 'funny' names. haha..but it was incredibly horrifying then? cos' my face swelled up and i had to see a doctor. ruth even ran a fever and got me so worried. when we returned to school (reluctantly) after days of rest, people wanted to help peel our skins cos they  assumed  that it was  fun . hurhurr.   On a brighter note, japanese cucumbers are awesome as it helps to cool and at the same time, whitens and brings glow to your face.   Method:  1. Peel off the skin and put it in the fruit juice extractor 2. Mix the paste and juice together 3. Add a little fresh milk/olive oil 4. Dip in cotton wool and put it onto your face for 10 minutes 5. Clean off with water  Have fun trying that out! :) peace out. xox.   P.S : You know you want to see  urlLink this .
     
    
</post>
<date>06,November,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Dearest Sonority,   Sometimes its murder being a headteacher. here are the opening words at the website of Birkbeck School, North Somercotes, Lincolnshire. i do not doubt their sincerity.   Achievement By Caring  It is my pleasure to introduce you to The Birkbeck School.  We are a successful 11-16 mixed secondary school close to Grimsby and Louth.  We are a friendly, caring school, with dedicated, well qualified staff who share a vision of striving for the highest levels of success and achievement for all students.  We offer students of all abilities the chance to succeed. Our aim is to identify the unique needs of all children in order that we can help them attain the very best results from their time with us.  The school has three core values, Learning, Respect and Responsibility. These values underpin everything we do.   We believe very firmly in a partnership between the school, the children and their parents.   Our mission statement is simple. Achievement By Caring  Being successful at Birkbeck is as simple as ABC.  We think that The Birkbeck School is a great school, but don't just take our word for it. You are most welcome to see us in action. We will arrange for a tour of the school for any prospective parents.  Please call 01507 358 352  G P Loveridge (Headteacher)    Something tells me that the phone will now be  urlLink off the hook .  A 14-year-old boy died 4 days back after being stabbed inside the Lincolnshire school he attended, police said.  A 15-year-old student at Birkbeck school, in North Somercotes, near Louth, was arrested and taken to Skegness police station in connection with the death.  Frankly i was amazed that the website was still functioning. it soon may not be. 
     
    
</post>
<date>06,November,2003</date>
<post>

     
       "Variation on the Word Sleep"   I would like to watch you sleeping,  which may not happen. I would like to watch you, sleeping.  I would like to sleep with you, to enter your sleep  as its smooth dark wave slides over my head and walk with you through that lucent  wavering forest of bluegreen leaves  with its watery sun  three moons  towards the cave where you must descend,  towards your worst fear.  I would like to give you the silver branch,  the small white flower,  the one word that will protect you  from the grief at the center of your dream,  from the grief at the center.  I would like to follow you up the long stairway  again  become the boat that would row you back carefully,  a flame in two cupped hands  to where your body lies beside me,  and you enter it as easily as breathing in.  I would like to be the air that inhabits you for a moment only.  I would like to be that unnoticed  that necessary. 
     
    
</post>
<date>06,November,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Dear Sonority ,  Hello hello. well i had some time and boredom was killing me so here i am writing. serene composed another song on the guitar this afternoon while i tried to figure out the chords of "why can't i" by  liz phair . she makes great music and has an awesome style as an individual. in addition,  tiffani wood , previously known as tiffany wood from  bardot  has an upcoming single which would be released in feb 2004 and her 26th birthday is in 2 days time. happy birthday tiff! =)   Mr lee, jeremy, lucas, jason(weihoong), weizheng, junhong and i had lunch together. jason and i initially thought of treating mr lee to lunch due to something he had done for 3B1..but he just wouldn't accept our treat!? i got really excited asking about his sons..ehee. i wonder how they look like and seriously can't wait til' the 17th. woot! life is on the run.  Geetha and i are gonna hit the gym at 8am tomorrow before math. yayyy..i can  finally  do a proper work out instead of doing jumping jacks, sit ups, push ups at home. =\   Keep grooving and stay healthy guys. peace out. 
     
    
</post>
<date>05,November,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Shut up Just shut up, shut up  Shut up Just shut up, shut up  Shut up Just shut up, shut up  Shut it up, just shut up  We try to take it slow But we're still losin control And we try to make it work But it still ends up the worst And I'm craaazzzy For tryin to be your laaadddy I think I'm goin crazy  [Check this out:  Black eyed peas   Shut up ]   The holidays are here yet it seems rather ironical because i still am in between the normal school days and exam mood. i think i'm crazy. i'm even staying up until midnight to complete my homework. and to tell you the truth, this is the 1st time i am starting on my homework  this  soon. i have always, in my  entire  life (at least til now), left holiday homework to the  very last  week of the holidays. as a matter of fact, i have never seriously sat down and complete my hol homework. teehee. can somebody tell me what is wrong with me? i feel as though i'm kidding myself, but i ain't. what exactly is causing this gargantuan change to happen? gee, motivation, such an aggravation. or..is it, just me. 
     
    
</post>
<date>04,November,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Dear Sonority,   the new layout is up thanks to blogskins.com for the different types of uber kick-ass templates. this one's kinda er...  mooooooo -ey hey? i duno i guess i just got inspired from some of my mates off the internet. so far i've spoken to zuhayr, dan, val, jo, geetha, allan, jolene and quite a coupla' other people. i'm rather exhausted now and my eyes are as dry as meatballs. i still have a few more questions to go for a-math and i'm done with the extra homework given by cutie pie mr lee.   i am seriously considering whether or not to join the vocal lessons. i am so incredibly enticed!! will anyone say anything?
     
    
</post>
<date>04,November,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Dear Sonority,  i'm like SO glad my net is fixed..finally. i can keep up with people then. i'm really excited cos i'm gonna put up a new layout! this one is a lil' depressing.   i've been playing with my guitar and composing music with serene lately. she is sucha' great song-writer! i have so much to catch up on hey. i really gotta learn the skills. yesterday,  jiax  and i hit the malls and caught the movie,  "ong-bak" . it is excellent. then i wenta music concerto to check out the array of courses they had.  "VOCAL"  lessons. ah! $78 per month for 3 months for the basic course. do you think it would be worth it to sign up? everyone thinks it's kinda' er...useless, but i truely love singing. music is my life.  in addition, i have been actively involved in  npcc  at school, because exams are over and i am an NCO (not officially though). i love my life right now. it's so...productive. whenever i am free, i either read, play the guitar, work out or revise my school work. hopefully i will be able to do the same..now that my internet is back.  take care ya'll. *huggles*  
     
    
</post>
<date>30,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
          Good charlotte - Riot girl   The latest: 1).  urlLink Iran quake death toll hits 28,000  2).  urlLink HK pop star Anita Mui dies  3).  urlLink China confirms Sars case   So many things have been happening lately.. whether sad, or happy. That is why I believe that it is essential to count our blessings and remind ourselves constantly of how lucky we are. Even if it is as simple as having a roof over our heads, it should not be taken for granted. Take the earth quake in Iran for example. Although it did not affect us, Singaporeans, greatly, we should think of the less fortunate, feel for them, and we even can do our part by praying for them. Thus, I have decided to create a  urlLink blog  whereby I write down 3 blessings a day. It is a a great way for all of us to get into the habit of counting our blessings and appreciating life. I sincerely hope you all will join me in doing it.
     
    
</post>
<date>28,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
          Sum 41 - Motivation   Yeehaw! I feel soo GOOD. I just got back from a swim and a sauna at my Dad's club. Sundays are wicked cos' your parents finally get a day off to spend time with the kids.   Anyways,  Christmas celebration  was marvellous. My family and I stayed home and had a scrumptious Christmas dinner YUMMY...  We watched The Christmas Wish and cracked up so badly.. And I suppose I could tell you about my Christmas pressies :P Mainly food la. Honey roasted almonds chocolate galore... Gosh! Haha.. There are like brownies, cookies, HEAPS of chocolates that could last me for years (*Teehee*), cool clothes from OP picked by my Mom and Dad! (*Huggles*) Earings, bracelets and stuff like that. I am so thankful for everything that I have received.   On the 26th, a buncha' NPCC peeps from my school and tss went to West Coast Park for a BBQ. It was ather amusing! Senior edwin brought twines along and made use of it when it started pouring by building a shelter with a canvas sheet. Glad am I that he was around! And thanks to Val and Xiongster for organising this activity! Thanks for all the presents too..  Yesterday was my Granny's 75th birthday and I had forgotten all about it until my lil' sister rang me up on my mobile. I had only 30 minutes to rush home before they leave the house and I was at bras brasah with my seniors. So I had to take a cab home. And.. *heaves a sigh of relief* I managed to reach home just in time. On a lighter note, my couzzie's girlfriend happens to be from ct as well. I think her name is Liting. Graduated last year. She's very amiable and angelic. :D I love being with my relatives. They are so easy-going and cranky, especially Auntie Enjaneek. *Muaks*   Take care everyone. Make good use of the remaining days of the holidays. Til then, xox.
     
    
</post>
<date>24,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
          Stacie orrico - More to life   Don't know why, I just wanna spend a quiet christmas at home with my family, enjoy my Dad's white wine, feast, watch telly and get some good decent sleep.   I feel strangely subdued, I just want to be alone this evening, away from all the noise, the endless complaining and whinning. I want a peaceful christmas, listening to my Christmas songs and tv programmes. I got lotsa' new year resolutions this coming 2004... but before that, I would like to retreat into my tiny shell and not hear a single thing from the world outside.   Wham's "Last Christmas" was playing on my PC just now, reminds me of how crazy I used to be over the 80s. Haha. I love the 80s!!!! Big hair, bright colour clothes, big dangling earrings... and Madonna writhing in "Like A Virgin" video. Pop was good then... 
     
    
</post>
<date>22,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
          Green day - Minority   Nora and I headed to town today and wenta' fish and co. for lunch. The food was fab, and so was the ambience. The restaurant played all my favourite songs too.. *Laadeedaaa* We took 2 sticker prints, unfortunately, I can't scan them out because my scanner is stuffed up, so I can only upload them when Nora comes online tonight. On our way home, we thought of a brilliant idea to swop mobile phones so now, I am a proud owner of a white  urlLink SGH-S200 ! :) It's sucha nifty phone and I'm in love with it! Nora hearts my pink nokia 2100 too! By the way, Ignatious, we do not belong to the  sorority sluts  okie.. how mean of you to think that we belong to that group. *Sniffles* :,( Ahaha ok kidding lar little boy :P I just found it rather amusing when Nora told me about it. Huhur.  I miss my classmates.. Jeremy, Jason, Jessica, Amily, Dingling, Geetha, Jiax, Amelia, Karen, Simon, Ruth, Eileen, Gerry, Siti, Zu, Fiona, Narin, and everybody else. Can't wait for school to re-open! But I haven't completed my homework. Geez.
     
    
</post>
<date>21,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
          The all american rejects - Why worry   Reuben is super duper cool because he's buying me  urlLink this  Slick Shoes album for Christmas! Talking about Christmas pressies, I went Christmas shopping a coupla' days back and bought heaps of chocolates, soft toys, flowers, cards and earings. I don't really mind spending all that I've got in my piggy bank because Christmas is all about giving... and sharing... and being happy.  Yesterday's campcraft training showed improvement in terms of our team spirit and the quality of our tents! I am incredibly impressed by our never give up spirit. Seniors beng, xiongster, edwin all played in the mud.. barefooted. Haha. So gross I tell ya! But it seemed rather fun.. and Jolene kept whining because she wanted to join in the fun by taking off her shoes too. Nana and I were craving for food by the time training ended so we went to BB's Mac and bought ice cream! YUMMMY! She bought bubblegum flavour while I purchased my all time favourite, HOT FUDGE!   Val, Pinky, Faizal, Beng and I caught  Lord of the rings . Yay like finally! I was desperate to see it. The movie was  marvellous . The sceneries were jaw-dropping and the hunks and babes were all so adorable.  Must see it .. :) Faizola and Beng met me below my block to return me $ and we talked quite a bit before returning home for dinner. I didn't want to go back up so soon actually. I should've walked them to the bus stop. I have so much to say.
     
    
</post>
<date>20,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
          Good charlotte - Wondering   I have this little box  Filled with memories of you. Sometimes I open it  And remember the times we shared.   It makes me feel whole, just as much as empty,  Happy, just as much as sad,  And, loved just as much as lonely.    As I pick up the scattered memories,  I feel as though I am picking up  Pieces of my heart.   I smell them, feel them,  Touch them, and remember them.    When I put them together,  I feel as though as I am constructing a mold of my heart,  Replacing each piece of the frame.   Every time I open the box,  The frame gets stronger and less fragile.    It makes me smile to know that  At one time I was loved and that I loved.   Many pieces remind me of the pain you gave me,  But with sorrow and grief... comes power and triumph  And I feel as though I have won.    You may have broke my heart  But you taught me something;  If you love someone, really really love them,  Love will give you the strength to let them go.
     
    
</post>
<date>18,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
          Dashboard confessional - So impossible   According to Val, Sir Faizal wants us to wait for him to return from NS (Taiwan) before watching the  Lord of the rings: The return of the king . However, I'm way too ecstatic to and I'm intoxicated with my sisters because they keep talking about it. I have no idea when is he coming back and I've gone ape! So if I happen to feel an extreme itch, I  will  not hesitate to catch the movie without waiting! But I'll trrry my very best. Haha.   On a brighter note, my parents have arrived safely! My father mentioned that it was one of my mom's elite holidays. I'm glad that they relished their stay there, because eversince my mom had stopped working at MOE and transferred herself to work as an admin manager in a school, she has been too caught up with work to even spend quality time with us. She rarely smiled, and has become so 'blur'. Now that she's back, she's all smiley smiley!  :)  Yet I'm quite sure she misses her work. She's such an efficient worker, she does her typings on the computer at home and revises her 'homework' as well. I am so proud of her. Oh yes! My mom and dad bought us such adorable keychains for our mobiles, and also bought other stuff such as handphone pouches, scarves, winter clothing,  bracelets  and handbags. And it's amazing, the stories they've related. Life at the moment is so fulfilling.  I am learning , to be grateful for all the things in life. It means to be thankful and express admiration... It also means to grow or appreciate in value. As you  appreciate life , you become more valuable, both to yourself and others. 
     
    
</post>
<date>17,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
          Amy studt - Misfit   Hola there, do you like the new layout that I've created? :) It isn't very chrismassy but i like its simplicity. Anyways, have you guys seen ' The making of the Lord of the rings ' on Channel news asia just a while ago? It was incredibly nifty! I absolutely cannot wait to see it in the theatres. *Girly screams* I'm glad my parents are returning home from their business trip tonight because i need some cash urgently. They didn't leave us with any money when they left for China. *Sniffles* But i survived. Ooh yes i did. Mwaha. Then maybe i could catch the movie with Val and all. 
     
    
</post>
<date>16,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
           Reliant K - Pressing on        STILL STANDING:  urlLink SANDRA  IS SOLE SURVIVOR         Thirty-nine days, 16 castaways, four tribes, dozens of broken alliances, a quitter,  a grandmother who isn't really dead , and now, one Sole Survivor!  Sandra Diaz-Twine , the 29-year-old office assistant from Ft. Lewis, Washington, captured the million-dollar prize. In the gut-wrenching final Tribal Council, Sandra pleaded to the Jury that she went along with whatever alliance would have her without asking questions. Sandra claimed she never got in anyone's way, staying quietly in the background, and that she deserved to be the Sole Survivor. The Jury agreed in a  6 to 1 decision , making Sandra the Sole Survivor and the recipient of the one million dollar prize.    urlLink More...    SURVIVOR  was TEH B3ST! I was hoping that Darrah or Sandra would win, and Sandra did. She definitely deserved the million dollars. I respect her utmostly, especially her incredibly truthful and straightforward personality. In addition, she is the only sole survivor in the  entire  series who has NOT EVEN  ONE  vote casted against her!!! Amazed? YES!  I hate to be judged so I try my outmost best not to judge people... as I always believe there is more to the physical. Like what Shaun has mentioned, there seems to be different aspects of depiction of every character in the game. For example, the more triumph moments of RUPERT BONEHAM! 
    
</post>
<date>15,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Dear Sonority,   CAN YOU TELL?? I'M SOOOO PSYCHED!!!! I WATCHED * ELF * with jiax AND IT'S SOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO MILLION-GA-TRILLION-DEE-POPPIN-FRREAKIN-ZILLION KICK-ARSE!!! IT'S HELLA' GOOD I'M NOT KIDDING!! It's sucha' great movie YOU ALL SHOULD GO WATCH IT WITH YOUR FRIENDS AND FAMILY! dang i'm in the X'MAS mood.
     
    
</post>
<date>14,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Dear Sonority,   I so need to complete my holiday assignments. an emphasis on the so. when i awoke this morning, i felt as though i was bobbing up and down the waters. teehee. nice nice feeling. anyways! i'm going to the gym tomorrow with val and we're doin homework with xiongster after that. geesh! i really need to train my stamina for tuesday's campcraft. oh yupp, new photos uploaded! :)
     
    
</post>
<date>13,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Dear Sonority,    Tres  (3, in spanish) new links! :)  urlLink nora ,  urlLink sophian  and  urlLink grace .   How is  todo el mundo  (everyone)?  Spanish is sexy.  I amor espa ol!  (i love spanish!)   Adios!  (goodbye!)
     
    
</post>
<date>13,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Dear Sonority,   I thought i'd share the joke which i came across the internet after watching Michael Jackson's home vids :)    A little kid asks his father, "Daddy, is God a man or a woman?"  "Both son. God is both."   After awhile the kid comes again and asks, "Daddy, is God black or white?"  "Both son, both." "Daddy, does God love children?"   "Yes son, he loves all children."   The child returns a few minutes later and says, "Daddy, is Michael Jackson God?"     Anyways! today was THA' B0MB! val, xiongster, beng, edwin, meiyi, yati and myself gave ourselves a common surname because we belonged to the similar 'family'! so now we're called the " dabeaches ". don't ask how we came up with that name, we just did. we headed to siloso beach for a kick-butt outing! it was mad..you can read it at val's OD too. we soaked in the sea and played silly coconut bomb games. then val and i played some kayaking water-polo(?) game with a buncha cuuute boys. yes an emphasis on the cute. we were kayaking around the area when we accidentally bumped into their kayaks so later they approached and asked if we wanted to play. at first we ignored them and kayaked away. haha. but since they asked a coupla' times, we obliged. teehee. and! kana beng's super power sand ball! * bish !* oouch..haha. val and i did brainless stunts such as impersonating kate winslet and leonardo dicarprio in a titanic scene. edwin and all also dug a hee-uge hole and burried val in it as an xmas gift for her! haha. her entire body ached so badly after a bashing. that poor soul. oohs you had no idea how much i enjoyed myself today :D
     
    
</post>
<date>12,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Dear Sonority,   It's time for the Friday five.   1. Do you enjoy the cold weather and snow for the holidays?  Where's the snow? i'm living in a tropical country. we don't have snow here, teehee. but i'm dreaming that someday it will snow. we do have a cold weather. yet i don't quite like the monsoon season. storms are scary. okay, you get the drift.   2. What is your ideal holiday celebration? How, where, with whom would you celebrate to make things perfect?  I usually celebrate Christmas with my family, loved ones, relatives and friends. we have this yearly family reunion. it's held at our grandparents' place/s, where there are lots of christmas goodies, foods and gifts; and where everybody is happy :)   3. Do you do have any holiday traditions?  Nope!   4. Do you do anything to help the needy?  Yupp. i donate money and old stuff to the salvation army.   5. What one gift would you like for yourself?  LOVE and HAPPINESS :)
     
    
</post>
<date>11,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Dear Sonority,   I've been vomitting and diareough-ing(sp?) for the past 2 days..i couldn't eat. so i lost quite a bit of weight. i'm quite certain that i'll gain back those few pounds though. haha. i'm presently feeling better already. but everytime i stand up i feel naseous.   Anyways, about Bali.. it was a great place. however, the first night was rather shocking. there was a flood after we touched down at about 10pm and my sister, cherryn, lost her luggage. things got worse as when we were on our way to our hotel, "kuta paradiz" (aka kuta paradiso hotel)...the jeep we were in broke down cos water went into the exhaust pipe (due to flood). it was an eye-opener..seeing people who live on the road sides sweep water out of their homes because you NEVER see that happen in Singapore. fortunately, a few teenage boys came around to help us. they pushed our transport about 200m to our hotel and ironically, seemed to enjoy being drenched.   The next morning, we received news that my sister's luggage was found and was on its way to Bali in a Singapore airline. it wasn't removed from the cargo and was flown to Sydney. 2nd day was more of a relaxation thing..cos we strolled at the beach, went swimming, played pool, went shopping and all. we also had dinner by the beach. it was simply relaxing..  3rd day was pretty much hectic. we managed to get this really nice taxi driver, uncle wayan, to take us around Bali. he drove us in a huge toyota jeep to many places. we saw the kecap dance, went to silverware shops, art museum, the monkey forest, some mountains which was terribly cold. haha. so we were out for more than 12 hours today. so bumped out! ;P oh yes, we also went to the specific area of the Bali bombings, also known as Ground zero. am i right? it was crowded..many vehicles. there were tee-shirts hung on gates with the words "F*** TERRORISTS". we also met an australian lady at the beach who had that tee-shirt on. they sell it at every market in Bali. built at the memorial site was a huge wall which had the names of the deceased carved. * sniffles * i feel for them.  We had breakfast the next day as usual and went for a swim before departing. wenta' Pacung mountain resort at a mountain. it was cool. about 22 degrees celsius. we took about 2-3 hours before arriving. the scenery is absolutely amazing. again, it was an eye-opener! the resort and our bungalow over-looked the padi fields. and unlike the pictures depicted in the lower sec geography text books of the terrace thingies, the ones that i saw at the mountain was nothing like that. it was just undoubtedly....BEAUTIFUL.  At this point..i was already sick. i had a sore throat and runny nose. so my mom could only feed me with heaps of vitamins. haha. i think i've never had so much...fun before. we spent heaps of quality time together as a family. teehee. i wish those moments would never ever end. we all just layed at the couches at the lounge and talked and talked. then we could hear the farmers singing at 9pm + at night. the ambience was incredibly awesome. soo amiable :) so sweet. so relaxing. so pleasant. so positively-everything.  The last day of our tour approached quickly and it was time to leave Mount kinta-something. haha sorry i haven't got all the names of our destinations right (except for Bali) cos' i'm still in a state of being nauseous. anyhow, we left for the airport and then arrived in Singapore at about 6pm.  HOME SWEET HOME! i was really glad to be back cos' i needed to see a doctor urgently. unexpectedly, my sisters and i started passing out u-know-what and vomitted many times. my mom brought us to the doctor at about 10, 11pm + and the doctor confirmed that i had a flu virus and food poisoning. * double sigh * so now i'm just resting and recuperating at home. i didn't eat for 42 hours..just drank water and glucose. haha. quite an accomplishment i would say! but the abdominal cramps are really..like pain until wanna die that type. yeah.. but they always say,  "there will always be sunshine after a rainy day."  (quoted by mr lee. teehee) hence, i assume that something sweet will be coming my way.   This trip has been one of the most enriching so far. i believe it's because i've grown up. okay not exactly but i've grown a lil' more as compared to the past years. i've seen, with my own eyes, the lives of the extremely poor Balinese and those who have an average-income, just like uncle wayan. i guess uncle wayan is already quite fortunate to secure himself with a job. though so, he has to support his family (2 daughters) by working as a taxi driver (day time) AND a cashier at a hotel (night time). he has only 5 hours of sleep daily. he  really  is a good man. anyone going to bali in future, give me a ring and i'll let you know his contact number if you need a ride around Bali. anyways, i've learnt much more..but it'll take me forever to type it all out. i presume you guys know what i mean. all these takes true experiences to comprehend. no matter how horrible or how kick-arse my written reflections are in my blog, you will unable to understand the TRUE meanings..  On a lighter note, take care my friends, and have fun, as...TIS' THE SEASON TO BE HAPPY! :D
     
    
</post>
<date>10,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Dear Sonority,   I'm feeling very weak now..thought maybe can update about what happened in Bali but i think some other time la. suffering from food poisoning...
     
    
</post>
<date>05,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Dear Sonority,   I'm leaving now!! haha. toodles guys! :D teehee. rmbr to flood my inbox!! haha. miss ya!
     
    
</post>
<date>04,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Dear Sonority,   Yay! the layout is much more colourful now. TIS' THE SEASON TO BE HAPPY!!! woot! now do you feel a touch of the  christmas vibe? :D  I'm leaving in 3 hours time. so excited!!
     
    
</post>
<date>04,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Dear Sonority,    urlLink I've never been this terrified.   To make things worst, i had a nightmare. it was a depiction of me, contracting  SARS . this is the 4th time! * shrieks * =\
     
    
</post>
<date>04,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Dear Sonority,   I deleted the post on TAMPONS because it absolutely did not make sense and i was out humiliating myself. it was just the usual nonsensical ramblings by pearlyn yap. hahaa. Anwyays, i'm off to meet val and all at JP! tc babes..
     
    
</post>
<date>03,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
       To see more photos from the  ROD  (esp cute boys like the one on the left, who is chek whye, haha!) click  urlLink HERE .  To view photos which were taken at  work (MOE)  this afternoon, click  urlLink HERE .   Tmrw will be fun. seniors and i are going to soul garden for lunch :) that'll be my last time seeing them before i leave for Bali on friday evening! i'm worried. i've sat the aeroplane more than 10 times but..somehow, i'm quite scared..ahh... not to mention, i have altophobia. i've heard from many that Bali is a great place, especially for tanning! i'll also be staying at one of the resorts on some hill, near some plantations. haha. i don't know why but i'm soo excited cos i love the food in the aeroplane! it just tastes special. don't you all agree? or maybe i'm just weird! but yeaa..i love the desert especially! haha. it's like, of the highest quality. but the only thing i find it unfair about is that i'm gonna miss SURVIVOR! sigh.   Okies...good night!  To  NATALIE :  HAPPY BIRTHDAY TO YOU!!!  *huggles!*
     
    
</post>
<date>01,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Dear Sonority,   Today is my 3rd  and  last day of work. miss chua said that there isn't anything left to do since we've completed coding and checking all the o level mother tongue scripts. cherryn insisted on staying to help, whereas i suggested not surrendering our temp staff passes to the security. time passes really quickly at work hey, especially when you're enjoying every moment of it! :) besides, the pay is extremely satisfying. $5.60 per hour. you can't find any other job which pays you this much, is fully air-conditioned, has kind and helpful staff and supervisors, provides comfortable office chairs tables for your own use, 2 tea-breaks + 1 lunch break, free tea and coffee, sparkling clean rest rooms, can listen to discman and slack a bit after working for a long time and can work at your own pace one leh.. MOE ROCKS!!! haha. aiight..sue me....mwaha! Went through the o level chinese paper today..quite badly done sia. for my batch of scripts, majority failed and scrapped through the passing mark. the minority scored higher than 55/80. i'm quite worried about next year when it comes to our turn.   YESTERDAY  was the  ROD  for our unit's NPCC. haha. seniors weipo, yati and bernard graduated from our unit's NPCC le..haha. 3 cheers for our kick-arse seniors! * woot !* i'm very happy for them! and i'll miss them heaps!!  yati, bernard  and  weipo  rocks my socks!!! jiayou in the future CI courses!  I'll post the pictures up as soon as i upload them all :)
     
    
</post>
<date>01,December,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Dear Sonority,  S$45 X 4DAYS = S$180. I've finally realised the value of money.   Anyways! today's my very  1st day at work . basically, my sister, her friends, senior xiongster and i have to report to work at 8.30am daily at MOE (tiong bahru examination branch) to do  coding . it's fairly simple. we handled the O level malay and tamil papers today. copying and checking of marks. heaps of paper work. the staff there are really nice though! they gave us tea-breaks, spoke to us patiently and taught us how to go about doing stuff right :) i would say 45 bucks is good money! snr xiongster and i are gonna eat rice tmrw. definitely! heh. cos we were still hungry after eating a bowl of S$2 meepok today. it was wicked, yet a rather small portion, considering our big bellies! we ended work at 5pm and i don't know why i'm still feeling quite pschyed! but at the same, pretty much beat, cos' i woke up in the middle of the night at 3.30am to look for food *oops!* then at 6am to get ready for work. i also have a muscle ache from the sat's monkey bar.   On a brighter note, i can't wait for tmrw's passing out parade. *Woot!* :D til' then, keep loving!
     
    
</post>
<date>30,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
          Bowling for soup - Punk rock 101     Geetha, Martini, Dingling, Liuming, Jess and I went to IKEA to have lunch at the restaurant and purchase stuff for the class after school today :P We talked heaps and cracked up until I choked on my food a coupla times.. Silly nuts! I love my friends.. I truly love their company. I can't believe how supportive my friends have been. Martini bought each of us fingers puppets cos the girls made him to! He also bought us those lil' red hearts with arms on his  own accord .   Still have history lessons tomorrow.. Woo! Hopefully it doesn't rain, so training can be held smoothly. Toodles kiddos! Peace out. xox.
     
    
</post>
<date>29,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
          New Found Glory - Eyesore    Fascinating. 1).  urlLink An Unsealed Room   2).  urlLink Baghdad Burning   3).  urlLink Gothamist   4).  urlLink The Agonist   5).  urlLink Put Down The Donut  
     
    
</post>
<date>24,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
          BBMak - Out of my heart    I love everything I do... But somehow I have gone nuts over  people  and things. I realise how funny I get myself into sometimes.  When I doubt something will happen... it will happen. If I want it to happen no matter how miraculously hard I try.. it never falls perfectly.   Mrs Chua makes a perfect class parent. Unfortunately, she's only our English teacher. If only... =)   On a deeper thought, all the time, I believe that there is always more to the physical. Don't you ever judge a book by its cover. Mrs Tan needs to learn to understand our class. She can't just go around pretending that she 'cares' for our class when all she does is brings us down with her critisisms and negative judgements.  So it is today that a smile kills me.    "Too often we under estimate the power of a touch, a smile, a kind word, a listening ear, an honest compliment, or the smallest act of caring, all of which have the potential to turn a life around."  -- Leo Buscaglia
     
    
</post>
<date>24,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
          Simple plan - Perfect    This is sucha depressing song, it just makes me all the more guilty and forlorn.   I went to school for NPCC training, which is unusual because today is the 3rd day of Chinese New Year. On the other hand, most people would know how committed I am to my CCA, so yupp, it definitely isn't a chore to go when I can interact with my little kids. (Haha, sir Faizal I stole your word :P) Honestly speaking, I love my sec 3s. At first I didn't think that way because I  thought  I would be unable to handle them. But I've made a promise to myself that I am going to do my best in training them to become outstanding NCOs in the near future. As the quote by George Soros goes, " Once we realize that imperfect understanding is the human condition, there is no shame in being wrong, only in failing to correct our mistakes. " No matter how many/few mistakes they've made in the past, as long as they are all willing to learn from them and not commit them again, I would already be satisfied.   I yearn for them to grow up and become good people in the future, serve the nation, be loyal to Singapore, never stop learning and give their best in whatever they do, because as much as I am giving out my 110% in disciplining them, I hope that they will give me their 110% as well.  Training ended not-very-nicely. The Sec 3s were planning to sing Junior Jolene a birthday song, yet I screwed it up by losing a Casio watch which I had borrowed from a Sec 1 cadet. I passed it to Hafiz who was in-charge of one of the stations cos he didn't have a timer, and he brought it to the toilet and left it there. Before we could find it, it was gone.. We combed the entire school thrice, reported to the general office too. No news. * Sighs * I feel  really  bad for losing the watch.. It costs S$60. =\ Val forked out $10 while I paid the kid $50. Also wrote a letter to his parents informing them that I will take full responsibility. Val is right though, money can't solve all problems. I just hope that someone finds the watch..  Somehow....  Somewhere...
     
    
</post>
<date>22,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
          Nickel creek - This side        You are Hhomi K. Bhabha! You're the most important post-colonialist alive. You taught at the University of Chicago for a while before you were finally hired up by Harvard. You actually only have one book, but it's a really important book, and everyone respects you tremendously. You are not dead.    urlLink   What 20th Century Theorist are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    
     
    
</post>
<date>22,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
          Oasis - Wonderwall       HAPPY BIRTHDAY NANOKO!   Heaps of hugs and kisses,  Yoshiko  :) 
     
    
</post>
<date>21,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
          The ataris - The saddest song    The photos of the CCA open house 2004 have been  urlLink uploaded . In addition, the Chinese New Year photos taken today are up at the class webby :) I adore the photo with Mr Lee, Miss Koh and Miss Halizah in it. Amelia's blog also has a link to her set of photos.
     
    
</post>
<date>18,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
          Jewel - Stand       4B1 ROCKS ME AND MY SOCKS!!!     Oh my goose! Today has been so incredibly enjoyable! We came in  2nd  at the Chinese New Year Singing competition! Honestly speaking, although we were rather disappointed that we did not come in 1st, we accepted the results quickly, because our competitors, Christine, Jiamin and Selina really kicked out butts! I ain't kidding, they were much better than us in terms of vocals.. but of course, our creativity is better than anyone else la.. multi-racial somemore! Teehee.. But nonetheless, everyone was in high spirits and on cloud nine! We have learnt so much about one another during the past weeks of consistent practice, and the fact that we have bonded in one way or another has been such an awesome and inspiring experience. I promise, I will never forget the times we've spent together, the fun times, and the not so fun times.  Weizheng ,  Jason hoongy ,  Ruth ,  Siti ,  Jessica  and  Geetha , YOU GUYS ROCK! A big thank you to our 'stage managers', Jiaxin and Wenxing as well.. Haha! Our supporters.. I love you guys!   What a way to start the new year! We also ate "Yu Sheng" and "Lao" with the chopsticks until there was veggie all over our bodies!! Ahahah! Jiax prepared it with her mom. Thanks babe! The guys were very high, threw the veggie everywhere.. Mdm Liu had veggie on her arms.. HAHA.  Mrs Rajah  also gave me a box of chocolates for CNY.. I think cos i got her chocs for X'mas :) while  Mr Lee  got me a box of tissue?! Teeehee, to clean my hands. A pity I wouldn't be able to go to his place to "bai nian" because I would be with my family for the next few days. We took pics together as well, I shall upload them asap!  Wenta' town with the chicks after school to take sticker prints and lunch.. YUMMY! Had jap food :D I'll be leaving for my granny's in a while. I love new years! Hope you guys collect heaps of "hong-bao"! To non-chinese peeps, have a great holiday!    Happy Chinese New Year everyone! Gong Xi Fa Cai!  :) 
     
    
</post>
<date>18,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
          Good charlotte - Boys and girls    New layout! Green. Green is excellent for the eyes.   Ma'am broke down yesterday during the debrief. It shocked me. Ncos - what an utter disappointment. We still have one final chance to prove ourselves. Are we worthy our positions? Yes? No? We will find out soon. Drastic changes to be made. Stay tuned.
     
    
</post>
<date>17,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
          Get up kids - One last kiss   Once we realize that imperfect understanding is the human condition, there is no shame in being wrong, only in failing to correct our mistakes.  --  George Soros 
     
    
</post>
<date>15,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
          The all american rejects - Happy ending   Ayes! Haha. My tummy muscles have been working way too much. Mrs Chua's lessons are so incredibly fun-filled.. every word she says cracks me up. In addition, Geetha and Martin are such corny jokers.. Ms Shelley Low's lessons are so interesting too. We're so blessed to have such teachers in CT. Brian embarassed me yesterday during Mr Lee's lesson. Aahh.. I knew this day would come! That nuthead, pinched him like don't know how many times after that. =P   I have been staying back til evening almost everyday to practice the Chinese New Year performance. I can't wait for the audition! Btw, I'm the Squad IC for Sec 3s. Congrats to Staff xiongster who's the NCO head! The first few weeks of school sure is hectic, I hope the next few would be a lil' more relaxed..    (: Yoshiko</post></Blog>