<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   1pmlaying in the tub of hot water, watching the water fill up. Feeling hot water surround me, relaxed my muscles, made blood pump thru my viens. Steam filled the room, the water turning my skin red. Borderline 1st degree burn. I felt nothing but perfect water temperature. The water level hit my chin and I scooted a wee bit down till the waters edge was surrounding my face. I was starting to tingle all over when I drifted out. I always take naps in baths.   Else Where.   Jake sits in an interview room in the local police station, he sits staring at the clock, its only 8:34am. And time is moving slow, almost backwards as he waits for more officers to come and ask him the same questions he has answered 3 times previous. He asked for coffee, they gave it to him, he asked why it is so important for him to be there, they kept him in the dark. Around 12:30pm they were ehgausted and found nothing out. Jake started to sweat, he said it was very important they let him go now, they wanted to know why. They demanded to know why. He tried to go without telling, so finally as time pressed on he explained his girlfriend was planning to take her life own life in the next hour. And he had to go and stop her. They finally let him go under the stipulent they would drive him to where he needs to be. He drove and they followed. He went to the local center and he ran to her room and she wasn't there. He was in panic, its now 1:30pm, he started yelling for me and in pure panic ran for the bathroom pulled the curtain in the showers then over towards the bath tubs and pulled those curtains. All are empty but the last, the horror of the sight he first saw. Blood and water every where, he was in sheer pain. He plunged into the hot water, he pulled her out sat me on the floor and took towels and tied them around her wrists.   Holding her, putting his head next to hers praying for a miracle, saying in another language "please, tell me I didn't fail!" Begging for a sign of life. He went with the ambulance to the hospital and the officers watched him close but had no reason to worry about him, he didn't do anything he just can't explain where he is from. They pretty much let him alone to deal with his new greif. He stayed by her side all the time. When she woke up and looked at him, she had no clue as to who he was. He put his hands on both sides of my face and started speaking in that bizare language. After a few words the language became clear and memories started to pour into her head. She was able to remember who she was, why she was there and also what had happened while she was there. Being in a place filled with so much hate and depression, over whelmed me and consumed me to feel the same.   

						
</post>
<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    The Shrink found it necessary to send me to a clinic for imediate help. Since I was a good 20lbs under weight he wanted me to make sure I was re conditioned. Since the center didn't see my progress for 6 full months of starvation and odd behaviour they are taking full credit for my illness and paying for it all. Also keeping it a great secret. Before they sent me, because they knew I was freaked out about being caught. They brought in a doctor who was a specialist at the clinic they want to send me to. To their luck, I had an instant attachment to the doctor. He was tall, rugged looking, completely attractive and gentle. I also felt as if I new him before. I was more plyable for the nurses and shrinks to run tests. They learned of all my bad habbits and used me as a teaching tool for the rest of the students. I was the first full out blown dangerous case they have ever seen.        Since they wanted to make an example out of me, against the request of the doctors the center put me back in with the masses then used me as a point in meeting. My lodge staff proved how evil she was, before dinner she had me stand up and she raised up my shirt to show off my stomache and rib cage. Everyone made a refferences and oooo and aweees . Several girls were just down right mean and violent towards me. The staff were laughing and it was just a big joke. I was currently very fragile. The students poked me and proded me and others tried to save me, but as everyone went to eat I went to my room, found me rogue razor and then went to make a phone call. I was given the phone number to the doctor at the clinic and at his home. I called his home, he hadn't yet gotten off work so I left a mesage on his answer machine. I said "You said they wouldn't know! you said they wouldn't make reffernce to it! You LIED to ME." Once I hung up I went upstairs and draw a bath. I made it supreme hot and I put on my pj's then sat in the tub water. once I was comfortable I slit both wrists nice and deep. The hot water was drawing out the blood faster than if I hung them out over the side. I did tho hang out one wrist over the side, I was pouring out blood like no ones business. I could hear nothing, and see nothing.        The doctor came home right after the message was left. He decided he would call everyone from his car phone. As he rushed over, he started yelling at the Center director of Residential livingfor the problem at hand. He was so angry, he knew what I meant he knew it, for he told them pasfically to do the opsitie. For I wasn't able to handle any more trauma on the subject. He called several others, Several staff members running to my aide, but its been a good 25 minutes since the point of contact. Staff ran to the bathroom upstairs and started yelling for me, demanding I answer, they went every where looked everywhere, and finally found me. In the far tub, blood all over the floor the water was dark red, the side of the tub red. They were in shock as to how fragile. The doctor, Jake Petersen. Was coming up the drive when the staff members were running with me to the center clinic. He went in they prepped my wounds for long term travel, he told them he was going to take me straight to the clinic anfter he yelled at them for a good amount of time.He tookme to their emergency care andgave me new blood to replentish my body.      I woke up in the hospital. Bright room around me and no one else around. I am in a gown and only wearing underwear underneath. I My wrists were bandaged up and it was freezing in the room. I got up and saw a another blanket in a locker near my bed. I went for it and caccooned myself in it. I slept for a few hours that way. Jake came into my room and saw my caccon and laughed he asked me what I was doing and I told him I was freezing. "Its 72 degrees here."   "yes, thats freezing. Up that temp to like 82 and I'll be comfortable."                

						
</post>
<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Time for death to knock, my body sore from trying so hard just to walk. Insane thoughts pouring into my head. Dreams turn to nightmares. Spending more time sleeping than awake. No one noticed or cared just as I thought they would. 3 months of the same behaviour and still I am free from spectators. Since my clothes are bulky, no one can tell esp during the winter months. Every few weeks going to the mall on center given trips for my necessities kept everyone aware of being alive, and that was good enough. After 4 months of my current situation. Since I was alone and care nothing for anything at this point I was starting to lose it. My weight now being 141lbs. A good 19 pounds under weight. While on the bus to my trip into the city I was rather weak and having trouble moving. I made it into the mall and wondered over to the Target on the far side of the building. I went in, sat at the Cafe and rested for about 3 minutes before finding a basket and going after my needs. I found some dorm food and shampoo conditioner, and other needed hygine products, I did also catch up on my supply of vitamins and sleeping pills and razor blades. Once I had a heavy basket a person started watching me in the store because I was leaning over and having a hard time standing, at first he thought i was trying to steal. The guy asked me if he could help me and I said "no thanks." I then lost my balance and landed on my butt and was unable to get back up with out my legs giving way. He then rushed to my aid and helped me get up. he said he would call an ambulance and I begged him not to, and he rang up my stuff at a register just for me and then took me over to the cafe and then bought me a slice of pizza. Another worker recognised me as a job corps student and I didn't finish the food but drank all the liquid. I wondered back to the bus and we left back to the center. The manager had tried to call but got a message so he left a vague message "I am Rian, a store manager at Target in Rushmore Mall I would like to discuss a student who passed out in my store today. " He then left his number and no one had gotten back at to his call till monday, and then nto till evening time. He was there and Mr. Bevil called back and the Manager Rian came to the phone and said "I witnessed a student of yours pass out in our store on Saturday, I wanted to know if she was ok,""can you tell me what she looked like" said bevil."Tall, blonde, with the dark eyes.""Sounds like Shauna, she is the only tall gal here. I wasn't under the impression anything was worng wtih her. Thank you, I will look into this matter a bit closer. .""Your welcome."During Lodge meeting I was sitting between two couches, on the floor hidden from all and barely functioning and the residential director came in and sat and watched the meeting, keeping a watch on me. He then told Marlus, our lodge staff to call me after to talk to him in her office. After the meeting I was getting up and she asked me to stay behind and talk to her for a minute. I did Bevil was in the office he asked me about my trip to Target. I said "What about it." My head down, and my focus stays on the floor, but not looking up. I am wearing a nice over sized sweat shirrt with the hoody up. He then asked me to sit and put the hood down. I did but kept looking down. My hair just normal stringy, and my skin tone pale white. He demanded I look at him. I looked at him the action of just raising my head caused me to get dizzy and start to call, he then caught me and he noticed he was just holding up bones. He asked me when the last time I ate was. I said "This morning" "He asked what did you eat?""Energy bar.""Thats not healthy"I became agnry and looked at him and he asked me "How much do you weigh?""I waight about 165lbs.""I doubt that." "Doubt what yee will." "I want you to go to the clinic, tomorrow.""Fine"He gave me a pass and that was the end of it. I went to the clinic before class and the nurse had a full room she asked me what was wrong with me and I said "I just need some bandaids." So she gave me a box and signed my pass to go to class. I was free from that trip. In the clinic was Patrick Cohain the center Shink he asked the nurse where I was. She told him and he left after me. He found me at the pavilion and I was resting. He said "Nice try."And he came over to talk to me. "Hi how are you doing?""Fine, thanks.""I want to talk to you.""Um, ok.""Tell me whats wrong.""If I don't tell you, then you can't fix it right?""right.""I then have nothing to say,"I tried to walk away but I wasn't able to get far due to being dizzy. He decided to walk me to the clinic. He had a hold of my arm and he had a tight grip and when we were in the clinic he let go and saw a bit of blood on his hands he asked me to raise my sleeve and i tried not refuse, but I reliezed i was not getting out of this tight spot. I did he saw my wounds. Mostly bandaged and a few infected. He asked me to bring up the other sleeve and it was the same only not scabbing over, more like close to being scarrs   

						
</post>
</Blog>