<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>28,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      hey hey hey everyone welcome to my blog thingy...anyways juss blog away cause right now im bored and i have to go juss talk bout whatever u want i gotta go....if u have anyone u want me to add juss give a hollar...well im outi...luv yalls lottzz
      
</post>
<date>27,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yo wassup. Jus testing this out to see if i can get this to work, I think this should work... if i am lucky... last time i tried this my internet failed right b4 i hit post... so lets pray that doesnt happen this time... 1...2...3... 
      
</post>
<date>27,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      hey look! i'm here!! yaaay!! but i cant update the layout :( cause the button's not up there.. i dont have the power!! ahh, oh well.. okay buh bye :) :) :)
      
</post>
<date>27,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      hey julie!

juss called to let you know i've joined!
this is such a bright blog!!

hey julie can i join the "monkey jumper" blog?

see ya !
*Surfer
      
</post>
<date>21,September,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      hey hey hey pple its me its me its lil juuulie...anyways this is another blog by me..of course, ashley and anna and hopefully i can get amanda to do it to...and also u betta still look on the othr blog  www.beachbumblog.blogspot.com cause its better than this..lol o well im leavin and this new blog better be cute ashley lol jp chiken...neways..g2g..luv ya lottzz
      
</post>
<date>31,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      well... as far as teaching him the "right way to treat a girl" thats kinda pointless cause when we are done with him there wont be enough left to teach... but yeah
      
</post>
<date>29,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      ok alicia is the beautiful talented girl, and nick is her former boyfriend, thank god, the prick. we all believe including Julie we should go to Clinton Louisiana and show him the right way to treat a girl, after beating the crap out of him and draggin him behind sam's big red van. taht's the story ttyl and ttfn
      
</post>
<date>29,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well its jus me... jus sayin hi an that we had an awsome time @ the MercyMe  Michael W. Smith concert... everyone shoulda come cause it was awsome... i even made 5 bucks for screamin out "YOU ROCK BABY" 2 the chick who was singin,  patrick dared me 2 an her gave me 5 bucks for it... so i was happy. But then on our way out rodgers got lost... u would think a 10th grader could remember where we parked............. but he was on the other side of the building and was compleatly lost...... we were gonna call him but nobody knew his cell # so we got 2 groups of peeps out lookin for him an we finally found him... i was thinkin he got mugged or somethin cool but he was just lost :-( well i gotta go... cause i can smell spaghettii... and its like one of my favorite foods an knowin my family they will start eatin w/o me and that would really suck cause if i dont get in there fast i wont get 3rds or 4ths... so luv ya'll an ttyl
      
</post>
<date>29,October,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      who in the heck are yall talkin about? and what the heck is a prick??

i'm helpless, blonde, and confused.

and that isnt a good combination. lol

cya
</post></Blog>