<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>09,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      It has been two days that I've been feeling down...I just don't know why. I feel so upset, I feel so unergetic, I feel so tired of everything...Why did I  missed that "Friends" comedy show, again?! onh.. I had class tonight from 6pm-8pm. Hmmm...I missed the one show that could have made me laugh:9 hmmmmm...Maybe everything will be okay tomorrow...  That's all for today, I guess...Better go to bed, now!
      
</post>
<date>07,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      My day started around 1 pm, today. Yeah...I finally got the chance to sleep in as I wanted a long time ago. I slept for 11 hours, and I still felt so sleepy. I guess cumulative lack of sleeps can't really catch up, after all:p Hmmm...Maybe I'll may have to sleep in for the entire day to recover all my energy. Or...I can go to the gym and get sweating. Nothing but some good sweat to help me feel more dynamic^^   So, YMCA, please bring out all your towels cause suensuen is ready to sweat!   :p Ewwwwwwwwwwww...
      
</post>
<date>06,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I never really experienced car driving during the winter time because people have told that the road are too dangerous and too slippery. I think this is perhaps the reason why my mother doesn't allow me to drive as much as during the summer. Well, I have been driving a lot lately, I don't  see any differences with my driving skills. Of course, driving more carfully and slowly helps, when driving on snow. But, what about the road vision? Cars are five times dirtier to compare with than the rest of the year...  I was driving with my dirty windows, today. I found out how dangerous it was to switch lanes because it was like impossible to glance at my dead spots without giving my full concentration to see right through the dirt on my windows. I think I should really consider getting my car washed tomorrow before heading on the road, again:p  What is it about washing cars during winter time? When the minute you drive on the street, the car will be dirty, again. Now, isn't it obvious? Driving with a clean car does not only means greater appearance, it also means to have better windows to see the roads.   Onnnnnnnnnnnhhh...This is like a win-win solution!!! ^^   hmmm...I just hope the car washing place will be open, tomorrow :p
      
</post>
<date>05,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      It has been months I have been trying to update my homepage...I can't believe how much time it takes to add something new and to modify something old. I worked on it the entire night, yesterday, and I haven't finished it, yet.:9 GEss...  Today, I went to work around 11h30am to 14:45pm, and came back home around 3h15pm. I am so exhausted and angry. I can't really believe that it has been two days in a row that I eat only once in a day. I have been starving and stuffing myself with one big meal...;p hmmm...What is the problem with myself?  School is starting tomorrow, again. Onhh! I feel so tired... I still can't believe I will have to start reading and studying again...Ishhhhhhhh!   I am so so tired...I think I better stay in bed for the rest of the evening ^o^ 
      
</post>
<date>17,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      It is so rare for me to be mad at someone. I don't know why I am so mad at this friend of mine, tonight! I hate it when someone denies the fact that he/she is wrong. Such...Stupid misunderstanding and arguments have ruined my day...So stupid that I don't want to write about it anymore!!!  So, I've finally tried this dessert called "La coupe dragon" or a name similar to it. It is a fried ice cream dessert!! Kinda interresting for a dessert! It is at the same time hot and cold! I tasted the green tea flavor! Soooo delicious!!!! :p
      
</post>
<date>13,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      It is already almost 1a.m...I shouldn't have watched that chinese soap on t.v a while ago. I should have started revising my English grammar and verb tense. My UWT (University Writing Test) is tomorrow, and I still feel unprepared!! What am I going to do?  Well...I just hope to pass it:( In the next half an hour, I will be going through all my past English essays. My English has gone so bad lately. Maybe, I should really consider reading more:p  Ishhhhhhhhhhhh...I have to work from 9:45am- 2pm tomorrow, and my UWT will be at 3pm. Then, after my exam, I will have to rush back home to get my car, and to go pick up some friends of mine around 6pm, so we can go to MIKASA sushi bar before 7h30pm (Apparently, I've made reservation at 7h30pm). hmmm... What a day I am going to have!!! &gt;  No wonder, most of my friends say that I am a very busy woman =^^=
      
</post>
<date>13,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      It has been days now, since the last time I wrote on this page. You know what happens when you feel down, right? Well...When I feel down, nothing really matters for me...I only cared for a good laugh, I fake one&gt;  Yeah... I can get kinda weird sometimes too, when I am upset. Wandering around alone, looking down, not speaking...   Some people told me that I hide my feelings very well, and some people have said the contrary, What do you think? hmmm:p Confusing isn't?  I went to school today...I had two classes :p Didn't really know what I learned today&gt;  Around 4h30pm, I went to the YMCA. It was so good to have sweat... I felt so great after exercising! I think It is a good ways to get away from follish ideas...  So... You want to know why I was sad for the past few days? hmmm...I think loneliness have finally got to me. I feel so alone, I think it is time to meet new people, a boyfriend can help! Maybe? What do you think? I kinda would have to stop rejecting people from now on. Perhaps, I should start think about giving a chance to...  Or is it only PMS??? You know that girls get mood swings the week before getting periods, do you?   Well...What can I say else? I am so tired...still (Tired of being single, or tired of life in general?) Can't really say...Let's see what happens tomorrow....
      
</post>
<date>23,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I went to school, today (Jan 22nd), as a attempt after my very ill day. It was almost like I was crawling to go to school by bus and metro today because I had such trouble breathing with my breath and lungs. I don't don't what happened to me, it is like I never exercised in my life. WHICH IS FALSE...Cause I am a very active person!!!   For the first time of my school life, I felt the need to be QUIET!! Yeah... Talking wasn't at my best, today! I am finally losing my voice!! &gt; Hmmm... Considering drinking more water, now!  So, after my last class (4pm), I decided, for some unknown reason, that I should stay at school to continue my readings that was due this week! Hmmm... I did finished parts of my readings, but my energy did suffered a bit! I already had some problems concentrating because of my headaches and my giggling stomach nausea. I still wonder why am I doing all this to torture myself.  Weird...very very weird!  I came home, took my shower...and I discovered that those nasty little zits are appearing again on my skin...Something resemble to rashes:(  Looks like I am dying...HELP!!!
      
</post>
<date>21,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      "gastroentérite"...So, that is what I had, yesterday night! &gt;  Yeah... Vomiting for at least 10 times made me feel so dizzy and painful. My body was so sored and hot.   hmmm....Maybe, I better sleep more...
      
</post>
<date>01,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I went to work today, late again&gt;   A worker call in sick today; she was so sick that she couldn't even move a muscle, I replaced her the whole day of work...YEahh!! I skipped my Chinese class for work!! haahaa! At least I am earning money!  Ever happened to wear high heels for more than 8 hours??? Well, that is what I had done, today! I wore heels the whole day!! Such a bad decision!  Waaaaah! I can't believe how much pain I am having right now!!! I really need some foot massage!  In the evening, I went to my friend Khammy's birthday, we ate at "Zen Ya", a classy Japanese restaurant on St-Catherine. The place was nice and romantic, I loved it especially because our waiter (David) was cute and charming!! he eheee Awwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwwww...I am dreaming, again!  Anyhow, I couldn't really flirt with him cause a friend of Khammy was already flirting with him!! hee hee... I will surely go again to see him....huh huh...To eat their delicious sushis, I meant ^o^ onh.. I heard that they have that tempura icecream, too!!! NIcE:p
      
</post>
<date>30,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I told myself each day that I will head home to read my books...It never happened:p Each time I start reading a third page, I fall asleep~ What is wrong with me??? &gt;  Hmmm...Sleeping in the library is not such a bad idea! Though, I have to admit that I sleep a lot to compare with my reading time! Wahhhhhhh! Maybe I should start drinking coffee again!  What is it with me and sleeping??? Hmmm...Maybe sleeping on an average of  6 hour a day is really not enough!  Okieeeeeeeeeee...Got to go ZZzzZZZzzz...
      
</post>
<date>28,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I think being part of a radio team is very hard, nowdays. Every time you do a show, you have to make sure that there are enough Djs in the room to host a show, and you have to find a topic that is talkable. Well... It doesn't sound that hard, when read these two tasks. Is it?  I really must say that people have to experience it to feel the pressure. I am hosting this radio show for about half a year, now! Our team is falling apart. I can really see it happening...  Today, Phillip called me to advise me that he won't be attending any show from now on, but he said that he will still show up a couples of time to be a guest on our show. Moreover, as if three in a team wasn't bad enough, Wendy called to tell me the same thing...Her resignation!!!   Well...I must understand that they ARE busy people and that being home around midnight on each Wednesday is hard, indeed. But, why didn't they thought so before joinging the CREW...I feel so outcast, right now! I am lacking evergy to lead...I really want to abandon everything! But, I CAN'T because I have my respect! My DIGNITY  Hmmmm... So, what is it about giving their resignation to me? Have I become the leader, somehow without knowing? YEahh... Since, the very beginning, everyone kept addressing me as if, I was the main person of the team, or may I say.. The leader of a group. What responsibilities does a leader really have, when other members fail to take on responsabilities?  Is there a way that I can find a responsible and respectful volunteer, who will want to dedicate an hour, and a half of their time each week for some radio broadcasting? HELppppppppppppppppppppppppp!!!
      
</post>
<date>27,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      So, what is a zit anyways? For weeks, this small zit located right above my nose and between my eyes don't want to go away!!! Argggggggh! What is that? I never had anything on my face since my puberty...Is this my second puberty? :p While I was taking my shower, I tried to get rid of it using my nails... haa haa... It did went away&gt;  YEah yeah yeahhhhhhh... Some of you reading this must be thinking that I am too paranoid, and that you didn't even see it, the last time you saw meh! &gt;</post></Blog>