<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>30,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      My head still hurts ::moan::   
    
</post>
<date>29,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      my head hurts
    
</post>
<date>24,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      It's my dad's birthday. Yummy German Chocolate cake for me tonight!!!! At dinner they told us that some of our friends at church invited us to go with them to visit their family in the Philippeans this summer...  Now if we could really go, would that not be INCREDIBLE?????????        I'm already excited, and I'm probably not even going.   Today I feel "unpretty"  Maggie told me I looked like MY DOG!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!  mean huh?  she didn't really mean it... it was funny oh and my mom took my cell phone away from me for the weekend so if you want to talk to me, you'll have to call the house
    
</post>
<date>23,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      We SO should not have been at school today!!!  EVERY other school was out...  Even Rockhurst.  and it was cold... (f***ing cold)  I had five shirts on, two pairs of tights, sweatpants, my skirt...  At least I was warm INSIDE!!!   oh well.
    
</post>
<date>21,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm exhausted... I was at church babysitting for my service hours.  Wow kids are a handful!!  One little boy started screaming every time I tried to put him down, It's nice to know I'm so loved, but other kids wanted me to pick them up too...  AHHHH!!!!!!!!!!  My right arm is numb...    My parents are seriously considering letting me transfer to O'Hara, I'm just so incredibly stressed out about school now...  But would I really transfer???  I doubt it.   
    
</post>
<date>20,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      MICHING MALLECHO... (it means mischief) -- says Hamlet to the fair Ophelia  Finally I have dirt on somebody.  I'm not going to tell you who becuase then I won't be able to use this dirt when and how I want.  (If I were capable of an evil laugh, i would... but it's just not like me!!) I'm depressed again today (NO ITS NOT BeCAUSE OF yOU, YOU PIG-HEADED...)   Today I like the Used again...  this time it "Bury Me alive" 
    
</post>
<date>20,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Where did I see this??? It's pathetic... You would slit my throat and with my one last gasping breath I would apologize for bleeding on your shirt. Is that lyrics to a song or something???  It's stuck in my head. I wrote this the other night... I don't know what's the matter with me...  Anymore it's all crap.  I've had a crappy day, I sit and stare at the girl in the mirror that is not me. I am 2 dimensional. I wonder what you see in her. I don't take off my make-up,  I'm too tired It doesn't matter anyway, I'll just look like a racoom in the morning.
    
</post>
<date>19,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH    BORED OUT OF MY MIND!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!   I really need to call some people for newspaper, but I really REALLY REALLY don't want to.  I hate newspaper, the only part I like is having my pictures in the paper.  Maybe I'll drop it next year and pick up some art classes so I really can get into Corcoran ( see link at  I found this spiffy Elven site today too.  I need to find somebody to teach it to me, I LOVED it in the movie. I'm sure I'll be back later... Oh what am I listening to right now?:::  korn...   fun stuff
    
</post>
<date>18,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      This was on some other guy's blog, its funny: "so he texted you want to have sex or watch LOTR later? how arrogant. he can go to his damn motels alone. and i've seen LOTR already. " lol, wow, but then you might not find it funny, I have the oddest sense of humor. I also find this funny... Doubt thou the stars are fire Doubt that the sun doth move doubt truth to be a liar but never doubt i love --hamlet 
    
</post>
<date>17,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Let's see, who am I in love with today???  Probably the Used.  They're going to be at the Warped Tour, I'm excited!!  Right now I'm listening to Relient K...  Becca made me listen to them last night, and now I'm dying for the cd.  I need to be friends with somebody who listens to good music and can burn these cd's for me, I've only got, like 20, and in this day and age that's very very sad.(Chantele, you're still working on Disturbed for me aren't you?  You can borrow SR-71 if you do lol) Oh and while I'm thinking about it, what do you guys think of the Vines' version of Ms. Jackson??  I laughed the first time I heard it, hated it the second time, and its been growing on me ever since. Today I pinned my hair up, it looked incredibly cool, rather like Padme's in Ep. 2 when its all loopy, ya' know? But now I have a headache from having those pins stuck into my scalp all day. lol, yeah you GUYS, you just don't understand.  It hurts like hell. And apparently, there have been rumors going around about me being suicidal?  Well, I'm not.  I'm about as close as you can get without actually being suicidal, and making a comeback, so don't worry about me, I'm fine really!!!! We discovered today that I'm a little on the stubborn prideful side... basically, once I've done something... I've not going back on it, even when I do regret it... poor me. Oh and last night I decided that Marshmallow Fluff is supposed to be refrigerated, just so you know. (lol) PS...  you guys might call me tonight, make sure I haven't passed out, I rather feel like it just now
    
</post>
<date>17,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I knew you guys shouldn't have let me sit at home by myself tonight.  I've been reading Margret Atwood. My favorite quotes from books come from her, and I'm really bored (aren't I always??  I say that every night)  so I'm going to type them all out so I have them all in one place. --" 'It's absolutely no use saying you should stop loving someone.  It doesn't work like that!'     'Well you should if you know its bad for you,' said Charis.    'Bad for you had nothing to do with it,' said Roz.   'I like hamburgers,' said Charis, 'but I don't eat them.'    'Hamburgers are not an emotion,' said Roz.    'Yes they are,' said Charis.                                             --Robber Bride  (that one's my favorite)  "On that day, blood ran like water, so afterwards it must have been very clean."                                                       --the Blind Assasin  "I am a fool to confuse this with goodness. I am not good.  I know too much to be good.  I know myself. I know myself to be vengeful, greedy, secretive, and sly.                                       --Cat's Eye  "I think about becoming invisible.  I think about eating the deadly nightshade berries from the bushes beside the path.  I think about drinking the Javex out of the skull and cross bones bottle in the laundry room, about jumping off the bridge, smashing down there like a pumkin, half of an eye, half of a grin.  I would come apart like that, I would be dead, like the dead people. I don't want to do these things, I'm afraid of them.  BUt I think about her telling me to do them, not in her scornful voice, in her kind one.  I hear her kind voice inside my head.   Do it. Come on.  I would be doing these things to please her."                                -- Cat's Eye       
    
</post>
<date>16,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      AHHH, I'm bored out of my mind.  Today I'm in love with All American Rejects..  If you didn't notice earlier...lol.  There's a song, on their website, Don't Leave Me, I love it.  And I'm just listening to this song by spoon???  its interesting
    
</post>
<date>14,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      yes I'm back again.. I feel like ranting, the snow is melting.  Last night was the last straw, but now I'm left with an empty cup. Nothing is ever what it seems, and once again, I've brought this on myself, and for me there is no going back, Will you catch up?  The tears will not fall, but the pain will go away.  I sit and laugh, because I have been here before and will be here again. Its okay, I'll live, I always do, its my sense of humor that saves me.  Sarcastic as it may be, and as much as you may hate it, It has saved me, I would have gone long ago if not for it, my trusty shield, you never got as close as you could have, it saved me.  It ruined me. hm, rather abstract tonight, huh?   
    
</post>
<date>14,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!   All American Rejects comes out Feb. 4th, Don't let me forget!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!
    
</post>
<date>14,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      The snow is GORGEOUS!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!   I've already gone out and shot 2 rolls of film this morning.  I love my Baby. (NO CHANTELE, YOU WERE NOT THE FIRST PERSON TO NAME IT THAT!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!)  yeah, um back to the snow...  Its weird how Bobby has picked up my snow day habits.  Snow days are the only no school days that you don't sleep in.  We get up, put on  a ton of clothes and go out into the woods and look for animal tracks.  We always walk single file, to mess up less snow.  The only reason Bobby does it is because he knows I would SMACK him if he didn't. (hee hee)  Oh and I wrote this last night too: The girl is beautiful her pale silouette outlined against the dark hair  spread across her pillow Glowing in the light reflected off the snow outside her window she is beautiful and so am I  Its pretty crappy, but I thought you'd like it (yes you Chantele)
    
</post>
<date>14,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Today we had fun.  I threw a banana at Chantele, and we discovered my lightning fast reflexes.  Chantele and I also decided that we were going to take over the world like Alexander the Great... It will most likely entail having affairs with world politicians and then poisoning them at breakfast. Poor Sama lost her voice and had to call us really REALLY bad names to get us to pay attention to her.  I would also like to take this opportunity to point out the fact that I am MADLY in love with Joel from gc, and Deryk (?) from Sum 41.  MADLy i tell you.  Well I suppose I'm done for now.  I'm horridly tired and bored, I need to get out of this house!!!!!!!!!!!
    
</post>
<date>13,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Its really weird how everyone feels so overprotective of me, I mean, my parents...  Need I say more???  And I found out today that Chantele's been threatening people with the "If you ever hurt her..."  Some of my friends won't even hug me because they think their gonna "break" me. I hear the "DOn't do anything I would do" thing all the time too.  WHy is it that everyone I know is so bad that they have to warn me that whatever it is their doing is wrong?  Io it bugs me.  I like a certain amount of protectiveness from my guys, its cute, but I get tired of it after awhile.  Oh and what's up with this nickname for Rachel thing? I have a gazillion different names.  Rachella... rather reminicent of Cinderella.  Popo...  not quite so much of a "poet pope" any more...  My papal visions have gone Kaput.  Um..  Baby- Reminds me too much of that wonderful performance of mine in the Fall play, and besides, that's my camera's name.  Poke...  no I don't like it when people touch w/o some kind of prior warning, but its neccessary to remind everyone of this new kind of entertainment... "Watch Rachel Cringe"????  BE A JEAN!  (that was for Chantilly)  Let's see... what else?  SHeep...  baaaa?  NO. RaeRae...  doesn't bother me so much, I'll answer to it but I didn't win state in soccar last year!!! The list is endless..  poor me.
    
</post>
<date>11,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Funny thing, life is.  You know, its really cool to think about the millions/thousands of people you meet/see/walk past in your lifetime that all have this unseen force in them that gives them the ability to walk/think/gain intelligence etc.  I was babysitting this little two year old boy last night and he fell asleep on my shoulder, it was so cute, I love the feeling of having a sleeping child in my arms. I wonder if I'll ever end up having my own kids, creating life...  hmmm...
    
</post>
<date>06,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I wonder what's the matter with me?   I've been the BIGGEST bitch lately, and I'm not really like that.  I want to lay down and die.  If it were that easy, I probably would too!!  Too bad I'd never really be able to do it. Oh well. While I'm thinking about it, someone needs to come up with a name for me...   Some guy came up to me the other night and called me Xyloa...  I'm afraid to find out what that means, in elvish, or whatever it is. But then its not like I ever actually play D, I just hear Chantele's stories, and Kevin really wanted me to play with him at one time, except I don't think he does that kind of stuff anymore, now that he's converted to Daoism. Poor me. I'm so bored...   
    
</post>
<date>05,January,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      UHG!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!  I have to go to school in the morning, I think I'll cry.  I felt like crying this morning when I woke up. (Of course I didn't.  I need to stop that, someday, I think I'll die from withheld tears or something)  I get like that sometimes, its weird.  My mom thinks its hormones, but I really don't think so, I know what hormones feels like.  I'm just moody. (wow, I picked a good name for this, I'm already ranting.) I HATE confirmation class.  I hate every single person in the class except for Kristy, Jessica, and Rachel (no not me, I'm not quite THAT pigheaded)  You should have seen Larry, I wanted to kill him...  No wait, I take that back, I shouldn't be that mean.  He REALLY REALLY REALLY pissed me off, just by being alive.  Can't you tell I'm in a horrid mood tonight? I WANT IT TO RAIN!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!  It started sprinkling yesterday and got me all excited, and the clouds were really cool, and it SMELLED like rain, I could even SEE it raining in the distance, but what did I get?  Disappointment. Ok, Chantele needs a name for her mag, what'll it be?  huh?  huh?  Didn't think so. 
    
</post>
<date>28,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I've had a really good past couple days.  Wednesday I found out I'm going to be photo editor of the newspaper next year.  That means I'll get to spend all my time taking pictures, and will have to write very few, if any, stories for the paper.  Even though Mr. Thomas said  that considering my past couple stories, I'm a completely different writer than I was at the beginning of the year (that's a really good thing, I sucked so bad at the beginning of the year)  and since the juniors and seniors have been gone all week, I've been the only person in my newspaper classes, so Mr.Thomas has been talking to me about photography...  He's sort of taken me on as his "apprentice"  and he was showing me different techniques and stuff.  It was fun.  So yeah there's that, and its snowed the past couple days, which makes me happy, and Andrew and I actually had a civil conversation yesterday!!!  Oh, and I haven't had any homework all week, so that's a TON of stuff I don't have to worry about this week, although I should probably go do some of the Latin due on Monday...  Nah.  I'm such a slacker.  Speaking of Latin, the JCL test is in a couple weeks, its a standardized international Latin test.  Last year I did really well on it..  Magna cum Laude or something... I got a silver medal... Only Kate did better, but that doesn't really bother me.... I'm NEVER going to do better than Kate, freaking GENIUS!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!  Ok well, who knows what I'm doing tonight, I may be around, I may not, but if you call and I don't answer, leave me a message... I'll probably either be talking to Chantele on the phone, or at a rave and can't hear my phone... lol, jk...  I'm not going to a Rave... yes Kevin I'm sure.  I'm NOT GOING TO GET MYSELF HIGH!!!  nor have I ever done such a thing!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!  
    
</post>
<date>25,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hee hee, my music favorites files full...  I'm  gonna have to start sub dividing my bands... how sad. Interesting stuff tonight.  I'm so tired, I think I'm going to bed.
    
</post>
<date>22,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      oh and go listen to Gershwin's rhapsody in blue...  that's the mood I'm in right now
    
</post>
<date>21,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Its okay, I'll live, I always do. :~)   We went to the dedication of the cathedral today, and I saw a ton of people that I know.  It feels really good to walk through a church that big, and get stopped every couple of seconds by people I know.  A friend of my mom's hadn't seen me in around four years, and he didn't even really recognize me, he just looked at me, and I smiled and waved at him.  He came over and was like, You're... You're...  so I told him who I was and he like freaked out.  He was like wow...  you're a lot older now, you've gotten to be absolutely gorgeous.  I hate it when people tell me that...  I know its not true, but sometimes its still nice to hear that someone really thinks so.
    
</post>
<date>21,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      UGH!!! my parents... I think my dad is having a midlife crisis, and my mom's starting menopause... oh god!
    
</post>
<date>19,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      let's see... tomorrow night is the charity volleyball game at Rockhurst...  let me take this opportunity to say that the Rock is going to be ground into dust, they just can't take the heat of the stars...  but then Friday we're playing sion, and THAT storm is DEFINATELY going to blow  over.  and I think we're doing something with Ish too.  I think Chantele's going to spend the night, and then Saturday morning is the rededication of the Cathedral...  which I got tickets to because of our leadership role in the youth world of the Diocese  (yeah I know, where the hell did they come up with my name?)   Saturday night is the battle of the bands at Rockhurst, which is going to be great... and something must be happening sunday.. hmmm I'm listening to Relient K, and Home Grown...    oh and that one song...  Make up your mind....   who sings that???????
    
</post>
<date>18,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      look what maggie wrote: . hate. you.  i hate you like halogen lights  i hate you like wet socks  i hate you like no sleep nights  i hate you like "we need to talk"s  you disgust me.  i hate you like jealousy  i hate you like boys  i hate you so violently  i hate you; i have no choice  i. hate. you. trust me.   and then i would add: and yet, for some reason, I still love you. 
    
</post>
<date>17,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I was over at sama's house last night, working on our history project, which is a comparison of indian and american weddings, and i found this poem: "Give me a kiss, and to that kiss a score; Then to that twenty, add a hundred more: A thousand to that hundred: so kiss on, To make that thousand up a million. Treble that million, and when that is done, Let's kiss afresh, as when we first begun." -Robert Herrick Its really funny, and those of you that need to know why its funny, know
    
</post>
<date>15,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      wayway  WAY too much sugar yesterday... but we had fun last night. Mary and I drove around for a couple hours after school, we went to her house, and then Sid's house.  Maggie, Lauren and Elise came by.  We went to Winstead's and watched Lauren be mean to her date, and then we went and saw How to lose a guy in 10 days.  There were a whole bunch of drunk freshmen in the row in front of us and we made fun of them.  I missed the last 15 min of the movie though because Chantele had to leave at 9:40 and couldn't go by herself... Her parents think she's going to get mobbed
    
</post>
<date>13,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Supposedly I'm cute today..  what ever am I going to do with you people?????????   Right now I'm listening to Green Day...  At the Library...  I'm in love.  I talked to Cindy for like an hour last night about stuff, I feel better now.
    
</post>
<date>09,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm so tired of doing this...   what's this you ask?  well, since no one really reads this, I could tell you, but then with my luck, someone, like just the person I don't want reading this particular thing, would come and read it..  haa haa. funny isn't it, that's how my life works. I was talking to Cindy today, and she said Mary Mueller wants Chantele and I to go to the rededication of the Cathedral, and representatives of Youth Leadership in the Diocese...  Wow, Youth Leadership in the diocese, and MY name comes up??  ha ha, I like that.  Of course we're going, and we're both really excited. the Father/Daughter Dance is tonight at Union Station.  Its more like a costume ball than anything else I've ever been to.  My dad and I are going as Woody and Little Bo Peep, from Toy Story.  I'm gonna be stuck all night with people telling me how incredibly cute I am. Speaking of people calling me cute, I need to explain about my problem with this.   I get called cute ALL THE TIME, and quite frankly, am VERY sick of it.  Even at HYU, I LOSE MY VOICE, and its ADORABLE!!!  At church Its all I hear too, I f you must say something, tell me I'm unbelievably gorgeous, Please.
    
</post>
<date>06,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Fav. Verse from a song: Mama and Daddy's got the best cocaine Riddellin's (sp?) never gonna be the same 24 hours on an empty brain I've got my finger on the trigger and you're in my way                         --Sugarcult, Bouncing off the Walls  --- band newly discovered by me today::  Erase the Grey...  read the lyrics to Rain, they amuse me. also still intrigued by the title of Audiovent's last album:: "Dirty Sexy Knights in Paris"  yummy
    
</post>
<date>03,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      i've decided no one reads this anyway so I can write whatever the hell I want...  but now I can't think of anything evil to say... oh well
    
</post>
<date>02,February,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      HAPPY BIRTHDAY KATE!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! We had fun.  We went to Town Center and I bought Kate a shirt that said spin my driedel (lol)  and I bought me a new ring, and got yelled at for wearing it upside down...  long story...  don't ask.  Then we went bowling and scored like a 57 or something.  My name also changed several times through out the night  i started out rae rae, but then I was Poke (seriously, this 'let's watch Rachel cringe and laugh at her hysterically' thing is REALLY not funny.)  and then later it something else, and then VVVVVVVVVVVVV m...  again, don't ask.  Sama was having control issues with the computer, hah a We went back to Kate's house after that and watched 10 things I hate about you (one of my favorite movies, aaaaahhhh  Heath Ledger...  HOTTIE!!) and a Walk to Remember, and guess what, a TEAR ACTUALLY ROLLED DOWN MY CHEEK!!!  what is that, the first time since HYU? and I'm not even gonna go into what happened this morning,   I don't even really know, i just woke up with Chantele sitting on me, grinning evily, holding my cell phone...   I think she was harrassing Andrew...  UGH!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! 
    
</post>
<date>27,March,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      today was weird, We had our NHS induction assembly, which made me feel lazy and worthless, but after that I had fun.  I felt loved today. except for Chantele I swear to god some day i'm going to beat the crap out of her.  But yeah, London ditched school and came back and told us all about it...  stupid girl.  In newspaper, Katy took my second story so I have less work to do now... I've got all kinds of pictures to take, but that's a good thing.  Then I was talking to Britanny, she's going to be editor of the Dart next year.  She was talking to me, and then all of a sudden she goes, "Oh my god, you are SO gorgeous.  I can't believe you don't have like 5 boyfriends."  I was rather shocked to hear her say this, partially because SHE'S the one who's gorgeous, and people don't normally tell me I'm gorgeous.  I'm alway cute.  But that's only one of the reasons I hate it when people call me that. People always tell me my hair is really pretty, but I'm never pretty. but that's only one of the reasons I want to chop it off.  hmmm... While on the subject of my appearance, I would like to talk about how everone thinks I'm anerexically skinny.  Its funny really.  My mom tells me I'm fat all the time, and yells at me if I eat more than she thinks I should... I really don't eat that much anyway... but I guess she thinks so.  But then If I should decide to skip a meal, THEN she drags my dad into and they practially shove food down my throat.  Its so weird.  Should you ask Chantele, she would tell you that I'm really normal sized and that I fake being skinny...  She will..  and seriously mean it too..  ugh  When I'm really skipping meals though, nobody notices... I probably shouldn't say this, but then wait, no one reads this anyway so it doesn't matter...  I can go for weeks without eating virtually anything, and no one will notice... But then I start eating again for a while... It all depends on the mood I'm in.  Oh well.
    
</post>
<date>25,March,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      another day gone by...  It's weird some times to observe time passing...  relativity, what and interesting concept... you know its true, the barriers of time are only in your mind.  What would you do if you were some where with no clocks, and you couldn't see the sun to see the day pass by...  what would it be like?  Hmmm??? Would you know several hours had passed when you were hungry again?  or would you never be hungry because to you, no time had passed what so ever?  I wonder how long the next six years are going to seem, if I live to see the next six years that is.
    
</post>
<date>24,March,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      ... wow, its been a while hasn't it???   hmmm... there's lots of stuff i feasibly CoULd tell you, but probably shouldn't, since its NONE of your business...  Spring break just got over, I'm already hating school again.  The break was quite interesting... I went to TEC, and met some really cool people, and got a chance to recenter my self, In most ways anyway... I got WAY off in other ways.  Monday I was in the most bizarre mood and said things I shouldn't have.  Tuesday night Chantele came over and I talked to Andrew some... Wednesday and Thursday were mostly uneventful, Friday night I talked to Andrew for five hours on the phone... i was happy after that, Saturday was a good day until my parents ruined it, and Sunday I was at church half the day, then I realized that i was going to have to go back to school today and did a little freaking out, and then I talked to Andrew some more...   So yeah that's my break... and then today???  I HATE Ms. Rowland (latin teacher)  I don't know anyone else in the WORLD that could make me feel so STUPID!!!!!!!!!  oh well.  CALL ME I'M BOReD&gt;&gt;&gt;  luv y'all
    
</post>
<date>30,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Goodbye, he said to the flower. But she made no answer. Goodbye, he said again. The flower coughed.  But it was not because she had a cold. I have been silly, she said to him at last, I ask your forgiveness.  Try to be happy He was surprised by this absence of reproached.  He stood there all bewildered, the glass globe held arrested in mid air.  He did not understand this quiet sweetness. Of course I love you the flower said to him. It is my fault that you have not known it all the while. That is of no importance.  But you- you have been just as foolish as I.  Try to be happy Let the glass globe be.  I dont want it any more. But the wind - My cold is not so bad as all that The cool night air will do me good.  I am a flower. But the animals- Well I must endure the presence of two or three caterpillars if I wish to become acquainted with the butterflies.  It seems to me that they are very beautiful.  And if not the butterflies- and the caterpillars- who will call upon me?  You will be far awayAs for the large animals- I am not at all afraid of them.  I have my claws. And, naively, she showed her four thorns.  Then she added: Dont linger like this.  You have decided to go away.  Now go! For she did not want him to see her crying.  She was such a proud flower. -The Little Prince Antoine de Saint Exupery 
    
</post>
<date>28,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      DAMN IT Let's see... what shall I pretend today?
    
</post>
<date>17,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Don't think I don't see... These opaque eyes of mine see everything EVERYTHING Don't think I don't know I was never as nieve as you thought I was I see I know  EVERYTHING
    
</post>
<date>17,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      the irises are blooming the irises of my eyes blooming like the blood on the white sheets blooming like the bodies buried, hidden coming up roses here's the knife let me carve out the part that hurts lay it on the altar an offering
    
</post>
<date>15,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I love this weather, I thrive on tank tops, shorts, and playing in the rain...  Of course I love the snow and all, but the rain's so much better.  I love going out and getting soaked to the skin, feeling the drops hit my face... and I love the sound of thunder. It sends chills down my spine every time I hear it.  mmm...  Just thinking about it makes me smile.  Supposedly I haven't been able to stop smiling all day.  I had Latin first thing this morning, and London was singing at the top of her lungs...  Oh it was the funniest thing ever, I laughed so hard I had tears streaming down my face. (Note:  London could NOT sing if her life depended on it, it was more like screeching, but I think she was doing that on purpose.)  What else happened today...  I finished my newspaper story, so I don't have to worry about that any more, and Mr. Thomas said it was a good story, which made me feel better because, I thought it was crap... Supposedly I'm overly critical of myself, because I hate most of the pictures I take, I hate everything I write, everything I do is always screwed up, but people are like... Rachel, this is incredible, what's your problem?  oh well... maybe that's a good thing though, because then I try harder... maybe.  hmm... It just occured to me that I haven't written in a couple of weeks, in which a lot of things have happened, but the only person who now even knows where this is (that'd be you Andrew)  knows all that stuff, so I don't need to worry about it anyway.  :-)
    
</post>
<date>30,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, let me put it this way, I'm listening to Konstantine, on purpose.
    
</post>
<date>26,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      ::sigh::
    
</post>
<date>23,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      what a pretty rain.  It used  to make me happy...  now it...now it... i don't know how to explain it to you... its like... I know it used to make me happy, and now it pelts every mistake into my soul...  and that's still not quite it.  the thunder still gives me goosebumps though..    I'm in an off mood right now.  I'm tired of being me again...  but that's nothing new.  it doesn't matter anymore anyway.  I want to go home, curl up in my bed, and never do anything ever again.
    
</post>
<date>21,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      silence ringing monotony a metal rod driven through my head. It cannot  touch me it is not solid  not a true quantity It cannot  touch me it cannot make me cry you are solid but still not a true quantity you can  touch me you can  make me cry  
    
</post>
<date>10,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Shelley sent me these lyrics.  I found that rather amusing... This will NOT happen. John Mayer - 3x5 lyrics I'm writing you to catch you up on places I've been You held this letter probably got excited, but there's nothing else inside it  didn't have a camera by my side this time hopping I would see the world with both my eyes maybe I will tell you all about it when I'm in the mood to lose my way with words  Today skies are painted colors of a cowboy's cliche' And strange how clouds that look like mountains in the sky are next to mountains anyway  Didn't have a camera by my side this time Hoping I would see the world with both my eyes Maybe I will tell you all about it when I'm in the mood to lose my way but let me say  You should have seen that sunrise with your own eyes it brought me back to life You'll be with me next time I go outside just no more 3x5's  Guess you had to be there Guess you had to be with me  Today I finally overcame tryin' to fit the world inside a picture frame Maybe I will tell you all about it when I'm in the mood to lose my way but let me say  You should have seen that sunrise with your own eyes it brought me back to life You'll be with me next time I go outside just no more 3x5's no more 3x5's  
    
</post>
<date>09,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      so I fixed the quotes....   wow.  Really, I am just not capable of typing a whole word without screwing it up.   Seriously, I've backspaced about a hundred times already just typing this.  I think I'm getting sick too.  One of the guys from the St. Louis office called this morning, and when I answered the phone he said I sounded like I had been into some bad whiskey this weekend.  I told him not to tell my dad.  It was kind of funny.  I seriously can not wait till next week.  I need out of the house SO INCREDIBLY BAD.  I can go to HYU  have fun with people who don't need to know anything about me, and forget about my real life.  The thought is horribly pleasing.  If only I knew it was going to be the same as last year though,  that was fun.  Oh well, we'll see.
    
</post>
<date>08,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      ugh.  I got my grade card and summer reading list today.  ugh.  I somehow managed to pull off a 3.4  ::sigh::    It's not like there was ANYTHING I could do about my morality grade.  Everyone knows that's ridiculous.   Oh well.  
    
</post>
<date>06,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      So I've been reading Margaret Atwood again...  It's almost like listening to Konstantine.   Anyway, I've got to keep these quotes somewhere...  otherwise I'll forget them. "I'm stuck on that wretched term paper.  Once I went to the zoo and there was a cage with a frenzied armadillo in it going around in figure-eights, just around and around the same path.  I can still remember the funny metallic sound its feet made on the bottom of the cage.   They say all caged animals get that way when they're caged, it's a form of psychosis, and even if you set the animals free after they go like that they'll just run around in the same pattern.  You read and read the material and after you've read the twentieth article you can't make any sense out of it any more, and then you start thinking about the number of books that are published in any given year in any given moth, and in any given week and that's just too much. Words,' he said, looking in my direction finally, but with his eyes strangely unfoucused, as though he was really looking at a poin several inches beneath my skin, "are beginning to lose their meanings.'                                                        -The Edible Woman  And this is the one I'm reading now, this is how it starts: "I don't know how I should live.  I don't know how anyone should live.  All I know is how I do live.  I live like a  peeled snail.  And that's no way to make money. I want that shell back, it took me long enought to make.  You've got it with you, wherever you are.  You were good at removing.  I want a shell like a sequined dress, made of silver nickels and dimes and dollars overlappin like the scales of an armadillo.  Armored dildo.  Impermeable; like a French raincoat. I wish I didn't have to think about you.  You wanted to impress me; well I'm not impressed, I'm disgusted.  That was a disgusting thing to do, childish and stupid.  A tantrum, smashing a doll, but what you smashed was your own head, your own  body.  You wanted to make damn good and sure I'd never be able to turn over in bed again with out feeling that body beside me, not there, but tangible, like a leg that's been cut off.  Gone but the place still hurts.  You wanted me to cry, mourn, sit in a rocker with a black-edged handkerchief, bleeding from the eyes.  But I'm not crying, I'm angry.   I'm so angry I could kill you.  If you hadn't already done that for yourself."                                                                      -Life before Man.  I wish I could write like Margaret Atwood.  I love reading her books.  They are examples of books that are not junk. ... that I can actually lose my self in.   I can be depressed because of the book, instead of being depressed because of my life.  That's a good thing.  Samantha was talking about how "fiberous" I am.  She said everything I do has something to do with paper.  I love paper, I love the way it feels.  Its very personal.  That's why I write letters to people so much.  I don't know anyone else who does that.  I just sit there and think...  I should write to so and so... and so I do.  They mean more effort than just calling somebody up, you have to spend 37 cents for a stamp and actually put it in the mail.  Taking the effort means its important to you.  I wish people would realize that.      I really have been sick of myself lately.    I wonder what's the matter with me.   Well, I know what's the matter with me... But I should have figured that out by now... It's the same old...."I'll be fine."  "I'll be fine."  I keep telling myself that... Maybe eventually I'll believe it,  maybe eventually I will be fine...  Maybe I'll be better than fine.  Maybe I'll be happy.   Those words echo over and over again in my head...  Maybe... eventually... Someday...    and I think, "ugh." 
    
</post>
<date>02,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      ::drum roll please:: AND THE RESULTS ARE:   I didn't do nearly as bad as I said/thought I was going to.  C's stand for "special Commendation"  and A's stand for "Needs Attention"  therefore, c's are better than a's.  I had 34 C's, with things like "Wow!" and "Beautiful" and "YES!" written after them, and I knew I was going to get those 3  A's, I was so nervous, my left hand was a quarter of a beat ahead of my right hand (UHG!)  and I really screwed up my scales (as usual.)  So yes Bobby did better than I did, He got 34 C's and no A's... so its not really THAT much better, and he had easy peasy songs. but still, its the principal of the thing.  oh well  ::sigh::  I've been doing a lot of "oh well-ing" and sigh-ing lately... does that tell you anything about the kind of mood I'm in?  ::sigh::  :-)   My parents are coming home tonight so I should probably go get some work done.  ::sigh::
    
</post>
<date>02,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      mmm.. I like this one better anyway So, we all knew I was going to do this.  Today is the day of my competition and I can't remember a note of either of the songs I'm supposed to play.  I can't even play my scales.  I am so incredibly nervous.  I knew I was going to screw it up.  Oh well.  and then I have to go and have lessons with my teacher right after that.  but then we don't get our results till next week, so she won't be able to yell at me for how horrible I did until then.  Bobby'll go and do incredibly well, and I will have SUCKED!!!!!  oh well.  This was supposed to keep my mind off of other things I didn't want to think about but now I don't want to think about this either.  I really need to figure out how to stop thinking all together.  That would be so much easier, no emotions, no intelligence, I envy those   people who are vegetables.   I think I would enjoy that blissful oblivion.  No such luck though I guess.  I've got to go though... guess why... Bobby wants to use the computer  (which makes sense, I stole it from him in the first place, but hey, it used to be my computer.)
    
</post>
<date>30,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Eeeeevvverrrrrrrryyyyyyy boooooooooooodddddddddddyyyyy eeeeeeeelllllllllllsssssseeeeee  wwwwaaaaasssssss dddddoooooiiiiiiiinnnnnnggggg iiiittt. {what a horrid excuse for bor-ed-dom}  1) WHAT COLOR ARE YOUR KITCHEN PLATES? ivory w/ pretty lil'green leaves on them 2). WHAT BOOK ARE YOU READING NOW? ummm... I still haven't finished Eleanor of Aquitaine...  but I'm almost done, and its really good, I just don't have time to read, because people keep calling me &gt;:-) {just kidding I love talking to you} 3.WHAT'S ON YOUR MOUSE PAD?  "Welcome to STAR COUNTRY... St.Teresa's Academy College prep for Young Women Since 1866 lol....  wow. 4) FAVORITE BOARD GAME? does twister count? its more of a mat game... 6.) FAVORITE SMELLS? coconut verbena...  and anything that kills brain cells...{I"M JUST KIDDING!!!!} 7) LEAST FAVORITE SMELLS? cigarette smoke {yukky}  nursing homes. 8) WHAT IS THE FIRST THING YOU THINK OF WHEN YOU WAKE UP IN THE MORNING? ... happy thoughts...  I usually roll over, and watch the sunrise and think how pretty it is... before i groan, and curse at the ungodly hours of the morning {anything before eleven} 9) FAVORITE COLORS? Green, and that weird, off color of blue... my eyes are that color sometimes, its kinda cool. 10) LEAST FAVORITE COLOR(S) I inherited my mother's red-ophobia... except for the fact that my homecoming dress is red... 11) HOW MANY RINGS BEFORE YOU ANSWER THE PHONE?  it depends on who it is... if I want to keep them waiting, I'll let it ring four times and hit it right before the answering machine picks up... or if its my cell, I rarely answer, and always have to call people back. 12) FUTURE CHILD'S NAME? girl: Saloriana, boy: Calvin 13) WHAT IS MOST IMPORTANT IN LIFE? wait, life is important?  imagine that!... um... God I suppose...  well I know... 14) CHOCOLATE OR VANILLA? swirl, just because I like being different 15) DO YOU LIKE TO DRIVE FASTno I'm a good lil driver. 16) DO YOU SLEEP WITH A STUFFED ANIMAL? my lil' teddy bear!!  no, not really  17) DO YOU LIKE STORMS? there very little else which I love more.  19) IF YOU COULD MEET ONE PERSON DEAD OR ALIVE WHO WOULD IT BE? Kate Spade?  Mommy Schilling? um...  Michel Angelo, i suppose, though he was probably horribly mysoginistic (sp?) 20) WHAT IS YOUR SIGN  WHEN IS YOUR BIRTHDAY? Scorpio, November 14,  D YOU EAT THE STEMS OF BROCCOLI? If I have enough ranch dressing to dip them in and make me fat... FAT I TELL YOU!! 22) IF YOU COULD HAVE ANY JOB WHAT WOULD IT BE? Photographer in residence at National Geographic  23) FAVORITE FLOWER? crazy colored daisies that make me delirious, lol, I'm never going to forget that one, that was great.  24) HAVE YOU EVER BEEN IN LOVE? yes. 25) IS THE GLASS HALF FULL OR HALF EMPTY? needs to be refilled. 26) FAVORITE MOVIE/S? west  side story, tammy....  27) DO YOU TYPE WITH YOUR FINGERS ON THE RIGHT KEYS? of course !I'm the queen of speedy typing... lol, that's funny isn't it? 28) WHAT'S UNDER YOUR BED? my secret stash of stuff to glue into my book, lol, its a mess! 29) WHAT IS YOUR FAVORITE NUMBER? 847 30) WHAT IS YOUR FAVORITE SPORT TO WATCH? volleyball... since I can't PLAY ANyMORe!!   {and my docter said this time, that there isn't anything they can do about it, I'm just messed up.  oh, and Marching Band, which is NOT pointless..  its like a peanut butter and jelly sandwich... :-) 31) WHAT IS YOUR SINGLE BIGGEST FEAR? wouldn't you like to know?  36) FAVORITE SINGING GROUPS: sugarcult, starting line, ataris {but they sold out}  37) FAVORITE NIGHTTIME SHOW: david letterman.  hee hee funny guy he is. 8) MUSTARD OR KETCHUP? relish.  39) HAMBURGERS/OR HOT-DOGS? heh.     heh.       heh. 40) HAVE YOU EVER BEEN TO THE GRAND CANYON? no, but I'll be flying over it on Saturday! WHAT SCREEN SAVER IS ON YOUR COMPUTER NOW? lol its a bunch of pics I took  COKE OR PEPSI? pepsi  43) FAVORITE APPLIANCE? the brave little toaster  OLD FRIEND MOST LIKELY TO END UP IN A TRAILERPARK/JAIL. Ashley. 45) PLACE WE SHOULD ALL GO LOOKING FO YOU WHEN YOU GO MISSING.  like i would be stupid enough to tell you that?  46)SIX STOPS IN ORDER ON YOUR WHIRLWIND AROUND THE WOURLD TRIP, TWO WEEKS MAX, MONEY NO OBJECT. 1}New York sTate 2}England 3}Bologna Italy, Again.   4}  Cairo 5}tibet 6} sydney  random thoughts in my head: ~i swear the wheels are turning on that car that's parked outside!  ~three pieces of pizza are gross when it comes to little ol' me.  ~i've been vague lately haven't I?   I'm sorry.   that's just how i've been lately.  I'll be better when I come back  i had SO much fun last night, I really did.  Chantele's a dork,{you're a dork chantele}  i want my whole life to be like that.  fun, fun, fun... i think I'll just start party-ing all the time... {no I'm not going to go get drunk, there are parties without alchol you know...  and I have good friends who would never do such things anyway}
    
</post>
<date>29,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      yay, Sean and Chantele are over...  but I suppose those are  the only people who  read this anyway, so there's really no point in me telling  you... {who are you} this? .:sigh:.  what an interesting day.
    
</post>
<date>28,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Sometimes,    I think my name is Jane.                                and sometimes,                                it is Eleanor. Who are you? oh,           you would be                          ... one of them. I'll shake my head in disgust                       of you. pull my hat down over one eye,                   so I'm mysterious.       Aren't I mysterious? See me disappear, all that's left is the mist...                    reach out,                                    touch the place where I was... but don't cling to it,  its dangerous to your health.    lol... who ever it was who called me a poet was sadly mistaken {duh, it was kate... THAT's where the second half of popo came from... I was the poet pope, lol} .  I'm just random. 
    
</post>
<date>27,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Bless you               {you sneezed} 
    
</post>
<date>27,July,2003</date>
<post>
</post>
<date>27,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      why? because its always like this. and I don't want it like this. .:deep breath:. I've had my signs. 
    
</post>
<date>26,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I should know better than to do this to myself. Haven't I learned my lesson?
    
</post>
<date>26,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      This world is so beautiful.   I'm tired.  and kind of sad today. I think I'll go take a shower, and then... retire to my quarters... .:I'm reading a book about Eleanor of Aquitaine:.
    
</post>
<date>25,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I went shopping today.  :-)  I bought two dresses, on sale.  heehee, its kinda funny, they're completely different.  One's like fire engine red, and comes just past my knees, sort of retro 50's-ish I guess, and the other one is white and has a huge full skirt of layered tulle, like a cloud.  Its really pretty.  I love trying on formal dresses.  They make me feel pretty.  like Maria...  {... I feel pretty, oh so pretty, I feel pretty, and witty, and bright! and I pity, yes I pity, any girl who isn't me tonight...    sad, that I can type those from memory isn't it?}  anyway...  and I went to visit Rebecca and gave her her birthday present finally...  her birthday is in September. lol.  Tomorrow I'm driving to Rolla... I want to stay home and talk to my friends... well, everybody's leaving tomorrow too, oh well.  .:sigh:.   Last night, I had the most fun sitting in my room by myself I think I've ever had. {wow, that makes me sound like a pathetic loser doesn't it?}   I was on the phone with Samantha and Chantele... wow, I had forgotten how much fun we have when the three of us are together.  and I had forgotten how incredibly insane Chantele is.  We were joking around about her boyfriend Ben's evil laugh {which is incredibly scary}  so she calls him on her cell phone, and sticks it up next to the other phone and makes him do it over the phone...   Its even scarier that way.  lol.   
    
</post>
<date>24,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      My family means the world to me. They've always been there for me, and I think I know that no matter what I do they will always love me. I have never been as grateful for them as I should be, but I will always love them too, and I would never consciously do anything to hurt them. I hope that I'm the kind of person who would never intentionally hurt anyone, especially those people who are so very close to me. I seem to have forgotten all of this though. Sometimes my frustrations get the better of me. I feel horrible. I'm sorry. I seem to have found a way to mess everything up lately. I'm sorry.
    
</post>
<date>23,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Yay, I drove home tonight with my radio blasting this [VVV] song, I'm in a pretty good mood again... You people always make me feel better.  Saves the Day  See You   My gut is burning. Won't you find me some water? Hey, just forget it can you bring me gasoline and collect a couple forks, hold them three feet apart and wait for lightning to strike to burn me up? Cause I don't think that I've got the stomach to stomach calling you today. My head is swirling. It's been carried off in the sky and where it lands is where is lands. So I guess that I will get another head and then get on with my life and leave you somewhere beneath the waves of time. And I'll wear glass shoes and plastic wrap. No, I'll just wear my insides. You want to know who I really am? Yeah so do I, yeah so do I. Cause I don't think that I've got the stomach to stomach calling you today. Right now I am turning off the lights cause I don't think that I've got the stomach to stomach calling you today.   
    
</post>
<date>21,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      don't you know i was never ready for any of the things you said? i can count the years i've lived      {the years that have passed me by} on my fingers and toes... so can you, but only in reality. don't you know that i am going to be happy? don't you know i won't cry for you anymore? don't you know that it IS better this way? {whether you like it or not?} don't you know that SOMEDAY IS NOT TOMORROW? {not even today} don't you know that you were never even real? you were a dream              or maybe a nightmare I'm waking up now. don't you know? haven't you always known? I'm waking up now.
    
</post>
<date>21,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      So I'm back again... I'm bored today.   You know, I had forgotten how depressing Dashboard Confessional is...  That sort of deflated my "happy balloon" {wow, what a dork}  but I'm still in a pretty good mood...  I have youth group stuff tonight, and I'm hoping Sama and Chantele and I are going to see Legally Blonde 2 tomorrow night {just because we're really cool like that... we need a girl's night out anyway, what better way to solve that problem than to go  see the biggest chic flic ever??????}  and I was planning on going out Friday night...  but somebody decided he didn't want to pay his brother to drive him out to lee's summit &gt;:-I  {jk... you know I luv you-- but you better get your insurance soon!!}  Saturday is my cousin's wedding reception thing, I guess... they had a little civil court house ceremony, and they're just having a party in some park in Rolla {yay!  more sun for Rachel... at this rate, i just might not be paper white when school starts}   
    
</post>
<date>21,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      mmmm....  This past week has been really good.  I'm happy again.  {which is a good thing, because I eat more when I'm depressed}  I love my friends {I love you guys}  I spent all day yesterday having fun with Lisa and David and Stephanie, and then came  home, talked to Sama for an hour and a half, went to bed at like 8:45... I love knowing that there are people who really care about me, that I can trust.  I really am so happy today, I just want to wrap it around me, and curl up back in bed and sleep all day, being happy {because if I'm awake something's bound to ruin it} Of course I still have bad thoughts floating around in the back of my mind... but I'm not letting them surface at the moment.  I'll just deal with those bridges when I come to them :-)
    
</post>
<date>21,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I LOVED Thoroughly Modern Millie... it was so much fun!!  I think i have a new favorite musical... well next to West side Story of course... that'll always have a place dear to my heart.  I hate people who are inconsistant. {don't be inconsistant} I want someone to send me flowers... lol, just kidding. tomorrow i get to go to Worlds of Fun with Tiffany and Aaron and Stephen and Alex and maybe Jason  and all those people.  I'm excited.  I always have fun with those people.. 
    
</post>
<date>19,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I had  so  much fun last night... We all went over to Tiffany's house and everybody else went swimming... and I thought I had done a good job keeping myself dry lol.  I ended up quite wet thank you very much.  hee hee... So much fun.  Tonight my confirmation sponsor and her husband are coming over for dinner.  My mom's going crazy.  Tomorrow night I'm going to Thoroughly Modern Millie with my dad (yay!) 
    
</post>
<date>18,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Oh, you should have seen the sunrise when I woke up this morning.  The sun wasn't even up at all yet, the light was just barely starting to reflecting off the clouds.  It was that blood red color that only the sunrise has, and there were only a few touches of it, it looked like paint brush strokes.  I wanted a fisheye filter for my camera to contort it, but those things cost a lot.  
    
</post>
<date>17,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I want to be superficial.  I have this song stuck in my head Sugarcult - Hate Every Beautiful Day lyrics Something's gotta change again I'm losing, my inspirations gone, oh no oh no Seeing through some different eyes I can't find, my medications failed, again again  I can feel a change I can feel, can you feel it See it on the street watching heat from the pavement  Cause I'm here, ready to take it all here Everything's feeling unclear I wish it was raining Cause I hate every beautiful day  Faces in the crowd Fake smiles for miles My imitations wrong of them again Trapped inside this cheap hotel Bored as hell turing the channels 'round  I can feel a change I can feel, can you feel it See it on the street watching heat from the pavement  Cause I'm here, ready to take it all here Everything's feeling unclear I wish it was raining Cause I hate every beautiful day  I can feel a change I can feel, can you feel it See it on the street watching heat from the pavement  I can feel a change I can feel, can you feel it I'm not the same, not the same lost my feeling  All I know I'll never know All I know I'll never know  Cause I'm here, ready to take it all here Everything's feeling unclear I wish it was raining Cause I hate every beautiful day Every beautiful day Every beautiful day Every beautiful day    It doesn't mean anything... just that I listen to this cd WAY too much
    
</post>
<date>16,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
         urlLink This is my aunt's ranch.   I'm so random.  Oh my god.  I just found out that the brother of one of the guys i went to grade school with was electrocuted to death.  I never particularly liked Brady or his brother, but the guy was only 18... what a horrible thing to happen.  Its all in the newspaper too.  urlLink article   Crappy week.  I had fun last night at church though.  I don't think I've laughed that hard in a really long time.  {ask me about it some time, it was quite an amusing story}  funny isn't it? Tuesday night I was crying, Wednesday night, i'm laughing.   .:sigh:.  that's my life for you ;-) ugh.
    
</post>
<date>16,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      What can I say?     I have too much pride for my own good. My mom wants to know if anybody besides her knows how horribly depressed I really am. Do you know?  You can't possibly. I'm very good at hiding it.  I'm getting no where. I'm going no where. I need out of  here. There isn't anywhere to go?  Yes, I know I'm being vague.  Assume what you like. It doesn't matter anyway. Nothing matters anymore.
    
</post>
<date>16,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      so, I completely snapped last night.  I just really couldn't deal with the stress anymore. I don't think I've cried like that since I was five.  I was violently sobbing {as much as I hate to admit it}  and I couldn't stop.  I think I cried for almost an hour.  It was really horrible.  I feel better now though, I've released all that anxiety.  
    
</post>
<date>15,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      There's an article in the paper about how three local golf courses' pro shops were broken into last night.  Its a mystery!  Just think, I could go, and gather clues... and be just like Nancy Drew!  I can see it now... My books would be green, instead of that weird yellow color, and the very first one, with a giant #1 on the front of it would be "Rachel and the Case of the Missing Golf Clubs".   wow, am I bored or what?  and my parents are gone too.  Too bad I don't have anyone to talk to.
    
</post>
<date>14,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      You know you're obsessed when the first thing you do after you get payed is go to the camera shop and blow 50 bucks, and a whole hour, talking to the woman who owns the shop about different developing processes... which I did, today.  and I'm still very excited.  I can't wait to go home and try out my new filters. wow... that really is sad isn't it?  They asked me to do a reflection on my relationship with God for a whole bunch of Middle Schoolers tomorrow night.  Supposedly I'm good at this kind of thing.    So I have a lot of thinking to do between now and tomorrow night.  {Note:  I STILL have D.C. Sleeps stuck in my head...  Its been what two weeks now?}
    
</post>
<date>14,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm bored. nothing makes sense to me anymore.  I think I've lost my head. Perhaps I'm having a nervous breakdown... its quite likely actually.  Maybe that would explain what's been wrong with me for the past three weeks or so.   
    
</post>
<date>14,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
         Look its my self portrait.  I'm scary.
    
</post>
<date>14,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      lovely... just lovely 
    
</post>
<date>10,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      and as time passes, the wait grows longer the end seems less likely to come. is it worth it?
    
</post>
<date>09,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      darn.  We didn't win the lottery.   I would have had fun with 216 million dollars.  that's a lot of money I think I'm going miniature golfing with St. Robert's youth group tonight.  I haven't been putt-putting in forever.  lol.  St. Robert's is adopting our youth group over the summer since Cindy went a got a job with the state so she can talk to kids with REAL problems. lol.  But yeah Pat (LPM) and Josh (RDL) have apparently volunteered me to help out at St. roberts with this middle schoolers thing every night next week, and play volleyball Sunday night.  yay.  I'm excited.  I missed volleyball.  
    
</post>
<date>09,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
          its supposed to rain this afternoon, or tonight.  I wish I were home so I could go out in it and get soaked.  its so warm, this would be the perfect day for it.  lol... this fun.  look, Samantha's coming over saturday to teach me how to make guacamole... which looks like this:  lol.    
    
</post>
<date>08,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        ::me messing with html again...::  {does it work?}  Hey, cool, it does.  i'm a genius.
    
</post>
<date>08,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Can you tell I'm bored? This is funny [&gt;&gt;&gt;]    urlLink Barbecue anyone?   and my new favorite website {besides this one of course}  is simplyvintage.com   I want every t-shirt on the site.  lol.   Speaking of websites though, I also really like this one too.  Someday when I get really good at html, my site will look like this  urlLink Intensify   {but I'm doing ok for teaching myself dont you think?}
    
</post>
<date>08,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Poor Rachel. :-(  lol... she's a dork...  and a weirdo too. what is the world coming to?
    
</post>
<date>08,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      think  happy  thoughts... {lol sound of music, favorite things... Rachel style} ...hmmm... late night conversations ;-) finding out something I didn't know before warm sunshine on my skin rain on my face sleeping in on Saturdays till noon zipping along in my car with the radio turned up ALL ThE WAY  {even though my speakers suck, so i can't turn the bass up all the way :-( } Bobby, when he's being a good cute sweet little brother {we're not even going to think about the bratty lil brother I've got sometimes... but ok... let me interject this story really quick.  Bobby has this program on his computer that came with a little camera, and lets you record and cut and edit video and all that, so he makes these movies with it.  He's getting really good at it.  the other day he did one that was a talent show, but it was all him, with different hats etc. on... lol  it was hysterical.  I can see it now, he's gonna be the next Steven Spielburg.... lol and I'll be nobody.}  anyway... moving on... happy thoughts... getting flowers, even if they are crazy colored and make me think I'm delusional watching the patterns of light change in the forest as the light filters down through the leaves being loved doing absolutely nothing and knowing that there isn't anything i should be doing while I'm doing nothing. {Not that that happens that often...  I should be doing other things right now...  like working... oh well} having money spending money knowing I'm really lucky and should be grateful for all of the above.  We're going to be in California the first full week of August.  I think we're leaving on the second. I think that'll be ok.  I miss people, but I'll get to spend time with my family, and we're going to go tide pooling...  Did you know those are some of the most diverse self-contained ecological systems in the world?   Can you tell I'm excited?   My dad thinks I should go and shoot all black and white film, and mess around with different filters and stuff.  I think I'm going to like this trip.   Maybe eventually I'll get my dad to set up my dark room for me and I can actually start on my college portfolio.  
    
</post>
<date>07,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      The wise man is he who possesses a torch of his own; He is the guide and leader of the caravan. That leader is his own director and light; That illuminated one follows his own lead. He is his own protector; do ye also seek protection From that light whereon his soul is nurtured. The second, he, namely, who is half wise, Knows the wise man to be the light of his eyes. He clings to the wise man like a blind man to his guide, So as to become possessed of the wise man's sight. But the fool, who has no particle of wisdom, Has no wisdom of his own, and quits the wise man. He knows nothing of the way, great or small, And is ashamed to follow the footsteps of the guide. He wanders into the boundless desert, Sometimes halting and despairing, sometimes running. He has no lamp wherewith to light himself on his way, Nor half a lamp which might recognise and seek light. He lacks wisdom, so as to boast of being alive, And also half wisdom, so as to assume to be dead. That half wise one became as one utterly dead In order to rise up out of his degradation. If you lack perfect wisdom, make yourself as dead Under the shadow of the wise, whose words give life. The fool is neither alive so as to companion with Isa, [=Jesus] Nor yet dead so as to feel the power of Isa's breath. His blind soul wanders in every direction, And at last makes a spring, but springs not upwards.                                    Rumi   I've got that song {D.C. Sleeps... The Postal Service} stuck in my head again. I need to get my hair trimmed again. I have piano tonight what do I need from the grocery store?
    
</post>
<date>06,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      mm...  I was going to rant about time/clocks/watches... like what it says about our society that we are so dependent on time that we all carry little miniature clocks around on on our wrists {or in several other forms as well}  but I suppose thats just me being ridiculous {again}. I found a cool old watch in our basement yesterday, that's why i was thinking about it.  Anyway...  Lately I've been extremely jumpy, even for me.  My mom reached over and patted my arm at dinner last night and I MAJORLY freaked out.  It scared the crap out of me.  I woke up last night virtually in tears... I keep having these dreams that bad things are happening to the people I love, and there isn't anything I can do. {there isn't ever anything I can do... not even in the waking world}  I couldn't go back to sleep, every muscle in my body was tensed up... so much that I'm still sore.  once again, I wish there was a way I could prevent my dreams from coming.  I need real sleep.  I don't know when the last time I had real, solid sleep was. {well, I guess it was when I was heavily sedated last week... }
    
</post>
<date>06,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      So, I guess its kind of like this... I already told you I've fallen to pieces, except the pieces are still together, just broken, and it takes every ounce of my being to hold the pieces together.  And every ounce of my being is tired {exhausted} of holding the pieces of me together.  I DON'T WANT TO DO THIS ANYMORE.  {too bad I don't have any other choice.} There isn't anything else left.  I know what could put me back together {two things actually}  but neither look about to happen in the near future.
    
</post>
<date>03,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      this shade of red looks more and more like blood it doesn't matter now it doesn't I know what will happen it will be better that way don't tell me I'm being silly I know what will happen. Elizabeth?
    
</post>
<date>03,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      ...look at me... teaching myself html...  well, I suppose its half-way decent, isn't it?
    
</post>
<date>03,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      My name is Rachel.  {duh, we already knew that.}  rachel is hebrew, and means ewe {ya know, like a mamma sheep} Ewe also somehow converts into meaning lamb, or mother...{those are other quote-unquote definitions of Rachel}  So, I'm supposed to be lamb-like, and motherly {I suppose that's rather amusing isn't it?}  so I was sitting here, looking at my name on the piece of paper in front of me, and I realized just how hebrew my name really is, I mean, look at it... Ra-chel...  those aren't normal syllables found in our language.  And since my name is hebrew, the language of the Israelis, or used to be the language of the israelis.. am I supposed to be devoted to the israelis, and scorn the palestinians?  {am i really jewish???} The more I look at it the weirder it looks. {rachel rachel rachel rachel rachel rachel rachel rachel}  Hey that [ wow... I'm psycho.
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Another depressing song... I don't know why I like it.  I suppose you might call it mainstream but hey...  radiohead   There, There In pitch dark I go walking in your landscape Broken branches Trip me as I speak  Just cos you feel it Doesn't mean it's there Just cos you feel it Doesn't mean it's there  There's always a siren Singing you to shipwreck (Don't reach out, don't reach out Don't reach out, don't reach out) Stay away from each rocks We'd be a walking disaster (Don't reach out, don't reach out Don't reach out, don't reach out)  Just cos you feel it Doesn't mean it's there (Someone on your shoulder Someone on your shoulder) Just cos you feel it Doesn't mean it's there (Someone on your shoulder Someone on your shoulder) There there!  Why so green and lonely? Lonely, lonely  Heaven sent you to me To me, to me  We are accidents waiting Waiting to happen  We are accidents waiting Waiting to happen   
    
</post>
<date>01,July,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I've been falling to pieces for the past several months, and I think I'm finally losing it.
    
</post>
<date>31,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm suffocating. My lungs are bursting. If you hit me,  I would pop like a brown paper lunch bag clenched in your fist. minus the air. inhale inhale inhale, shaky, like a child who's been sobbing on my shoulder for eternity. sigh... perhaps I'll float away, like a big red balloon. oxygen deprived, plenty of helium.   really... I am so incredibly odd...  I should not be allowed to sit around and think by myself, I turn rather insane. 
    
</post>
<date>30,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      peaches are the nectar of the gods.  mmmmmmmmm...  Sometimes, when I'm laying awake at night, in the ungodly hours of the twighlight morning, I forget things...  and remember other things I had forgotten before. I remember.  remembering isn't always a good thing. That's when I fall asleep, I fall asleep to forget again, before I do something I dare not. before I do something drastic.   I'm rather anxious about starting the new school year.  I want to know if its going to be  a good or bad year. I want to know how things are going to be now that they're different.
    
</post>
<date>30,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      AHHH. I need a pillow to scream into. oh, and this book I'm reading?   guy's version of Briget Jones's Diary. its alright. when you're procrastinating, anything is alright. Do you miss me? 
    
</post>
<date>29,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        Young.  Really young.  I'd say anywhere from 15-35. But you'll go out with a bang.  You'll get in a car accident or be shot.  You'll never have to see yourself get old.  Sad though.  Really sad. By the way, its common knowledge that more people with great goals and aspirations die young.  And if you want to die old, you'll die young and vice versa.    urlLink   At what age will you die?      brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
    
</post>
<date>29,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        that's Sama... 
    
</post>
<date>29,August,2003</date>
<post>
</post>
<date>29,August,2003</date>
<post>
</post>
<date>29,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        this one looks kinda cool squished like that...    
    
</post>
<date>29,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        yay for uploading my pics on to angelfire, and then putting them on my blog... except they're really big, and I have to resize them, and it distorts them a little. anyway, let me know what you think.
    
</post>
<date>29,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, so this is the last time today, I promise...  I'm just being really REALLY good at procrastinating. Tomorrow, I will only post once, because I have five and a half pages to pull out of thin air. {that's a lot of work you know}  In a minute, I will go to my room and sit and read the book I am reading.  It's called "my legendary girlfriend"  which is... quote-unquote "a novel for those who have dumped, been dumped, or live in a dump."  that in of itself was enough to get me to pick up this book at the library.  I've only read the first page though, so I can't tell you if I like it or not.  Speaking of books though... I thought this was interesting.  {I don't neccessarily agree, I just thought it was interesting.} "'So one time when I was working in this motel one of the toilets leaked and I have to replace the flapper ball.  Here's what it said on the package;  I kept it till I knew it by heart:  'Please Note.  Parts are included for all installations, but no installation requires all of the parts.'  That's kind of my philosophy about men.  I don't think there's an installation out there that could use all of my parts.'   Lou Ann covered her mouth to hide a laugh.  I wondered who had ever told her laughing was a federal offense. 'I'm serious, now.  I'm talkin mental capacity and everything, not just parts like what they cut a chicken into.'  By this time she was laughing out loud.... 'They can always use a breast or a thigh or a leg, but nobady wants the scroungy old neckbones!' 'Don't forget the wings,' I said.  'They always want to gobble up your wings right off the bat.'"   The Bean Trees  Barbara Kingsolver  Isn't that interesting?  Rather ironic I suppose, but I love ironicizims... {yes I know I'm making up words, but hey, its my blog}  I need to go back and start reading Kurt Vonnegut again. Good-night.
    
</post>
<date>28,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      oh, and I forgot...  last night at cantor practice... I consistantly hit a high F...  I can't begin to explain how excited I got.  That was the good part of last night.  Then it got bad, but that's ok.  I'm good now.
    
</post>
<date>28,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      So, I got a new commenting host... I didn't like the old one, but I think I messed it up anyway... I put it in the wrong spot in my template... Silly Rachel...lol. anyway...
    
</post>
<date>28,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night was NOT a good night. {end of story} Today was... interesting. Anna Stewart is coming back.  I thought I was finally rid of her. .:sigh:. {maybe she's changed, and she's really a good person, and I shouldn't hold grudges against her...} London and Kate together... oh what a combination. If one more person asks me that god forsaken question...  I think I will drive my car into a brick wall at 150 mph.  Seriously... you're never done when you think you are.  I still have a huge paper to write. I am  procrastinating. :-)
    
</post>
<date>28,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Sometimes, I swear this song is about me. 3am  Matchbox Twenty  she say its cold outside and she hands me my raincoat  shes always worried about things like that  she says its all gonna end and it might as well be my fault  and she only sleeps when its raining  and she screams and her voice is straining   (chorus)  she says baby  its 3 am I must be lonely  when she says baby  well I cant help but be scared of it all sometimes  says the rains gonna wash away I believe it   shes got a little bit of something, God its better than nothing  and in her color portrait world she believes that shes got it all  she swears the moon dont hang quite as high as it used to  and she only sleeps when its raining  and she screams and her voice is straining   (chorus)   she believes that life is made up of all that youre used to  and the clock on the wall has been stuck at three for days, and days  she thinks that happiness is a mat that sits on her doorway  but outside its stopped raining   (chorus)   Are you asleep?  would you tell me if you weren't?  what if I needed you right now? 
    
</post>
<date>28,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      so much for sleeping...  I know what time it is... I know what time it used to be. I think maybe I know what's happening. I think I just like pretending I know. I know how things are supposed to be, and by golly, I'm gonna make 'em that way.  Do you think reciting the things I think/know makes me feel better? Perhaps once they leak out of my head, I no longer have to think/know them. and then I can think/know other things. Perhaps. I like that word... its so hopeful, in a sort of not going to happen sort of way. Perhaps.
    
</post>
<date>28,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I am: a miserable failure incredibly irresponsible, late, never good enough, an ungrateful wretch, undeserving, unintelligent, not who you need me to be.  i'm sorry. I am so, so  sorry.  
    
</post>
<date>27,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      hey I've had almost 300 hits... WHO ARE ALL OF YOU PEOPLE????????????
    
</post>
<date>27,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      This is that Sylvia Plath poem I was talking about.  Tulips                 Sylvia Plath        The tulips are too excitable, it is winter here.      Look how white everything is, how quiet, how snowed-in   I am learning peacefulness, lying by myself quietly   As the light lies on these white walls, this bed, these hands.   I am nobody; I have nothing to do with explosions.   I have given my name and my day-clothes up to the nurses   And my history to the anaesthetist and my body to surgeons.   They have propped my head between the pillow and the sheet-cuff      Like an eye between two white lids that will not shut.   Stupid pupil, it has to take everything in.   The nurses pass and pass, they are no trouble,   They pass the way gulls pass inland in their white caps,   Doing things with their hands, one just the same as another,   So it is impossible to tell how many there are.   My body is a pebble to them, they tend it as water      Tends to the pebbles it must run over, smoothing them gently.   They bring me numbness in their bright needles, they bring me sleep.   Now I have lost myself I am sick of baggage -   My patent leather overnight case like a black pillbox,   My husband and child smiling out of the family photo;   Their smiles catch onto my skin, little smiling hooks.   I have let things slip, a thirty-year-old cargo boat      Stubbornly hanging on to my name and address.   They have swabbed me clear of my loving associations.   Scared and bare on the green plastic-pillowed trolley   I watched my teaset, my bureaus of linen, my books   Sink out of sight, and the water went over my head.   I am a nun now, I have never been so pure.   I didn't want any flowers, I only wanted      To lie with my hands turned up and be utterly empty.   How free it is, you have no idea how free -   The peacefulness is so big it dazes you,   And it asks nothing, a name tag, a few trinkets.   It is what the dead close on, finally; I imagine them   Shutting their mouths on it, like a Communion tablet.   The tulips are too red in the first place, they hurt me.      Even through the gift paper I could hear them breathe   Lightly, through their white swaddlings, like an awful baby.   Their redness talks to my wound, it corresponds.   They are subtle: they seem to float, though they weigh me down,   Upsetting me with their sudden tongues and their colour,   A dozen red lead sinkers round my neck.   Nobody watched me before, now I am watched.      The tulips turn to me, and the window behind me   Where once a day the light slowly widens and slowly thins,   And I see myself, flat, ridiculous, a cut-paper shadow   Between the eye of the sun and the eyes of the tulips,   And I have no face, I have wanted to efface myself.   The vivid tulips eat my oxygen.   Before they came the air was calm enough,      Coming and going, breath by breath, without any fuss.   Then the tulips filled it up like a loud noise.   Now the air snags and eddies round them the way a river   Snags and eddies round a sunken rust-red engine.   They concentrate my attention, that was happy   Playing and resting without committing itself.   The walls, also, seem to be warming themselves.      The tulips should be behind bars like dangerous animals;   They are opening like the mouth of some great African cat,   And I am aware of my heart: it opens and closes   Its bowl of red blooms out of sheer love of me.   The water I taste is warm and salt, like the sea,   And comes from a country far away as health. 
    
</post>
<date>27,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      So... I had another one of those dreams last night...  except this time it was {or at least I was telling myself it was} my fault.  Bobby and I were driving somewhere... on the highway, and all of a sudden a car come flying up an exit ramp, and of course, we were right at the end of the ramp, and I was boxed in, so there wasn't anywhere I could go.  It was like it was in slow motion, and I could see the car coming careening drunkenly at 100 miles an hour towards Bobby.{no not towards us... towards Bobby, that's what I was thinking.} The other car slammed into Bobby's side of the car, and we got pushed into the car on my side too... so I've got blood all over me, and I can see Bobby disgustingly mangled... so I pick up my cell phone, and call 911, but I'm so disoriented I have no idea where we are, so all I can do is cry   Help me, help me, help me help me help me, and then I blacked out.  Then I woke up in the hospital,and there were all these people in my room, and it was all white... {reminds me of a Sylvia Plath poem... I'll look it up  in a minute}  but the second I realized what happened I was screaming for Bobby... WHERE IS HE????  BOBBY  BOBBY... WHERE IS HE??  and everybody just sort of looked at each other, and somebody was said something like "hes in a better place now..."  I was sobbing, sort of chanting under my breath... no.. no. no. no.. I woke up choking on my tears/screams... Its a good thing nobody was home to hear me.
    
</post>
<date>27,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      mmm... strawberry tea for breakfast. Tomorrow I think I will be depressed.  Tomorrow is orientation...  which means I need to get my shiz-nit together, and stop being such a lazy bum...  which reminds me... I still have a TON of schtuff {MY WORD!} all over my room, and I have six pages to write before tuesday, AND I have to vacuum the downstairs for my mom... oh, and I need to wash my hair...{I got pancake batter in it this morning... just because I'm THAT GOOD!!!}  The other day, I was screwing around on the phone with Samantha doing the ditzy voice {yes also known as the "Hi, I'm Baby, don't you wanna slap me?" voice... DON'T ask!}  and Sama was like... you're way too good at that... maybe its because that's like the anti-you, and you just have to get all that out of you somehow.... And some people would say that's the epitome of me.... hmmm.. yup, I'm rambling... I think I'll go now.
    
</post>
<date>27,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Yay for a new layout!!  Yeah, I know, I need to get more complicated eventually... but until I get the hang of this html stuff... oh and yes... that's me over there [&gt;&gt;&gt;]
    
</post>
<date>26,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, so I lied... Fed up isn't playing Friday night... Its The Underdog conspiracy... A Promised Victory, Falling Short, the Seventh Chapter, Rivendale, NOt Quite White and a Silent Ending are all playing at Rotary park... Its on vesper, off 7 hwy, if you need directions, email me, or call my cell {after nine... I used all my minutes talking to Sean for two hours earlier... :-)} umm... yeah... five days till school starts... UGH
    
</post>
<date>26,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      well, today I went to church and talked to the music director for  two and a half hours... then I went and got my mom some lunch, and picked up my mom's book at the library.  When I got home I did laundry.  Sean came over at 5, and we hung out, and watched Moulin Rouge...  Amanda's having a show friday, Underdog Conspiracy, and Fed Up are playing, and I don't know who else, Amanda said six or seven bands... its from 5-10... you should all come.    I like daisies.
    
</post>
<date>25,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, now I'm done, I swear!  
    
</post>
<date>24,August,2003</date>
<post>
</post>
<date>24,August,2003</date>
<post>
</post>
<date>24,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      soo... I'm being eclectic....    
    
</post>
<date>24,August,2003</date>
<post>
</post>
<date>24,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      some words are hard to make come out of my mouth.
    
</post>
<date>24,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, so I'm going to post some more. Honestly I really am happy. I love my life the way it is right now. I suppose some people might think I'm kind of odd saying this, but I feel like I'm doing what God wants me to be doing.  This is where I'm supposed to be.  I'm so happy to have the people that I love so much, who mean so much to me.  I'm happy to have the tasks I have to be doing.  People keep telling me I go around looking like I'm glowing, because I'm so happy.  This world is too beautiful to waste my time here being unhappy.  When I was at World Youth Day, Alexandro {a guy we met there...}  called me 'the Smiley girl'.  At the time I thought that was an insult, but now I see that it was really an extremely nice complement {well, he didn't mean it that way, he DID mean it as an insult but hey...} I wish I could give people little slices of sunshine, and rain showers with a little thunder on the side... maybe a few hugs and a kiss, a years supply of friendly smiles from people you don't even know, and perhaps then all people could be happy like me.  I'm still telling you too much.
    
</post>
<date>23,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Random somewhat ironic thoughts in my head:  1. I try to be understanding...  but there is only so much I can comprehend.  2. Every time you try to slam a door in my face, a window swings open.  Its funny how words bounce around in my head like that, until they run into each other, and hook up into at least semi-comprehendable phrases like that, until my thoughts become a constant refrain of these words, and I have to get them out.  Sometimes I think I know too much, sometimes I think I see too much.  Sometimes I think I think too much, and sometimes I think I'm blind.  Its also funny how words bounce around in my head, and I can't let them out, because then I would be saying too much... Or maybe I would be saying just enough, but then I would be feeling too much.  There are things I want to explain to you, but I'm so bad at this.  I told you that didn't I?     There are lots of things I wish. Silly things, I should be glad to be the way I am... I'm not unsatisfied with the way I am, but sometimes it just seems like, if I were a little different... if only I could just...   then everything would always be perfect.  Wouldn't it?  I told Sean maybe I'm pouring too much into this.  I think I'm right... you can see too much of me here. and that's dangerous.
    
</post>
<date>23,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      yay for watching old musicals... with Judy Garland and Fred Astaire...  its even better than a chick flick fest!
    
</post>
<date>23,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday was a very very long day... and I was really crabby for most of it.  We had to go uniform shopping for Bobby, and we went about ten different places to find the right size.  We were at Oak Park mall for a while, so when Sean called me, I told him to come save me.  About ten minutes after he got there, my parents decided that we were done shopping, and that I had to go home with them...  so then I was in an even worse mood...  but then on the way home I asked my mom if it would be ok if Sean just came to the house and we hung out there for a while, and she said that'd be fine... so Sean came over to the house, and had pizza with my family, and then we sat out on the back patio until he had to go home.  So I didn't end up going to bed in a bad mood, and I woke up in a REALLy good mood this morning. ;-) Today I have to practice my harmonies for mass tomorrow.  Otherwise I might mess up, and THAT would be bad. I'm hungry... I'll probably post more later.... 
    
</post>
<date>22,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      From the Pratt Institute of Art book I got in the mail today:  "How do you see the world? Here's a simple test: Find a plain cardboard box.  Cut a rectangular hole in one side.Put the box over your head, and look through the hole.  Now, what do you see, or more to the point, how do you feel?  Boxed in, limited, or claustrophobic? Or do the edges of your box suggest new ways of looking at the world, of isolating and composing elements, of telling a story?  Okay, you can take the box off y our head now.  It may seem like a silly exercise, but the truth is, most filmakers and photographers live their linves in that box, shaping individual images and whole worlds within those few simple lines.  The experience isn't limiting... its liberating."  YAY!!! That's how I feel... I see the world through a BOX!!!!!!! that sounds horrible I know, but I LOVE IT... love it more than anything...   
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      ugh  I had forgotten,   You don 't know  who I really am  So don't think any differently   of me than you did before.  Ignore the little glimpse of darkness, It's just   a little piece of me  If only I could laugh   like Lauren Krum  You would laugh too  and forget the little piece of me you saw  
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
           Disorder      Rating        urlLink Paranoid :    Moderate       urlLink Schizoid :    Low       urlLink Schizotypal :    Moderate       urlLink Antisocial :    Low       urlLink Borderline :    Moderate       urlLink Histrionic :    High       urlLink Narcissistic :    Moderate       urlLink Avoidant :    Moderate       urlLink Dependent :    High       urlLink Obsessive-Compulsive :    High       --  urlLink Personality Disorder Test - Take It!  --       I am a mental case. I need psychological help. oh wow. 
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      "so long sweet summer" {I think... it might be called something else} dashboard confessional {YeS AgAIN!!!} So long sweet summer  I stumbled upon you and gratefully basked in your rays So long sweet summer I fell into you   Now youre gracefully falling away  Hey thanks  Thanks for that summer Its cold where youre going I hope that your hearts always warm I gave you the best I gave you the best that I had You passed on the letters and passed on the best that I had  So long sweet summer I stumbled upon you and gratefully basked in your rays So long sweet summer I fell into you   Now youre gracefully falling away  I hate the winter in Lexington I hate the winter in Lexington Lexington Lexington Lexington  {I hate the winter... in Lee's Summit...  hee hee}  Top 15 Fun Times of the summer... in no particular order: 1. HYU... I already can't wait till next year! {except my mom's threatening to not let me go because they're hoping to let me go to photojournalism camp at Corcoran next summer} 2.The couple of times I spent on the phone 3-way with Sama and Chantele... oh wow. 3.getting my car :-) 4. ...going tower climbing with St. Roberts... THAT was cool.... I climbed like 55ft up in the air, and then jumped off the top... WHEEEEeee!!! 5. when Sama came over and taught me how to make guacamole... 6.going swing dancing with Sean and Meghan, 7. playing in the rain with Bobby... back when it DID rain...{Sean LIED to me last night and told me it was going to rain, and I got all excited, and it didn't.} 8. prayer jams at St. Robert's 9.going to Thoroughly Modern Millie with my dad 10. doing the Excited About Christ week at St. Roberts...  that was the weekend Sean came over for the prayer service , and then afterwards we went over to Tiffany's house to go swimming, and I got thrown in fully clothed.  oh that was probably the best. 11.going to world's of fun with David, and... yet again, the St. robert's people 12.going to california with my family 13. The day Chantele and Sean came over, and we went swimming and screwed around all day. 14.going to see the Sound of Music with Samantha, 15. and Samantha's birthday.  wow, its all me hanging out with the same people... Chantele, Samantha, Sean, and the St. Robert's people... well, i know i'm guaranteed to have fun when I'm with them... so I guess I kind of seek them out. .:sigh:. well, the summer was satisfactory,  and now its gracefully falling away... so long sweet summer!
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was another good day.  I drove to school and got my schedule changed... well that wasn't so good, but I'm not going to think about that right now, and then I had a liturgy planning commitee meeting and I got to see Katherine... I love her SO much.  And I talked to Samantha and Chantele both today... I had lots of stuff to tell them... and then I met with Fr. Don tonight, and talked about the youth group and a scholarship I got from the parish, and liturgies and other general topics.... THEN I had my first cantor practice for mass sunday.  Yes, I will be singing at noon mass on Sunday... I don't think you can even BEGIN to understand what a big step that is for me.  but I talked to the music director, and she wants us to get more youth music started and wants me to help.  So give me two weeks and I'll have St. John's whipped up into tip top shape for youth ministry!!!!!!!!!  Don't you just HATE having to do everything yourself? anyway, I'm excited about my general prospects for the future, I can't wait to see the new journalism room at school, and hopefully I'll get to see more of Sean once school starts, and I'm already over in that direction anyway, and I'm praying I won't be so stressed out at school this year  {I won't have to worry about the social issues I did last year} and NCYC is in November, and hopefully I'll be getting to sing lots of fun songs at church now....  la la la la la la la!!!!!!!!!
    
</post>
<date>20,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      hee hee... the Two Towers comes out on DVD Tuesday...  Don't let me forget!  except we probably won't buy it... my mom has to wait until she can buy all three of them together... .:sigh:. but I'll go rent it and then watch it eight times.  I can't wait till the Return of the King comes out... will you come with me to go see it?  I'll probably have finals or something that day... I did last year, but Chantele and I went afterwards.  I was looking at pics and stuff though, hee hee... Eowyn's still my favorite. 
    
</post>
<date>20,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I miss Italy...  it was so beautiful, and there was so much to take in.  When I'm in college I'm going to spend a summer there, in Bologna... no commercialized English speaking cities for me...  I was fourteen when we went before...  I don't think I really quite understood what an incredible experience I was experiencing {don't you love repetitiveness?} The culture in Europe is so much richer than what we have here... Thinking about it makes me feel shallow... Am I shallow?  I'm pretty sure I am.  Seriously... I'm sixteen years old, and incredibly naive, and I intend to stay that way, and if being shallow is the  price I have to pay... .:sigh:. oh well.  see look, I'm so shallow I can't even stay on topic...  but then I'm famous for my ramblings aren't i?  ANYWAY... and someday, I'll go back to Italy for Lent/Easter, and go to the Carnevale, the Venician version of Mardi Gras. Its amazing, people get dressed up in incredibly ornate costumes and everybody wears masks, so you never know who you end up partying with, and people, because everyone's wearing masks, do things they'd never do as an ordinary person... doesn't that sound like something I'd do?  The piazzas and vias of Venice {Venezia} are filled with an incredible mix of the most vibrant colors, and the sounds of laughter and singing and music...   and after then go to the Duomo basilica in Florence for Easter Sunday mass... they light fireworks during the mass.  i thought the italian guy was lieing to me when he told me that, but apparently he wasn't.  and I suppose that's enough of my hopeless dreaming. Last night after I posted I sort of got in a bad mood again, so I went and listened to "The Best Deception" like eight times  Well don't you see, don't you see that the charade is over? And all the "Best Deceptions" and the "Clever Cover Story" awards Go to you So kiss me hard 'cause this will be the last time that I let you You will be back someday And this awkward kiss that screams of other people's lips Will be of service to giving you away To giving you away  I'm waiting for blood to flow to my fingers I'll be all right when my hands get warm Ignoring the phone, I'd rather say nothing I'd rather you'd never heard my voice  You're calling too late, too late to be gracious And you do not warrant long good-byes You're calling too late You're calling too late You're calling too late   {Dashboard confessional of course}  and then Sean called and made me laugh, and we talked for a couple of hours...even though he had to go to school today :-P after that I felt a lot better ...I fell asleep smiling. ;~)
    
</post>
<date>19,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      mmm... fun. So, we went to applebee's...and Sama and Chantele and I all ordered salads... and I just made Sean eat the rest of mine...and then the applebee's people all came out and sang to Sama, and we all went back to Samantha's house.  I love that house, that family, really... I feel more at home in that house than I do anywhere else besides my own house.  We messed around for a while, Chantele tried to pluck Sean's eyebrows while I was sitting on him, which was just mean, but Samantha caught her just in time. I'm content.... well sort of anyway... there's always school starting, and other things making me anxious/excited.  Sama call me if you read this tonight... I need to talk to you.  Having the three of  you right now means the world to me... I'd never be where I am right now. mmm... I thought I was done, but the plot continues to thicken... its so thick its dried concrete, and I'm standing on it now.  standing on it laughing at you.  you can't do it. and suppose you think its you I'm talking about...  don't be so selfish... do you think you're the only one I think about?  of course not.  Someday  I'll slap some sense into you pretty one... but right now I need you where you are. but I sound mean that way... I have to harden myself sometimes... eventually... "You need to be more harsh..." I think I'll go to bed.
    
</post>
<date>18,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      happy birthday to you... happy birthday to you...  happy birthday dear Sama, happy birthday to you!!!  yay, I'm excited to go out tonight. except I really am exhausted... don't let me fall asleep in my soup! I babysat last night, and I told Sean that I'm never going to have chubby kids because I would never be able to lug them around all the time like that... seriously, I was only there for three hours, i can't even imagine all day everyday I started reading The Bean Trees by Barbara Kingsolver.  I only read ten pages or so, but I was amazed at how fast that book drags you through different emotions, it goes from astonishment to pity to amusement to anger...  
    
</post>
<date>18,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I had a good night last night, Sean came over and had dinner with my family and me, and then we made brownies, lol.  and then after he went home, he called me and we talked through a lot of stuff... and I feel a lot more comfortable with that situation now... and today was boring... so yeah. tomorrow is Samantha's Birthday!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! and we're going to go out to dinner or something and Sean's gonna come, and hopefully Chantele's not grounded, and maybe Katherine'll come TOO! yay, What fun!
    
</post>
<date>17,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      well lets try this... note comment link in top left corner.
    
</post>
<date>17,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Look, my dad put our  urlLink California Pictures  on the web! and again, i am not responsible for my unphotogenicness...  seriously though, I am the most unphotogenic person i have met in my entire life...  thus the reason I stay BEHiND the camera... :-)
    
</post>
<date>17,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm wondering what you think of when you think of me. won't you tell me? do you think the things you say? do  you laugh? I hope you laugh. I think of warmth, safety and yellow. I think of security, and smiles. I think of thorny roses, and mauve. Maybe you don't know. maybe I don't either. WHO ARE YOU? WHAT DO YOU WANT FROM ME? perhaps today I will be sweet and innocent. Do I dare be anything else? I think I'm rambling. broken thoughts. I've drifted in to vagueness again. but there are things that just can't be said. and so I release my thoughts like butterflies and watch them flutter away... Perhaps you'll catch them in your net... and read the patterns on their wings. 
    
</post>
<date>16,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       Climb every mountain, search high and low Follow every by way, every path you know Climb every mountain, ford every stream Follow every rainbow, till you find your dream A dream that will need, all the love you can give Everyday of your life, for as long as you live   Sama and I want to go see Sing-a-long Wizard of Oz at the Lied Center in Lawrence...and Yo-Yo Ma, and the Miami city ballet... we need season tickets!  urlLink http://www.lied.ku.edu/    I am sixteen going on seventeen, I know that I'm naive Fellows I meet may tell me I'm sweet, and willingly I believe I am sixteen going on seventeen, innocent as a rose...   I'm getting over being annoyed with people at church calling me cute all the time... at least I know they don't think I'm ugly!!  I went to noon mass this morning by myself {I was a eucharistic minister.} and Mrs. Honkomp was there, and I talked to her for a while... She was there when I was born.  seriously. That church is full of people who have known me since I was born, and that really is a cool thing... but sometimes its a little scary too.  I also signed up to cantor at the noon masses...  I'm diving in head first!  AND I have a meeting with Fr. Don Thursday night to talk about this scholarship I'm getting from the parish, and a little bit about the youth group too....:groan:. He said that they'll be hiring a new youth minister by January...  JANUARY... there will be no point in hiring a youth minister by January, we won't even HAVE a youth group then... .:sigh:. oh well.   What would this day be like, I wonder What will my future be, I wonder...  It could be so exciting  To be out in the world to be free My heart should be wildly rejoicing Oh what's the matter with me  I've always longed for adventure To do the things I never dared Now here I am facing adventure Then why am I so scared  Captain with seven children... What so fearsome about that  Oh I must stop these doubts all these worries If I don't I just know I'll turn back I must dream of the things I am seeking I am seeking the courage I lack  The courage to serve them with reliance Face my mistakes without defiance Show them I'm worthy And while I'll show them...I'll show me...so...  Let them bring on all their problems I'll do better than my best I have confidence they'll put me to the test But I'll make them see I have confidence in me  Somehow I will impress them I will be firm but kind And all those children, heaven bless them They will look up to me and mind me  With each step I am more certain Everything will turn out fine I have confidence the world can all be mine They'll have to agree I have confidence in me  I have confidence in sunshine I have confidence in rain I have confidence that spring will come again Besides which you see I have confidence in me  Strength doesn't lie in numbers Strength doesn't lie in wealth Strength lies in nights of peaceful slumbers When you wake up, wake up!  It tells me all I trust I leave my heart to All I trust becomes my own I have confidence in confidence alone...  I have confidence in confidence alone! Besides what you see, I have confidence in me.  
    
</post>
<date>16,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I think I'm glowing right now. but I almost fell to pieces again. I know better than that now. I've learned my lesson. I learned it for myself. With a little help from  the divine signs sent to me. I saw them. They made me happy. and I am happy. and you can't take that away from me anymore. don't even waste your breath. I'm happy... so very happy. Thank you.
    
</post>
<date>15,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      oh yeah, I forgot. I watched "The Hours" with Chantele last night.  I LOVED it.  It made me cry, and you know how I am about things like that.  The  soundtrack was gorgeous, and the photography was enough to take my breath away.  It had an incredible attention to detail, and it was an extremely well made movie... four and a half stars out of five from Rachel...:-)
    
</post>
<date>15,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      mmm.... I had so much fun last night...  I really needed that.  Chantele and I went over to Sean's house at like six, and we just basically screwed around all night... listened to music, and just hung around ;)...and then I spent the night at Chantele's house.  You'd think that since she's my one of my best friends, and I talk to her all the time, we wouldn't find it neccessary to talk until four o'clock in the morning...  but we do anyway.  I think its something about the dark... its more conducive (sp?) to these conversations we have. Tonight I'm going to Starlight to see the sound of Music with Samantha... I'm excited.  It's going to be fun.  I haven't seen Sama in a while.  We're going to sing along with all the songs, hee hee.  we're in like the 34th row of the very very last back corner section, so I don't think there will be anyone around to mind. This is going to be a good weekend.
    
</post>
<date>15,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink I love these ...   my next mission?  learn how to do gouache or however you spell it.
    
</post>
<date>14,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Incubus-- Warning Bat your eyes girl Be otherworldly Count your blessings Seduce a stranger What's so wrong With being happy? Kudos to those who See through sickness Yeah Over and over And over and over  She woke in the morning She knew that her life Had passed her by She called out a warning Don't ever let life pass you by  I suggest we Learn to love ourselves Before it's made illegal When will we learn When will we change Just in time to see it All come down  Those left standing Will make millions Writing books on ways It should have been  She woke in the morning She knew that her life Had passed her by She called out a warning Don't ever let life pass you by  Floating in this cosmic Jacuzzi We are like frogs oblivious To the water starting to boil Now I flinch and We all float face down  She woke in the morning She knew that her life Had passed her by She called out a warning Don't ever let life pass you by Pass you by     today is a Rachel feels fat day.
    
</post>
<date>14,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Your Political Philosophy   According to your answers, your political philosophy is left-liberal.   Left-Liberal  Left-Liberals prefer self-government in personal matters and central decision-making on economics. They want government to serve the disadvantaged in the name of fairness. Leftists tolerate social diversity, but work for economic equality.  interesting...  lucky charms are yummy.      
    
</post>
<date>14,August,2003</date>
<post>
</post>
<date>13,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      So I've been a little depressed the past few days...  not near as depressed as I was before, but once again, I'm tired of being me...  having to deal with the things I always have to deal with...  I want to deal with someone else's problems for a while... surely I'd be better at than than stuck in this stalemate I seem to be in with my own issues.  I'm tired.  I want to be done for a while... I'm never done.  Oh well.  I'm going over to Sean's house tomorrow night for a party, and Chantele's going to come.  That'll be fun, I haven't seen either of them since before I left.  and I'm still looking forward to November too. Stupid scheduling people didn't give me an extra elective, next to newspaper... I have to have those credits or else I won't graduate!  so I have to get my schedule fixed.  I have four classes a week with Chantele first semester... and I'm thinking just four with Samantha too, because she's in the smart people classes... sigh... every time I think about that it makes me sick... I'm basically screwed if I want to go to a normal college, because my grades are crap, because I got jipped out of honors classes freshman year, and have been screwed ever since.  anyway...  I'll have four classes with Samantha... Latin III  I'm so incredibly excited to start that class!!!!  {that would be what is known as EXTREME sarcasm.}  I'm going to fail that class... miserably.  but no, I'm going to do well this year, I am NOT going to get stressed out... I will NOT worry about other people... I will NOT get stressed out... I will NOT get stressed out...  {that's one of those things I think, if I say it enough, I might actually believe it}  I will NOT get stressed out...   ugh. but school's still two and a half weeks away...{what? have I started my six page summer reading paper yet?  no...  Do I even have the book yet? no...   I will NOT get stressed out!}  lol. There are things I want to say... but I can't.  I'm afraid....   terribly so.  I would like to explain...but I can't.  That's too dangerous.  I'll end up broken hearted...   again. Nickelback's come out with a song called "someday"... ironic how that word haunts me.
    
</post>
<date>13,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I GET TO GO TO NCYC!!!! I'm going to have the best birthday... I'll have one here at home with friends and family, and then I'll have one with 30000 catholic kids... in HOUSTON... I'll be WARM  on my BIRTHDAY!!!!! and I just got back from hanging out with all the St. Robert's kids I'll be going with, and I have so much fun. I didn't stop laughing the whole time...  I haven't ever been with them and NOT had fun! oh, I'm so excited!  And Happy Alfred Hitchcock's Birthday!     Gravedigger when you dig my grave could you make it shallow so that I can feel the rain oh Gravedigger  
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      look its my cell phone!   aren't  I cool?
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      don't you just love songs with nonsense words?  like ruby ruby ruby ruby so-ho? or aweemba-weh aweemba-weh lol
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      poor poor nastily sick little Rachel.
    
</post>
<date>11,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      for Sean... hee hee   I'm SORRY I couldn't resist...  I just thought it was funny!!!   CHANTELE... CALL ME!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!    
    
</post>
<date>10,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I have a fascination with light and the different ways it is manipulated.  Before I started school, I remember going into my parents bedroom in the mornings when the sun would shine through the prisms my mom had hanging in her window, and I would sit there warmed by the sun and watch the rainbows move across the walls as the day went by. {Pollyanna was always one of my favorite movies too}  When I was in sixth grade, I made my own kaleidoscopes for a science project, and experimented with number of mirrors involved and what angles they were placed at.  Now I have this infatuation with capturing light on film.  Digital cameras are boring; they have nothing to do with the light, all they do is translate real life into pixels.  With film, I can manipulate the way the light is recorded, by experimenting with different chemicals.  I cant wait till I have my own dark room so I can learn the tricks of the trade.  Im looking forward to going back to school, if only to be photo editor of the newspaper.  Last year, I really fell in love with journalistic photography when Mr. Thomas asked me to stay after school the day we had had a shooting at a house behind the school.  He handed me the staff camera, and walked over to the scene of the crime with me.  I could feel the adrenaline pumping into my blood, pulsing through my hands as I tried to hold the camera steady.  We slipped into the taped off section for the press.  I felt so important I almost actually belonged there.  There were reporters from news stations and local newpapers, and I was threading through them to get the perfect shot.  When the negatives came back everyone exclaimed over my pictures, and how good they were.. I wasnt that impressed.  But Mr. Thomas helped me pick the best one to be printed.  {as the year went on, he spent a lot of time at the light table with me, helping me pick photos.  Im hoping Ill be cured of my self consciousness and be able to decide on the best photos faster this year otherwise well never get anything done.}  Anyway, the picture I had taken of the shooting ended up being published on the front page of  The Dart {our school newspaper}  I dont think I had ever been so excited to see my name in print, Photo by Rachel Straughn    Last week I was perpetually getting myself grubby crawling around places to get the perfect shot.  My mom kept yelling at me for laying flat on my back in the dirt to take pictures of the sequoia trees, but it was the only way I could get the perfect angle.  When we went to see the tide pools, I was wading around in them with my jeans rolled up to my knees, braving the dangerous crabs that were as big as my toe.  Of course I had my camera with me, but I kept a careful eye on the waves coming up behind me so as not to get my beloved wet, and that night I carefully wiped off all the ocean salt.  When we climbed up on Morro rock I wriggled into a tight crevice to get the perfect shot of the mountainous horizon framed by the crevice I was in.  I cried when I left a roll of film on top of our van. { I had been standing up out of the sliding door shooting pictures of the mama bear and cubs that we saw.}  It rolled off down into the valley.  I was a little consoled when my dad told me it happens to every photographer.  I got more than a little upset later in the week though, when my mom asked my dad to take some pictures of a waterfall instead of me, when I already had the camera.  She said, Im sorry Rachel, you just shoot film like its water, and I dont want you to waste it.  I think I got a little huffy after that.  I love every part of photography, everything from the so-called mundane cropping photos to be put in the paper, or flipping through negatives to shooting the pictures themselves, or seeing my name in print.  This is my dream.  I want to be buried with my camera.  Maybe theyll decoupage my casket with the pictures Ive taken with my view of the world.  There have been many instances where I have wished I could show people the world in the way I see it, and with photography I can begin to do so. I only wish I could completely convey the emotions I feel or the things I remember when I see the images I capture.  Perhaps someday I will be able to that.  Perhaps someday I will be that talented. 
    
</post>
<date>10,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      why is it that all of a sudden punk music is so depressing??   so won't you kill me? so I die happy...    I still love that radiohead song though...  {see the archives, from a couple weeks ago...}  I seriously listened to it over and over and over again on the airplane...  its weird how I get stuck on one song like that.  definately not normal...  {yeah, yeah... weirdo ;) }  so a lot of stuff happened while I was gone that I wished I could have been here for, but that's ok, I'm home now...  but now I feel unloved, Chantilly won't ever call me back, Sama's supposed to be home, but isn't when I call her... and Sean is incessantly mean to me...  poor Rachel.
    
</post>
<date>09,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Psychic spies from China  Try to steal your mind s elation  Little girls from Sweden  Dream of silver screen quotations  And if you want these kind of dreams  Its Californication  Its the edge of the world  And all of western civilization  The sun may rise in the East  At least it settles in the final location  Its understood that Hollywood  sells Californication  Pay your surgeon very well  To break the spell of aging  Celebrity skin is this your chin  Or is that war your waging  Chorus :  First born unicorn  Hard core soft porn  Dream of Californication  Dream of Californication  Marry me girl be my fairy to the world  Be my very own constellation  A teenage bride with a baby inside  Getting high on information  And buy me a star on the boulevard  Its Californication  Space may be the final frontier  But its made in a Hollywood basement  Cobain can you hear the spheres  Singing songs off station to station  And Alderon s not far away  Its Californication  Born and raised by those who praise  Control of population everybody s been there and  I dont mean on vacation  Chorus  Destruction leads to a very rough road  But it also breeds creation  And earthquakes are to a girl s guitar  Theyre just another good vibration  And tidal waves couldn t save the world  From Californication  Pay your surgeon very well  To break the spell of aging  Sicker than the rest  There is no test  But this is what youre craving  Chorus  ~~~~~~~~~~~  Rodeo Drive...  $$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$$ Legoland...   Bobby San Diego Zoo...  Pandas Sequoia National Park... HUGE trees, and a Mama black bear with two cubs Monteray Bay... Blue and Humpback Whales  and some of the prettiest highway scenery I've ever seen Hearst Castle...  Walked on gold leaf floors--  I wish I had that kind of money Ventura beach...  sun, sun, sunburn {again}  I missed you guys.  I wish I could hang out with you all RIGHT NOW 
    
</post>
<date>01,August,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Lucky 7-- California Girl  I saw her about a month ago Long blonde hair and turned up nose Eyes shine like a diamond ring She looked at me and I gave her a smile Asked her if we could hang for a while  cruise in my caddy with me  (chrous) 'Cause she's so fine And I wanna make her mine all i want is to see her with the Rag top down Starlit sky Pretty little blue gleam in her eyes, she's my California Girl Rag top down Starlit sky Pretty little blue gleam in her eyes She's my California Girl  Summertime is always the best Hangin out chilling with my friends Drinkin' juice making memories But summertime will never be the same Until that smile falls on me again  Do you know what she means to me  (chrous)  feelin' all alone dog with out a bone she fills me up fresh apple pie so warm inside she's all that i need    ok well, my hair's not blonde, but when I get back in a week, I'll be a california girl too! lol, yeah I know, I'm a dork... but you know you'll miss me! :)
    
</post>
<date>30,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       another sleepless night turns colors black and white  twenty one days... I'm going back to curl up in bed. maybe I'll find away to make myself sleep. It doesn't really matter what I want. I want a lot of things. that doesn't mean that I get them, or that that is what's right. but who knows whats right anymore? do I care?
    
</post>
<date>29,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      silence swinging by a thread to and fro and somehow the words echo before they are even spoken. it is raining now and  I would sleep curled in a corner feeling grey and cobalt blue tears tremble unheard these are my silent tears you will not know  such pain that crumbles my world. and my delicate iridescent orb of happiness is shattered again.  bent hairpins remind me of that which cannot be, and my fingertips are bloodied, slit open by my own  masochistic dreams and I wonder if  you know what that means. do you?  I might have told you, but now it is late, perhaps an eternity late too late, and whispered words pass away unheard, like the butterflies I loved too, butterflies and fireflies shattered with the green glass vase which is no longer green but blue a deep dark mourning cobalt blue
    
</post>
<date>29,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      an infinate confusion begins the cracks in this green glass vase, that is no longer green, but blue, a deep dark, mourning cobalt blue.  afterwards, the vase is shattered to pieces falling to pieces all over again and thats what you get this is what you're left with, the shattered pieces of my heart.   
    
</post>
<date>28,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      do you know what I am thinking? I am thinking far away. away away away. maybe some where closer to where I want to be. maybe some thing closer to who I want to be. maybe some day closer to when I want to be. I want to be. I want to be  some where some thing some day. I want to be great. I want to be magnificent. I want to be me, and I want to be who you want me to be. I want  I want  I want I need. some where some one some day.
    
</post>
<date>27,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Chantele and Bobby and I all went to see Pirates of the Carribean last night. it was fun. I don't think my house has ever had that much alchol in it before. interesting.... P.S. no we didn't have a kegger while my parents were gone.  hee hee.
    
</post>
<date>25,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      samarae00000 (8:13:02 PM):  samarae00000 (8:13:10 PM): its a mousie samarae00000 (8:13:27 PM): it works better w/ a quiggly tail samarae00000 (8:13:38 PM): but this font goes  samarae00000 (8:13:51 PM): hey it worked! samarae00000 (8:13:56 PM): thats the real mouse samarae00000 (8:14:14 PM): wait,    samarae00000 (8:14:19 PM): that better samarae00000 (8:14:27 PM): the 3 is too big samarae00000 (8:14:35 PM): sigh  I ran into the grocery store earlier, and they had the prettiest roses out.  I love roses.    and more Margaret Atwood: you might get it, and you might not, read it all ok?: "And that is how we go on.  He asks a question, and I say an answer...Before, every word that came out of my mouth was as if burnt onto paper, and once I said a thing I knew I could never get the words back; only they were the wrong words, because whatever I said would be twisted around, even if it was the plain truth in the first place... But now I feel as if everything I say is right.  As long as I say something, anything at all...   I feel as if he is drawing me;  or not drawing me, drawing on me -drawing on my skin- not with a pencil, but with an old-fashioned goose pen, and not with the quill end but with the feather end.  As if hundreds of butterflies have settled all over my face, and are softly opening and closing their wings.  But underneath that is another feeling, a feeling of being wide-eyed awake and watchful.  It's like being wakened suddenly in the middle of the night by a hand over your face, and you sit up with your heart going fast, and no one is there.  And underneath that is another feeling still, a feeling of being torn open; not like a body of flesh, it is not painful as such, but like a peach; and not even torn open, but too ripe and splitting open of its own accord.                     and inside the peach there's a stone."  That's not really how I felt, it just reminded me of that.  I'm much less dramatic about it.  I think that's everything.  
    
</post>
<date>24,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        Thom: Design Doctor    urlLink   Which Member from Queer Eye for the Straight Guy is your type?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   hee hee.
    
</post>
<date>24,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I blogged out on xanga... silly Rachel.
    
</post>
<date>23,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
           I'm a genius. Why do I know random things like that? only guys are supposed to know about stuff like that...
    
</post>
<date>22,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      So I'm kind of behind on recent events, but I really don't feel like typing out every thing that's happened in the past week or so... it hasn't exactly been a good week...  I mean it CERTAINLY had its good moments, but in general, over all, I need a vacation...  already.  When's Thanksgiving? Ms. Dolan, my english teacher is kind of sad.  She's really cute, and really funny, and she's only like 28 or so, but she's single, and she seems really unhappy, in general anyway...  Today she was talking about how she has no life, and never goes out on weekends and stuff...  and she has this way of twisting her claddagh ring around rather wistfully... {yes Chantele, I took mine off, and put the demon ring back on, just because you wanted me too...  even though it doesn't really mean ANYTHING} anyway.. I think we should set Ms. Dolan up with someone, lol. oh, and I saw this old junky beat up sedan car with an NOS sticker on it... that made me laugh... {I can never remember what the s stands for though... its Nitrous Oxide  systems?   I dunno.  maybe I'll go look it up.}
    
</post>
<date>22,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      so I've been awake for two hours now.  I'm not quite sure what's the matter with me... but I don't really mind being up... I like it quiet like this.  and I like lying in bed, watching the waning moon cross the sky.  I also like feeling empty, and not being hungry....  its not like being anarexic, that's not what I mean...  I just like this feeling of emptiness, like if my stomach is empty, then I can be empty of everything else as well.  lying awake, its kind of like anything I want to be real, can be...  projected on to my ceiling or walls, or wrapped up in my sheets and pillows.   my sweet dreams are waking night-dreams...  and I don't want to sleep for fear of missing them.
    
</post>
<date>21,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        so I've been remembering how I used to be.  How I woke up in the mornings with a horrible sickening lump in my stomach... how every day I wished that I didn't have to get up, that I could just stay there and not have to deal with the world, and the people in it.  I kept promising myself that if I just stuck it through that eventually everything would be all right.  I had dreams of someday so distant that I knew they wouldn't come true.  I was suffocating, drowning, dying away. but then somewhere I found the strength to swim to shore, I was safe again.  and I'm so happy now, I love how things are now.  I can't get enough of everyday.  And there are a few people who mean so much to me, thank you, for everything.   
    
</post>
<date>20,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        hee hee... its raining!!!!!!
    
</post>
<date>20,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        Butterflies are so pretty.
    
</post>
<date>19,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Jimmy Eat World-- My Sundown I see it around me, I see it in everything. I could be so much more than this. I said my goodbye's this is my sundown. I'm gonna be so much more than this. With one hand high, you'll show them your progress. You'll take your time, but no one cares. No one cares. I need you to show me the way from crazy. I wanna be so much more than this. With one hand high, you'll show them your progress. You'll take your time, but no one cares. With one hand high, you'll show them your progress. You'll take your time, but no one cares. No one cares. I could be so much more than this. No one cares. I wanna be so much more than this. No one cares. I could be so much more than this. No one cares. I wanna be so much more than this. No one cares. I wanna be so much more than this. No one cares. I wanna be so much more than this. Good goodbye lovely time. Good goodbye tin sunshine. Good goodbye I'll be fine. Good goodbye, good goodnight.  
    
</post>
<date>18,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      So I'm reading Margaret Atwood again... "Out of the gravel there are peonies growing  They come up through the loose grey pebbles, their buds testing the air like snails' eyes, then swelling and opening, huge dark red flowers all shining and glossy like satin.  Then the burst and fall to the ground." "If I am good enough and quiet enough, perhaps after all they will let me go; but it's not easy being quiet and good, it's like hanging on to the edge of a bridge when you've already fallen over;  you don't seem to be moving, just dangling there, and yet it it taking all your strength." --Alias Grace for other margaret atwood quotes see: June 6 and Jan 17
    
</post>
<date>17,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      So, I've been being really bad lately.  I've been saying things about people behind their backs, and I really shouldn't do that.  I'm being snotty and 'clique-y'. Mandy doesn't even consider me a friend any more because I've shoved her aside so many times to do stuff with Sama and Chantilly...  Alison Jaros has really been getting on my nerves with newspaper and stuff but still, I shouldn't talk about her either... I was teasing Chantele today about not having anybody to sit with since Sama and I had psat prep, and she was like... I have other friends... I'm not as picky as you are about the people I hang out with...   so maybe as much as I try not to judge people, or snub any one... I'm really bad about it.  That really bugs me when I realize stuff like that.  I don't want to be a bad person.  On a different note...  I was talking to Mr. Thomas about my photo column for the newspaper today, and he was like..."We need to figure out a good way to display the photographical genius you'll be showcasing this year..."  and I burst out laughing, and he was like... "I'm not laughing... I'm serious."  That made me feel really good.
    
</post>
<date>17,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I told my chemistry teacher that I haven't been sleeping much lately, and she was like, " Rachel, that's bad!.  It's only the third week of school, and if you're already so stressed out that you can't sleep... you need help.  You need to go take a yoga class or something... and learn how to sleep at night."  I think I really am stressed out.  List of things I need to remember/have to deal with: Chemistry test tomorrow Latin test Monday Photo Editor Duties -shoot center spread pictures...  how do I get parents checking up on their kids if I can't use my friends?? -shoot my photo column -shoot internet piracy/are you addicted to the internet pictures -collect photo assignment sheets -keep track of what film goes where -keep track of who's shooting what story -make sure pictures are decent -scan all pictures into the computer -become queen of photoshop -make film canister labels continuing on... Church Duties -Thursday night rehearsals for cantoring -youth group -youth minister hiring committee -lector/eucharistic minister... {crap  I have to go to a retraining session tomorrow night!} -volunteer babysitter every tuesday night. -liturgy planning piano lessons every Monday night practice piano at least 30 min a day {YEAH RIGHT!!!!!} an average of 2-3 hours of homework every night does my car have gas? ...if I make the play {fingers crossed, but not getting hopes up} PSAT prep class darkroom class? ...friends {aka sanity} family {ack!} eat/sleep  {Heh, heh} liturgy planning committee at school {Where do I find TRACY HADEN?????} um... St. Roberts stuff...  I need to start practicing the music for the Oct. Contemp. Mass  ... and that's just all of the stuff off the top of my head...  I think I'm a little overbooked, what about you?  oh... and I forgot stuff like  HAVING A LIFE!!!!!!  and also add to that the fact that I memorized a 1min 30sec monologue over night monday... I'm meeting Allison during my free tomorrow to go through the newspapers negatives from last year... club registration is Friday, and I want to be president of Photography club I need to figure out what I'm wearing to Cindy's wedding... {I'm doing the guest book!} homecoming is in four weeks... I need to start putting my portfolio together if I want to go to college the NPDA is coming Oct. 25 {Saturday}  and I need to memorize the metric system by tomorrow... {except I think I've got most of that done.}  and my allergies are killing me and I'm exhausted.  I hope I live to see twenty.  
    
</post>
<date>15,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was a crazy day.  Ms. Dunlay yelled at me, and you know how I get when people yell at me.  Then I had to sit there and let people take my picture.  I despise picture day...{unphotogenic...ehem...}  I'm so incredibly tired... maybe if I slept every now and then... mmm... hee hee... I'm watching the black and white Nancy Drew... from like 1936...  the guy just said "gee that's swell..." lol.
    
</post>
<date>14,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        for some reason, I find that disturbing....
    
</post>
<date>13,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
                  lets play this game. what random word did I type into google to get all these pictures? 
    
</post>
<date>11,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Notes on yesterday: I'm not sure you even noticed. I just can't. oh wow. obsessive compulsive {Smack!} indecisive?  of course.  So that was me being vague... and now I can tell you what happened... I went home with Chantele, and then Ben and Sean came over, and the four of us hung out... nothing TOO terribly exciting.  For some reason I have a tendency to sit in a corner and watch in situations like that. {which isn't really like me... I don't think.  Unless I've been lying to myself about who I am for the past four years.}  I think it might have something to do with the competition thing... taking myself out of the contest I don't want to be in... That is not one I have any desire to win. not that its bad... just not right, right now. I don't think I'm making any sense.  I'm going to go take a shower.
    
</post>
<date>11,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      You know what's really bad?  When its only the second week of school, and you're already so stressed out about school that you intentionally go to the library and get really dorky, girly books about dorky girly teenage girls...  who are dorky and girly {get the point?}  and always have adorable boyfriends, and do the most dorky girly things that are so stupid you laugh out loud in your bedroom all by yourself, when really you should be doing your chem lab instead of reading dorky girly books... and now, I'm going to go attempt to go finish my chem lab... or maybe study for the Latin test?
    
</post>
<date>10,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I am fully and completely exhausted. Its a really good thing I have a late start tomorrow.  I think I'm going to go take a brief nap, and do my chem lab until Chantele calls me and tells me what the crap is going on tomorrow. {I want to tell you something...  I wish you already knew... but I don't know where to begin.}
    
</post>
<date>10,September,2003</date>
<post>
</post>
<date>09,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, I am an official Catholic, on my own now.  I have recieved the Holy Spirit... THough I kind of feel like its been a summer long process...  I've made I lot of decisions this summer that I could feel God guiding me through. so yeah. I'm confirmed now. My forehead is oily. lol
    
</post>
<date>08,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      beyond my wants...   beyond my fears... what is this that I fear? what is this that terrifies me so? why so many questions? yes, yet another, ironic isn't it? the walls of my head are a prison. my thoughts prisioners,  held injustly, against their will. and with no crime no charge against them at all. so many questions? that curve and a final dot it mocks me. ?  and for some reason some reason {what reason?} I know that this is good. {though I may not be.} This is it this is now. oh, but whatever happened to yesterday? and when shall I wonder about this yesterday which is now?     so today was weird, I was in an incredibly good mood this morning... {maybe I just happened to start it out right}  but you know, having the homework piled on doesn't exactly keep your spirits up.    I did have a little brownie for breakfast today, but I guess it wasn't enough, because I really couldn't stand up right all day without blacking out...  I was so close to falling over on the stairs, and there were a ton of people behind me, that would have been really bad.  So I just kept walking, which is always good. I just got back from getting my new outfit for confirmation, and I got really excited because I actually fit in a size five pair of pants!!!!!!!!  Because before, my hips were too wide...  anyway, I'm sure you really wanted to know what size pants I can fit into now... horribly enriching content I've got on this site, huh? 
    
</post>
<date>07,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      well, I really cried today... violent sobs, yeah all that... it was really bad.  Then I had to go to the grocery store all gross and splotchy...  That's what kind of a day it was... all gross and splotchy... I still feel gross.... once again though, nothing I do is ever good enough.  I'm never quite what I should be.  I'm never who you need me to be.  I am a miserable failure. I shouldn't have eaten dinner, I knew I wasn't hungry.    I did get to talk to Sean for a little while though, a little bit of an escape.    Then I had confirmation rehearsal...  Those people bug me so much...  all those guys I went to grade school with... yeah, the kind of guys that after they look at you, you want to go run and take a shower...  so then I felt even more gross...  but I talked to Kevin for a while... about how he cut my shoe laces off in first grade...  lol.   but yeah, so now I'm going to go take my shower, and then maybe I won't feel so gross.
    
</post>
<date>06,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
        Goodnight, I'm going to bed, to see if I can sleep this off. otherwise, I might do something drastic.
    
</post>
<date>05,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I need to escape from my house... will you come kidnap me? please? I'll tie my sheets together, and I can climb out my window, and then we can go sit out in the middle of nowhere and look at mars, k?
    
</post>
<date>05,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, so I'm getting really sick of my parents freaking out every time I want to do something.  I wanted to see Sean this weekend, but my mom decided that I already had too much to do, and I haven't seen Sean for almost two weeks, which isn't fun.  and then I asked if I could go out with the St. Robert's people for a couple of hours, and I was going to be home before 8:30, and they still made the huge deal of it, and yelled at me and stuff.  I'm really getting sick of it. I'm sixteen years old, and I do have a life, whether or not my parents like it. and I want to live it!!!!!!!!! Chantele... we're all doing something next weekend.
    
</post>
<date>05,September,2003</date>
<post>
</post>
<date>04,September,2003</date>
<post>
</post>
<date>04,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink read my profound xanga entry   I'm getting paranoid that people really honestly don't like me. I'm not really so sure, but I just get this vibe that people just don't like how peppy I can be sometimes, how I'm always happy/smiling...  I think I lot of people think I'm a "poser" too... when I'm really not... I'm not "punk"  I don't have bracelets all the way up to my elbows or anything, but I really like a lot of punk music, and a LOT of my friends are "punk"  but I'm definately not a "prep" either... I dunno, I just get really dirty looks some times from people like Marcy and  Rose, who are both people that I think are very interesting... but I think they both hate me.... I dunno.  And Sarah was talking about my "giddy-ness" again today...   ugh.
    
</post>
<date>04,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      can you tell my brain is fried today, and I'm bored, so I'm coming up with random things to post?  First best friend(s):Ryan... he was my next door neighbor First real memory of something: I think its riding our big wheels down the hill we used to live on a break neck speeds... First car: my lil' white mazda First date: um...well...  that depends... First real kiss: oh... First job: working at my dad's office First screen name: um, I think it was the one my dad came up with for me... Im4vball? First self purchased album: um... I can't remember, First funeral: My great-grandma elsie I think First pet: Oscar and Grungetta the oscar fish First piercing/tattoo: my ears First house/flat/apartment: when I was born, we moved into a duplex, then our old house a couple months later First credit card: um First true love: um First enemy: Ashley Williamson First big trip: we went to Disney World when I was four.  First play/musical/performance:I was the great thanksgiving turkey spirit in third grade. First musician you remember hearing in your house:  the beatles   Lasts Last car ride: home from St. Roberts Last kiss: I'm avoiding these questions. Last good cry: sometime in July I think Last library book checked out: photography books Last movie seen: lol, some disney movie Last cuss word uttered: crap Last beverage drank: diet vanilla coke Last food consumed: tortilla Last crush: ...well, I'd have to say Sean... Last phone call: I'm about to call Sean... Last tv show watched: I don't have time for that nonsense Last time showered: last night, but i'm bout to take another one Last shoes worn: nikes Last cd played: sugarcult  .:surprise:. Last item bought: food Last annoyance: Chantele, duh? Last disappointment: ...... Last soda drank: diet vanilla coke last ice cream eaten: vanilla bean w/ chocolate syrup last time scolded: for my $188 phonne bill last shirt worn: baby blue polo last webpage visited: xanga
    
</post>
<date>02,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      hmmmmmmmmmm......................?   You have a mysterious kiss.  Your partner never knows what you're going to come up with next; this creates great excitement and arousal never knowing what to expect.  And it's sure to end in a kiss as great as your mystery.    urlLink   What kind of kiss are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   that's odd...
    
</post>
<date>02,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was a good day.  I somehow managed to remember how to conjugate verbs into future tense in Latin, and after school I went in to talk to Mr. Thomas about photography, and showed him some of my pictures, and he really liked them.  He was like, "These are REALLY great Rachel." {take THAT silent bob} Mr. Thomas has sort of become my photography mentor.  He wants me to come in a couple nights after school so he can show me how to use Photoshop, and he's going to help me put together my portfolio for the NPDA thing.  I always feel so much better about my photography after I talk to him, and he always gets me so excited about it.  and my mom's going to sign me up for darkroom classes at the community college!!!!!!!!!!  I did get kind of depressed listening to Chantele talk about her art stuff today... its kinda hard to explain though.
    
</post>
<date>02,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I think I am an insomniac G_G
    
</post>
<date>02,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Interesting conversation I had today: Sarah was talking about how Chandler didn't seem her usual perky self today, and then she said, "well, but then again, nobody's very perky today... except for you Rachel, you're always perky.  I think you have an extra organ inside you that manufactures your caffiene for you."  and I said, "Wow, I must be really annoying then if I'm really that hyper all of the time..."  " Well, I'm not really around you that much, so its just kind of nice, you make me smile, but if I were around you all the time it might get kind of annoying."   Does that mean I need to tone myself down a little bit? I don't want to be annoying.  oh, and just in case you were wondering, my first day of school went very well compared to how I thought it was going to go.  I hope tomorrow is better though, since I have all the good classes tomorrow.
    
</post>
<date>01,September,2003</date>
<post>
</post>
<date>01,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Good Morning... did you know that its easier to sleep until eleven when its cloudy and the sun doesn't come up shining right in your window?
    
</post>
<date>30,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      So its that same question I've been asking since I was old enough to have my own identity {about third grade}  Who am I really?  and who do I want to be?  Do I want to be the person I know people want me to be?  because I want other people to be happy, and so I will be who I am to make them so?  Do I want to be the person I know my parents want me to be?  Do I want to be sweet and innocent?  Do I want to be strong and powerful?  Can I be both?  Do I want to be the person that can be depended on to always say 'Yes'? Do I want to be the one people feel protective of, and be 'babied' to a point?  Do I want to be the one who is wildly successful, though has given up every thing else to be so?   WHO DO I WANT TO BE?  WHO AM I NOW?  am I who I've heard people think I am?  Am I really the one who, {supposedly}  when my best friend is having her first child, will be in the amazon, connected by cell phone yelling support?  Am I the graceful beauty some people say I am, {though I see things quite differently}?   Am I as 'good' as I've heard others say?  {I know I'm not.}  Am I catty and mean?  Am I a fraud?  Am I just a brilliant pretender, so good I've even fooled myself?  Am I worth all the trouble?  Am I a horribly irresponsible child?  a slacker?  lazy bum {lol, yes}?  Am I really who you think I am?  Who is that?  Am I someone?  Anybody at all?  Who am I in relationship to this world I live in?  in relationship to the God I praise?  In relationship to myself?
    
</post>
<date>29,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      So I had another revelation while I was driving with the radio off tonight.  I was think about how we're supposed to be able to see the Aurora tonight, and I thought that would be the coolest thing ever to be able to see, I decided that I am meant to see all these amazing things that God has made, and that I just have this longing in the depths of my soul to see every miracle in this world that there is to see, and that I should do so... I just don't know how my catholic faith fits in with all that... its not like I can go to mass on sunday when I'm out in the ocean, or in the middle of Cambodia or something. I'm sure it'll all work itself out by the time I actually get there.
    
</post>
<date>26,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I want for everything to just be fine for a while.  I want to not be yelled at every time I come out of my stupid room, I want to know that's its ok that I want to do what I want to do, I want to not have to drag myself out of bed to go to school, I want to just get up, and be excited to go, but I'm not.  I want to not have to think about anything for while, but there's always something... and if there's not, then I'll make up something.  I want to sleep through a whole night.  I want to be warm.  I want to feel safe.  I want to not have to worry about other people.  I want to know what you're thinking.  I want to know if you really mean it.  I want to just chill out for a while.    I can't wait for NCYC.  I need to go away from here, and be with people who don't know who I am and don't know all my problems, and with whom I can be who ever I want.  and I won't have to worry about what anybody thinks of me.  not even my parents, or my best friends.    I feel so encumbered right now. I want to be set free.
    
</post>
<date>22,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      So yesterday I went to the Kansas City Art Institute to have my portfolio reviewed, and I think it went really well.  Milwaukee and Cincinnati both really liked my work, but they said I need to start drawing...  so I suppose I'm going to start drawing... UGH!  Albany tried to accept me right on the spot, which was kind of cool, and then I was like... uh, I'm a JUNIOR.  so they changed their mind.  The lady from the art institute of chicago didn't like my conventional photography though, she liked the work I had done with my altered book...  So it was a very learning experience for me, and I'll be ready for this when it comes around again next year.
    
</post>
<date>22,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      ARG! oh look, I have 705 hits...   that's a lot, though not considering how long I've had that counter up. I </post></Blog>