<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Lindsey, We're 14, not thirteen. We're actually more mature then most girls our age. We're NOT drama Queens. YOU did say something and the qoute, 'Hello?! She's ruining one of my bestfriend's life and you expect me to stand here and do nothing?!' Yea, who ever said this, Yea, YOU said this, and Yea, *I* nor Leigh-Anne made it up. Yea, I'm the other girl on the phone, I'm sorry, but are we a level to be stooped upon just because of our age and grade level? That's pretty shallow. Leigh Anne's not mad at Rosie, nor at anyone, but i'm angry because of this, I did NOTHING. I was protecting my friend. I have dislike for you already Lindsey, but im not about to go off being a bitch about it all because I can't do that in here. Anywho I'm out of here.  Lily The Psycho Powered Goddess
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Joah. god I hate you.
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just for the record... Rosie nor I said anything to Leigh Anne or whoever was on the phone.  We just said hello and they kinda took it from there because they asked where you were and I said you were in the bathroom.  I don't know where they got everything else.  All thirteen year olds are drama queens cuz they want their lives to be interesting and its not.  Sorry if she cried; she brought it upon herself.  And you don't help it much by tolerating her controling you're life.  But I'll stay out of it.  No more advice, etc.  Bye, Josh.  See You Monday.  If you want to get mad, fine.  If you want to sink to their level, that's cool.  Just don't bring it out on the DI team.  Oh, and we're about as happy with you as you are with us.
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      *laughs Insanely* JOSH!! YOU HAD BETTER PICK UP THE PHONEEE! Anywho, hahahahaha Anywho, Sit, im getting addicted to Leigh-Anne's words. BYE JOSHIESSS!!! BYE BYE BYE BYE BYE! * screams* BYEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEEE!!!!!!!!!!!!1  Lily the Psycho Bitch
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, some ground rules...  Any of my invited people who check the team roster will see some people that they probably have conflict with...so no conflict or I kick you. I might just kick all of you anyway, nothing personal, I was sort of planning for this to be just mine, I put all of you on in a mini-fit.   And now to the problem.  People are fucking retarded. SURPRISE! Look at the name of my BLog for God's sake.  I don't want to understand anything anymore, I'm getting sick of that shit. Understand  me ! Understand why the fuck I get pissed off so fucking quick. Of course nobody will, I'm supposed to understand first. And that shit doesn't make sense. That is so gay.  Everything is so gay.  I swear to God, she is pissing me off. AGGGGGGHHH. I wish she wasn't, too.   Dirt  by Alice in Chains  I have never felt such Frusteration or lack of self-control I want you to kill me And dig me under I wanna live no more  One who doesn't care is One who shouldn't be I try to hide myself from what is wrong for me For me  I want to taste dirty A stinging pistol In my mouth, on my tongue I want you to scrape me From the wall, and go crazy Like you made me  One who doesn't care is One who shouldn't be I try to hide myself from what is wrong for me One who doesn't care is One who shouldn't be I try to hide myself from what is wrong for me For me  You, you weren't so special You have the talent To make me feel like dirt You, you use your talent To dig me under And cover me with dirt  One who doesn't care is One who shouldn't be I try to hide myself from what is wrong for me One who doesn't care is One who shouldn't be I try to hide myself from what is wrong for me For me
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I want to talk about something that interests me.   But I can't think about it right now, not awake enough.
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      No.
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Call me 
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       River of Deceit  by Mad Season  My pain is self-chosen At least so the the prophet says I could either burn Or cut off my pride and buy some time A head full of lies in the weight tied to my waist  The river of deceit pulls down, oh The only direction we flow is down  Down, oh down (x4)  My pain is self-chosen At least I believe it to be I could either drown Or pull off my skin and swim to shore Now I can grow a beautiful shell for all to see  The river of deceit pulls down Yeah, the only direction we flow is down  Down, oh down (x4)  The pain is self-chosen, yeah Our pain is self-chosen  Down, oh down (x4) 
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Um well...  There was another classic example of me misreading a girl. She was all mad because she thought I was going out with Lindsey, and I guess she thought we were ok, or something...  As the last part of the history said on my woebegone Tin Haven, "the present has a lot of potential", and it does...it's really weird.   I'm not saying it's all better. I'm just saying it's not worse.  This settles a lot of things with me, faith mostly, I've prayed a long time for something to turn out right, and perhaps I'm getting a second chance.  Maybe I'm luckier than I thought.
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Posted in Kenzie's BLog about five minutes prior:  Hiya Kenzie, guess what fucking happened....  First, this is the new secret  urlLink BLog . Tin Haven got deleted by Leigh Anne, and you'll see why in the rest of this post. Second of all, some shit happened. My friends had my cell at that DI meeting, Leigh Anne called and kept calling. At one point, I went to the bathroom, they said something  really  horrible to her, she started crying.   I think she hates me now...after everything, after I ALMOST fucking had it.  "I love you" she said last night. I was able to make her laugh for hours, I was able to do it all. I was perfect. And now this shit, and Leigh Anne's taking it out on me for shit they said.   It  amazes  me how pathetic my luck is. I just really want to take everyone I've met this year, all my friends and everything, and scream at them til I lose my voice, sleep it off, and do it all over again until I choke on blood and die. I really cannot believe how much my friends want me to die, thinking they're doing the "good deed" for me by ruining things with Leigh Anne. She's hurt me a lot, but these things are in the past, gone forever, I can forget about that weakness I had, I can forget the depression, but somehow the scars it created seem to come back and haunt me, the scars surface and they never forget how I treated people when  I  was in darkness.  Somehow it's fine for Leigh Anne to take everything out on me, when I have a bad day. If something bad happens to her, like she said, "If you knew what happened to me today you'd know that I really don't need this (being cussed out/whatever happened by Lindsey and Rosie at the meeting)", then NOTHING ELSE bad can happen. Even if it's not me but my friends. I'm supposed to take responsibility for my actions, like it's all my goddammed fault. Why is that, Kenzie? Why is it that she can only see the bad in me when we're not together, and she only sees the good when she's at her worst, and I'm at my best.  At some point, her and Lily put down the phone. I've been sitting here, waiting, listening to the silence, for the past hour and fifteen minutes for someone to pick up, because I want to sort this out and get on with it.  I FUCKING CANNOT BELIEVE MY LUCK. I CANNOT. GODDAMN.  Will something please turn out right and stay that way, please? Give me just one grant God, universe, nature, any-fucking-one, listen to my soul screaming and give me this.  The time for sadness is over.  And anger is in season.
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Welcome to the new secret BLog...  I can't believe I'd ever need another one. I can't believe my luck, it's incredible.   Incredibly fucked.  Tin Haven was deleted by Leigh Anne in a fit of anger, goodbye Tin Haven. It doesn't matter.  For now, I want to post all that happened in Kenzie's BLog. I'll put it here eventually. It just seems like I'm talking to Kenzie when I do it, and it's a lot easier than feeling like I'm talking to no one here.  Welcome to Antiphilanthropy, down with this wastrel existence.
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Eww...nice ear description there, Josh....ick.  Anyway, wow.  About your last post yesterday.  You know what I mean.  Click.  Yikes.  But I'm glad that you changed your mind.  You're a great friend, Josh.  Love having you around.  And there ends the mushiness.  ;)  ~Z  
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's been a pretty nothing-doing day.  I played Counterstrike/was on the phone with Alex most of the day, I lost pathetically and was consequently made fun of. But who cares, the game is waaaaaaaaaaaaaaayyyyyyyyyyy too real, and  games  that focus on reality aren't even worth playing. Call me a n00b if you must, since I am, but I just like games that take the emphasis off of "get shot=dead" and more on "get shot a few times=use god powerup=RESURRECTION=get shot a few more times=run like hell using speed powerup=get hit by opponent's gun powerup=dead". Yeah, y'all get the idea.  I listened to POOR BASTARD all the way through,  Died  is a little mest in the middle, I probably won't reburn it though, it took forever to get all those songs together, and a little blip in the midst of the song isn't gonna change anything major.  Ugh, my earring ear is bleeding and dripping all over the place, heh. I felt a few drops on my shoulder just now and I was like, "Agh, ceiling's leaking freon or something" and then noticed the remarkable scarlet hue.  And Happy Chinese New Year all, I hope you're all enjoying the year of Yog-Soggoth......I mean, the Goat.  Because  I  am tired for some reason, caffeine overload.  Happyhappyjoyjoy.
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I remember that time I had mono, it was in seventh grade.  I remember I was at my dad's and one day there was a storm. My mom and sister came over and sat with me. I was running a berserk fever, 106 or something, she was putting a rag on my head and I was screaming at the top of my lungs. I started hallucinating at the storm, it scared the shit out of me, I threw off the blanket, I got cold, I put it back on, it was making me sweat, over and over again. I stepped outside for a while and felt good, and then it started to rain and they were afraid of me getting pneumonia so I got dragged back inside. Plus I was cold again. I shook like I'd never thought possible, trembling from head to toe, and painfully, no less.  And when it was over, it was over. I woke up one day and it was completely gone. But I was really weak for a long time, and I lost a lot of weight, like 20 or so pounds.  POOR BASTARD is the CD based off of songs that have influenced my thought over the past six months, some of which have been posted in Tin Haven or Bad Vision. And I just burned the CD so copies for everyone.  I dunno where she is, gone I guess.  And with that, the beginning lines of a new, and soon to be famous post. There was the "dark marks" one, there was the "thank you for being there" one, there was the very cryptic one at the end of November, "I'm not at liberty to say what happened, but just know that I am really confused right now,". I sounded like a child there. And now, this...  Is anyone out there? Is there anything good at all?  Because lately it seems that even the best made tapestries have to unwind, all the metals will rust, everything is going to die even as it lives and lives after its death.   It seems like some big cosmic trick, that somethings never last..."somethings never last they tell me, sometimes lies are what we are" I wrote for no reason once, and now it's beginning to take shape.  Everything I've ever written, no matter how inconsequential at the time, has come to being, has become reality, the feeling from the song takes substance and becomes my life, not just because I am hearing the song, but that the world is affecting it all, making it all spring to being, and the subject matter in the song becomes true.   My Solution  was the start of it, the feeling of cagedness, I tried to off myself once, I left it to fate. It was just after I wrote the song, I had my dad's pistol, I put it to my temple, I pulled the trigger.  And fate said, "CLICK", and no more. And since I have never thought of suicide as an alternative to ANY situation, because that is NOT the end of the road. Things didn't work out with Leigh Anne and me, and they really aren't right now, but that's no reason to make myself dead, because if I am, what can I do about the situation? What is the point in creating my death? To end pain? And then what, when the immortal soul carries on, I still live with that pain, but then, it multiplies because there is nothing that can be done for me, I am dead, and the living care not for the haunts of the dead.  So the points so far...somehow, I have known what was going to happen to me through my songs, and that suicide is no longer my option. I remember where I was going before this now...  The other songs have really come to be after that,  Bitter  was rewritten using the term "sunshine"; Leigh Anne referred to herself as "an undiluted ray of sunshine" thereafter, and the first lines of  Bitter : "Where did my sunshine go, I think it's ever-fade". I wasn't taken aback. The others songs have come true, why shouldn't this one take substance in some manner or another?  Red Flowers  came true,  Shut Up  came true.  Veil  came true, and still is. All the songs have come to life to haunt me. It's like harnessing a demon, the demon takes his toll eventually.  And unfortunately, all the songs have no semblance of hope, they only portend anger and fear, sorrow and the end of a dream, of a life, of a history.   The only hope I have is in the earliest version of the song  Oh Morose , because in that I was finally standing with myself, not trying to pick up the pieces of myself. And in the new one, it's about being beaten down by my devils...and it's already happened.  What the hell am I trying to say...   Is  there any semblance of good, of change, of things taking a good discourse from the norm?  Because the worst is reaching a brand new low for me now, and at the same time I am numb. Why?  What happened to me, shouldn't I be sad that I can feel misery?  But I answer, there is no misery left for myself, that is not the way to go.  In a way things are better, in myself they are better, and outside they are getting worse.  The winds of change are blowing again.  And my book grows thin of these pages.  
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Shut up Rosie, you shall ever be wrong, plus I do not care what you say.  Everything's just so fucked.  It's weird, I'll explain it later.
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, I'm WAY behind.  First, what the hell is poor bastard???  I HATE BEING SICK!!!  Rosie  Z, I don't fit the mold- I'm in all those "classes" that Rosie hates, even the prep  popular ones to an extent because they're all my middle school friends.  Not that I'm perceived to be in these groups by onlookers, but I'm there, just the same, whether I want to be or not.  Yall are my real group though.  Anyway, I MISS YALL!!!  And where's Lily lately?  I haven't gotten in my weekly bitch moment this week, and Lord only knows I need one (I'm just kidding.  I'm not really a mean person  Josh will even back me up on that one.)  I'll see you guys later.  Apparently I'll end up in the hospital if I don't go to bed RIGHT NOW.  God, mono sucks.
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      POOR BASTARD LYRICS   Blood Brothers  by Papa Roach  Watch your back because the next man is comin' And you don't know if the next man is dumbin' Survival of the fit is what it is I got your back you got my back and that's the biz Blood is rushing through my veins I got the power Channel the energy and with my strength I will devour Sickening thoughts are running through my head That's when I realized I'm glad I'm not dead  Corruption and abuse The salesmen of our blood For the public's craving Existence in the dark  It's in our nature to destroy ourselves It's in our nature to kill ourselves It's in our nature to kill each other It's in our nature to kill kill kill  It was a dream and then it hit me, reality struck And now my life is all shifty and it all moves fast Close to a buck fifty, we all stand strong In respect to the family in the times of Enemity, and through world of profanity I describe my dysfunction family Blood brothers keep it real til the end Deeper than the thought you think, not a trend  Corruption and abuse  The salesmen of our blood For the public's craving Existence in the dark  It's in our nature to destroy ourselves It's in our nature to kill ourselves It's in our nature to kill each other It's in our nature to kill kill kill It's in our nature to destroy ourselves It's in our nature to kill ourselves It's in our nature to kill each other It's in our nature to kill kill kill Again and again  Corruption and abuse The salesmen of our blood For the public's craving Existence in the dark  It's in our nature to destroy ourselves It's in our nature to kill ourselves It's in our nature to kill each other It's in our nature to kill kill kill kill kill Kill kill kill kill kill Kill kill kill kill kill Kill kill kill kill kill Kill kill kill  It's in our nature to destroy ourselves It's in our nature to kill ourselves It's in our nature to kill each other It's in our nature to kill    Pertinence  : The theme song of Tin Haven, of Rosie's depression fits, and my love life. The chorus says it all, "it's in our nature to kill ourselves". First utilized in a fit of extreme anger.    Hey Jealousy  by Gin Blossoms  Tell me do you think it'd be alright If I could just crash here tonight You see I'm in no shape for driving Anyway I've got no place to go And you know it might not be that bad You were the best I ever had If I hadn't blown the whole thing years ago I might not be alone  Tomorrow we could drive around this town And let the cops chase us around  The past is gone but something might be found To take its place Hey jealousy Hey jealousy, hey jealousy, hey jealousy  And you can judge me not to think And not to sleep around And if you don't expect too much from me You might not be let down Cuz all I really want's to be with you Feeling like I matter too If I hadn't blown the whole thing years ago I might be here with you  Tomorrow we could drive around this town And let the cops chase us around The past is gone but something might be found To take its place Hey jealousy  Tomorrow we could drive around this town And let the cops chase us around The past is gone but something might be found To take its place Hey jealousy Hey jealousy, hey jealousy, hey jealousy  Tell me do you think it'd be alright If I could just crash here tonight You see I'm in no shape for driving Anyway I got no place to go And you know it might not be that bad You were the best I ever had If I hadn't blown the whole thing years ago I might not be alone  Tomorrow we could drive around this town And let the cops chase us around The past is gone but something might be found To take its place Hey jealousy  Hey jealousy Well she took my heart There's only one thing I couldn't start    Pertinence  : Firstly, the Blossoms put me in a good mood all the time, and secondly, the line "If I hadn't blown the whole thing years ago, I might be here with you" applied to my struggles with Leigh Anne, thinking that I was an asshole before and that's why she hated me now.    Sorrowful Farewell  by Rotting Christ  Counting the time Waiting for the crime A loss of innocence A faint reminiscence I am into a light Surrounded by the night Their memory's been disgraced The scene is still unchanged  I praise the song of defeat I am the bottom, and he's the summit A sorrowful farewell Where does salvation, does salvation dwell?  I keep still I'm trying to feel The hate that's within you I'm going to win you I was mistaken I was forgotten Unbroken silence Absolute violence  I praise the song of defeat I am the bottom and he's the summit A sorrowful farewell Where does salvation, does salvation dwell?  The time is near The message is clear The battle will be fought Fight now, fear not  Counting the time Waiting for the crime A loss of innocence A faint reminiscence I am into a light Surrounded by the night Their memory's been disgraced The scene is still unchanged  I praise the song of defeat I am the bottom and he's the summit A sorrowful farewell Where does salvation, does salvation dwell?    Pertinence  : It was mostly a rocking song and I needed one badly at the time. The vocals suck ass, but they really preached to my anger. Also, the line "I am the bottom and he's the summit", probably a reference to some demon in this case, spoke to me as, "this is what you are, that is what you could be, this is how you can get there, and this is what it's going to take".   For Whom The Bell Tolls  by Metallica  Make his fight on the hill in the early day Constant chill deep inside Shouting gun, on they run through the endless grey On they fight, for they're right? Yes, but who's to say For a hill men would kill, why? They do not know Stiffened wounds test their pride Men of five still alive through the raging glow Gone insane from this pain that they surely know  For whom the bell tolls Time marches on For whom the bell tolls  Take a look to the sky just before you die It's the last time you will Blackened roar, massive roar fills the crumbling sky Shattered goal fills his soul with a ruthless cry Stranger now are his eyes to this mystery Hears the silence so loud Crack of dawn all is gone, except the will to be Now they see what will be, blinded eyes to see  For whom the bell tolls  Time marches on For whom the bell tolls    Pertinence  : None, really. I picked up  Ride the Lightning  at the middle/end of December, and listened to it again, it reminded of the severe but serene loneliness I had when I first started listening to Metallica, so what A GREAT IDEA listening to music that depresses us. YES.    All I Want  by Toad the Wet Sprocket  Nothing's so loud As hearing when we lie Truth is not kind And you said neither am I And the air outside so soft Is saying everything Everything  All I want is to feel this way To be this close, to feel the same All I want is to feel this way The evening speaks, I feel insane  Nothing so cold As closing hard when all we need is To free this hole But we wouldn't be that brave I know  And the air outside so soft Confessing everything Everything  All I want is to feel this way To be this close, to feel the same All I want is to feel this way The evening speaks, I feel insane  And it won't matter now Whatever happens will be For the air speaks of all we'll never be You won't trouble me  All I want is to feel this way To be this close, to feel the same All I want is to feel this way The evening speaks I feel insane To feel so close Let it take me in Let it hold me so I can feel insane    Pertinence  : One of the few songs I think as beautiful, this song. It's haunting. I listened to it a long time ago, picked it up again in mid-December. And "You won't trouble me" was my favorite line when I started listening to it again, guess why...    Hold Me Down  by Gin Blossoms  So I guess I must have just been dreaming  When I thought I heard myself say no  Anyway it looks like no one heard me  So here I go  Cause when you're in the company of strangers Or just the strangers you call friends  You know before you start just how it's  Going to end   When the doors swing open  And all the drinks are passed around  Anytime the pickins look too easy  Hold me down   I can't remember why I like this feeling  When it only seems to let me down  Soon I find I'm searching for the exit  From the ground  If I think the room is turning faster  Then I think the music is too loud  By then I've lived another broken story  To let me down   When those doors swing open  And all the drinks are passed around  When half the party moves into the bathroom  Hold me down  Or if you're at the tail end of the evening  And Dr. Feelgood comes around  Anytime the pickins look too easy  Hold me down   Down if I want that part  Down if I've gone too far   Well I guess I must have just been reeling  When I felt myself begin to fall I realize I'm bounding down the hallways  And off the walls  If my bed was standing in the corner  I could just fall into it right now  And know that I'd just be staring at the ceiling  Going round   When those doors swing open  And all the drinks are passed around  Anytime the pickins look too easy  Hold me down  Down if I want that part Down if I've gone too far    Pertinence  : It's a happy song about drinking and partying. That's why it's so great. Picked up about the end of November, along with  Lost Horizons  and  Until I Fall Away .    Poem  by Taproot  Overbearing panic attack Entrenching my veins In an hour I'll be ok And pray this pain will go away Permanently someday  I've seen more than I should have to I've seen this on my own  This song is a poem to myself It helps me to live In case of fire Break the glass And move on into your own Your own  Reoccuring drowning effect Entrench my brain I hope you'll be ok someday So I can say That you moved on in the right way  We've seen this and We've breathed this and We've lived this on our own  This song is a poem to myself It helps me to live In case of fire Break the glass  And move on into your own This song is a poem to myself It helps me to live In case of fire Break the glass  And move on into your own Your own, your own  Break  This song is a poem to myself It helps me to live In case of fire Break the glass  And move on into your own This song is a poem to myself It helps me to live In case of fire Break the glass  And move on into your own Your own, your own, your own    Pertinence  : Well, their "pain" sounds pop-theme inspired, and that's how I always felt mine was, just drawing off things I've seen. And that's why I connected with this song. Picked up at the first of January.    Died  by Alice in Chains  I could climb until I reached where angels reside Ask around to find out where the junkie apply You just up and left me on this rock all alone It's my fault for knowing not what I should have known  Oh, my heart is tired of beating slow It's been deflating since you  Died Died You died You died  I could drop until I touched a sinister side Visit all attractions slipping back at a slide Still you leave me rotting on this rock all alone It's my fault for knowing not what I should have known  Oh, my heart is tired of beating slow It's been deflating since you  Died Died You died You died  Oh, my heart is tired of beating slow It's been deflating since you  Died Died You died You died Died Died You died You died  I could climb until I reached where angel reside I could drop until I touched a sinister side  Oh, my heart is tired of beating slow It's been deflating since you  Died Died  You died You died Died Died You died You died    Pertinence  : It's a cool song, it was the anthem of my headbangage at the beginning of August when all the weird stuff was happening. That was when the depresion first started, I think, and this song made it worse, but I listened to it anyway. And now's it just hardcore    Lost Horizons  by Gin Blossoms  The last horizons I can see Are filled with bars and factories And in them all we fight to stay awake  I'd drink enough of anything To make this world look new again I'm drunk drunk drunk in the gardens and the graves  She had nothing left to say So she said she loved me And I stood there grateful for the lie  I'd drink enough of anything To make this world look new again I'm drunk drunk drunk in the gardens and the graves  Turns summer trees to bones and ice Turn insect songs against the night With words we build and words we break I'm drunk drunk drunk in the gardens and the graves  Maybe I could use you To reassure myself I wouldn't wish this indecision On anybody else I'd drink enough of anything To make this world look new And when the sin smiles How can it be wrong  The last horizons I can see Are now resigned to memories I never thought I'd still be here today  I'd drink enough of anything To make myself look new again I'm drunk drunk drunk in the gardens and the graves    Pertinence  : Picked up the day before Thanksgiving, I was sitting there listening to this, driving by the Capitol park, and thinking, "what the hell am I doing to myself", whereafter things worked out. I credit this song with the inspiration to say all the right things.    Until I Fall Away  by Gin Blossoms  I wanna tell if I am or I am not myself It's hard to know how far or if at all to go I've waited far too long for something I forgot was wrong  I don't know all the answers Things that I'll find Won't have it within the time But it's all that I'll have in mind  Until I fall away That won't keep us waiting long Until I fall away I don't know what to do anymore Until I fall away  My fear, pretend, that I'll never be in love again It's real to me, but not like these fools and not like this scene I won't find, or have it within the time  If it's all rusted and fade in the spot where we fell Where I thought I'd left behind And it's loose now but we could try  Until I fall away That won't keep us waiting long Until I fall away I don't know what to do anymore Until I fall away  When there's no good answer To those new questions Another personal disaster There's nowhere to go but down  Until I fall away That won't keep us waiting long  Until I fall away I don't know what to do anymore Until I fall away...    Pertinence  : UMMMM. Read the song again, please? Manic depressive central, holding on to a dream that's fading. Picked up at the same time as  Lost Horizons  and  Hey Jealousy , I actually did an acoustic cover of this song that turned out pretty good. The only song that ever puts my depression in words.    Chemical Tribe  by Jerry Cantrell  If I live so long To see 'em droppin' bombs Rather have you near Check out what comes after here Ah here What comes after here  Generation turned a chemical tribe Don't really care if we live or die Generation turned a chemical tribe It's a lie and it's no surprise, die  Let the black odds roll Why we can't tell Crawl inside Rolling over, is this hell? Is this hell?  Generation turned a chemical tribe Don't really care if we live or die Generation turned a chemical tribe It's a lie I can tell you why  No last supper rite Bitchslapped 'fore you reached the table Born in ending times Leaning more toward Cain than Able No last supper rite Bitchslapped 'fore you reach the table Born in ending times Possibly more truth than fable  Generation turned a chemical tribe Generation turned a chemical tribe Generation turned a chemical tribe Generation turned a chemical tribe It's alive, so say goodbye  No last supper rite Bitchslapped 'fore you reached the table Born in ending times Leaning more toward Cain than Able No last supper rite Bitchslapped 'fore you reach the table Born in ending times Possibly more truth than fable No last supper rite Bitchslapped 'fore you reached the table Born in ending times Leaning more toward Cain than Able  Bitchslapped 'fore you reach the table Could it be more truth than fable?    Pertinence  : It's a really scary song. I was listening to it in those dark endless days in October or so, when we all went to Firehouse that one time, that was about when I was listening to it. And it was killing me because it made me feel like dying, and got me really afraid for some reason, but I could never put it down. And now it just sounds cool.    Dam That River  by Alice in Chains  I clothed you in the canyon I drowned you in the lake You would think that I would tremble Only thing I'd not embrace  Oh you couldn't dam that river And maybe I don't give a damn anyway So you couldn't dam that river And it washed me so far away  I pushed and then you stumbled I kicked you in the face You stared at me so humble Got to keep that killing pace  Oh you couldn't dam that river And maybe I don't give a damn anyway So you couldn't dam that river And it washed me so far away  I burned the place around you I hit you with a rake You piss upon my candle So proving you're a fake  Oh you couldn't dam that river And maybe I don't give a damn anyway So you couldn't dam that river And it washed me so far away    Pertinence  : A hard hitting song, it came to me at the midst of August when I started having problems with my parents. There's nothing like listening to this song and kicking your door in, which I did. Plus, the line "You piss upon my candle"...wonder where I got it from now?    Mrs. Rita  by Gin Blossoms  I can see it in her letters On the paper with her pen Her response is getting stranger Think she's coming 'round again So tell me Mrs. Rita What's it say in my tarot Read my palm and tell me Why do lovers come and go  Is she comin' 'round for me once again Around, or was that the end and I just hope she's coming 'round again  Well I've been keeping myself busy With my books and with my tapes And everyday's much better Since I've slowed my drinking pace There's no swimmin' in the bottle It's just someplace we all drown And I lost myself in sorrow I lost my confidence in doubt  Is she comin' 'round for me once again Around, or was that the end and I just hope she's comin' 'round again  Get in the car and drive to town Down the block and back around Pretending that she's there with me, we drive Gone forever  Well my patience keeps me plaintive My high hopes keep me alone My lover's will is shakin' I wish she would just come home So tell me Mrs. Rita What's it say in my tarot Read my palm and tell me Why do lovers come and go  Is she comin' 'round for me once again Around, or was that the end and I just hope she's comin' 'round again Is she comin' 'round for me once again Around, or was that the end and I just hope she's comin' 'round again  I just hope she's comin' 'round I just hope she's comin' 'round I just hope she's comin' 'round I just hope she's comin' 'round I just hope she's comin' 'round I just hope she's comin' 'round I just hope she's comin' 'round    Pertinence  : When I started to figure out, "hey, I dunno what it's like to love someone like this", this song came into play. Me wondering if I was doing anything right, and starting in on the depression again, looking for an answer when there isn't one.    I'm With You  by Avril Lavigne  I'm standing on a bridge  I'm waitin' in the dark  I thought that you'd be here by now  There's nothing but the rain  No footsteps on the ground  I'm listening but there's no sound   Isn't anyone tryin' to find me Won't somebody come take me home   It's a damn cold night  Trying to figure out this life  Won't you take me by the hand  Take me somewhere new  I dont know who you are  But I I'm with you   I'm looking for a place  Searching for a face  Is anybody here I know  Cuz nothing's going right  And everything's a mess  And no one likes to be alone   Isn't anyone tryin' to find me Won't somebody come take me home   It's a damn cold night  Trying to figure out this life  Won't you take me by the hand  Take me somewhere new  I don't know who you are  But I I'm with you   Oh, why is everything so confusing  Maybe I'm just out of my mind  Yea, yea, yea, yea, yeah   It's a damn cold night  Trying to figure out this life  Won't you take me by the hand  Take me somewhere new  I don't know who you are  But I  I'm with you, I'm with you   Take me by the hand  Take me somewhere new  I don't know who you are  But I I'm with you, I'm with you  Take me by the hand  Take me somewhere new  I don't know who you are  But I I'm with you, I'm with you, I'm with you    Pertinence  : It's just a really peaceful song, the first time I heard it, it got stuck in my head. Yeah yeah, she's a poser, but the song is still nice. And I said it was going to go somewhere, I had a lot of space left over, so I stuck it in. Picked up about three days ago from this post.    Got Me Wrong  by Alice in Chains  Yeah, it goes away All of this and more of nothing in my life No color clay Individuality not safe  As of now I think you've got me wrong So I'm sure you run from something strong  I can't let go Threadbare tapestry unwinding slow Feel a tortured brain Show your belly like you want me to  As of now I bet you got me wrong So I'm sure we reach for something strong I haven't felt like this in so long Wrong, innocence too far gone from love That don't last forever Something's gotta turn out right  You, sugar taste Sweetness doesn't often touch my face Stay if you please You may not be here when I leave  As of now I think you got me wrong So I'm sure we reach for something strong I haven't felt like this in so long Wrong, innocence too far gone from love Strong, I haven't felt like this in so long Wrong, innocence too far gone from love That don't last forever Something's gotta turn out right    Pertinence  : Well, this song is about me, I think. "You've got me wrong", I think I was really misunderstood during the "bleeding months", like why I was killing myself over shit that was well within my control. And "reach for something strong", find another thing to solve my problems, like talking to others about it, to find that ultimate "answer". "I can't let go"...:Individuality not safe". A good summary of my changing personality during the last six months.   Happy Happy Joy Joy  by Wax  Happy happy joy joy...  Hello boys and girls, this is your old pal Stinky Whizzleteets, and this is a song about a whale! No! This is a song about being happy! That's right! It's the "Happy Happy Joy Joy" song.  Happy happy joy joy Happy happy joy joy Happy happy joy joy Happy happy joy joy Happy happy joy joy Happy happy joy joy Happy happy joy joy joy  Happy happy happy happy happy happy happy happy joy Joy  Happy happy happy happy happy happy happy happy joy Joy  I don't think you're happy enough I'll teach you to be happy And I'll teach your grandma to suck eggs  Now, boys and girls Let's try again  You are granted that we're all liars The little critters of nature They don't know that they're ugly  That's very funny  Happy happy joy joy Happy happy joy joy Happy happy joy joy Happy happy joy joy Happy happy joy joy Happy happy joy joy Happy happy joy joy joy  JOY Hey hey hey  Happy Joy Happy Joy Happy Joy  You are granted that we're all liars The little critters of nature They don't know that they're ugly  That's very funny  Happy Joy Happy, joy, happy Joy  Like a fly marrying a bumblebee I told you to shoot but you wouldn't believe me Why didn't you believe me? WHY? Why didn't you believe me? AUUUUGGGGGGGHHHHHHHH    Pertinence  : This is mostly for Kenzie, it's the funniest song ever. We were both sorta depressed and talking about cartoons, and I mentioned I had this CD with  Happy Happy Joy Joy  on it. So I went and got it, and listened to it...GOD. The end is the best part, the little "AUUUUGGGGGGGHHHHHHHH" is quite possibly the greatest part of any song, ever. We listened to it about 130495243750475294 times and were feeling much better after it. Picked up at the midst of January.    My Solution  by Stranglebox  Asylum was the answer The opened doors and let me in And told me time was not unmaking  They told me I could finally win I seek now retribution Raised my eyes and then I saw The steel and lonesome of my prison Bang my head against the stone cold floor  Now that there is no good escape Now that there's nothing more than just walking far away Now that there is no level plane My solution, sell my soul to the end and fade me away  Silence now my reason I sat alone inside myself I gave the all that I had in me They stole my life and gave me hell Addiction was the cancer And God, the price I paid And slowly dying I surrendered My poisoned soul as it fades to gray  Now that there is no good escape Now that there's nothing more than just walking far away Now that there is no level plane My solution, sell my soul to the end and fade me away, yeah  Now that there is no good escape Now that there's nothing more than just walking far away Now that there is no level plane My solution, sell my soul to the end and fade me away  Now that there is no good escape Now that there's nothing more than just walking far away Now that I've laid my life to waste My solution, sell my soul to the end and fade me away My solution, I'm gonna find out the only way to escape And my solution, that I break free from the cage    Pertinence  : Well, one part of the story is, I wrote it. And the other part is, it happened to me. This is the summary of rejection and depression throughout the span of these six months, and I called it  My Solution . It's about suicide, if you haven't noticed. Being trapped to one part of myself and finding no other way to leave it, knowing what is wrong for me, and doing it anyway. This is the song I wrote for just that, for just not making the cut, for just not being on the level to get what I wanted. And the only way to get myself away from it was to end myself.  The song was written in early September and finished in October or November. It took a few months of work to nail, and it was a really agonizing process. After that, we took a long break; we're back now recording  Little Rhyme , still getting it down, along with  Bitter  and  After Memory Has Faded . It should be finished sometime at the end of summer, there's going to be about a session a day then.  Don't ask how long this took. Suffice to say, HOURS.   Enjoy when you get it. I'll put a link in the template to this day so you can go back and read the lyrics in the future.  Whoo.
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      josh see my blog asap haha you were wrong
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Jeezus, everyone's got mono these days.  Umm well, what's new...  The future that was full of potential is now full of uncertainty, for a lot of reasons. I'm worried that Kenzie is turning in to me, she sounds  just  like I have the past few weeks.  I had a thought, you may think someone's tortures are pathetic and stupid, but be a human and help them. That was very philanthropic, but it seems like everyone who has a pathetic problem is casted off as such, and were we to do this, we would be no better than animals...I think it's time to change the focus a little.  Happy Chinese New Year's Eve.  I just got finished burning POOR BASTARD VOLUME ONE (AUGUST 2002-JANUARY 2003). And it is GREAT and REALLY different from the first intended, this actually encompasses a much broader scope than the end of August, it strectches into the really bad part of the beginning of August, lots of weird stuff happening, parental conflicts, et cetera, mega depressed, which is why the stuff at the end of August started happening.   There's a lot I haven't talked about yet. Ask me sometime.  AND NOW, THE FINAL TRACKLIST, lyrics when I feel like it, there's 17 songs.   POOR BASTARD VOLUME ONE (AUGUST 2002-JANUARY 2003)  -------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- I. Blood Brothers - Papa Roach II. Hey Jealousy - Gin Blossoms III. Sorrowful Farewell - Rotting Christ IV. For Whom The Bell Tolls - Metallica V. All I Want - Toad the Wet Sprocket VI. Hold Me Down VII. Poem - Taproot VIII. Died - Alice in Chains IX. Lost Horizons - Gin Blossoms X. Until I Fall Away - Gin Blossoms XI. Chemical Tribe - Jerry Cantrell XII. Dam That River - Alice in Chains XIII. Mrs. Rita - Gin Blossoms XIV. I'm With You - Avril Lavigne XV.Got Me Wrong - Alice in Chains XVI. Happy Happy Joy Joy - Wax XVII. My Solution - Stranglebox (our current band name)  Vanilla Coke makes me depressed now.  I'll post a short description of the pertinence of each post with the lyrics.  And let's see if this thing posts, because my dad's computer sux today.
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey, Rosie, just a question.  Why do you care?  I for one am perfectly happy in my lack of social standing.  I have thought of this subject before, however, and have decided that I don't care.  And since when do I fit the mold?  I'm one example.  There have to be others.  Linds, maybe.    No smiling.  This I order.  ;( hehehe  ~Z  P.S. What interview?
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hey people, SO Joah...why is it so important that you hate Gunter. Can you do me a fave and let it just be.  Have you realized how fake our society is. I mean think about it.....the whole world believes that everyone has there place and if they leave it......here comes the tidal waves. Crossing social barriers in BHS is next to impossible without whispers and stares. Is this what they call America, the most welcome country? Everyone plays to the role untill that role is all they have, so they stick to that role through life then pass it to there children. Ugg why can't people be themselves. Why can't people NOT fit the mold for once?  Smile all, life's great.  oh and the interview went well
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, not much to say.  Apparently Linds has mono...which really sucks.  I still can't think of anything worthwhile so I will leave you now.  See you on Monday but I will probably post again before then.  ~Z  
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Agh, I had a huge post last night explaining about Poor Bastard 2 last night, then my computer froze. GOD.  I posted the new track list to Poor Bastard 1, which includes Gin Blossoms (a lot of 'em), Rotting Christ, Taproot, Alice in Chains, Metallica, Papa Roach, Nirvana, Wax, myself...mostly Gin Blossoms.  Now the second one, like I was trying to say, is going to have a lot of the stuff I left out the first time.  A few more from  New Miserable Experience ,  Cheatin'  if it's not on this one, and  Cajun Song . Plus one from  Congratulations I'm Sorry ,  Competetion Smile , which I typed down, and NOW IT'S GONE.  And Alice and Metallica, say  We Die Young  or something off of  Sap  or something really hardcore, and  Dirt , of course, for Alice, and  My Friend of Misery  for Metallica, say.  Definitely more Jerry this time,  Give It A Name , and  Dickeye . There are two others that are really good, but I can't stand to listen to them anymore, they get me really depressed for some reason,  Breaks My Back  and  My Song . They're good, but I'm not going to put them on any of these.  I posted Toad once, so I'll put that song on it,  I Will Not Take These Things For Granted . What a change from the other songs, it's... peaceful .  And the Avril Lavigne song,  I'm With You , and Soundgarden's  Outshined .  I wanted to put  Glory of Sadness  by Roting Christ on the first one, but it's long, four minutes of music, like nine minutes of silence, and a weird outro for about two minutes. So I'm going to find a way to cut it down and then I'll put it on there. Plus  Khronos , it's not a lyrically pertinent song, it just makes me feel weird when I listen to it.  If you noticed, the full title of the first one is  Poor Bastard Volume One, August 2002-January 2003 , so that's about six months or so. I probably won't wait that long on the next one, it just depends on how quick I find about sixteen songs that mean something. I really also want to wait 'til Alex and I get  Little Rhyme  recorded, so we can put one of our own on every one of these things... My Solution 's on the first one, the last track because it's SOOOOOOOOO special.  One will be ready as soon as I get to my dad's today.  Well, I was gonna post a ton of those songs and then it bombed, and I really don't want to right now, I have the whole night ahead of me, and it's a free period in school right now.   I will restate my threat, GUNTER I AM GOING TO FUCKING END YOU. You'd reallllllllyyyyyy better apply what you say to yourself before you say it. I called him a dickhead in first today, Rosie comes back and says he said the same about me last night. This dude has too much arrogance blinding him. At least when I'm being an asshole I figure it out eventually. This guy fucking  never  will. I'm not really concerned, it's just the fact that he called me as he did and knows absolutely nothing about me, firstly, nor have I done anything like he's doing. I know his kind well enough, plus his exploits equal asshole, so that's where I get it from.  Why the hell am I wasting my energy...  HEYY it's the 31st today, I thought it was yesterday...heh oops.  Well, I get to go home today and play Counterstrike, that should be fun. Then I get to cry a lil' more here, and burn a few CDs. And other stuff.  I don't have cable at my dad's anymore, him and his bitching about not having money left over after bills, what he has still gets him by, and  trust me , he doesn't NEED anything else, you can find ANYTHING in "The Hole". God, well, he'll get it back in about a week when he realizes how much he misses it.  "I Hate Myself And Want To Die" by Nirvana...what a great song title.  And with this, I bid you adieu.   Cajun Song  by Gin Blossoms  Well she's leaving today I do know So far away I'm feeling so blue and it shows In every single way Once that girl, she was mine For such a short time We used to spend every night Now all I do is cry  They say that you can't miss Something that you've never had So tell me why Why I could feel so bad  Well we used to walk down the path Just like lovers do She'd hold my hands and we'd laugh And I'd stare in her eyes, they were blue Once that girl, she was mine For such a short time We used to spend every night Now all I do is cry  They say that you can't miss Something that you've never had So tell me why Why I could feel so bad Why I could feel so bad Why I could feel so bad   Ok, a little corny, but it's a driving song.   We Die Young  by Alice in Chains Scary's on the wall Scary's on his way Watch where you spit But I'd advise you wait until it's over Then you got hit And you should've know better  And we die young Faster we run  Down down down you're rollin' Watch the blood flood to the muddy sewer Take another hit And bury your brother  And we die young Faster we run  Scary's on the wall Scary's on his way Another alley trip Bullets seek the place to bend you over Then you got hit And you should've know better  Faster we run And we die young   Whee, I'm on a roll.   Competetion Smile  by Gin Blossoms  Looking up I saw nothing but  Blue in the bluest sky And now it's creeping across my eye And falling down in my mind Down in my mind I'm high and I'm hopeless so Help me to get untied Fast asleep now I'm going blind And falling down in my mind Down in my mind just fine  Emulate the style A competetion smile  Now I'm running not looking and Opening up my brain Where it's easy to lose my name Looking dumb in the rain Dumb in the rain I'm hoping you'll notice that No one else helps me grow Oh it's not easy to let you know What I'm dying to show Dying to know you'll know  Pretending all the while A competetion smile  Now I've thrown something far And it haunts me like a curse I'm like a stone falling hard And I'm only getting worse  Looking up I saw nothing but Blue in the bluest sky And now it's creeping across my eye And falling down in my mind Down in my mind I'm high and I'm hopeless so Help me to get untied Fast asleep now I'm going blind And falling down in my mind Down in my mind just fine  Pretending all the while A competetion smile  I'm hiding high I'm hiding high   The story of my life in that song.   Hold Me Down  by Gin Blossoms  So I guess I must have just been dreaming When I thought I heard myself say no Anyway it looks like no one heard me  So here I go Cause when you're in the company of strangers  Or just the strangers you call friends You know before you start just how it's  Going to end  When the doors swing open  And all the drinks are passed around Anytime the pickins look too easy Hold me down  I can't remember why I like this feeling  When it only seems to let me down Soon I find I'm searching for the exit  From the ground If I think the room is turning faster Then I think the music is too loud By then I've lived another broken story to let me down  When those doors swing open  And all the drinks are passed around When half the party moves into the bathroom  Hold me down Or if you're at the tail end of the evening  And Dr. Feelgood comes around Anytime the pickins look too easy Hold me down  Down if I want that part Down if I've gone too far  Well I guess I must have just been reeling When I felt myself begin to fall I realize I'm bounding down the hallways  And off the walls If my bed was standing in the corner  I could just fall into it right now And know that I'd just be staring at the ceiling  Going round  When those doors swing open  And all the drinks are passed around Anytime the pickins look too easy  Hold me down   They're so drunk, I love 'em.   My Friend Of Misery  by Metallica  You just stood there screaming Feeling no one would listen to you They say the empty can rattles the most The sound of your own voice must soothe you Hearing only what you wanna hear And knowing only what you heard You, you're smothered in tragedy And you're off the save the world  Misery You insist that the weight of the world Should be on your shoulders Misery There's much more to life than what you see My friend of misery  You still stood there screaming No one caring about these words you tell My friend, before your voice is gone One man's fun is another's hell These times are sent to try men's souls And something wrong with all you see You, you'll take it on all yourself Remember, misery loves company  Misery You insist that the weight of the world Should be on your shoulders Misery There's much more to life that what you see My friend of misery, my friend of misery  Misery You insist that the weight of the world Should be on your shoulders Misery There's much more to life that what you see My friend of misery  You just stood there screaming, oh My friend of misery   'Tis beautiful.  Motivation is cool.  And that, friends, is the end.
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You shouldn't feel shame, Josh.  At least one person will be standing with you...me.  I like Avril Lavigne.  No problem here. I like that song, too.  If you want ME to post it, I will to alleviate your feelings of shame.  I wouldn't say I'm shameless, but maybe more so than you in this case.  When will PB 1, 2, etc. be available?  I want one!  Or two or however many!  ;)  See you people tomorrow.  And what am I, Bureaucrat?  I think so.  I have escaped the vacuum that is Walt.  ~Z  
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Heh, Switzerland is cool, my neighbor is from Switzerland.  At least her ancestors were.  I made a post yesterday, but it didn't come through. AGH, there was a great song in there,  Outshined  by Soundgarden. That was how I was feeling yesterday, I'll post it again, it needs to go on PB2. And...umm....  I've got a stupidish song stuck in my head that I'll probably post here (if I can choke down the shame) and put on the second CD, it's an....uh......Avril Lavigne song.....put those rocks down... I'm With You , I feel like I've heard it a long time ago, perhaps some song that someone else did that sounds a lot like it. Or psychic foresight.   I was really tired last night, I shouldn'tve had those two Cokes yesterday. One, en moderato, two, in x s. Sweet.   "Heya Gunter what's going on? crowbarSMACK" FIGHTFIGHTFIGHT  Josh sees the deeper surfaces........Rosie.........so be careful when you say  I'm  wrong about Asshole (capitalized to denote a person). Am I actually good about seeing underlying intentions and just don't know it? Hmm, maybe SOME PEOPLE have been giving me the wrong idea, "No no you're wrong,"...you know who you are.  Vincent? Might need to explain that one a little.  Time for  Outshined .   Outshined  by Soundgarden  I got up feeling so down I got off being sold out I've kept the movie rolling But the story's getting old now Oh yeah  Well I just looked in the mirror And things aren't looking so good I'm looking California And feeling Minnesota Oh yeah  So now you know Who gets mystified So now you know Who gets mystified  Show me the power child I'd like to say That I'm down on my knees today Ooh it gives me the butterflies Gives me away 'Til I'm up on my feet again  I'm feeling outshined Ooh I'm feeling outshined outshined outshined  Someone let the dogs out They'll show you where the truth is The grass is always greener Where the dogs are shedding Oh yeah  I'm feeling that I'm sober Even though I'm drinking And I can't get any lower Still I feel I'm sinking Oh yeah  So now you know Who gets mystified So now you know Who gets mystified  Show me the power child I'd like to say That I'm down on my knees today Ooh it gives me the butterflies Gives me away 'Til I'm back on my feet again  I'm feeling outshined Ooh I'm feeling outshined outshined outshined  (arbitrary "ooh"ing and "outshined"s for an interlude)  So now you know  Who gets mystified So now you know Who gets mystified  Show me the power child I'd like to say That I'm down on my knees today Ooh it gives me the butterflies Gives me away 'Til I'm back on my feet again  I'm feeling outshined Ooh I'm feeling outshined outshined outshined  Show me the power child I'd like to say That I'm down on my knees today Ooh it gives me the butterflies Give me away 'Til I'm back on my feet again  I'm feeling outshined Ooh I'm feeling outshined outshined outshined  Godddddddd, I would do  I'm With You  if it weren't for the shame of being in school and having everyone watch me look at Avril Lavigne lyrics. This doesn't happen often, but even still....while it is.  PURE TORTURE, I haven't heard it in about three days. So it'll be stuck for a long time. I have to quit cold turkey.  Simply not listening is like really weak methadone.
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Really, I am coming.  It's just taking me awhile.  I should be there by third period, I think.
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yeah, Liz, Switzerland...Real Good...I hadn't thought about that until Jackie posted on my blog.  Then it all came back.  See you tomorrow...I"M COMING BACK!!!!  Almost excited...
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Indeed I do remember that, Linds.  And even though I know very little of that story, I believe that there are some definite similarities.    Josh, I really have to say thanks for calling me "the wisest" earlier on in the lifespan of this site.  That was really sweet.  I have no experience in these kinds of problems, as some of my friends can't help reminding me about, so I will not get involved.  I have read the entire thing so far and I just want to be here if you need help, ok, Josh?  I shalt pass no judgement.  I am Switzerland, the neutral party in this war.    Okay, bad...metaphor? but get over it.  It's just my way.  See you all in Scumbucket tomorrow.  ;)  ~Z 
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ugh.  Not again.  Well, just let me know what the new address is.  There's no advice on this post, notice.  I'm restraining myself.  By the way, do you know Jackie... [Disclaimer for Leigh's sake: Jackie is engaged so there is no possibility of there being competition.] This whole thing reminds me of her thing with Vincent.  Do you remember that, Elizabeth?  If you do, you'll see the similiarity.  [Second Disclaimer because I always tend to get things wrong: If Leigh happens not to like Josh at this particular moment, please don't bitch me out]
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      so is the addy changing again?
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Josh, IM SORRY!!!! I didn't mean for her to see it! I didn't mean for her to get angry at you and stab your balls with your drumsticks. Im SORRY! *cries* I didn't mean it. I Swear. *kicks Josh* Why don't you liike Ray? The one we met at the library?! He's AWESOME! And so adorable and cute and tall, and NICE. Anywho, SORRY!!!!!
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well here's the last post on badvision...  Lily was editing it at the library, Leigh Anne looked over her shoulder, boom. That was the end of it.  So let me say something.  Friends understand each other, they understand why others do things, and they are quick to forgive. Friends want friends around, and if they really don't, then they really don't want to be friends at all. Something, but not friends.  And friends listen to others. Perhaps the answers we're all looking for lie in the ones were ignoring, probably because they're right. I know this, I have found this several times.  I know who my friends are.  I know what I don't understand.  I know that if this understanding is to come, it's on the part of the thing not understood.  I have seen my mistakes.  I've tried to fix them.  I cannot.  Because they never die.  The funny thing about any problem I have is, none of them are bad at all anymore. The thing is, they're just so well timed. Things are good for me and suddenly it's a one-two punch and it all falls down again, I think it's not going to be that way for much longer, I see myself looking at these things as no surprise, and with no more surprises, they'll just stop happening.  I revamped the song  Bitter  for the third time see what you can get out of the first lines: "Where did my sunshine go, I think it's ever-fade"...if that tells you anything.  Play with fire and you get burned, though, that's the way the cookie crumbles, the ball drops, the bee stings, one two three whee. I should've seen this coming, if it's public access it's bound to end up that way.  But I hope you all know why I made the posts I did, I hope you all know why I do these things, and I think you do.  Because if not, just leave off of me.  And again I turn the page.
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      joah..........how did it happen AGAIN? 
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hmm someone's pissed.
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      JOSH, guess who found it?
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      GUESS WHO'S READING THE BLOG RIGHT NOW SITTING RIGHT NEXT TO ME?  AGHHH WHY DOES THIS ALWAYS HAPPEN? AND SHE'S READ ABOUT EVERYTHING IN HERE SO FAR.  So great, I'm trying to find a way to get her away, any suggestions? Please?  It smells like burnt...something in here.  And I am FUCKED.  FUCKED.  That's right.   FuCkEd.  fUCKED.  FuCKeD.
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hahaha.  Remember when things weren't so complicated? That was fun.  There's fun in this, just weird fun. O well o well.  Je vais aller a la bibliotheque aujourd'hui, dans Nashville. Ce vais etre super, c'est la premier rendezvous avec la jeune fille qui a la nom Leigh Anne. Zut...je ne crois pas si je veux faire la rendezvous. J'ai peur. Mais, c'est la vie.  (I am going to go to the library today, in Nashville. This is going to be great, it's the first meeting with the little girl who is named Leigh Anne. Damn...I don't know if I am able to do it. I'm scared. But, that's life.)  Why did I do that, I dunno. I wanted to test mon technique de francais. I'm did for shit in that class last nine weeks.  And I get to meet Kenzie's friend that likes me, Laurie, heh she even asked me out last night, she's seen the "bird" picture, apparently, but she didn't know that was me when she did. So that's going to be fascinating.   But god, I couldn't believe it, how quick she was. "I need to get to know you better" and I knew it right then. And then later I flashed over to talk to Leigh Anne and I flashed back, and Kenzie was like, Laurie wants to know if you're available, and I was like, yah sure. I really hope she's not serious.  She's a redhead, I hear.  Godddddddd......  This could be a fucking  BAD  trip. Or good. But I don't know.   Do I ever?
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Let me start the second part of this long, long night with a song, because it IS going to be long, already.   Iris  by the Goo Goo Dolls  And I'd give up forever to touch you Cuz I know that you feel me somehow You're the closest to heaven that I'll ever be And I don't wanna go home right now And I can taste is this moment And all I can breathe is your life And sooner or later it's over I just don't wanna miss you tonight  And I don't want the world to see me Cuz I don't think that they'd understand When everything's made to be broken I just want you to know who I am  And you can't fight the tears that ain't coming Or the moment of truth in your lies When everything feels like the movies Yeah, you bleed just to know you're alive  And I don't want to world to see me Cuz I don't think that they'd understand When everything's made to be broken I just want you to know who I am  (interlude)  And I don't want the world to see me Cuz I don't think that they'd understand When everything's made to be broken I just want you to know who I am I just want you to know who I am I just want you to know who I am  I was thinking of this song because of a few things: I started thinking about Zoe's Blurty, and in that you can be affiliated with certain groups of common interests. One of them was for cutting and understand why they do it, and also to help them get over it. There were a few quotes from songs in there that relate to it, and one of them was:  Yeah, you bleed just to know you're alive . So I thought about that. Then today, I was taking a nap and I remembered it and resolved to post it here. It sounds just like me.  I used to realllllllllllyyyyyy like the Goo Goo Dolls, I haven't listened to them in a while though. I guess I'll be picking that one back up soon.  Iris  shall be on Poor Bastard Vol. 2 (and yes, the first one's official title is Poor Bastard Vol. 1, Aug 2002 - Jan 2003, the list is a little different since Tinblogged got deleted and that was the only place I put it).  And now to the pressing matter.  It seems that one of Kenzie's friends wants to go out with me. I brought it up with Leigh Anne and she was like, "Well at least it'll get you off my back," and I said, "Oh no, you can't shake me that easy," and she was like, "Damn,". Ok.  But the thing is, it was really half-hearted, to the point where even I could take it that way, and second, when she's trying to shake me off, she'll use the phrase, "Just move on,".   I need some interpretations, by the way: "It's going to be really funny when you find out you don't care about me." and "You lied; you said you loved me."  Actually, I know what they both are quintessentially, "I want attention", the Leigh Anne fling. It's amazing how desperately she needs it.  But right now she's talking to Brittany, and Brittany has a lot of sway over her, whether she'd like to admit it or not.  It's going to be a long night. This would've been longer had she not called back just now.  ARGH.  I'm weird, but my shirt smells really good right now.  HeeHAW.
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      okay. The little note of goodbye was what I did to xi. Deal with it. I didn't want to go in circles and I really seemed that you hated me and wanted me gone. I didn't want to "defy" you so I left, for now. You know the Xi story.   Anyway. Yeah about Gunter I get what you're saying. Gunter is out of the picture now forever. He's out of it too so don't take anything to heart. 
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok Rosie, the biggest thing that pisses me off about Gunter.  The fact that you say you're all over him and so is he. And that fact that he says so and is being so fake...well...I just can't take fakeness, or arrogance, which he has in abundance. Like today when he called Alex stupid for not knowing a Calculus problem. He's probably the only geekass on the fucking planet that knows the answer to that. And then he jibed at him. Alex was just doing it for fun, but Gunter didn't have to react like he did, "I'm better than you because I'm a senior and I know more math stuff and you can piss off and suck me you underling". SO GAY. I wanted to fucking BLAST him today. And I wanted to throw the Gilgamesh box at you too for being all "HEHEHE" at him.  Yet I  know  he isn't over it (I was like him a long time ago, the "sutble flirt"), and if you're being all overly nice to him and trying to get into his head like you are he's going to take it the wrong way.  I can't tell you to stop, because I wouldn't listen either in that situation.  But I'm telling you to look to the horizon so as to prevent the present from closing in.
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      And two more things.  I found Camille's (my new kitty's) purr spot today. Whee.  And Lindsey, the word that encompasses it all:  FEAR.
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      To Lily (adendum):  Does she really? I really don't know.  Every time I bring up the point that you've said something along those lines, she's like "You really believe her?" and actually...I do. Most of the time I think it's just me clinging on to a crumbling ledge, but maybe you really are right. Idon'tknowIdon'tknowIdon'tknow. I don't know. I think she does myself.   But then I tell myself, that's just what you want to think, not what really is.   I wish she would just find one she could confide in, that would make things a lot easier for me.  But who said it was going to be easy?
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      To Lindsey:   I don't expect advice, but if it needs to be given, I'd really like to hear it.  And sorry for being crazy, I don't blame you or Rosie for that matter.  Paul? You'll need to tell me about that.
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, here I sit again.  "Uh oh" you say, you go and grab a drink because you know this is going to be one of  those . You sit back and stare blankly at the screen, letting a bit of spit fall from your open jaws as you sort through this post and get the message: "I wanna bitch". It's the same one tenfold, but for some reason there's something new to get out of it every time.  I'm not intending for this one to be long. Which means it probably will be.  I want you all to know, especially Lindsey, that you all did  not  screw up my life. Let me see if I can retell this plainly.  Leigh Anne called back shortly after Rosie to ask for Brittany's phone number. After a while she handed the phone to Lily. Lily's mom picked up and told her to get off because she needed to use it, whereafter she didn't use it. But anyway, Lily put down the phone and forgot about it.  Meanwhile, I set up this BLog and posted that one at the bottom in Kenzie's, where, shortly after, I deleted it, for reasons that will become apparent in a few lines here.  I had a silent line for 93 minutes before Lily noticed the phone off the hook and picked it up, whereupon she said "Hello?" and I said, "Umm...hi,"...there was a round of laughs, then Leigh Anne was inspired to talk to me and say that she was upset with me and didn't hate me anymore. After a minute, she told me they were setting up a tent and that she was going to go and help them. She was trying to get away from them for a second by locking herself in a closet or something, and I didn't think it worked, because she eventually gave in and just said, "I love you," and hung up.  So that was ULTRA cool for me. I went and played darts with my sister's friend who was staying over, I won.  They called back shortly after. There were a few more Iluvu's in there, there was some sappiness, which Leigh Anne alleged would happen, and then she hung up at about 1:30, whereafter, Lily tells me, they went to sleep.  So the next day I guess Leigh Anne was still like that for a while. Things went bad at about 5 that evening. They got worse at 6:30. Then I went to my dad's house feeling generally pissed at my dying fortune.  And then that night she just asked me to forget about it again. That she wasn't interested in a relationship with anyone, that she needed a friend. There are some other things that were more personal when we were together that came up, but they eventually were also rescinded until there was nothing left but a big fuckin' gap of silence, whereafter I put down the phone and read your posts. I had said no arguing, I felt like there was some here, so I just decided to call the other people off. Plus Rosie's  ultimately  childish post of "Joah...God I hate you." As if I needed anymore of that stuff.   I posted it to see whom of you would stick by me no matter what. It really seems though, now that I look at it, that Rosie was reallllllllllyyyyy eager to give up on me...some friend :), well we've got things straightened out for the most part.  Then I woke up the next morning and felt stupid because I really enjoy the outside input at times, so I went back on it but it was a little too late for that. So today in fourth I answered Lily's post for the most part(there's more answers for her and Lindsey after this one, by the way), and I resent an invitation to join the BLog since Lindsey had backed out and was mad at me.  So that is the story. Last night things were pretty good for a while. But I really don't care. Actually, at one point, Leigh Anne had this horoscope thing on her cell and was telling me to think of a question and tell her...at one of them I just said, "Can I just keep it in my head?" and she said ok, and the real question was, "Will things ever work out with me and her?", and the VERY astonishing answer was a bunch of star alignment bullshit followed by the interpretation, "Give it time and it will work in the near future,". I was like, WHOA. She asked what the question was and I was too stunned to think for a second. Then I said something about if I was going out to eat or not that day.  She always thinks of something bad when I'm making her laugh, and she bring it up, after which it'll be a thorn in my side and I really can't be humorous anymore and she'll start talking about all these guys...I swear to god, this girl has no female friends, and the ones that could be considered so, she can't connect with them, or they're lesbians and they're after her.  So that's about it for now, that's the story so far.  Fucking story. 
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sorry, Josh.  I think I'm gonna take a backseat with this one for a while.  Screwing up your life was not intentional.  I promised myself I would never do what Paul did to me and I haven't yet; I just want to make sure I don't.  So if I start giving you advice or anything just tell me to shut up.  But there is something pretty important that I need to tell you.  Call me when you get a chance.  It's not urgent or anything.  
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well that's encouraging. The problem is wondering how hard to hold on, if it's really worth it at all to go so strong.  I did before and that was stupid. So I'll just wait for the winds to change.  That FUCK YOU post was really in angst against her taking it all back, that's just the lil' screaming child post coming to life. It's hard to stand strong when so many things are hitting you, like being an oak in a hurricane.  Pretending yes, as to how, I really don't know. I just like to conceal little things about myself.  And sorry to everyone for being an idiot and not calling certain persons back (you know who you are Lindsey :) ), some major stuff was up that night and I forgot about it eventually. VERY SORRY! I was kind of worried, though, as to what I would tell you anyway. So that was probably a part of it.  Gonna try and reinvite Lindsey, pick up the pieces of this BLog and all my friends and such.  Girls...  Argh.
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sorry Joshies! I had to work the whole day today then i went swimming, it was an INSIDE POOL! Anywho, Josh, if you feel that way so badly why don't you just tell Leigh? *I* know she can be an ass sometimes, and I know how much you like her, I know she likes you too, she just has this problem of showing her actual feelings, I suggest for you to hold on a while longer, if she doesn't turn then I think you should forget her, I know how much you've tried and they'll pay off one day. She  REALLY  likes you, she just doesn't know how to show it. You've been pretending thw holw time? Josh, that's not very nice. I mean, I tell you the problems I have with Kenzie because I can't talk to anyone else about it, just let me in on a few things! I don't want you to pretend to me. Anywho, Erm..... I can tell Hua likes you to the point that she'll admit she loves you. She's just really secretive. Yeah, all girls/women are fickle. She'll turn around someday, but it's your choice if you want to hang on to her or not. I'm about to have a serious talk with Leigh. See you people around Later! Oh, and Joshies, I'll call you in a little while!  Lily the psycho powered one
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You're reading way too deep into this.  I didn't say that I never wanted you as friends, I just didn't want to be criticized for the things I've been doing, and I was getting that.  Especially from Rosie, unfortunately. I hope you remember your reaction at Lindsey's house on Friday. Because I sure as  hell  do.  I've decided not to remove anyone, that was Leigh Anne's wish that there be no one but myself on here, and it would be foolish to adhere to it, considering she'll never find it.  I really don't know what to find out of anyone anymore...I really want to see what's left after all that's happened so far. Perhaps last night's post was to test my real friends from the ones who really do use me and this plight as entertainment, and seeing as how I wasn't attacked directly, and in fact the matter at hand wasn't attacked, I really have found the ones that will stay.  Not that that was my preliminary intention; I know this probably did cause a lot of damage, but I cannot apologize, I had to know.  To understand me, you have to know that my world is made up of definites, and anything that goes against that will not work. My fear of commitment and God, all because they are not definite.   And the real me is a screaming little boy. He's locked away and huddled over and screaming his lungs out, he's cold and alone and he loves it that way, even though he hates it, because I could let that boy out but I am afraid to, because I don't know if he'll be the one to change from it.  Plus the fact that the things he wants to show all of you and tell you that he's seen. No one would like what he sees, he envisions the world as innately evil, and truly, he is right, but he knows the depth of it.  It scares me because the boy is cunning. He's something else...I could call him wicked but that's not what he is, he's been twisted by his thoughts.  He only comes out at my worst, he came out on the last post and did something that probably destabalized the people it was aimed at. But it's something he wants you to hear so that it will stop bothering him, it's bothering him that he could ever think that he was being blamed for something that isn't his fault.  Don't expect an apology, that post wasn't pure malice. That was the reality in my head.  To understand me, find me at my worst and learn.  But never judge.  
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Joah. One time I asked if I knew you, really knew you. I didn't know all of you but most. What heck do you mean by acting like you are just now telling us that you pretend. You've been telling me since day one and you expect me not to try to find the real you? I've been trying ever since but apparently you don't see that. I never thought that we would ever fight over the true you or even Leigh. She was there for you, to help you but sometimes she wasn't there. I wanted to talk to her about that. I have no sorries to give. Leigh is as she is and I supposed that you see her life with yours. Enjoy. I cared about you Joah and since you never want us to be friends apparently I have to say bye. 
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm outta here.  Bye, yall.
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm taking all of you off. I knew it wouldn't work, it was a bad idea. Sorry, but if I can't have one of you, I won't have any of you. And remember, it's nothing personal, it's just something I need to do for now, I need to listen to myself and only myself. Trust that you'll be back very shortly. I'll give you all one last post unless I hear otherwise, attack me and not each other...although the rest of this post is going to be damned contradictory to that last part.  Why is it...  Everything I do is hopeless.  Everything I say is worthless.  Everything is just dead. I don't understand why things are so great one minute and ruined the next. Leigh Anne and I were together today, and all of a sudden, she decided to take it all back.  And it wonders me that I can't just let it all go and hang up the silent phone right now, the silent phone with that girl's bullshit as she takes back slowly everything and acts like she's all above it. Like none of this will ever come back to get her.  Believe me, when it does, I'd love to say I'd be the first one to point and laugh, but I know I won't, and the rest of you know it too.  It is ridiculous how much I punish myself...  But it is more grossly fascinating of how much strength I have. With this, I could conquer the world, and instead I foolishly spend it on a girl who loves me sometimes and is irresolute the next, one who I'll always come crawling back to.  After all, having her is a dream. You always chase your dreams, and when it's in your grasp, you grab it, no matter the consequence.  I need to talk to someone with an answer, not just good ideas. Not people at war, not people that look at the surface and laugh or get angry. Not any of you who mock and jeer when I'm down because it's all my fault in the end, everyone, whether you'd like to admit it or not, points the finger at me...and you should all be pointing them to the girl who said, "I think I'm in love with him", and twenty-four hours later, "Why can't you forget it?; I just take it back,"...you do for a while, you did, but your posts shine through that.  "Joah. God I hate you."..."We're about as happy with you as you are with us."...what friends I have, friends who will never look deeper than the surface, whether they like to admit it or not.  So maybe that tells me that I should really stop being so kind to all of you since you really don't deserve it. I've noticed I get struck when I can't defend, right here in this BLog. Doesn't it make you feel invincible? Do you ever think that I won't respond, I'll take it and be apologetic? Should I, anymore?  And the answer is: Yes, it does, Yes, you think I won't say anything, and No, I shouldn't apologize. I really didn't ask any of you to get involved if you noticed. My depression was my silent cry, but you didn't have to listen, I've borne it all on my own before and got through it. I was changed at the end for the worse, but at least I didn't care what was happening to me.  I want something to happen to everyone else all at the same time just so I can feel a little better, just so I won't be the hopeless, the lowman anymore.  I need something beyond me. I have a hope and it's dying, I still hold. I have a dream and it's fading, I still seek it. I have memories and they burn, they become real and they haunt me.  She haunts me, who is the one who will not let go?  She is a liar, and I am a fool.  Lily, I need to talk to you about some things seriously...we've already been over a lot of this before but I need to ask it all in a different way. So just give me a call as soon as you can.  Kenzie, I probably blame you the least for all of these things, but I won't forget some things...I forgive them, but I cannot forget.  Lindsey and Rosie...what can I say...I could apologize for some things, but I deserve it for others.   Elizabeth, I don't know what you think, and you are probably the wisest.  And Leigh Anne...  FUCK YOU FUCK YOU FOR EVERYTHING FUCK YOU FOR THIS FUCK YOU FOR TAKING ME AND BREAKING ME FUCK YOU FOR DESTROYING MY HEAD FUCK YOU FOR BOTH THESE TIMES AND THE ONES TO COME THE ONLY WAY YOU'LL EVER BE GOOD IS WHEN YOU ARE HUMBLED AND BROKEN AND I WAIT FOR THIS DAY I SEE IT COMING AND I LONG FOR IT AND I HOPE IT KILLS YOU LIKE IT KILLED ME OVER AND OVER AND OVER AGAIN AND I HOPE YOU LONG FOR AN ANSWER AND NEVER GET ONE AND I HOPE AT THE END OF IT ALL I'M THE ONLY THING LEFT THEN IT ALL STARTS OVER AGAIN THE WAY IT SHOULD HAVE BEEN THE WAY I ALWAYS HAD IN MIND THE WAY THAT COULD HAVE WORKED THE WAY WHERE NO ONE WINS THINGS JUST ARE WHAT THEY ARE AND ARE NO MORE THAN THAT   Trust in this, because it is coming . If you put in too much it gets spit up at you when it can't hold anymore. I know that better than anyone, what comes around goes around.   To all of you...  See me for who I really am, not what I pretend to be.  And know...  I think I've been pretending the whole time.  Sorry. 
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hmm, so far in Poor Bastard 2...   Outshined  by Soundgarden  Cajun Song  by Gin Blossoms  Pieces of the Night  by Gin Blossoms  Iris  by The Goo Goo Dolls  Dirt  by Alice in Chains  Glory of Sadness  by Rotting Christ  Ira Incensus  by Rotting Christ   And probably not  Little Rhyme , I don't want to wait that long, and I'll probably have a lot of songs by then.
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Umm...interesting, Josh.  Yes, I am alive.  Just wanted to drop by.  Sorry that Friday sucked for all of you without my glowing presence...yeah.  Right.  I wish.  ~Z  
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Agh, Nigel is gone.  We kinda decided after the fact that he's too feral to live here. For the first seven months of his life, he lived in the woods and under my aunt's bed, and would never get comfortable here, so...  Getting a kitten instead, in about two weeks.  SOB. He was great, I opened his lil' cage and moved his blanket, he BUSTED out of the cage and DESTROYED the room. It was SO AWESOME. I LOVE that cat. But he's GONE. FUCK.  Well maybe the cat shall be just as crazy.  I hope.
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, Nigel is here...  He's scared as hell and just sitting in his cage. His ears are HUGE. He's so awesome.  Chloe saw him a minute ago and hissed at him, then walked off and started smelling all his stuff. Chloe's out of the computer room now...  I don't know how well this is going to work out.
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What did you mean, playing on your emotions? (you know who you are)
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      YAY! I'm getting a new puss in a minute here.  His name is Nigel, he was abandoned, and my aunt takes care of abandoned cats and stuff...well, my dad saw Nigel a few weeks ago (say before Thanksgiving) and decided to take him...he's been "rehabed" shall we say, and he's gonna be here in a few minutes. He's REALLY black and REALLY soft and REALLY little.  I hope Puss/Chloe is ok with him.
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      She didn't mean Leigh Anne, Rosie.  Remember the fact that I'm dead, and that should give you a little insight into Lindsey's distress.  See now?
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Heh, I know, I know.  It's just that since the main point of conflict has vanished (i.e.: Lily hasn't posted here in forever/the night of the DI meeting is, in part, forgotten), I thought to introduce some MORE conflict! Heh, well actually, she wanted to talk to Rosie about some things...not that those things matter anymore, nor do I know how any of this is relevent anymore...  Then again, I'm always jumping to conclusions...you'll see when she gets here, probly not 'til Monday.  But time will tell. 
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      um......lindsey i don't think it's leigh....it says brittany
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      [In Response to the Team Issue]   Oh my God.  Are you OUT OF YOUR FREAKING MIND?????  Rosie is going to KILL you if I don't get to you (or her, for that matter) first.  Do you NOT remember what she did?  Oh my God.  Oh my God.    Oh. My. God.  Note:  That was not advice.
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Might have a new person coming on soon, 'sides Kenzie.  It's a SURPRISE! Although all you have to do is click the Team Button.
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Whee everyone, whee.  Well I have been explained the Herd. Sweet. I figured it was something along those lines.  To summarize the day after I got home...  Alex called and him and Steven came over, whereafter we pulled sticks from a fallen tree in our yard and battled. I took a few hits to the legs but I gave the point to Alex and Steven a few times. Then Alex lost the keys to his truck and we spent an hour looking for them in the freezing cold. After a while he found  a  key but not  the  key...he left, and after that I grabbed a flashlight and hunted for another half hour or so, but no avail.   And then I got home and started watching  Lord of the Rings , because I had wanted to all week, and drinking Vanilla Coke and stuff.  And NOW I am updating, because I haven't even posted in my own BLog in the past thousand days. At least here I have a computer that works and all.  Sick, Z? I had to play Speed with Will today in 5th, I got my  ass  kicked. It sucked a lot. Becca was in a really bad mood today and I tried to cheer her up the best I could. I know those kinds of days that she was talking about, I heard the same words I had said 1000 times in the past, "I just want to disappear", although in her case it was for the next few hours or so. She presses herself  way  too hard, I think. I hope she'll be ok.  I hope Rosie is having fun at the S party with five of her alleged six boyfriends, and I hope Bob isn't bleeding too bad. Heh.  What is this I feel...tired? Must I resign now? I feel to die of shame for this atrocity. AGH. I just had Vanilla Coke, this isn't fair. Especially even after I got some extra sleep this morning and everything. DAMN. I'll just do something to entertain myself for now.  Like rest my eyes.  I'll certainly be back.
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Awww, what Z is trying to say, but won't cause she hates mush, is that we'd miss you, Tao-Tao.  Life wouldn't be the same without you.  And Z, I won't be a legal adult when I go to college... I'll be seventeen, but you're right about the graduating early being a mess...too many horror stories out there for my taste.  And Josh, if you don't ask, one of these days when I'm really bored I will explain the herd.  As I said on my blog, I most likely won't be back at school or church next week.  Sorry yall.  Pass the word along to my other friends (and if you're feeling really generous, my teachers too.  Just the ones we both have.)  Hmmm.  I woke up about 4:45 this afternoon to find that nobody went to school today!!!  I was excited because that means that's one day less I have make up work for!!!  And Rosie, call me if things get too insane around your house.  Your calls entertain me.  And stick with interact...scholarship, remember?  And why take it all out on Will?  What did he do now?  Anyway, I'll see yall later.  I officially have my days and nights confused.  I'm what the zoos refer to as "nocturnal" currently.  But I am getting tired.  I'm going in for more blood work tomorrow to make sure they didn't screw up the diagnosis.  I hope they didn't.  Otherwise, that could mean a trip to the hospital for me to run tests to see what it really is.  Fun, fun.  So I'm going to go to bed now, I do believe.  See yall sometime this month, I hope, I hope. ~Linds
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      love the tao-tao guys, you can drop it anytime =)............please? 
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I hope you don't, Tao-Tao.  I don't think that's the best idea...you'd still only be 16, right?  Or 17.  You wouldn't be a legal adult and it would probably be a big mess.  Anyway...that's all I have to say.  ~Z  
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Heh Rosie, you crazy kook, chill out. Never thought I'd say that, but yeah, every day is d i  f f e  r e n  t , as much as they all may suck or get really great, but it's all changing. Chill out.  Graduate next year? Cool.  YEAH I ALMOST HAD IT. Actually, I noticed I missed 10:58 when I first posted it, so I came in, cut the text from the first one, deleted it, and made a new one. The school clock said 10:58, but Blogger said 10:59. Obviously, my frusteration.  So  that's  who they are. I was just curious. As for the Herd...hmm...I'll ask if I think of it.  Kenzie lost  Poor Bastard ...and all of her CDs for that matter. MANY TEARS ARE SHED. But that's ok. "Here at Johnny Rocket's we do service with a smile"...the funniest thing ever said by any man, I'll explain it later. We might go again this weekend, perhaps perhaps.  And there's the bell.  Good day all. 
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My mom is drving me insane...............if this doesn't end soon I'm going to graduate next year................I can't take this anymore! Linds talk to ya later.............i hate interact, i people, i hate will, i hate my life right now
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Oh, 10:59!!!  So close!  OK, to explain: Ronnie is this guy that went to Woodland with me and Becca. He was part of the Herd.  If you don't know what the herd is, it's a long story, get Becca to explain.  He and Rosie know each other because they hang out at Chinese New Year.  Their parents know each other really well too.  Vincent is not important, but if you really want to know, he's Jackie's ex-boyfriend and a friend of mine, kind of.  He's not really important because he doesn't dare show his face at church very often anymore.  Anyway, Jackie still likes him, even though she's engaged.  And to even have a semblence of knowledge as to who Jackie is, you'd have to come to church, because she's just too complicated.  Anyone want to help me out on these explanations? Tao-Tao? Z?  Ok, I'll see yall later.  Oh, and Rosie, I want to see the car!
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow...you put Tao Tao.  The point of that name wasn't for your glorification, it was to make fun of you. Please don't take it the wrong way.  And you will turn over. Into a ravine and will blow up and DIE. Have fun!  Umm...I don't think I drank after ye in the past fifty days. Does thinking about it count? I don't think I thought about it either. O well, it doesn't matter, I'm getting sick as is. Have to take Centrum...that shit is REALLY COOL. You could probably take one of those every day and live if only it had some calories in it.   Who's Ronnie? Who's Vincent? Who the hell are these people? I'm confused in my own BLog.  This period is a waste of time.  Do note that I am intentionally posting at 10:58 (or closely whereabouts) to scare those of you who have noticed that most of my posts that do occur in the middle of the day, occur at 10:58.  I don't have a computer right now...damn. If I think of something, it'll be lost for the next few days. My mom works at home, and the state computer networking linkerupper thinger inside the computer is mest, so she has to take it in and get it worked on over the next few days. AGH. Can't do anything at home now. AGH.  O well, that's more quality time with which to read...  AGH.
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Lindsey how's life.....still boring?  So yeah, my car came yesterday, hopefully I won't turn over in the Explore.=)  talked to ronnie last night, he's sweet linds and don't take that oo far.....really. it would be easy to hate him too. jacob/mike thing....well i'm busy right now so it'll start tomorrow.... I'm supposed to be meeting becca here but apparently she's not here. I gotta go strangle someone.......see ya -tao tao
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      poor linds
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Oh, that makes sense (that was in response to my last post.  I keep sleeping through the answer only to find them later.)  And why won't the teachers let you out?  Just because of the whole "sick thing?" Coach King would get you for saying it's like a prison though.  Right Z? ;)  Oh, and I hope none of you drank after me in the past 50 days or so, otherwise, you're gonna be out with me.  I'm watching "The Diary of Anne Frank" on A  Yes, that is just how bored I really am. 
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yeah, that's what Z and I said a lil' before that. Good that you're catching on, yo.  The horrid pull and expulsion of the diseased permeate my silent world. Yeah, everyone's really sick. My whole biology class was deadgone, there were about thirteen people in there today...out of about twenty-nine.  Plus, the teachers are keeping us in the rooms, under STRICT command to let none of us go during class for any reason.  It's like a prison...well it always is, we were always wondering when they'd take the next step, anyway.  Fell asleep a billion times during geometry, gonna go home and take a nap, if European History isn't too bad...and I hear it is, fucking DBQ writing schtick.   Although I probly won't take a nap, I'll get a Coke or something during lunch.  Damn am I stupid.  And nobody answer that either.
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      the Gunter thing is now never to be brought up ever again
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow Joah, I knew I was pushing it when I posted the HAHA's but I never thought that you would get THAT mad. Sorry....I wasn't expecting that convers so I decided to let you know about it. Again sorry if it really pissed you off. As to your advise of cutting Gunter off, well it prolly won't happen but I'll try to not pay as much attention as he wants k?  The subject is really getting old.....It's history and if you hadn't brought up the fact that it might not be over, I wouldn't have worried about it. Thankfully all of us have brains so I say history stays there and we never study it again.
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Heh, I confer, actually. It'll never go away if we don't let it slide completely. So that's it, close the book on that assclown.  This is my last post for the day, I just wanted to remark on what a week it's been.  What a week it's been.  I hope everyone's week was great, posters and viewers alike.  And see you when I see you.                 ToasTY
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      No offense to Josh, but can we PLEASE move past this already?  It's gotten way annoying.  ~Z  
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Down in a Hole  by Alice in Chains  Bury me softly in this world I give this part of me to you The sand rains down and here I sit Holding rare flowers in a tomb In bloom  Down in a hole and I don't know if I can be safe See my heart I've decorated like a grave You don't understand what they thought I was supposed to be Look at me now, I'm a man who won't let himself be  Down in a hole Feeling so small Down in a hole Losing my soul I'd like to fly But my wings have been so denied  Down in a hole and they've put all the stones in their place I've eaten the sun so my tongue has been burned of the taste I have been guilty of kicking myself in the teeth I will breathe no more of my feelings beneath  Down in a hole Feeling so small Down in a hole Losing my soul I'd like to fly But my wings have been so denied  Bury me softly in this world (Oh I wanna be inside of you) I give this part of me for you (Oh I wanna be inside of you The sand rains down and here I sit (Oh I wanna be inside of you) Holding rare flowers in a tomb (Oh I wanna be inside)  Down in a hole Feeling so small Down in a hole Losing my soul Down in a hole Losing my soul Down in a hole Out of control I'd like to fly But my wings have been so denied  Wanted to post this one since it's really harmonic on Layne's part, and I had it stuck in my head about three seconds ago.
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      O ok, he said I sounded like a moron.  Now I don't know what the hell Rosie told him, but he had the pointed forwardness to say I sounded like a moron when he has no  fucking  idea about me, living in his little shell of "the world is mine because I'm smart".  I can judge, why, because I've seen people just like him before, number one, and I've heard the stories of what he's done and how he's done things, and I must say it really isn't an impressive personality type by any stretch of the imagination.  Yes, Rosie really loves those resiliant, down-to-earth guys. That was staunch sarcasm, by the way.  When I said drop it, I meant the "HEY IT'S OVER" shit, questions about the past are cool :) ok, just making sure it didn't look like I was biting anyone's head off other than Rosie's.
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sorry to not drop it, but I obviously missed the Gunter judging you part.  Please explain.
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      SHUT UP.  Rosie, for the love of god, you are  testing  my patience to its fullest. If it really is over, why do you persist in proving to me that it is? Can't it just be over?  There's something in one of you that's trying to say "it's over but it's still ok to act like we were when it was going on". Perhaps inadvertently; however it is superfluous trying to explain this reasoning to your ultimately ineffible logic.  Gunter will still be an asshole, why, because he judged me groundlessly, whereas I had every right to, considering I had all the instances to do as such.   Your insistantce in trying to make me see this eye to eye is worthless.  So is it with me.  So drop it.
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I thought I already posted this but if not here is it: HAHAHAHA Joah you were wrong!! go check out my site......you were wrong about Gunter, you were wrong about Gunter, you were wrong about Gunter ( run, hide, don't smack me) so yeah check out our convers, it's kinda long so just skim it =)
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wellll the NyQuil was a bad idea.  I had nightmares and drunken visions all night, I kept waking up. It was awful. Plus, I got sicker than before. My dad woke me up and sat there talking to me for about half an hour, trying to get me to focus. It worked, but my head still feels like it weight a thousand pounds.  I have a DI meeting today.  And after that I'm coming home, I'm going to do whatever the HELL I feel like doing.  Whee.  Catching up on sleep, probably.  Shit.
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Gonna drink some NyQuil and go to bed. God this shit is nasty.  Gnite.
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A few things...  Has anyone noticed (especially those of us in foreign language that watch such films profusely) that Disney films still haven't lost their captivity since when we were kids? I just noticed today, we were watching Beauty and the Beast in French today, and even though we couldn't understand a fuckin' thing, I noticed how drawn in I was, and then, when looking around, noticed that everyone was mute with mouths opened. Disney is wayyyyyy too good at what they do.  The Greek language is awesome. I used to know how to say the alphabet in Greek...now I can't. I know a few words now... eu =good,  thanatos =death (thus,  euthanasia ),  khronos =time,  me servaso =something close to "sincerely"...it's a great language. Plus the fact that even though people take Latin, it's  Greek  mythology that gets studied.  And another Valentine's is gone. What a commercial ass holiday. Not that I'd be bitter for crying at home and watching Lifetime, I just hate to see these little sods going out and spending a thousand bucks on each other, only proving that no one is secure in their relationships. Keeping it sentimental with mentality just isn't the way to go anymore. It's more about the image, of course, everyone's succumbed to it, just about. People sicken me.  Die France. I'm REALLY getting sick of French. Fucking language.  Anybody know what "bok choy" means? It's some kind of Chinese cabbage. Just curious.  And all for now.
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Oh, and before I forget...  Leigh Anne tells me that Kevin (yes, the faggot one) tried to send me a Valentine...gay bastard. AUGH. And if it wasn't for her hating him right now, I could be holding a nice lil' red heart with mindless gay profanities upon it, myself braindead and bleeding upon the floor, a crunch-ed and broken mess of a human. HAHA YES, IT WAS RIPPED TO SHREDS. Thankyouthankyouthankyou Leigh Anne.  Why can't the faggots leave me alone?  And just what side of the tree is this guy climbing down anyway?  Whatever.
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today is going to suck, but that's ok because I'm in a good mood.  No sleep, for one. Another, I have a test in Euro today, and I didn't do any of the homework. But that's ok. I listened to the  Sacred Song  with Kenzie a few times, then I talked to Leigh Anne, and Alex got in there eventually, and we listened to some Metallica ( The Call of ...well...you know), then I went to sleep (on the phone of course), woke up this morning, felt really sick, went to my grandma's, forgot to take vitamin C, but I did have these chocolate Ritz crackers that were awesome.  Last night I played  My Solution  about five times, trying to get it perfect and sing along with it. Why, because we're going for the talent show, and yes, we have a prospective bassist now...Alex wants me to play lead but I'm sure we could find a lead guitarist sooner than the day, which is early March. We have some time. For now though, we have to get some practice, haven't had a session since forever.   I nailed  Solution  by the way. It sounds soooooooo cool, I got some new distortion and a new way of singing the last choruses. Now if Alex can exactly replicate the recorded version when we rerecord/play it live, it's going to be the greatest song ever...plus a new song in place of the second song,  Deadgone , this one's prototype name is  Rage , since  Deadgone  didn't really have much substance, and  Rage  is completely finished. I wrote most of it in 7th grade for a project, and now I've finished it and embellished on it. Nice catchy screaming now. And I got the lyrics done to  All Fall Down .  This is gonna be the weirdest album ever.   If  ever.  I don't have a phone at my dad's anymore by the way, dumb bastard cancelled it to "get his debts under control", so I've got my cellphone...if anybody needs me I'll be there.  And here I am typing and I need to go do Euro.  What a fuckup I art.
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night was so weird.  I was on the phone, then I fell asleep. I woke up at about 3 and felt really weird...I figured it out though,  where's the phone?  So I sat up and looked at the bottom of the bed, and there they were, hung up of course, but also perfectly organized, like...straightened and stuff, right next to each other. How do I know it wasn't someone else? My door was locked. How do I know that someone didn't get in? My mother felt like shit yesterday, she was out at about 7:30, and my sister doesn't know where the key is. It was quite bewildering.   I also had a practical application for the "" today, we were making a program for  Les Miserables  that's going on at the school, and we had to type the name "Thnardier". She was trying to teach us menus and all the people in my row (the geeky tech people and me) were yelling "ALT 130!" for about five minutes until they shot us with tranqs. Ok, not really. But the whole row was bugging out while she ignored them through the menu tutorial.   I was going to send a Valentine heart at school today to Ben through Brooks, but I didn't have the balls to go up there and do it. Alex had a few quarters, we were going to send one for Steven from me (Leigh Anne...are you sure about the whole "bad influences" thing?), again, no balls. And one from Kevin Smith to Stephen Jones, just to scare the poor bastard. But, no funds/nuts. Plus, they wouldn'tve let us anyway, I don't think.  And it's the end of the week, and a long weekend. Saturday's gonna suck though, a bunch of people are coming over to clean up my dad's house once and for all. Which means  I'm  gonna have to do something. Augh. I dunwanna. But hey, I have Monday to compensate.   Friday's gonna be a busy day, too.  Could it be...life has become... interesting , I dare say?  No way.  
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Fourth period is gay.  Surprise.
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Heheh, YES it feels better ANUS.  So now, perhaps I should like...lay out what I do on this site most of the time. If I'm not just talking about random stuff, I'm whining about something, read some of these posts, they got me in BIG trouble. Heh, well, I wasn't expecting to get caught. O well.........the past is the past.  Well, now ye canst say what you wanted to Rosie, and all these people that read it, I'm not exactly sure how many, but I know a remote few. So that's about it. I pretty much use this to vent angst and post songs and kill a few minutes every once in a while, it's fun fun fun.   Sleep time. Well not really. Ok, I go up to my room every night and start reading and then I get tired...I don't  mean  to fall asleep when I close my eyes and put a pillow over my head, I just mean to sit there and think or something...but I end up falling asleep and missing certain persons' phone calls four times in a row. Not that there was a specific case as such...although there was, like, yesterday.  And um...let me think. If I ever say anything about the "dark marks" post, it's about one day when I was really depressed and made my first dark post on my old BLog that got deleted, about stuff that's happened that I overlooked at the time and was starting to see again, i.e. the effects on me from my parents getting divorced, ect. Then there was the weird Thanksgiving posts that were all happy cuz things starting working out, then there was the time around Christmas where I was getting depressed again, then the "letter" which you read, then the "is anything good" post, then  Poor Bastard , the CD made up of songs that deal with me and this website...that's about it, the biggest histoires.   And every once in a while after a few short posts I make a HUGE one like this, although it's never explaining anything like this, it's just me being a lonely old faggot (props to Kenzie for that one). "I want to die because (long list)", you get the idea. It's a great, bright, cheery place.  Eat  my  heart out?  That's all...oh yeah, and I end every post with a short word or phrase. It's tradition.  Sweet.
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, josh, does your eye feel better yet?  I hope not, you morose motherfucker! ha. eat your heart out! 
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Gotta be quick.  I got popped in the eye by Brittany today, it still feels like it's sunken in the back of my skull.  My hair is really weird, too...for some reason it got ULTRA long all of a sudden. Well, to me, anyway. It's everywhere and out of control. I have chronic hair stickage uppage disease (CHSU for short, say), it makes life hell with long hair.  Anyone notice that Black History Month is the one with the least amount of days? It's like saying "Ok, have a month and shut the fuck up," Heh, so what if it's prejudicial, there's no limited White History Month. I can bitch all I want at that blatant act of racism.  I'm not going to have a computer at home for a few weeks, so be not expecting any updates any time soon until fourth. Even these are gonna be short, because I'm really not as interested anymore, and I don't have much time, we actually  do  things in here, versus Mrs. Mallard's class, where we did JACK  SHIT .  Lonely old Badvision, once we knew you so well.  Fare ye well.
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Augh, I'm tired.  And that is all.
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is a good day too. The annoying guy who sits next to me in this cklass isn't here today.  DI today, that should be a TON of fun. I had a Koke earlier, but I've been watching how long they work on me, and if I drink one right when I get in, I burn out about seventh period, so I figure I'll have an hour after the fact, but some of those strange Khinese foods I  always  am probably going to get over there may help...or s'more Koke or something.    Between Times ...I haven't listened to it today...but konsidering that that's all I've got at my dad's house, this weekend is going to be dedikated to Rotting Khrist. There is the komputer, but there's only so mukh you kan do with no internet. Plus, my dad's going to be  gone  on Saturday, he has a date. So I get to sit at home and listen to Rotting Khrist and other sukh tunes and play Unreal and EVO and other sukh games and watkh a kableless TV in a phoneless house. Sounds like a konstant stream of komplains, non? Well, at least, I'm away from the konstantky of my mom's for a few days.  "I think it's gonna raaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaain, oh, when I diiiiiiiiiiieeee" said Layne Stayley. Yes it is.  Goodbye all, until Sunday.
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The song  Faith in Nothing  is a great song now that I've rewritten it.  Then again, so is  Between Times .  Heh.
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, the day is over.  Result: not too bad. I kinda lokked horns with Brooks like I did yesterday. Kid's a fukking retard. It's really bad kuz he thinks he's the smartest person out there, when in fact he misses the point entirely  every time . It really pisses me off when I'm trying to explain to him that we need more information than just history for our Frenkh projekt, and he's waving papers at me, saying, "I've got the history right here dumbass, you're taking too much time, I kould do this SO much better than you," Then he went to the library this morning and fukked with the projekt, "spiffing it up", when in fact all he did was put a fill-effekt on the bakk of every slide, after I took about a YEAR to explain to him that it would look better if we kould find piktures of Lorraine, the region of our projekt, even  Franke  for god's sake. God, SO pissed at that asshole.  And I listened to  Between Times  five times when my mom got home with the K(C)D in her kar today. I was like, "YES!" and listened to it til it was koming out of my ears. And then I listened to  Exiled Ark(c)hangels  and  If It Ends Tomorrow  and  In Domine Sathana . GOD that last song is REALLY messed up. But mostly  Between Times .   I have DI tomorrow. That should be good. Then I'm going to my dad's and I'll probably go to Opry Mills this weekend and see Arthur...heh, "Here at Johnny Rokket's..." et cetera. The dude is HILARIOUS.  Gonna get  A Dead Poem  when I get my next allowance, just to listen to  Between Times . Little obsessed, ain't I? Where has it been all my life?  And I was thinking of great proof that sokiety has bekome ultimately shallow. Anal Kunt...they have an album called  Piknik of Love , there's a song kalled  Saving Ourselves For Marriage , and the lyriks as follows: "We just stood there, wondering what was next / But we knew not to ruin our love with premarital sex". Now obviously, this is a joke, after all, with songs like  I Lit Your Baby On Fire , this guy's an immortality nut, right?  That's  exactly  what I'm talking about, it says nothing about sex in that song, not that you kan understand anything he's saying. Most people just hear his skreaming and say, "Wow, that guy's just wrong in every aspekt. since he's saying  something  about lighting babies on fire, he must have blatant sex,"   Not that I'm denying it, after their song  Rape Women ...heh. Um, but yeah, I bet you took it at face value, you shallow bastard.  Me tiredisimo. Gonna listen to  The Fated Song  a little more and turn in.  Nice.
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Having an unusually good day today.  Kenzie started a language last night called "whahefukk", and I am proud to be a part of it. My new name under  this  language is Gaeshae Antonie Krikkopher Khandler. YES. Notice the lakk of "c"s. Well, sure, I was ranting about it. It was late last night, and we just sat there making up a language.  Yggil qaid dinngy. Bekause I  am  the apple. I'll post it all latr, when I can get to it. It's on a notepad on my Internet-unready komputer in my room. Sadness.   Between Times  is the greatest song ever, I listened to it about a thousand times minus 998 this morning. And I also listened to  In Dominae Sathana , which is also a good song because of the really amazing guitar work. And  If It Ends Tomorrow , and the beginning of  The Fifth Illusion , heh. "AAAAAAAHHHHHHHH,"...I listened to another on there, but I have since forgotten of the name of it, which is espekially gay when trying to put the names on a komputer database.   This day is just  unnatural , it's so good. Probably one of the best I've had in months. I got 100 on a geometry quiz, then I finished my homework in there, I got 100 on a biology quiz, I finished my homework in there, I got everything done for today in study hall, whikh is really happifying since I hardly ever do. Maybe that's the sekret to my depression, to finish all my homework  early  and not have any undue anxiety...  Nah.  A quikk random thing, the prinkiple of tires. Now, tires akt upon the funktion of gripping the road, mukh like a train grips the trakk. If you lose that grip (as I did during the last snow), there's no hope for you, exkept to hope to start gripping before you hit something. And in my case, I ran off the road. But that prinkiple of aktually holding to the road, as if we were on a trakk...awesome. And gay at the same time, I should know, since I did it, ran straight off the road, off a little hill. Some dudes kame and helped us push the kar out though, so it was ok.   Hope it keeps raining through the weekend, even though I'll be doing nothing at my dad's all that time, I enjoy the rain. Go listen to  Between Times  a few dozen times and drink some Kherry Coke and play EVO. Bones and ashes of my formerly komplicated life of talking on the phone konstantly.  Actually, I konsider this an evolution, since  while  being on the phone, I am also doing all these other things, NIK(C)E. Why kouldn't I see it before, exkluding my life from my sokiality probably would've ended me, had I not done something about it, which I did subkonkiously. I'll look bakk on myself one day and laugh.  Ha fukking ha.
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ti wra arxizei i synavlia to savvato? hail to thy... ti wra arxizei i synavlia sto gagarin?  It's Greek! What does it all mean?  My new name is Joshuae Anthonie Khandler, woohoo!  Here at Johnny Rokket's we do servike with a smile!  
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      God,  Between Times  is sukh a great song. It reminds me of rain, and I view rain as quite sakred. I would post the lyriks if they could convey the intensity of this song, but I don't think I kould do anything to give it justice. Just go download, I'll  pay  you to download it...ok not really. But you just  have  to hear it, at least the intro.  This song is starting to skare me. Yet again, I'm going to go upstairs and listen to it and try to memorize the lyriks. They're really hard on this one. I mean, I got  A Dead Poem  about the first day I listened to it, and  Sorrowful Farewell  the first time I read the lyriks. The rest of the songs are pretty unimportant lyrikally...well, ok,  Glory of Sadness ...and there's also the opening lines to  Khronos  whikh sound only too terribly kool: "Origin of time / The fak(c)e of old flesh / Devours the earth / My feet and brain"...what does it mean, NOTHING, why is it kool, BECAUSE IT IS. the word "flesh" is awesome as is, they should replake the word "skin" with "flesh" permanately and for all uses.  The guitars and drums in Rotting Khrist are aktually pretty amazing work. The drummer is just inkredible. He's primarily a "machine gun drummer (of course, first heard in reference to Rotting Khrist)", but just to hear that level of ability...inkredible. And the fact that guitarist/singer Sakis sings and plays with songs like  Glory of Sadness ,  Lex Talionis ,  Coronation of the Serpent ,  Exiled Ark(c)hangels ...they're all really pretty fast. The bassist pretty mukh does what the guitars do, which is nonetheless outstanding. And then there's the lead, whikh is both melodikal and fast. What a kombo...now sometimes it's more melodikal, but  what's the differenke ?   How kould I ever kome to love this band with its demon shrieking singer and mishmash musik?  Heh, "mishmash" is a kool word, too.
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Allo kompatriots.   Another kool language is German, for the word  Oktoberfest , just because of that "k". I love "k"s, it's the greatest letter. I think I'm going to start replaking all my "c"s with them. So if you see a "k" where a "c" should be, you'll know.  This is quite a kondeskenkion (that's a hard one) of the English language, but I feel it kompletely within my kontrol to manipulate this konfusing yet komprehensive tongue as I see fit, so there.  Actually, the "k" is a lot kooler  within  the word...I would show you the thing, it was on the  urlLink Rotting Khrist website  but not anymore...but there's still kool stuff to see, like some of the tour spots: THESSALONIKH, YDROGEIOS, don't know exaktly where they are or whikh is the equivalent of a kounty or whatever, but there they are. The kommon "yd/ygg" tekhnique is pretty kool too, as in "yggdrasil".  Wait a sek...what the hell am I doing...talking about "k"s and other fun stuff. It's time for the depressing part. And surprisingly, it's not on my part.  Really, you know who you are, just remember I'll be here all night, and I'm pretty mukh awake all that time...I know some other parties will be upset, but...gods...sakrifikes have to be made, I guess. Wonder where my loyalties will lie...it doesn't matter...to whom it may konkern, if you need any help, you know the number.  My dad doesn't have internet or a fukking  phone  anymore, it's SO gay. But I'm going over there anyway. Youse guys know my k(c)ell and whatnaught. I'd hate to push another number on you, I know you have about a thousand of mine as is. Sorry my family sukks.  I have a new favourite song (did you like that extra "u"? I'm overhauling my entire language), what a surprise. This time it's Rotting Khrist's  Between Times . It aktually goes on my beautiful songs list...can you believe it, just the beginning, it's so deep and weird sounding that it kan be klassified as such. It's like  Khronos  (natural "k"!), it makes me feel weird...it's just that  Between Times  actually sounds nice.   I ordered  Khronos  the other day, by the way. I wanted  A Dead Poem , but my dad was ordering off of   urlLink half.com , and  urlLink half.com  didn't have  any  kopies of their  most famous album ...I guess it's kuz they're so rare as is that the most known one goes fast...uh, yeah, that was rokket skienke. O well, for the less analytikal.  That reminds me, Russian has a lot of "k"s.   Ok, that's enough. I swear, I kan't be serious when I'm dong a komplete vokabularian overhaul. Aren't I weird?  Yes.
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      TIRED. And sick.  Hope I'm not up too late tonight.   O wait, it always happens.  Lied.
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow.  I woke up today feeling like it was going to be the worst day ever. So I went on like that for a while, just moping around, and then came study hall in first. I took a nap and now I feel...incredible. A lot less sick than this morning, but still sick, but I can prevent it, I think.   But I feel really tired. Thinking I'm going to have to drink some poison/caffeine to stay awake tonight. God, I don't like what that shit does to me. But I love it so.  It smells like popcorn, this school is weird. 
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      And today...  A HUGE session, it lasted about five hours, during which we only played about 2 1/2... but  we finished  Little Rhyme , actually started on  Bitter . It sounds cool, but a little too slow for me.   And Alex has succumbed to the poisonous melodies of Rotting Christ. We were talking about "machine gun drumming" (the first time I'd ever heard that phrase was in reference to Rotting Christ), and I said, "The greatest machine gun song ever is  Glory of Sadness ," then I attempted to play it on guitar and failed, but got the point across. Then I just started talking about all of their hard songs, mostly the ones on  Khronos  (which I ordered this weekend, whoo!), and especially about the one  If It Ends Tomorrow . He heard it and was like "...God,". And then we sat in my mom's car discussing the fact that if the singer was gone, the band would be great. I argued against it, saying the lyrics wouldn't work if it all wasn't screamed like he did. For instance...in  If It Ends Tomorrow ..."If it ends tomorrow / If it begins / It gives me no sorrow / No tears fall to my lips"...or how about  Glory of Sadness ..."I was straight asleep / It was that night / I fell into it so deep / Then I saw the light"...it just wouldn't work without the screaming like he does. And then the suggested (my mom and Alex) that the words be changed. And I said no. They're Rotting Christ, you can't expect them to talk about anything else except touchy, mostly religious subjects and emotions of fear and sorrow. C'mon.  But Alex liked  If It Ends Tomorrow , nonetheless.  And I played Counterstrike and EVO all weekend. It was a lot of fun, especially when my cousin called (kinda surprised)...since his mom was over at my house this weekend and noticed me playing Counterstrike the whole time, she told Seth and he call, all excited that I was playing. So play we did. He showed me the coolest maps EVER, fy_pool_day, and battlefield_rush. He also talked about d_day, which I've looked at since but haven't played yet. I would this weekend if it weren't for DI...it's keeping me at home this weekend. Sadness.  I had a fun weekend.   But this week is gonna suck.
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Counterstrike is a fun game, did I ever mention?  I played with Seth today, and probably am going to again before the night is over. For anyone that plays,  the  map is fy_pool_day. It's the most fun I've had since owning Alex on Aztec last weekend.  It was the same scenario this morning as yesterday, I woke up dead, no NyQuil this time though. And then my dad asked me, "Want anything dude?" and I was like..."Yeah...get me some Crunch Berries," So the balance of my morning was spent eating Crunch Berries and reading a collector's comic my dad borrowed from this fanbody at his office, called  The Punisher , it was really sick, the last chapter was through the mouth of this guy getting some teeth worked on, a mob guy, and suddenly The Punisher shows up and knocks all his teeth out, it is SO sick.  Gross.  More later, Seth called back.  FunFUNfUN
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OH yeah...  Hats on Monday, don't forget. And I'm probably going to keep the pants as is too, get them drycleaned, maybe. Heh. I don't know.  Just making sure we all remembered.  'Cuz we're all drunk now.  WHOO :)
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Rotting Christ once said, "It took an instant; the struggle was sharp...I remember what you had said: the challenger will prevail,"  And so it is true, in a many of ways, 'tis true. And  why  is this?  SECOND PLACE!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! SECOND PLACE MEANS  VICTORY !!!!!!!!!!!!!! AND NOW...................  State, and this time, we have plenty of time to work on it. Today was a sweep for us, considering the amount of effort prior and our total improv times before...we actually ran  over  the time limit. But it didn't matter, we still beat out Centennial even if they did finish. Which means we can clean up at state with some work.  At first I had thought we were counted down on teamwork because of my showoffishness...then I remembered Franklin's "Harp Girl", who did almost the same thing. So I guess it was simply that we were first, and set as a standard against the rest. That definitely contributed to our downfall...well, perhaps that's too strong of a word. With our work, we could've had first.  I must say, "GO TEAM!", we were fraggin' GREAT compared to the beginning, where we figured we were going to be slaughtered and abdicated from a mere shot at state. So we won by default, we still got  second  and went  first .  So...Sarah, Will, Elizabeth, Rosie, even Lindsey for the first practice, and me too!,  HURRAH! CONGRATULATIONS!  
    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is the day.  I feel a twist of nausea permeate the recesses of my box of a soul, filling the life force therein, corrupting the stuff of mortal existence with unescapable, tumultuous urges to vomit whatever went undigested from the past week or so. As I sit here at this monitor, being bombarded by light gamma rays or whatnaught, eating some leftover chips from my last meal at my grandmother's, and sipping a Cherry Coke with bemused fervor, I feel it, that twisting, serpentine hand of fear disassembling the scraps of my rationality, decaying the origins of my learning and assimilation of scenarios. I feel screwed.  Last night I was assigned to get duck tape for the DI team. Little did we remember, and my grandmother  did , that we are in the middle of a "fear terrorism" mentality and people have bought all duck tape and plastic with which to secure windows against the threat of viral warfare.  People, if the germ wants in, it'll  get  in, don't worry your poor, illogical, and incoherent heads.  With the two rolls given to me by my grandmother, and the one I found at the store while stocking up on  my  antiterroristic formula, caffeine, it gives us a grand total of SCREWED. The ones given me are strange...one is huge and yellow, while the other roll is...dirty. It has particles all over it.  Most likely, however, we have enough.  I woke to my  sister's  alarm clock, who, by the way, isn't at this house this weekend.  It's Getting Hot In Herre , the slut anthem of the new millenium, blasting through her open door, the new cat, Camille, scratching on mine. I was frankly overwhemled by this chaos...bombs really are louder in the morning, especially to teenage boys who  sleep . I rolled out of bed, scratching my frazzled scalp and rubbing the sleep for my eyes as I headed to the pandemonium out there, the Leviathan of noise called Nelly.   After five minutes of experimenting on how to turn off the alarm clock in the dark, and achieving my goal (worse, it happened to be my old one), I walked to the shower as slowly as possible, dreading the dire results of it ending. So, using your powers of deduction, one could ascertain that this shower consumed a quantity no less than that of the Nile's daily flow of water for five thousand years. As it ended the anxiety of which I spoke settled in on my shoulders and started shaking me, choking my being to mutate into a child of his disorder. Staving him is getting sufficiently harder with every glance at the clock, and seeing as how computer have said wonderful device  somewhere  on every screen, his iced grip colds my being with the seconds that wake.  The tick, tick, the incessance of the clock begins to drive me to chaotica, a state of complete euphoric insanity, humanity enveloped with the penchant to destroy in a mad and fearful wake. The tick is louded now, slower, it multiplies and divides faster than its amoebic kin (or is becoming as such at this point), I see my fingers smashing the keys at tremendous speeds, letting the blood from each repeated strike dance upon my lined, tired visage, my heart quickens, my brain begins thinking sans rationality, but with much in speed that the normal self would desire.  The world commences spinning out of control, the clocks are a wall of noise, my heart, on the verge of imploding on itself with its unending repetetions, the bag, once full of chips, both cheesed and plain, now on my head, suffocating my burning lungs, and the suffocation is a release from the madness, but soon becomes another twisted limb of its endless desire to give birth  again  to, to whelp  again , to create one new life in the masses of a sentient being   again  .   &gt;   a</post></Blog>