<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>31,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      haha. *hugs to my hemann twin* does anyone even read this blog? i swear, it's just a form of like, superfluous communication bt me, you, and ragie poo. hey, that rimes.   aww..........that was nice. u know, i should have left more time for u alone. bc of what should have happened. that didn't (?). sorry guys. me and my alone-ness shouldn't affect y'all. lol but glad u guys had fun.  be thankful yue, ur parents will always be there for ya at least. gosh my parents are so SCHIZO!!!! my mom has no qualms about kicking me   out   of cars, and my dad has no qualms leaving me places when i need to get picked up. i swear, between my parents, i'm going to need my own car sooner or later or i'll end up being a waitress in a diner in colorado just because i am stranded. dont ask where that came from. anyway.....  yes, my parents tell me i am a frivolous spender as well. :-( it's alright. but i am definitely getting that graduation snoopy for jason. or i dunno, i have many other, more worthwhile seniors i might wanna give it to. if he's an ass, he aint getting it. lol. or maybe i shant wake up early enuff to shop and get it. or i'll be too lazy to? yes, definitely. well i dunno. well.......most likely anyway.   so main events today: got up at 10.40-ish. rags called. GD you, you and ur waking up skills. ur mad. absolutely mad. goodness. thanks tho, if i had woken up later i would lost it. as in, bee later than i already was.  went shoping about 11.30-ish. got a lovely triple chocolate cake at sam's (later sampled at the party described below, and found to be too sweet for my horrible horrible throat.), and also listened to my dad grumble about the cost of tide. so i decided to be kewl and recomended some all to him after seeing all those supermodel butler commercials. also went shopping for shoes. had fight in the middle of shoe department about color of shoes. i won. i'm so glad my dad is so that if u just stick to ur guns, he'll always give in. he wanted me to get these really garish blue and gray sketchers. and u know my thing with/against sketchrs. so he gave in and i got white adidases. [adidii?] oh right i was supposed to look up what adidas meant. nike=goddes, puma=some sort of cat, reebok=deer thingy, etc etc.   had fun with raghu and yue. yes......she summed it up pretty well. and i added the getting left at borders thing.  the party, what we've all been waiting for: got there late, doesn't matter. had fun experience the west u lifestyle. ig ot it figure dout. bellaire --&gt; jewish and soccer mommish.  west u --&gt; town and country mom. lol. yah  anyway, had loads of fun. nice food , great people (best ppl in earth, i tell ya) and the intelligence level in that house musta been like a 200 IQ or something. i'm sure mine brought it down though. lol.  toasts for ms. medlen, mock round, presentation of gifts and letters, yadayadayadah.   oh but hte funniest part EVEr was the team pictures they took. ms.medlen got like 5 of us in various poses, but hte ones we got weren't that uptight either. of the various hilarious things in it, these are my faves:   thomas and his girly feet kevin and his "i'm a supermodel" look around the back pose. andrew and his short napolean, hand in the jacket pose eric with a wide berthe on every side of him will clutching his crotch larissa feeling up will's ass behind him sneakers on the entire frnt row kelly looking angry paul smirking like franklin and me, tiffnay, josh, and ruidi are just too happy. put all of us + hotze in a room....and damn u could have urself a margarita party. w/o margarita.  (dont worry yue, i wont have a hangover tomorrow morning i didn't drink. although i must say there is now a large half empty bottle of jack daniels on their kitchen counter now.........hehe)  i met noah's gf mary. more details later, or prolly i'll forget so yue ask me.   continuing my correspondence with stubbs. he asked me about the hemann twins today. man was that hilarious.  i'm so boring. ANYWAY.........nam goes to columbia. interns for NBC. was on AC. went to France speaks it fluently. he's me, cept.......a guy? *shudder*  anyway so i am really disappointed in myself cuz Paul said " quatre vingt treize" and it took me 5 minues to figure out. literaly. (that's 93 for those of u who dont know. and i have just disgraced myself EVEN MORE because until 2 seconds ago when i reanalyzed that i thought it said 1813. oh god what's happening to me).  all for now. love you all. see you tomorrow too.  i swear u guys, i am gonna be ur wedding planner u guys make my day. i'll start writing hte toast now since i'm bound to lose some things. oohhh i just thought of something really funny and cruel to say at ur rehearsal dinner. i guess we still haven't got how the secular wedding will go huh? 
    
</post>
<date>30,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      some things just feel so right. ahhh... savoring every moment w/ the one. :)
    
</post>
<date>30,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      ok. forget what i said yesterday for a moment. there are some times i just feel like i should stop caring, b/c some ppl (namely my parents) are just so unreasonable and insensitive. i just want to thank those of you who do care and make this life worth living. ^_^  anyways, today was fun. great time looking through those magazines at borders and commenting on whether the guys had pecs or some other more feminine feature. haha i think i'm in love w/ interior decorating/design now that i've seen so many of those "home" magazines. bed bath and beyond was nice (rags is in love w/ the towels/rugs/pillows! i don't blame him). jane's gonna become a wedding planner and hire someone else to do the photography (she needs to be carefull w/ the zooming) ;). i would so pay $20 for those soft towels. my mom thinks i'm a frivolous spender. so what if i am? it's all about the personal happiness! haha i think AS is catching up to me. and i haven't even read it! oh gawd what is happening to me?  anyways, a early happy b-day to my hemann twin! hope you have a great time at the AC party and NOT be on a hangover tomorrow at graduation. J/K!!! send me the directions so i can get that very important pic! thankie
    
</post>
<date>30,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      you can say that i'm disappointed. or maybe just not overly content? i mean this year has been... just a normal year. dismal in ways. i've witnessed and taken part in the breaking of the fellowship that was (some are convinced never was) BAM. i've watched ppl change from conservative asian to whatever they consider themselves now (jane and i think they're white prep wannabes who will never really be preps b/c they aren't white) and still criticize others for doing the same. i've watched other ppl read certain books *cough cough* and forget that human nature is not evil. i watched the same ppl ruin my life and my happiness for nothing (or maybe they get a kick out of it. who knows/who cares) each consecutive week. still others are just recluses that i no longer hear from (partly b/c they don't want to talk to me). maybe that's what i'll be next year. a hermit. that way i won't be involved in all the politics and such that is part of being in a certain "group." there used to be a time when you were either someone's friend or you weren't. now it's like she's not your friend so i can't be her friend. oh well. i doubt anyone would understand what i'm talking about. if not for lack of trying, for lack of caring. i don't blame you if you don't care. in fact, i see no reason that i do. 
    
</post>
<date>27,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      sorry jane. you know how i am. i don't do something unless i absolutely "have to". anyways, where were you today? me nd rags called you like a hundred times and no one picked up.  aww... you're sick. get better soon twin!  oOo. btw, tell me where the graduation is cuz i have nothing to do on sunday and i'm going to get that pic no matter what! ^_^ yes the crazy jounalist is kicking in. haha  tennis definitely, but lacrosse... don't we need equipment for that? haha  i must say, this first day of summer has been the dullest day of my life! i mean, there's only so much you can do by yourself at home. so bascially after giving up on the TV, phone, and comp, i resorted to completing that vocab workbook thing we never touched in class and looked at prospective cases for next year's LD (which took like an hour to upload to my comp for some reason). -_- somebody save me. tell me how you occupy your time w/o dying of boredom. please!
    
</post>
<date>27,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      i wish yue would write more. it seems like i'm taking it over. which is not what im trying to do.  finals are over. yay! but now i'm sick. boo!   just been checking email. i got one from josh with one of his poems attached. it was great.   he's   great.   i hope this summer is great. i'm not sure if it will be. yue.....lacrosse and tennis this summer right?  hope hte rest of u have fun at kinkaid or rice or wheerever the hell u will be going to.  sunday will be an ordeal. but it'll be nice nevertheless. my embourcheur (god why i can't i speel that) will give out long before "M' . shucks. and hte music still isn't here. maybe i just need a week to relax. but i'm not getting it so that's ok.
    
</post>
<date>27,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      oh right one more thing. it's come to my attention that a realy annoying trait i have is that i am easily swayed by the wrong people.  yue asked me today: "if jason asked you to do something, and liang asked you to do the same thing, who would u rather go with?"  i knew the answer right away. and it hasn't changed despite a few months of personal denial. i dont know why it ihasn't. i LIKE hanging out with liang more , and every experince with jason is merel a disapiintment, and i know it.   i just want to say i'm sorry. mostly to liang cuz she tries so hard to steer me back on the right track, but to everyone. i listen i really do. i was just about to make an excuse for it, but i guess i really shouldn't. i suppose i go for the buzz it/he gives me. it's a drug.
    
</post>
<date>26,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      i've got nothing much to say.  i'm tired. that's basically it. i stayed up late studying geography last night. of course i would have been to sleep 2 hours earlier if eleanor hadn't called wanting help with geometry. not that i am mad, i love it. i love being a teacher. i'd either be a teacher or a writer when i grow up.  but here's seomthing weird. i am sucha hypocrite. i tell ppl not to rely on intentions. i do the same. i tell ppl t o focus. i surely am not. i tell ppl to calm down and stop being immature. put me next to josh and i'm such a baby.  but the thing i feel like writing today is basically, me comforting myself that it's ok to be shallow. selfishness i got down like *snap*, but i need to stop being shallow. i'd always prided myself on not caring if a guy was all weird u know, or if a friend was not hte brightest crayon in the box.  but seriously....i think thre needs to be some limits. i will give anyone a chance, i really will to expect me to not reject someone i think is horribly dull or boring or stupid would just be denying who i am. i refuse to settle. i do not dumb down who i am. but i refuse to sit there and spoonfeed a normal conversatipn to someone. just as i refuse to pretend something about someone is not true, if i dont like it. i'm sick of it. i'll do what i want. and as shallowly as i can.  but then again.......i'm a huger hypocrite than that. lately i've been noticing that all i do is critique my friend's guys. for example, all i do whenever rags calles yue is just yell aat him and fight. i'm sorry i dont mean to be so ....... cynical and sarcastic and a bitch. really i am. i hope ur feeling kewler. and just today i told liang that "he" was a condescending little jerk. how hypocritical of me to day, when jason is probably the evillest of them all, and that i still go for that authoritative, arrogant attitude. infact, i demand it. how i can i detest him for hunching over when i myself go for most chubby guys? i need to calm down. sheesh.  i'm tired. party moved to next week, too many ppl busy, and i'm too pooped out. now all i have to worry about is the AC party. and then starting work at hte zoo. and crap. and getting meena to finish AS so i can give it to eleanor.  that book should come with a warning "WARNING: May wash your brain and cause extreme sarcasm, cynicism, arrogance, and egoism."  oh right, the reason i was evil is egoism may not be the same thing as egotism, but it sure does lead that way, which is why i need to turn back around.  but u know what, i think i'd trade all the attention and glamour and succes in the world for some peace. xi gasped when is aid that, and i was offended htat he did so.  if someone offered me to bypass the glory waiting for me in school and a career, i'd accept if i'd get a husband, a couple kids, and a farm in new zealand in exchange. plus a few good books.   i'm so tired. 
    
</post>
<date>26,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Shoe Dog  hopefully that helps narrow down your choices somewhat... it's scary how many diff. types of shoes there are out there... hehe  GO SQUASHES/MELONS/ZUCCHINIS/CUCUMBERS!!!  note: i am not isane
    
</post>
<date>25,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      wow. blogger is pretty unsafe. i tried to click on yue's link for pics, only to discover that it was taking awhile to load, so i clicked on back to just write a post,, and then go look at pics. -_- and it actually took me BACK!  to here....the unsafeness of it all. sheesh.  well anyway, as yue says, we did have rather...er.....discussion about pretty sensitive subjects. everyone we know is a prude. just about........rags, the most, abraham says SOMETHING at least....and well jason and kyle. u know how thye are. not that they are tell all, but if u ask a Q they will say everything that anyone could want to know. that we didn't want to know it, but if we hadn't, it would have been odd. not that we are great terms or anything either.  wow, and now blogger is constantly renewing the same pages with the posts. oh....apparently i have DHTML on THIS computer so it works out nice. i think it's cuz i've neglected to update my IE on that one. sheesh. it's the same.....!  anyway........not much to say except a bunch of literary comments.  Tender is the Night - has got to be hte second best book i've EVER read. damn you jane austin..u really suck. dont even get me started on what a phony dickens is. Daniel Defoe, i forgive you. u are still welcome in my sphere of influence.  The Catcher in the Rye  - has got to be the BEST book i've EVER EVER EVER read. yue says there is no point. at this point i cant really deny that, since i haven't found the point either. but really......it feels like thre IS one. i'm going to go read the cliff notes to it and see what the point is. anyway, i still think it's great. the digressions, the swearin, the run on sentences just about kill me. see? now i'm even talking like holden. holden caulfield.....man tha'ts gotta be the sexiest name ever. haha maybe i just like it bc it reminds me of my unedited manuscript, cept it's actually somewhat interesting and non-party of fivish. or, it could just be because he is in love with a girl named jane who he wont call. oh well.  what ever it is, i was up really late last night analyzing my life bc of it. im such a wreck. damn you atlas shrugged. i'm a cynical, sarcastic bitch. everything that comes from my mouth is a cynicism. not that i am not happier, but what is it really? it's.......nothing. i have no feelings. i am devoid of any non-objective emotions. i am not ever insanely happy, nor does anything ever move me to tears anymore besides cheesy movies. i can't even pretend that i love anyone anymore. of course, i really care for all of u guys and i worry about ur helathy/safety/feelings and all but.......that feeling. where your chest just wells up and you feel like ur going to burst from the warmth. yah, it's gone. replaced merely by a feeling of surprise. this is the most shallow part of it all but i can't even feel anything for a guy anymore. i, who used to fal in love with guys over the internet. i know it's not that the right one hasn't come along. there are so many people who are worthy of me getting a little teary. and i just can't. damn me and my philsophy. i dont even know who i am anymore. i'm......INGRID (symbolically, i actually admire her quite a bit.). i'm losing my chinese values. i dont want to. but i try to lose them purposely. and i try to plunge myself in a world of western capitalism and stoicism. but i hate it when i'm there. AHHHHH. damn you! and i hope the "you" is understood.  anyway, enough of that. i still dont get how yue's foot can get run over and her not be.....u know, in a cast or something. i'm worrying about hairline fractures.......or what u can call worrying inside me.   i'm sorry about ur parents. they are crazy. they really are. the room searching is horrible too.....*sigh*. but we all go thru that. yes, even me and my schizo parents. i wonder, how is liang. she seems happier lately.  itinerary (to remind myself of things to do):  coffee all week; i hope theye njoy the brownines. yes stefan, i've made more cake. tues: english and geo final. storm the admin. go home. slack off. study. wed: geometry. meet hotze. (maybe....a good thing?) argue for evil. AC practice. go home. slack off. study thurs: bio and debate. suck up a lot if my storming the admin hasn't been enough. movies. relax. no wait..i 'll read some more. fri: planning for/going to picnic.  sat: go shopping. must get some "conservative shorts" for the zoo. also, buy a dessert for the AC party. i wonder...pie or cake? or something else....cookies? hmm...i'll ask josh. go to party. mingle with people who will save my soul.  sunday..........sleep. relax. possibly go swimming for hte first time in forever. early morning, deffinitely. play tennis. jog. get exercise. be good to my body. try to recover my sanity in the solace of physical stress. then ti's off to graduation where i can lose my mind again. damn you ragz for getting out of it. i wonder, what shall i wear? oh right.....greeeennnn.  one of these days this summer, i think i will go on a spree of debate clothes. (haha yue....)  but i saw some disposable swimsuits in seventeen. what's the deal with that? how r they disposable?. are htye disposable only cuz they're cheap or cuz they're easy to put on, or what? i dont get it. but they look nice so i think i want some. except i prolly couldnt work it. haha. me and my boyish figure. but i still figure i have more hips than guys. one oft hose "sensitive issues". lol.  Ie is still constanly renewing the bottom window. scary.
    
</post>
<date>25,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      no need to worry, i shall tell now of yesterday's happenings:  life is just great. why? it’s just peach keen. HA! if only I could say that in a non-sarcastic way.  I go to dinner… everything seems fine until they start talking. Two ppl yelling in my ear until I put down my food and go to my room. I can’t sleep. my mom yells at me to finish my food. so I go downstairs again… I don’t know who to listen to, my dad who thinks I have a disease b/c I never speak to him, or my mom, who searched through my room while I was conveniently taking my English final at school. what a life. they keep on talking, both unaware of each other and of me; they don’t see I’ve begun crying. maybe they ignore be b/c they see it as normal. it’s a daily occurrence.  so basically after what seemed like forever of yelling back and forth, they come to this conclusion: 1) i can no longer associate w/ any guys 2) my dad has threatened to call the police if rags calls the house again -_-  and that's all that you will ever need to know about that  today's events: -woke up at 10-ish -got call from jane at 10:50 telling me to meet her and zuhair at borders at 11:30 -go to borders, and get debate definitions from the comm apps book, while david and zuhair do geog (lmao throughout, cuz jane makes me high... hehe) -finds out i'm not the only one w/ crazy azn parents: david's mom hears jane and me talking in the background when he calls her and comes to pick him up -_- -goes to little myako's for lunch (beef teriyaki bowl! i think they cheaped us out though. those slick japanese!) -had interesting convos w/ rags, abe, jason, and kyle about "sensitive issues" haha it was fun! -stopped by bridesmart to look at the ugly dress they have in the display. just as we were about to charge in and demand to see the other prettier one, we discover that they had closed 30 min earlier! arg!!! *gasp*) -went to smoothie king during a deluge of calls from rags... hehe it almost got to the point that the ringer tune was constant (you WILL learn how to dance! and will NOT become a truck!) -returns to borders and decides jane wants her bridal registry there, just so she can look at those cookbooks (i must admit, there were some pretty awesome ones! ^_^) -went home and typed up my debate stuff to send to ppl -update pics (they finally work!!!):  urlLink My Pics!   sorry (you know who you are) i only wish i could take those words back somehow. to repair the damage i've caused.
    
</post>
<date>24,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      let's see... i woke up at 9 today, only to go back to sleep and wake up at 12-1ish. i think i'm becoming narcoleptic. oh well  that was an interesting message by rags' pearland ppl... hehe  stooopid H and those publishers that never have anything in stock! -_- just when i've finally picked my violin up and tune it after a year of neglect, i can't get a bow (of course, i could just go by myself, but where's the fun in that?)!!! argness  jane: stop spazzing about my foot. it's fine. oh yea, if it bothers you that much, talk to him about that thing that he does all the time.  yahoo photos is aggravating me... i wait like 15 minutes for the pics to upload, then they tell me it's completed. but when i go check, NOTHING'S there!!!! something has to be wrong w/ their system or my comp... blish
    
</post>
<date>23,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      friday! the LAST one of this year! woohoo! -&gt; 2 finals down... 4 more to go.  near death experience today (rags please don't feel bad, it's NOT your fault!): we were walking back from meyerland after we both got our chocolate brownie frappucinos, and we are at this crossing sign thingy. the traffic light is red, so we decide we can cross. we get to the middle of the street, then cars start turning from the the other side. he tells me to walk back. i feel something, look up, and realize that a car had run over my foot. i'm fine... but he feels guilty he put me in that position. now he's being overprotective. which is very "awwing" but still... i'm not a baby!  oOo! add on to yesterday's stuff: obv jane can't walk while she's in my house... she kept crawling on her knees everywhere i went!  i think i'm gonna be posting up some pics this weekend if it's fine w/ u guys. please do not sue me for public exposure (is that what they call it?)
    
</post>
<date>22,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      hey everybody. well i just got home. and i'm back online. and not studying. who would have expected that?  i hope my twin and ragz had fun listening to me spread really badly. so do i have a tick or not? oh well...anyway. wow......the control panel is diff than on yue's comp. the note at hte bottom says that i dont have DHTML. wtf?! anyway..................  i decided what to do with my old blog. since it's undeletable (unlike this blog) then i'm stuck with it. and since i'm really weird and stuff then there's nothing i can do about it, and i can't bear to get rid of it. i'll keep it for personal musings that are mostly crap, and which shouldnt be used to waste space on this wonderful one. :-)   please refer to http://ix.1sound.com/schizo if u have ne Q's. lol  as fo rmy yahoo email add.....*sigh* i'm getting rid of it. oh well. i hope the spammers dont find me, they're getting out of hand. how many times do u have to tell someone that you aren't interesting in sexual aids? yetch...  speaking of which......  so there have been two analogies to driving safety these past few days.  1) jon and muthu said during their round "a mentally ill child is like a persistent drunk driver. u can't give them a choice, u have to take away their liscence to ensure public safety" (i can't believe the judge thought that was crap) 2) mr zumwalt pondering to hte entire class why we dont have to have licences before we have sex bc it's just as or more dangerous than driving. *ewwness*  
    
</post>
<date>22,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      we assume you know who we are.  jane is fascinated by: 1) this blog "so much better than ix!" 2) my telephone wiring 3) the window blind remote 4) the backyard 5) the tree in the front yard "it's a flagpole!" 6) my medications 7) empty bottles of chardonnay (don't ask)  things that we *me and yue( can't do together):  1) type 4) talk 7) breathe 2) pull above and 85 in db8. (resentetnt flows thru our veins......) 9) speeel  stuff that happened today: in the morning everyone congregated on the third floor by the windows to hide from the cameras. (jane didn't know this actually worked). jane wasn't there obv. (late)  nothing happened in class. it was a dismal ending to a dismal (yue thinks) year. i thought it was a great yr. the ending sucks tho. yue thinks the second sem was good now.    we found out that i (who else) was schizo as a toddler as well. i relate to u this story:  many years ago when i was 3............  jane's mom: let's go to the carnival jane: NO!! jane's mom: alright then, let's go somehwere else.  5 min later.......  jane: [crying] i want to go to the carnival!!!!!! jane's mom: it's closed.  someone tell me (yue) (*cough* JASON *cough*) how to post pictures.  anecdote of the day:  so i'm in french, and ms.simon says , looking at me "i just love it when ppl white out things and then forget to write nething in the space."  other anecdote of hte day: so me and my twin are searching ALLLLLL day for jason. apparently he was in an AP at lunch. RIGHT. anyway.......so we're at her locker at the end of the day, ready to chargge downstairs and barage him for my YB, when he appears. whether it was pure accident or whether he cared enuff to return it to me, i dont know. anyway, so he comes, returns YB, acts rather coldly, and yue says "pic!" . he says nothing but consents. anyway so we're standing. yue is focusing, and then........the screen blanks out!!!!! apparently the batteries have run out. and he has no finals. and is going to college. fun fun. however, his yb entry did provide SOME solace after shaft told us we had a 88 and 82 respectively, for our 6 week's avgs. -_- 
    
</post>
<date>30,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      i just read the old blog. wow my profile is so scary......listen to this:  "my fetishes: complements, compliments, blue eyes, smart, older, attentive................i just want someone so i can feel like i lived my life with some realized purpose."  that's a GOOD thing , believe me i did not settle for the first guy that came around. bc josh is AWESOME! lol 
    
</post>
<date>29,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      musings for the day:  no no no......that tank top was not a girls' size 16, it was a ladies XS. haha i know, much better. well come on..it IS!   your dad is hilarious.   i just found out that greenday did a remake of "paranoia" by harvey danger. i sure hope the one i dled was the original, there's enough fakeness here to last a lifetime. haha..i like all hte remakes of old songs. one esteemed mr garber finds that a little annoying but it's alright. hee hee hee. i will commercialize him out with me and my wonderful mix of commericial rock and pop. hee hee hee.......but i have yet to be enlighted so oh well.  went swimming today......looked in the mirror. dude ur right, i need to bulk up. wait a sec, if i bulk up, then the proportions will be all wrong again. lol. i couldnt help noticing that i need to do some situps. yees yes i now ur like "WHAT?!" but i mean....if i'm going to be that thin i might as well be consistently thin.  spent the whole day taking advantage of kazaa.   but anyways...i LOVED yesterday!!! being with you guys is really fun. but it's odd really, i had my "lesbian lover" time, my "alone to muse" time, and of course, josh time. lol. oh, but reading that judaism for dummies book was GREAT. i feel really smart. and of course, making myself feel good is the only thing that matters....JK JK!  but i'm still aghast: Old Navy does not carry skirts. or not the kind i was looking for anyway......remember that skirt from Express that i was obsessed with? i went to old navy to see if they ahd a similar, maybe a little more conservative one, and they didn't!!!! they only had really really really fugly debate skirts (ur right, i dont think prints work anymore) or like, jean ones that worked equally as badly. *tear* when will the day come when the khaki skirt will receive its glory?  hope u enjoy the beans.......i used to like em, but isn't it annoying how they keep getting stuck in ur teeth? and especially with the braces now.  i went over to josh's and had a very good time. his dad makes ribs   love all u guys.......... i spent hte whole day downloading stuff. i think i mighta said that already, but now i feel like abusing kazaa so tell me more stuff to download. i'll just write it down on te dry erase board and have an ass spanking good time ;-)  justin's back from camp. poor guy.  ani ohevet otrach, your judaica scholar
    
</post>
<date>29,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      ahh geezus... you are supposed to "happly oblige" whenever someone offers you a jelly belly... but no no  no ... mr. garber wants to avoid anything i give him apparently and the resentment continues.  i brought home that jar and my parents are once again aghast at my senseless spending. my dad thinks that all the jelly beans taste the same... so we made him close his eyes and try to guess which ones were which. he didn't get any correct.  i couldn't even tell which were which. even though they gave you a color key and such, the markings on the beans were quite obscure and there are like 10 kinds that are all orange!!! how am i supposed to tell the difference between an orange juice and a tangerine?!?!  i cannot believe that old navy's childrens size 16 is too big for you! haha you need to like bulk up majorly! j/k i love you just the way you are!!! *hugs* (oh gawd there's me and my bi thing again. hahaha)  btw: bertie bott's every flavor beans are made by jelly belly. i wonder if they did anything to the vomit flavored ones so that ppl will actually eat them?
    
</post>
<date>28,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      oh begeezus. parents. *shakes head* well, asian parents anyway....not even jewish parents can compare to them. i was talking to eleanor today, and apparently carly ( u know, from the zoo) is really out there sometimes. poor thing. she needs the loving care of an asian friends.......lol look how nicely eleanor turned out.  dont worry about your parents. my parents say the same things. *gasp* they think i'm too immatuer to keep friends? lol well i've heard that too, along with "friends at this age are useless, you will just lose them before they get to do anything for you but they will use you [hypocrisy mania here]" and "it's not that i am not allowing you to date, i just think that at this age you are too busy and you are going to get distracted and your grades will fall and you will screw up just like at pearland." salt in the wound all the way......but hopefully we can provide each other with a little water to rinse it out. why the symbolism today? i have no idea.  my day was actually rather dismal. i got up early, went to Uh with eleanor. we got all excited and went to lunch early with a bunch of uncut evidence to work while eating. well.......we had an early lunch (i got a LARGE chili and it nearly killed me, her large frosty nearly killed her as well. why is there no meds. at wendy's?), and then teh scientist came on and we got all "awww" so we were just like holding each other on the couch watching it. yes yes yes......beacoup de strange looks. well, qu'est-ce que je peux dire? lol. you know we'd do the same thing....i'm sure josh is saying right now "what freshmen" and shaking his head. lol.  but anyhows we get back and basically no more work get done because depression, anxiety, and panic attacks set in.  after independent reviews by josh, avinash, mr stubbs AND rach, the sad truth is that me and eleanor's evidence is pretty shitty. yes yes, most of them tried to spare our sensitive feelings and they dress it up but u know we're not stupid. at least rach was really nice about it though and he was all "well it's good stuff u just need to get deeper in the arg" and he kept smiling and those blue eyes kept twinkling with suppressed frustration and laughter and then when he left he offered to look for a few cards for us. wow, what an awesome coach. HE ROCKS!!!! lol i heard that he pulled a knife on shaft at a gas station. that i highly doubt as a) mr rach rocks and b) this story was told by shaft, but either way he deserved/deserves it. the next time i see him i think i'll "spill" hot coffee in his crotch.  so anyhows, josh leaves and i leave with him, he is doing some stuff with his dad so i go home. still depressed, bc now i've got stuff to do but not in a cool setting so i am all "i'll just go burn a cd". well......since compiling from multiple cd's was harder than i thought (but thank goodness i have a decent burner the stories i hear from eleanor's and jason's burner's were really disturbing), it took like an hour and a half. well of course, there is incompetence on my part as well, as always, so lol.....but anyway......in the end it turned out. it's pretty good too, cept i got pissed off cuz one of the best songs in the world wouldn't burn (anti-piracy software?) and i couldn't put it on there, and i had to substitute it for a less good song.   anyway, so yah just in case anyone wants to know what is the best song in the world by the cheapest most bloated recording label ever is...it's "angel" by sarah mclachlan. i demand all of you...DL it now!!!  not much else has happened. blogging, on aim, email. oh, i changed my signature and stationary. the stationary is now permanently "clear day" and my signature is basically a pretty naggy message telling you guys to all be happy. lol.   geez............u know what, i think i am really into that soccer mom thing. i was reading ur thing about u starving in college, but u konw what? u wont starve! i'll cook for u. i know u think i'm pretty incompetent at it, but really i think i'm starting to get it.....*cough* cough* but i still dont know anything so *cough* what i'd like for my birthday are *cough* cookbooks. lol. and sure, that "growing up chinese" book by iris chang cant hurt but watch it be the joy luck club all over........lol. but at least u wont be hungry in the mornings.........i hear my pancakes are lovely. :-) but my parents have to stop cheaping out and buying margarine. it didn't go so well.....or i guess they could just buy me a gallon of whipping cream and i could "shake, shake, shake ..... shake shake shake......shake my BUTTER". lol.  anyway.......yah since i'm bored and this is always a fun topic, ill talk more about our psycho parents.  your parents are really really cool in one respect: they are predictable. the stability....man i love it. haha maybe that's why i crave it, cuz my parents never gave me any, and bc i have none to offer anyone else. lol. well...i guess that goes back to the soccer mom thing. i just realized, i have been talking in circular tangents thoughout this whole post........................lol. but yah, they are predictably....uber conservative. dont worry, my parents are racists too (plus whatever not liking jewish ppl is).  but haha they ARE oblivious. i still dont get what you mean by that "i think your mom suspects" thing. how could she? lol she prolly just thinks i am getting too much into debate and eleanor. as for debaet, well i've heard that lecture before (it's taking over ur life!), and the eleanor lecture too (she's too crazy; she'll take over ur life!) but good thing she would not suspect the lesbian thing. haha, if i really was eleanor's girlfriend there'd be no diff in my habits so oh well. lol. woh, that came out wrong. lol. well u know what i mean.  tell rags to call me dammit...i'm not mad at him and he SUCKS for thinking that. kristy says liang has accepted josh? the total flipside worries me. and makes me think she's still being weird. *sigh* well it is sort of my fault for not calling. i will i will.....but geez i get home so late, i spend so long online......and then it's too late to call. sheesh.   now i'm just tired. my neck is aching.................  someone remind me to download all those songs, strongbad videos, the scientist video, the windows media update, and i guess it wouldn't hurt to try and delete my old blog. *shudder* those days absolutely scare me. haha i am going to reread them and get really freaked out. see, i told u a blog was a good idea........  well that's all for now.   ani ohevet otach!   jane
    
</post>
<date>27,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      my D drive is playing tricks w/ me. i'm trying to update my pics, right? so i put the CD-RW where i stored all my pics into the drive... and it shows up and tells me i've only got like 4.18 MB worth of pics on there when i know i should have like close to 300 MB of stuff. gah...
    
</post>
<date>27,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      the grade isn't terrible (1450) but my dad isn't too impressed (*gasp* you can only get into UT/Rice!?!). he tells me to do better the next time i take it... only now he can't say anything cuz i got that grade despite preparing for it. HA! man... he's expecting like a perfect score or something the next time... begeezus (however you spell that word... hehe)  sample of a daily dinner anecdote (this "joke" was told today by dad): one chinese family had an only child. a daughter. she went off and got involved w/ a black man. her family gave her an ultimatum: either marry the guy and be disowned... or find a "proper" [Caucasian] guy to marry.  i don't get what's so funny about that. but supposedly my dad's friend (who told him this story) told him to give his daughter a proper (racist, i'll bet) upbringing so my future's not "wasted". that's not funny either. gawd... i can't believe my own parents are still like that. my dad blames it on Chinese society... which has historically been closed and therefore does not welcome people of other races w/ open arms/hearts (so he says). but you'd think that after spending so much time abroad he would have become more tolerant? guess not.  we decide to go to the store after dinner to buy goggles. i turn the radio to 94.5 and dad starts listening to this song. he then  asks  (the radio or the guy singing?) "how do you know?" in response to the song lyrics, which where like "i don't think anyone feels the way i do... about you now". GAH!!! i wanted to strangle him so bad. so me and my mom had to explain to him that music is about self expression and art... not science! geez!!!!!  when we're at the store... my dad comments on how many b-day gifts i had to buy lately. he suggests to me to not have as many friends so i wouldn't have to spend  his  precious money to buy so many presents. i asked him how he would like it if ppl were stringent when it came time for them to buy him gifts.  we then get into a discussion about "jane's friend who is a boy" (i told them the goggles were for your friend so they wouldn't get suspicious). dad assumes that i'm only buying something to save face for you. he also says (get this) that any friend of jane's won't be her friend for long. apparently he thinks your too young to keep your friends or something... geh!!! again... the need to strangle. my mom still remembers jason from "the pizza place" so we talk about him. i tell them he's already graduated (they asked how old he was) and that he was going to trinity for college. so i gather that my dad's boss's wife also went there b/c UT austin was "too big".  i comment on how i thought that the yeast balls my mom bought look like food... and she says "then let the yeast ferment in your stomach" nice, huh?  and to add to all of that, i get a mosquito bite or swelling where the fire ant bit me... grrr. ooo btw the only mosquito that currently resides in my house just happens to live in my bathroom. i spent most of wednesday trying to get him... but he just decides to hide out in the hinges of the cabinets! ARG!! i guess i'll risk west nile then.  i desparately need to finish HP5 so i'll let jane blog now
    
</post>
<date>27,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      oh DAMNATION!!! SAT scores are in. i really don't want to see what it is. *crosses fingers*
    
</post>
<date>27,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      my parents have officially become slackers. i woke up today to the smell of chinese food wafting from the dining room... only to find out that they have ordered in from silver palace (btw...  does  that place look tacky now or what? i mean... neon green signs??? what were they thinking? their owner better be chinese or there would just be no way to explain it). i'm not complaining that the food was bad (it was a pleasant change from what my mom usually makes) but gawd... what am i gonna do in college when there's no meal at saturday evening and i'm by myself in the dorm starving? haha you all are going to have to teach me how to cook one day.  speaking of college... my dad has this crazy idea that we should start college visits this year... in fact... this July 4th!!! he wants me to go see the UT austin campus... under the pretense of visiting his old buddies there. somebody needs to get me a closet so i can hide in it until they issue a missing person's report. haha  anyways... sorry for the lack of details... there's really so much you can say about a person w/ no life.
    
</post>
<date>27,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      wow, you gotta love the supreme court. well.......almost. thank goodness sodomy laws are out. i can't believe that though, omg there must be a million homosexuals getting it on every night in texas, yet apparently its been illegal the whole time. it's about time someone got rid of those laws. besides being sort of oppressive and overly conservative, nobody listens to them anyway.  but that aff action thing is still ticking me off severely. -_-  anyway.....well i just realized i didn't have that much to say after last night.  zoo shorts just came in. damn, they are cute. i feel sporty. almost as sporty as if i was wearing the lacrosse skirt.  speaking of which, i had my interview with claire today. (she was in lax too) haha, she said "haha, u like the skirt? u can have mine." i can't imagine why. it's really cute but she seems more into savvy chic than preppy plaid and cute. lol. makes sense makes sense.....cosmopolitan verteran reporter, teaching flegding staff writer the ways of the world.....er...bellaire.  anyhows, so the interview went well. i think she might think i'm a little psycho, with me and my forced overenthusiasm. yue, i figured it out: the way to seem not bitchy, yet not to be from aluhbama, is to be overly enthusiastic. that's it!!!! so, there's hick jane, there's bitch debater jane, and then there's wonderful excited and overly spontaneous/smiley/frog on morphine jane. ;-) rememeber that?  oh WHOOPS! dude, get online, and remove the automatic signin from ur mom's aim at work cuz i just went crazy on her and told her all this stuff and she just replied "i am yue's mother." good thing i didn't say anything........incriminating lol.  i dunno why i am so hyper, i didn't sleep till 2.30, got up early this morning, and bennet spent the whole day making fun of me for my lethargy and "bahbah" spent the day coo-ing at me for it.  anyway....................  casblanca is still a damn good movie. still not as good as forrest gump though. i wonder, is there really a greenbeaux, alabama? hummers........................  not much else to say. working on debate. still not gonna get turned in tomorrow though. me and eleanor will tell rach: yah, we promise we're done, we just forgot ot bring hte file, it's on her dresser!   join cx damn you! lol u can be meena's partner if she decides to stay, or raghu's if he decides to do it at all.  is sunday good for y'all? going out i mean. i'm about to call you and meena and rags to verify so ima go now................  je vous aime!  jane
    
</post>
<date>26,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      ooohh!!! so  thats  how you got it to change. i was about to say, whoever made that template sure has a worse sense of style than Vogue Living. hahahahaha. lol but that's GREAT. omg ur right, the tomato theme could so work....html aye? *cough* you just go ahead and do that, i'll stand aside and not screw things up. ;-)  anyway, wow so who's the vague one now? lol. so what's up.....the lack of details is getting to me. srry about that phone thing today, but you know how psycho my mother is.   just got back from josh's house. ok, not just but basically the lack of a life goes on. we rented casblanca....it was nice! it's a good movie, i thought it would end just as dismally as that other classic 50's movie, Gone With the Wind, but you know what, it was good. cept i feel sorry for all the "bigger people" out there, who never get rewarded with simplicity and ease. hmmm..hmm...hmm.....i feel like doggie number #3. oh, and his dad kept coming in the room. lol it's alright when eleanor is there, she doesn't care but the asian-jewish parent who comes in to check on you is not exactly the same.  going to work tomorrow......arg.........  speaking of the zoo, robby, rob, and chris came by in the middle of the movie. so it's THAT chris!!!!! wow, how serendipitous that i knew him too....(from band, the great melder of cliques). so that just makes rob that id ont know. lol but he seems nice, he was wearing lovely swim trunks to match his hawaiian theme for the day. robby seemed a little starved for attention.....poor guy so that's what it is. lol he's alright.  well my dad just barged in the room and told me to go to sleep so this is to be continued.............................  ps josh reads this too. 
    
</post>
<date>25,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      ooohhh... why won't the margin turn green? so far the furthest i've got is the borders... grr this is angering me.  *looking through html book*
    
</post>
<date>25,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      have you downloaded "a voice within" yet? tell me what you think of it.  i think rags is the only other person besides us to check this blog for updates. haha it  is  just a convo between us. ^_^
    
</post>
<date>25,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      okay... i need to breathe...  the lightning is really freaking me out now... i mean i can  feel  it crashing down on earth... gah that is not a good sign!!!  i wonder how i ever lived in michigan... what with the daily tornado warnings during the summer thunderstorms and such... but at least they have basements to hide out in... :/  it's stopped raining... it's  just  thundering now. ahh!!! someone save me...  ok... it's begun to pelt rain now... at least it's a normal thunderstorm...
    
</post>
<date>25,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      congrats on making your continental breakfast jane!  yea... *sigh* the summer doldrums... rags says he needs a time and place for our "outing". call me  HP5 is progressing... although very slowly. cuz i start reading it at like 11 pm and i drift in and out of sleep while reading.  yay! it's raining!!! i see huge flashes of lightning (like those in cartoons that make the x-rays) but somehow the sound of rain against the window pane is still comforting... ahh now is THE time to curl up w/ my terry cloth blanket and read HP... but alas i'm in the computer chair blogging!  i woke up at 1 today due to that weird dream...   oh gawd... what is that thing they tell u about lightning and thunder and how you can tell when it's close to you? cuz now i just heard the thunder like as it was flashing... i believe i'm dangerously close to it... so being on the comp maybe not be such a good idea... eee  oh about the garish orange color... i tried to make the margin green so it could be the tomato theme... but as of yet (obviously) the template has not cooperated. i will figure it out. surely but slowly (i could read my mom's html book if i get really desparate)!
    
</post>
<date>25,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      summer's dismality has set in. i think it's really similar to the atrophy of winter break cept now i'm too unfocused to not notice.   possible solutions? - work on debate (assignemtsn are due this sat after all) - eat (we all know i need to tr harder) - start practicing clarinet again - piano once more? (NOO!!! torture for everyone's ears, plus angry frustration turned homicidal rampage for me) - sit on the couch and watch more movies (ugh) - try to get into the zoo (and redeem my black sheep status) - get out more and try to have a life outside of eleanor and josh. (how so when nobody else either goes to rice all week or cant get out either)  hmm........oh well. events for today............  i got up today at 11 (woohoo! somebody called me at 10.30 but my mom didn't know who. damn i should have gotten off my lazy ass).  decided to do a little self-indulgence with the soccer mom/eating thing. i made myself - chocolate smoothie - scrambled eggs (4) - pancakes ( 8) - toast (2 slices) - instant sausage (2)  of course, i got all the condiments: ketchup for the eggs, butter for the toast and pancakes, jelly for toast, sat down to eat and watch LOTR once more......and then i just lost it. its half an hour later. eggs are eaten, half a slice of toast is gone, while the beautiful pancakes and sausage are just sitting there......getting cold.......i should take a picture. like in the filter song. actually stuff i make never turns out this good so i really ought to. but anyway, point is, i got sick of eating, i got bored of the movie after watching boromir try to exploit frodo in a desperate rage, and now i'm online. reading debate yahoo group emails like a pathetic loser. and i can't even go out cuz its raining madly, the sky looks horrible, and i have tons of other stuff i should be doing.  *sigh* plans for today - call salem ASAP. no wait, better yet, email him. call tomorrow....??? or next week. procrastination pattie strikes once more. - practice clarinet. i might as well indulge myself. - do a little debate work. thank goodness rach sent us another way to get into lexis. sorry josh, you just have a little more integrity than i do. but that's a good thing. ;-)  wow my life is boring. grrrrr. maybe i should go take a rain jog. haha my parents would absolutely love that. i need to find my poncho...........the rains getting loud. spec-fucking-tacular.  i'm so bored.  sorry about ur allergies, yue. it sucks to ahve the sniffles.......ewwww. computer paper. now THAT sucks. what are u on again? allegra?  nice change of colors, but isn't he garish orange clashing with the baby blue? lol it's ok. how did u do it? maybe we can fix it so that it has a tangible theme.  eek....one more month. sorry.......but i've heard that same story before. *sigh* maybe we can get our braces off together.........in 3 months. hahaha.  u know what i'm going to do? put on some angry music to drown out the rain noise (it's not happy rain noise like usual, it's angry rain noise and i think my computer is getting equally as pissed at me.........illegal ops up the schizza), and work madly on debate. WOOHOO!!!!!   i miss calamity jane. :-( how's HP5 going? love ya lots...................  ms. zhou  
    
</post>
<date>25,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      i'm gonna see if i can change the appearance of this thing... hope i don't mess it up too badly! *crosses fingers*
    
</post>
<date>23,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      oh and btw.. b/c my allergy meds have run out and i'm not getting any more until next week... and i have run out of kleenex besides on my car... which is completely useless to me... i spent much of this morning sniffling and sneezing into paper towels (an improvement from that debate round where all they had in the room was plain computer paper... and  that  was  pain ful)  and that's the last you'll hear about the many things that ail me
    
</post>
<date>23,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      GRRRR... ONE MORE MONTH!!! HE TOLD ME TODAY WAS THE LAST TIME, BUT NO... ALL THE LADIES DO IS COMMENT ON MY "AMAZING" GUMS AND MAKE ME COME BACK ON JULY 30. STOOOPID ORTHODONTISTS!!!  remind me to get some italian ice cream sometime ^_^
    
</post>
<date>23,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      well i suppose i have some making up to do for my absolutely dismal posts the last few weeks.  zoo went....dismally. i suppose my insensitivity (or what josh lovingly calls getting over stuff easily) made me not feel it as much as some other ppl, but well basically i came late as always with carly, and we spent the morning together while the "chosen clerical" went over to the commisary to do their thing. i didn't care much, since i much prefer info booth to washing thousands and thousands of grapes for the birds, and honestly and truly we got stuff done. and had fun all the while.  but then while sheera and tinting   put poor carly! she is such a nice person, and here they are thinking she has changed for the worse and all, when in actuality she is the GREATEST PERSON EVER!!!!!! i mean, shes so fun and jovial and she still gets things done and i can't fucking believe that lauren and yusra and zuhair dont see that. and god bless deb, she is so cool. the COOLEST. EVER!!!!!  so anyway, after a puppet show strike (no thanks to lauren), me and carly go over to the DC on detour to the guard shack, and we make butter. i suppose i shook my jar incompetently and it just turned out as pretty frothy cream so after a demonstration by yue mine turns out - not well, but it turns out. so i refuse salt on advice from yue, and i eat the ritzes. prolly like 4 or 5 which makes me feel a little guilty since im a get some neway but lol ANYWAY......they are addictive. u couldn't even taste the butter. the DC ppl got a kick outa the walking sticks. i miss sarah. and bennet is AWESOME. days w/o barbara....*heaven*. that is the true meaning of theatrical zoocrew. i hope she fullfills her dream, takes some college math, and gets her teaching degree. for everyone's sake. :-D  well basically that was it. went home, and all the stuff happened as yue said.  except, right after zoo we saw raghu and she showed him "the scientist". aftre a condescending glance and a nonchalant "i dont play sheet music like  that ", the subject was dropped after a few attempts to stimulate convo by saying how horrible i was at it. my dad comes shortly thereafter, and so does raghu's mom. in the car, yue is bothered by it a little bit by how insensitive he is being once again. but the subject is dropped, and we go to the music store.  however, i opened up my email this morning and received a rather long, desperate sounding one from rags and realize they must have had a fight about it. *shakes head* u guys will work it out i promise, u always do, but honestly raghu, u should learn something from these experiences. read the reply. and both of u tell me when this is resolved.......i know it will be.   so i played the scientist at HH. wow that's the BEST it's ever been. though i can't control rythyms on either side (or spell rythyms) at least the correct chords were being played in sort of the right places of the melody). but i loved the shiny kiawa!!! damn those stupid overly shiny/yellow buffets.  so we come home, i become impatient, we burn the idiot's guide for yue, josh calls, i wait, josh calls again, we go, and i am happy but really anxious and the results of the day.  really i am sorry for the both of u if the day turned out as dismally as i fear it has.  (OH GOD!!!! I AM WATCHING SOAPS RIGHT NOW........THE WRONGNESS OF IT ALL!!!!!!!)  anyway...i'm so sory!!!! i really am. i wasn't sure how the compatibility of it all would work out, despite the success with eleanor, bc i mean yue is really watching out for me bc of what's happened before, and i know that really did come out as resentment, and i know josh's being a senior, not too talkative, didn't work out well..  but i love you BOTH! so much!!! yue you are like my twin, my best friend, and i love you for watching out for me!! but trust me when i say, that i know what i am with doing with josh. i suppose you are right, the feelings aren't exactly as strong as with jason (but anyway those feelings were both false and wasted), but this is REAL. i love him. and he loves me. and even though u think i am doing this merely bc i need someone (anyone u think), he is the  someone  that i need with me.   and the lulls...well i can't say that was the best of days. but it doesn't matter. i just love being with him at all.......i love finding out things about him, i love when i telll him things about myself, and i am sure as soon as we have more in common (friends, classes, clubs, grade level?) then the lulls will stop. but it's ok. we've talked about lulls before, and it's good. it really is. the convent in france will have to wait.  oh right, well anyways i'm sure u have the whole ER situation good. i never ended up going to the ER, but like half an hour after you left my dad came back and he at least called the ER, and after some "is it really necessary to bring her in?" stuff they were just like.....whatever u unfeeling asian parent there's nothng we can do anymore. *rolls eyes*. but it was alright, by that time, i suppose the benadryl had kicked in and the itching wasn't the eternal fires of hell anymore, and i was so tired from being so tense i just went to sleep. yep, on the couch.   but MAN i am so pissed off. i almost wish you had driven me to the ER, but yah that woulda been really really weird. i love you for offering though, and i appreciate you SOO much. but bejesus.....  ok, in yue' words, my mom is the typical asian: she'll do something, as long as it doesn't have to do with beaucracy or paperwork etc etc. she prolly actually woulda driven me if it was just me and her.  but my dad. omg...sometimes (most of the time) i think he is the rational one. after all...he drives on highways, made me start playing hte clarinet and quit piano, fought for me so hard to go to bellaire desp potential zoning issues and my flings with both debakey and HSPVA. and he was the one who yelled at my counselor, drove me to all those debate tournaments....wait a minute.  speaking of debate tournaments, he was the one who essentially blamed my not qualling on myself, first and foremost, despite the fact that he had never seen me debate before, i went against crosby A who wanted it so bad they made a new aff, lost the coin flip, and was basically running on an empty tank cuz id been there till midnite both days. -_-  so he is schizo. truly and honesty schizo. suppose he puts me on ther ight path to life. but what happens when he wants me to take a detour and i think otherwise??????   i wonder about my parents sometimes. which makes me realize why my friends are my real family. *sigh*  ya lublu tebya te amo yo te amo WO AI NI and  ani ohevet othach!!!!!!!!  i love you guys so much.  jane
    
</post>
<date>23,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      after zoo yesterday, we (jane and i) went to the music store to pick up her stuff. we browsed through the piano section to find a "quiet" one so she can play "the scientist" for me. the beginning chords actually sound correct, but when she started to play the melody on her other hand, she couldn't quite control the rythms of both hands.  we went to her house after that. she impatiently waited for josh to call while i read her diay and discovered she's been schizo all her life. haha. and i discovered "the idiot's guide to classical music" (kinda dissapointed though... cuz it's only clips of the actual pieces... hehe i want the full versions!)  we walked over to the park and met josh on the way. i believe my first words to him were "run... away from her!" (we were like 100 yards away from him and jane was talking about how she ran to him the last time... and i felt inclined to yell that... hehe) so i guess i sounded pretty resentful and that was definitely not the first impression i wanted to give to the captain of next year's AC team. but what else could i say? oh well. so what if he's the captain? acceptance into the team shouldn't be determined based on personal bias anyways. so i have nothing to worry about... besides the fact that i can't even take the test properly! haha  we played on swings for a while. despite my warnings... jane decided to get herself stuck in one of those kid swings. so we had some fun getting her out. then she tried to jump from the swing into josh's arms. on her first attempt, she kinda landed on the wood chips at the base of the swing set (josh wasn't paying much attention cuz he thought she wouldn't jump yet) while some ppl drove by and jeered. on her second attempt she made it, but just barely. those stupid ppl drove around again and flicked us off. then she sat in josh's lap (talk about withholding!) and tried to swing. i pushed them, but they were too heavy for the swing to move significantly. they moved to the bleachers to "do their thing" while i messed around in the empty playground. the see-saw thingies were so miniature! and sliding off the tube thing... well let's just say that i was almost the length of it.  i finally walk over to them (i didn't want to disturb them) and find their convo lacking. so we pick up the subject of sports and me and josh have a disagreement on why the vikings sucked last year. we discover that jane has a HUGE developing rash on her hand so we hurry home and take steps to control it: 1)washed vigorously with ivory soap (it actually floats! haha) 2)cover affected area w/ pack of ice 3)calomine lotion and cortisone cream up the shizza! hehe 4)more ice to numb her hand so she won't scratch it  the swelling/redness decreased on her hand, inflammations flared up on the rest of her body. ahh! jane thought she was going to die and that she was suffering condemnation from God. liang called and jane thought it was God for like 5 seconds (she prayed as she had never done in all her life).  i continue reading the diary and discover prevalent themes since the time she was 8: -wanting to be loved and to have someone to love -anger @ parents -thinking she is perfect -wanting to kill ppl and get revenge -schizoness ("HSPVA ROX/SUX!!!!" hahah)  i spent the rest of my time trying to prevent her from scratching herself (you can't trick me!). josh offered to take her to the ER, but that would just be awkward... she shows her rash to her dad and he acts all nonchalantly about it, so we decide to show it to her mom and see if she at least freaks out. she did, and was all paranoid about what caused it. still, her parents refuse to take her to the ER and make her take benadryl. her mom tried to get her to take her precription pills but she's afraid of mixing meds (aspirin+ibuprofen=internal bleeding   i hope you're better now... or at least is still resisting the urge to scratch.   i realized how lucky i am to have found someone with whom i can be myself and speak my thoughts. someone with whom there never needs to be a pretense. someone i can love without regrets.  jane realized that she cares for josh, but not as much as she did for jason. maybe this whole thing happened too soon after jason left. she was looking for someone... anyone to be with. the thought of instability scares her. she's still deliberating whether to end it. i hope the decision you make is because of the right reasons.  your dad was so oblivious at dinner! i mean... he was sitting right there and didn't so much as act like he heard us.  jason is evil, so is josh... for taking advantage of someone so vulnerable... knowing she will take flattery and attention in whichever way she can get it. may they suffer eternal damnation!
    
</post>
<date>23,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      never mind... gah... so jane explained to me what VC is, and i am the SCHIZZMASTER at it!!!  damn you, pseudonyms!  ^i meant that w/ the best intentions
    
</post>
<date>22,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      today... was pleasantly surreal indeed (another word for it would be magical ;) )  zoo was schedule-ly as always on monday, cuz of barbara's presence. we tried to do sun and sea at 10 but nobody who was able to come onstage showed up and we just read the story. we practiced for the frog show w/ barbara, but did get to do it in the morning cuz we didn't have face paint. at lunch (lisa, the other girl whose name i don't know, and i finished a crossword puzzle in people magazine! yay! go us! NVM that... you ppl don't know or understand the challenges that lie in actually completing one correctly, obviously... tsk tsk tsk) barbara went home to get more whipping cream and sarah got the acryllic paint. we came back late after lunch though, cuz of the puzzle to find barbara and sarah doing the butter thing. we were also about to do the frog thing, we had our faces painted and all, but lisa said she was hurting so we decided to cancel it and just let sarah do an eagle presentation at the normal 3 o'clock story theatre time. we did, however, sing the song to 2 uncooperating children and show they the model of frog's life cycle (with dead specimens very similar to those in the taxonomy lab.. eckiness...) so we finally washed the paint off in the barn restroom (which had a toilet that flushes prepetually, btw). there was a lot of scraping and peeling (that paint stuck on like glue once dry), but after struggling for 20 min. our faces finally looked human again!  k, none of that was what made today so "pleasantly surreal". it was the after zoo bit of the afternoon that made going to the zoo in the first place worthwhile (did that make sense? oh well... it doesn't matter) thank you for coming despite the heat and what common sense might have told you otherwise. so was it a good day? yes, but only because of those moments of pure bliss. ^_^  so this is the stuff i wrote in my journal thing after coming home (cuz i thought i'd sleep but no such luck):  so i fell asleep in the car while thinking about rags. when it came time for me to wake up (we got home) however, my dreams were about ron and hermione and i could hear chevelle's send the pain below in the background (the car radio). the first thing i notice when i got out of the car is that the edges of my socks were wet (we went through the misting thing in the park... twice) man... when i was getting out of my mom's building we were at a corner and i bent down to deel my socks and bumped into this guy, who was given an unexpected jolt. hehe  i think rags should give you some piano lessons. you need them before you destroy the concept of music for future generations. hahaha but seriously, i don't think that the music is that hard.  anyways... my stomach hurts so i'm going to lie down in fetal position and fall asleep again (i wish someone *wink wink* were here to hold me) ahh... *my insides twist*  which reminds me, we made butter today! *shake it up baby... twist and shout!* it was really fun... the music wasn't too bad either (haha we made the children shake to that disco song... can't really remember which movie it was from) i liked the butter w/o the salt better, cuz i thought the ritz crackers were already sufficiently salted. we barely had enough supplies for everyone, and we ended up have just enough for the last camp group (we had to use "recycled" ones that the ppl before didn't want to keep).  so back to bed w/ my book and the monkey (cuz the real one can't be here... what a shame...)  MANGOES ROCK!!! yea you heard me. i love  Mangifera indica !!! haha enough w/ the melon vs. squash fascination... this is something i actually enjoy eating! hehe
    
</post>
<date>22,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      continuing...  anyways, so risa was overjoyed cuz she finally got the kelly clarkson CD she's been waiting for. and guess who was the angel that gave it to her? yes... your's truly. hahaha so we listened to like 3 tracks from it, and kelly sounds like christina aguilera! i dunno what i would call what they do, cuz it's definitely not vibrato or anything else musically that i can describe. i'll just call it digging, and there's plent of it in both their vocals.  after everyone had seen and been horrified at the tremendous amount of calories and fat grams they were consuming by eating the chips (yes jane, there was distorted body image up the schizza; i mean, even weimeng was on a diet! gawd... i don't understand these ppl... *shakes head*), ppl kinda split up (i guess?). liang and kristy called their respective ppls; felona and xin played ping-pong; weimeng, lilly and wanjun played VC (btw, do you how to play that game? cuz everyone says it's a chinese game or something b/c only chinese ppl get it. but i don't get it!!! arg). but they all came downstairs to watch "just married" i thought it was a dismal excuse for a movie, even though the ending was all sweet and aww-inducing and such, but you can only take so much of ashton kutcher's stupidity, you know??? the second movie we watched was "spirited away", and all that i can say about it is that i missed the first 20-30 min. of it and i didn't get the rest of the 2 hour long movie. it was creepy though, and that was surprising of an animated film.  so we had cake (again with the distorted body image!), very good cake, and ppl started filing away and leaving in pairs.  i come home worried about where jane went (she didn't come home until 11:30... you'd think your parents would have more sense than to let you stay out like that... begeezus   so i'm glad nothing drastic happened. and i hope it never does. i also hope you and rags "settle" your dispute... only this time i'm not walking in 110 degree weather to rice only to hear a worthless debate while realizing how irritating he was acting that day.
    
</post>
<date>22,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      i'm listening to jane's horrific butchering of "the scientist" on piano (her keyboard) now. it is beyond belief. i mean, she's had it for 2 hours and still can't figure out the chords (which are 4 just alternating and repeating)! she's leaving her sentences half unfinished cuz she can't do two things at the same time. she'll never be able to get violin, or play this song successfully to josh either... that is if she doesn't get her badly needed lessons soon. so apparently she has problems shifting or something. i hope guitar isn't nearly as terrible for me.  and at risa's party: which jane conveniently missed, if you didn't already know. it was basically like the 8th grade party before we all went to the dance.  to be continued later... perhaps ;)
    
</post>
<date>22,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      why haven't you been posting? i know u read it cuz u quoted it earlier, but oh wells. i guess there is really just one prob: there's not much to say. school is over, we're asian, so there really isn't anything going on...  oh how's this. what was risa's party like? sorry i couldn't make it. i felt sort of crappy bc the whole week i'd been wondering what i should have done, whether i should go or not. yes yes, u have every right to hte me bc i said i would come but i'm reaaaaaaalllllyyyyyyy sorry! i didn't have time to get a present anyway and by the time i left UH it was alrady 5.30. and besides i haven't talked to her in like FOREVER and i dont know anything that's going on with that click......  oh wow. i am getting defensive. how horrible. *sigh* i'm sorry. if it makes u feel any better, eleanor and naeem came along with me and josh on our little anniversary.  how is "the order of the phoenix" coming along.....the cover looks dismal but since we went to that party i feel like getting back in the potter groove. haha, but i think now i am going to go get the book bc my little HP1-4 collection is going to get reeeaaaally lonely. but u know me, i prolly wont. plz lend it to me when ur done...i would still like to see how verbose jo's writing is getting, someone told me there was snogging in this book. how risque. anyway.......  i played DDR on sat at uh. only for like an hour after lunch, but WOW we have been missing out. it's not that bad, it's actually pretty fun. but i guess it's one of those things u have to be "in the mood" for. like studying for bio. there was this senior who went to HBU there and he was helping me out along with matt and eleanor (who eventually ditched me lol) and he was nice.....but maybe he's a little too into it. the ddr, and me. maybe i am too nice, eleanor told me i was talking to him too much, but anyways he asked me out to some mexican restuarant. not too blatantly but it was one of those "so ur here every weekend huh? do u like mexican? oh there's this great place on 59.....maybe we could go there after ur done sometime." things. weird weird weird. yue, be glad ur not in CX......  JOSH!!! PLLEASE JOIN DEBATE!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!  yue, what is ur comment on my eating and sleeping habits?  love u lots  tell rags to call me. and that he is a stupid wimp. until he calls me. ciao  calamity jane  ^ eleanor's name for the hick in me. i tried it out on ppl. it didn't go over so well. but it's addictive. come to think of it, even debater jane has a rather noticeable accent. thanks for bringing it out.....hahaha.
    
</post>
<date>19,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      i'm sooooo glad everything is ok for u. glad it worked out, it would have been horrible if it hadn't. but it has, and everything is better. this has been very healthy. i am so glad for both of u. u guys are both really really awesome friends, and if i didn't have you, (or if ur phones were off AND busy *cough*) then i wouldn't know what to do.  love you guys soooooo much.  oh but guess what......the newsletter is finished. *whew* thank goodness. i got to skip half of the theatrical day, but i'm sure barbara is pissed off now bc 1) we barely did anything this morning and 2) we were gonna to an actual puppet show in the afternoon and i'm sure she wouldn't want to screw with "mr sun and mr sea". jeez.  on the bright side, josh's parents found out about us. they are still rather civil to me, especially his dad, but they give him such a hard time about my being a goy.   on the even brighter side, my parents are suspecting as hell bc apparently eleanor called when i was gone and guess where i was? not at home. maybe she isn't either, bc she didn't come to the zoo today *cough* but anyway i said i walked around meyerland myself but that's a little bit unbelievable bc i was gone for two hours. they kept bugging me about if i was really by myself but i think they are just going to block out hte possibility that i was bc then they were just like "go call claire". speaking of which......  claire from TPP wants to interview me for the cardinal camp issue. *SCORE* i rock. lol.   it's actually been a good day. didn't do anything this morning, was in my forte in the afternoon (not really, apparently unedited, unrevised jane writing sucks monkey balls, even zuhair's mom said it was pathetic, and all my articles were "finalized" by lauren and yusra), and i cried when it finally came outa hte printer. i was about to murder zuhair though bc he wanted to keep moving the pics, and stuff like that. *ahhh* co-editorship. non-theatricalness. the shizziness continues.  so when i got home, i saw josh's dad on the street. weird glances exchanged. when i got to my room, my dad asked me if i was going to sleep and eat. i said no to the sleeping, but i did eat just a little bit.  two bottles of water drunk today...i am proud of myself.  the restlessness continues until 6. and he calls. and he is depressed. now i am worried. i run over and find he is still depressed. so i  am  the optimist in this relationship.  it's alright. he came out of it alright.   but then again i have been not myself lately. not as "gregarious" as i usually am. must drink more coffee...must eat more....must sleep more. all happening. next week? hmm prolly not. haha jk jk....of course it's happening. *shifts eyes*  love all you guys, the frisky one
    
</post>
<date>18,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      so he did call yesterday. at 10. and i noticed 2 things. 1. even though i was mad at him, just hearing his voice calmed me and made me feel better 2. it was painful for me to hear him cry and assume that it was over
    
</post>
<date>17,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      to rags: if you are reading this and feel like shit, don't. it's not that i don't love you anymore, because i do with all my heart. it's just that some of your habits seem more and more annoying and that is something i cannot ignore. something else i can't ignore is that there is nothing you can do to change yourself. not now. so please just give me time and space to think things through, let me decide whether it's worth it.
    
</post>
<date>16,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      i plan on taking a nice long nap when i get home. then wake up at 10 to think through some things. if my mom lets me (she insists on following me everywhere and inspecting everything i bring into the house), maybe i'll go see finding nemo by myself sometime.  i'm sorry if i've neglected my duty as friend for the past... i dunno... 4 months? a lot of time that i'll prolly never finish catching up on. a lot of time perhaps wasted with the wrong person.  so starting tomorrow, i'm gonna see who's actually home if i call during the day (gawd you ppl are so occupied! kinkaid, rice, testmasters, swim team... man...) and try to get back in touch w/ y'all. i can't believe you guys still care even though i've been such a selfish ass and neglected everyone.  thank you so much jane! i don't know what i'll do w/o you.
    
</post>
<date>16,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      well now aren't i just a horrible person?  i really can't support you either way on this w/o thinking that one of you is wrong. of course i still believe that you are right, you always are and his reliability is fickle as my heart is trying so hard for its own sake not to be.   do what you have to do. but remember what used to be there. take a siesta. a trip. a date not at meyerland plaza? call me all you want. i'll be there. for both of you. use me all you like. i dont mind.  but take care of urself the most. just try out a situation in ur head before u do anything. and most of all, stop isolating yourself. call me, call liang, call kristy if u feel like it (this one i'm not gonna force or recommend). call eleanor, call meena, call everyone! they miss you, you know. they want you to call.  and never ever forget i'll always be here for u, and support u no matter WHAT you do. if u want me to be judgemental, i will. if u want me to be practical, no shit i will. if u want me to dabble in some bashing, count me in.  be happy. i want you to be happy. i want everyone to be happy. and not ever feel want or need or disappointment.   ps this is hilarious  [jane walks in, robby is sitting and bored] R: hey janey J: hey robby Daniel: haha, you can't do anything to it cuz it's already robby. R: so how do you know josh? J: from AC and stuff, he's great R: would u go out with him? J: well i am R: [looks stunned, eyes open just a little bit wider than usual. silence for a few seconds] i'm going to have to call him.........  why does everyone say they need to call him?  "For Jane"  Restless dreams pervade my sleep And yet there is a calm that clamors in my ears You are something that night does not keep And yet your presence wipes away the tears, Removes the persistent fears, And I fade into sleep.   
    
</post>
<date>16,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      gawd... can't believe i was that blind. some of the other blog entries make me sick. -_-
    
</post>
<date>16,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      thank God you guys worked your thing out. so much for mediating. haha  he called me to say he's not calling tonight (why did i even bother to pick up? it's not like he ever does. i mean, it's not his fault when he's w/ his parents, but when we were trying to find him at lunch in rice??? geez). didn't ask why i've not said anything to him all day (maybe he doesn't care or notice? he'll prolly call you and ask  if  he  did  notice). just told me he wouldn't call. like i care. HA! the only other words he said to me today were "can i talk to jane alone?", "what is the time? (3 times b/c i didn't answer)", and "where are you?" nice. let's hear that again.  man... why couldn't i see this earlier? maybe it wouldn't have happened had i still kept in touch w/ liang and kristy... eek now i must undo this myself.  &gt;_</post></Blog>