<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         &gt;&gt;&gt; a letter sent to me by Melissa in one of her glory and glowing days ...       Hi Bes...    It's a Sunday, i'm the only phone rep here tonight save for BBand JQ whor'll busy answering emails. And me? My Eshare's all fucked up so I can't answer emails.    I want to text you and ask for the link where you can write what-have-you's but I guess you're sleeping so i thought otherwise.    I'm watching Possession, the movie i love because I can actually relate to it.    I love whatDodo did for me yesterday, Saturday. I was chatting with him at the start of my shift. I mentioned that I was the only rep here. Next thing i knew, he went offline and he showed up at the office.    He brought some pandesal, peanut butter and chicken spread, and grapejuice (which he personally prepared..di masyado matamis, pero ok lang!). How sweet!    I've always imagined someone doing that for me while on my weekend shift. Really nice of him.    He kept me company til5am. He left coz he had to pick her sister up at the bus station.    I think I'm genuinely starting to like him. I didn't know there was a sweet side to him. If only I get to see more of that...a bit of consistency.    Haaay...i was grinning stupidly while I was on my way home.I kinda missed the feeling. I am, as what I've been ranting about for a couple of weeks now, succumbing to what my vulnerable side has been telling me....that I am getting tired of being alone.    To have someone I can share my day with. Perhaps travel to places ive never been to.. discover things together...hohum..I'm starting to need somone to care for me.    Whatever.....  It's just a thought I'm dying to get out of my system.      ~ Meme    
</post>
<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       These weresome letters from Nemo. We'll be celebrating our 3rd year anniversary this December and I couldn't help but reminisce on old times and read old letters...              Happy 6 mos.           and yes we're BOTH still here.  I am happy we have officially become employees of SYKES.  and of course of MACROMEDIA #1.    6months and it just went by with no warning.  life here has been funfilled and adventurous.  full of love and tears.    what I am most happy about is our friendship.. which has grown ...  we don't need to say a single word and we would knwo how each other feels...  Our trialsand petty fights has made us more strong and more undefeatable.    My life has been much easier with you here. I hope in my own way I was able to touch your life,  and made you relaize what a great friend you are.    I wish you only the best in life. only the best. nothing but the best.    Imagine    6months.marlon.jonnel.anna.doc.rv.marky.galera.porch.whistlestop. 
</post>
<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
             My heart ached when I saw your almost throbbing hand yesterday. I felt your anger but decided not to rub salt on it by giving you unsolicited comments about what happened.   I resorted to just listening but hurting at the same time.
</post>
<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hi bes..   i'm so glad we were able to set this blog up so we can still stay in touch. We can still say what we couldn't say to each other verbally.   Yep, I'm in a different shift and it's like I'm detaching myself from you guys. I see you all scrambling at the start of your shift while I'm already on my way home. It's nice because at least I get to miss all of you.   Wow, you've started going to the gym. That's good. I wanted to tag along but i thought otherwise. Pagkatapos nyan, beach na tayo.   And about the guys who've been clamoring to get to know you...good for you, bes. But I do know that you'll make the right decision coz we both know that we deserve the best. And I'm glad you're starting to like a certain someone although you haven't told me much about him, I'll respect that and prolly wait for the time when you'll finally tell me.    What's up with me?    Well, I've been battling some financial issues at home. Katrina's been bugging me to let her ride on my credit card. I told her that I'm actually thinking of shelling out some moolah for Paolo's tuition fee that's due at the end of this month but she wouldn't hear it. She actually texted some of our tita's asking if she will be allowed to ride on their credit cards! Que horror!  Guess i learned something new about my sister (oh, wait! Macoy approached me to ask a question. I had to stop typing so I could cover my nose. ok, where was i)  . She will get the thing she wants one way or the other.  Hohum...sometimes I spend hours getting ready for work because I would always end up staring at the wall for almost half an hour just trying to figure out what i'll do with my life and my family. I'm afraid i'll end up following kaje and get a job in Dubai just so i can give enough for my family.  I'm scared because I might lose myself in the process. I'm afraid I won't be able to fulfill my dreams because of all these shit. I try to be selfish at times but everytime I go home and I see the empty cupboards, I am reminded of my neverending responsibilities.  I just wish I could get away for a couple of days and just enjoy myself.  I miss the old times we had. I miss the simple life we had but of course, with Ada entering the picture, one could never complain.    O well, life's a bitch. I guess I just hafta wait for my turn to wither and die.     love you bes! Always take care! Get enuf sleep if u can, hah. mwah  
     

    
</post>
<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Hi there Bes ...       you're on a different shift .. So am I .. oh well... we do need time just for ourselves.. to think and just muse around ..       Yes .. the badminton incident was like a dose of cold water ... I guess that's the thing about having a child ... when all your friends are single and able .. I got hurt ... well that's that ... I realized a lot after that ...       I guess that's why I choose not to attend parties anymore... or wait for an invitation to be extended anymore.. one rejection is enough ...       I love my 8pm to 5am shift .. I'm starting my post natal exercise program .. and hopefully it will be fruitful... did I mention that I was gonna be attending a wedding and I was a part of the entourage? well ... yes I am .. always a bridesmaid never a bride... hohum ...       I get messages from all over asking me for my number and other stuff .. thru friendster .. but I'm not really wasting my time over it... I don't get thrilled like I used to. I guess I've truly matured... I don't know bes I want someone I'm comfortable with ..       I think I'm liking someone ... but I'll keep it to myself for now .. I wanna straighten things out with Reker first ...       You'll be in that shift for the whole month ... I was thinking ... why don't we check into a hotel and I don't know .. brood??? we'll plan it ...       this will be for now..    Chin     
     

    
</post>
<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You wrote:    I miss Summer..we seldom spend time together.. she belongs to a different shift...I miss going out with her...coffee and smoking..reminds me so much of her..She seems to be fine with GT </post></Blog>