<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>29,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey you guys!!!!!! I'm really sorry that I haven't updated for a while!!!! One reason is that I've had to get mentally prepared to go to Texas :-P, and the other reason is that I am now offically obsessed with Newsies!!! What is Newsies you ask... well, it's only the best Disney musical EVA!!!! I tried to put pictures of this one character on here (Mush), but I can't figure out how to. Sooooooo I'm gonna put a whole lotta Newsies links on here.... allllllllrighty theeen!! *says it in a Jim Carey kinda way* TTY guys later, bon voyage!!
      
</post>
<date>15,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        You are Love.  You love life, you love all those around you and the world that you live in.  You are happiest when you are doing something for someone else or for the common good of mankind.    urlLink   What Emotion Are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    I think I'm becoming obsessed with these quizzes just like you Amy!!! 
      
</post>
<date>14,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        Your Heart is Pink    urlLink   What Color is Your Heart?      brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla  
      
</post>
<date>14,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        -Perfect- You're the perfect girlfriend. Which means you're rare or that you cheated :P You're the kind of chick that can hang out with your boyfriend's friends and be silly. You don't care about presents or about going to fancy placed. Hell, just hang out. You're just happy being around your boyfriend.    urlLink   What Kind of Girlfriend Are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    hehe, this quiz is a good one 
      
</post>
<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey everyone!!! Okay, if you know me like I think you do, then you know how much I luuuuuv ballet. Well, I went to City Ballet in San Diego this morning and tried out for their company... guess what happened.... I GOT IN!!!!! ahh OK when I was in the car on the way home with Amy (cuz she gave me a ride up and back) we were both so0o0o0o0o hyper!!!! We stopped at Jamba Juice and got smoothies, and you know how much sugar is in those right? Ohhhhmygosh we were like cracking up over nothing!!!! I did this "freaky rabbit face" as Amy calls it, and she like totally spewed her smoothie!! Well, it didn't actually come out of her mouth but she nearly choked herself, lol. She'll probably get mad at me because I said how *WEIRD* she is... oh well, I know you'll forgive me Amy Nicole!!! Okie dokie, I think I'm gonna go find some more quizzes to put on here.... ttly guyzzz, byebye!!!!    urlLink     What Finding Nemo Character are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
      
</post>
<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        Blue Eyes    urlLink   What Color Eyes Should You Have?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   
      
</post>
<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey you guys!!! I got a new screenname!!! It's awesome, but I'm only giving it to my friends so haha if you're not my friend, hah... ok I'll stop before I hurt somebody with my horrible comedic skills. ANYWAY... oh my gosh I can't get over how cool this new blog is! Amanda, I am so0o0o0o making a dedication page for you soon, lol. Hm... not too sure what else to write about now... oh I know!!! As most of you guys probably already know, I'm in ballet and have been for the past, like, 11 1/2 years. Anywho, I'm going to a ballet intensive in San Marcos from the 21st to the 26th. I'm happy about it though, because two of my friends will be there with me, Michelle and Emi. What I'm the most scared of though is that everyone from New West ballet (the school who is hosting the program) will be all like "perfect ballerinas," while I will be just standing in the back of the room stupified by my own uncoordinated, uh, dancing... hey now, I just made an oxymoron!!! Oh those are fun... ok new one, Jumbo Shrimp, hehe, hm, Stupid Genious, ha HAH, oh here's a good one... Microsoft Works. That's a keeper... ok I think I'm gonna go now... I </post></Blog>