<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>31,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      It's getting COLD!!!! what the hell is going on?? *Shakes head in disgrace* but its a funny thing...my house feels like I have...get this...AIR CONDITIONING....geee.  Well...I am deciding if I would still want to go see the West Side Story outside on a big screen...it's supposed to start by sundown but it looks like it's gonna rain...so maybe not.  I had the wierdest dream....I WAS XENA!! lol and i was eating....cheese!! Cheese apparently made me invincible..it was scary.  But who doesnt love cheese....^_^  now that u've read this...go on...I urge you...have some cheese *WINK*
     
    
</post>
<date>29,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Hey I know its a little late, but I just found this image, it cracked me up! By the way it's from  urlLink Beer Monkey   The image that was perviously here awas messing up the site design so I removed it. If you want to see it  urlLink click here . 
     
    
</post>
<date>29,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      fourthling (11:06:39 PM): You've gone monosyllabic Tevren7891 (11:06:44 PM): ?? fourthling (11:06:51 PM): Quiet fourthling (11:06:57 PM): One word response sorta stuff Tevren7891 (11:07:00 PM): but but but fourthling (11:07:05 PM): Lol!!! fourthling (11:07:06 PM): Very cute Tevren7891 (11:07:07 PM): heh i said but Tevren7891 (11:07:17 PM): heh heh but fourthling (11:07:32 PM): Lol - mommy!  he said "but"!!!  Heh. A little peek into my daily life. In case you were wondering I am Tevren7891, and I said "but"+t. Ha, I crack myself up but not. Anyway meeting up some people and watching movies, probably Braveheart, Shari's favorite. Today was fine expect that I saw a damn Hummer again. It caused me to be blind for three seconds. Also the world is now collapsing if you haven't noticed. Was walking Jaun's dog with him when I noticed that a homeless man had nice leather cushions. Man, a homeless guy with leather cushions! Tired to get the dog to piss on the cushions but it wouldn't. Then tried to make it piss on a really nice car, but again it wouldn't. Life Sucks real bad since that dog didn't piss on the hot car (not Hummer, yet I can dream). 
     
    
</post>
<date>27,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Well, I'm an idiot!  But a reasonably happy one, nonetheless.  I figured out why the AP people never sent me my scores . . . I filled out the address thing wrong.  Can you believe that?!  How *much* intelligence does it take to bubble something in properly???  I don't even want to know what I got anymore - if I can't write my own name and address, I certainly can't pass the stupid test.  Unfortunately, now that I've decided I really *am* just that stupid, they've gotten my actual address and are going to remail my scores.  *buries head in hands* In other news . . . um, I figured out how to delete posts all on my own.  It's kind of fun - so if anyone's been seeing posts that suddenly disappear five minutes later, that's just me reveling in my one discovered technological skill.  It's about the only thing I *can* do. And Conrad. . . you're definitely my favorite little brother ever.  Love you lots - maybe we should make a calendar and start marking down days? ^_~ Later!
     
    
</post>
<date>27,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Well...I thought I would make one post before I went to bed so here it is. POST. Anyway saw some friends and had some fun, besides that today was very uneventful. Think tomorrow will be the same, G'night all hope Satan doesn't wake you
     
    
</post>
<date>25,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Conrad's taught me how to post - I thought I knew, but apparently it takes more effort.  Wow,  that's  ironic.  Dollface, dearest love of my life, I'm going to try to call you later, but be prepared to pick up for a phone number you don't know.  LadyNeptune - well, first get a shorter name ^_^ - and I'll try to call you, too.  How could I not try to get ahold of my favorite lesbian lover?  And Conrad - you're definitely the best friend a demented gypsy could ask for.  Even if you won't admit you're my  little  brother.   Sedgie  - were you wearing the necklace this morning?  I didn't notice - and we're so calling you Sedgie from now on. ^_^  To all the rest of you out there in the ether, it's one of those days.  It's one of those lifes.  And I've had the same song stuck in my head for weeks and now I can't remember a word.  It's something like "I'm With You" by some girl.  Got it stuck in my head in the bus station in Texas, and now I've lost it.  Lost a lot of things.  And I can't find the shirt - which oddly enough, is the thing that currently matters most.  I'll be seeing you.
     
    
</post>
<date>24,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      I FOUND MY HACKY-SAC!! sad thing...it was in my sock drawer...for shame...so i spent quite awhile just throwing it into the ground....now i can actually play with it! hehehe...ms. gypsy....help me!! guess what i was doing! out of boredom..I WAS PLAYING STARCRAFT ALONE!!! ahhh!!...oooo...the world is ending.  and guess who's bday it is today!! HAPPY BIRTHDAY!! hope u liked the gift...and hope u didnt get too offended by the card :-D...well laters silly pple!
     
    
</post>
<date>23,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Do you know what's really funny? Well, to start things off my name isn't Conrad, none of us actually use our real names. I can understand if that isn't funny to you, but after reading the posts I discovered that I didn't know anyone named Summer Gypsy, I mean that isn't a name, more of a title, then I remembered that we weren't suppose to use our real names. Ha ha I forgot, ha ha. Yea I know that I am very sad, but that's the only way that I have fun.  By the way today is Gen. Sed. b-day, so happy birthday you damn bastard.  Come by the house  to pick of your gift, I have Sharifah's too. 
     
    
</post>
<date>23,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Damn you ugly! Just Kidding. today's been busy, yet fun. Anyway I didn't have anything special to day (as usual), but just wanted to post. By the way if you notice we have been getting visitors, and all you vistors should comment on these damn blogs, I stay sober so that I can type these damn things, so might as well comment. Oh that reference to Dollface by Summer was actually to Shari. Peace out homie G.
     
    
</post>
<date>22,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Breakfast this morning was delicious - and it's very good to be home. . . well, at Conrad's house, but it's still nice to be here.  He's making tea - but of course he's making tea. ^_^  Dollface -  darling  ^_~ - is coming over later.  I've been lost in the boonies of small college world recently, so I'm reveling in all the visiting friends.  And Sedg's birthday is coming up, so we get to screw around with him. ^__^  It's all good.
     
    
</post>
<date>22,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      All right...New site coming up, same people, but fresher posts and fresher, yet retro look. I call it Barrels Of Monkeys, its still a work in progress. Shari, Gen. Sed., Summer, Lady Neptune and I are all going to blog it. Hope you'll enjoy the fresh look, coming up next week (hopefully). Anyway back to bussiness. Today NYC experienced the worst weather, we had ten-mintute thunderstorms.  TEN MINTUES , what good is that? It's like fucking mintute men who can barely last, curse you minute men...Brings back memories of old...of Africa. Man, I am one sad mo-fo monkey, anyway peace out, keep your head out of the OJ.
     
    
</post>
<date>21,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
       THE THREE MOST ANNOYING EYESORES IN NEW YORK CITY  (seriously these things are really annoying) :   The New Hummer. Not only is this crap ugly, but it takes up the parking space of a mini van, and then some of the active road. Not only that, but it gets like negative four mile per gallon.  Those really annoying scooters. The people who use these machines are lazier than hipoes. I can walk faster than most of them.  They have wheels! Yet they want a petrol guzzling machine that will take them 10 miles per day. Why not get a mo-ped, even they are better! These scooters might have been less annoying if they were quieter, but nope, not even that.  Last but not least, the new Mc.Ds. It uses more electricity than a entire subway line.  Tsk, Tsk, Tsk, and I had to witness them all on friday, poor poor me. 8(
     
    
</post>
<date>20,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Hello all, Greetings my minions, I am the General, General Sedgwick to be exact, and welcome to my first post, i dont suppose I have much to say.  Im suffering a major case of seperation anxiety from the Summer Gypsy who has posted previously in this domain.  I'm also rather tired, but thats my own fault, so I cant really complain can I.  Well, i suppose that'll be all then, ta for now.
     
    
</post>
<date>20,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      iiiiiits..a small world...aaaaafter alll!!! yea its me....writing cuz mr. CONRAD asked me to lol....so i saw pirates of the carribean..actually pretty good..FUNNY....then i went back home..and it was BORING again lol.  la la la....so i played starcraft ms. gyspsy!!! lol crazy i kno.  so off i go!! muahz!
     
    
</post>
<date>18,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Today's been passing slowly...don't know why but it has. Anway there are going to be new people making posts, including Summer Gypsy, Gen. Sedwick, Shari and maybe someone else as well. Since today is going so slow, I decided to take some of those online "personality tests." Here are the sad, sad results.  My crappy little elf name is  Brookbank Hairtoe .  urlLink What's yours?   Powered by  urlLink Rum and Monkey .    My Iraqi Leadership Name is  Nusayyif Rashid Muhyi Amin Zubaydi .  urlLink What's yours?   Powered by  urlLink Rum and Monkey .    My goddamn rock solid ghetto shiznit name is  Wankmaster Teapot, Yo .  urlLink What's yours?   Powered by  urlLink Rum and Monkey .    My Mormon name is  Justan Tru Brantly !  urlLink What's yours?      urlLink How dumb are  you ?     urlLink What Kind of Drunk Are  You ?     urlLink Which Colossal Death Robot Are  You ?     urlLink Which Evil Criminal are  You ? 
     
    
</post>
<date>18,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Hey,how is it going? Today was fun...Really it was. My mom came home early, so I didn't know if I would be able to go hang out. After a completing a string of tedious commands, I was allowed to leave. I hung out with my mentor with for awhile. We went to this diner and lunch with one of his business associates, who was a one point a english teacher. The menu at the place was ridiculous. I ordered a crab-burger and had to pay like 9 dollars. The wasn't the worst of it, my mentor (Asok) had to pay 5 dollars for a tiny milkshake. After the late, but seriously expensive ($50) we headed out to the movies. You have to understand, I really wasn't in the mind for movies, but since it was his treat I agreed. We saw the new  urlLink Charlie's Angels: Full Throttle movie.  The movie was okay, not as great some people make it seem (*cough**cough* Sharifah *cough**cough*). It was reasonably funny, but a lot of the jokes were either really perverted or a little on the haha not really side. The plot was flowed well expect two points at end which I won't ruin for anyone who hasn't seen the movie. The soundtrack for the movie was pretty good, but it didn't flow with the movie that well, at some points you could say that you were just listening to a song with nice video graphics, but not like that of a music video. Otherwise all the songs are great, especially the one by Pink. The commercials gave away a big part of the movies, same with Pink's music video.  If you have watched all the commercials and Pink's music video ten to fifty times, well... You are pretty sad, but back to the point, it's like watching the whole movie.  The special effects which look really good when Lucy Lui is the one performing them are great. It's basically an extension of the matrix, almost as if they were all agents. For all the guys there is a part at the end when the girls are washing car and getting wet. *P (blind cylops with it's tongue out) Peace Out.
     
    
</post>
<date>17,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Grrr - one would think we *were* in Texas, since it's gray and rainy.  Posting now, 'Rifah?  I'm so remarkably bored right now - mainly because my minute (and by minute I mean younger and larger) cousins are attached to the comp/tv and irritating me to an early grave.  *sigh*  I could use a good natural disaster.
     
    
</post>
<date>17,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Eheheheheheh...I just found this really kewl graphic from  urlLink sword in hand . It'll better explain the situation in Texas and Summer's comments...The funniest thing I've seen all morning. This image was too large to fit on this web template, so I'll just giver you the link. For the picture  urlLink click here. 
     
    
</post>
<date>17,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Hi there this is just a test to see if this works.
     
    
</post>
<date>15,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Well, the surprise party was  indeed  a surprise, as I was far too tired to be anything more than mildly suspicious when I got dragged to a comic book store for half an hour.  *shrugs*  Who knew?  But I got ice cream cake and presents, so I was pleased. In other news, Lance Armstrong is still winning the Tour de France!  This, of course, is of international importance - well, it ought to be.  And a hurricane is going through Texas - I think its name is Claudette.  I'm still somewhat befuddled as to why we *name* our hurricanes, so if someone would care to explain it? I also got an email from one of my best friends earlier today saying something about  1984 , the book by George Orwell, and it's relation to society today.  I've never read the book, but the comparisons were interesting.  It was talking about making English *perfect*, aka politically correct.  It brought up the way textbooks are being written today, and how information can be parceled out in just such a way as to paint a completely inaccurate picture about the way things were.  I'm not sure I understand why this would be done . . .well, on a logical level, maybe, but . . .I don't know.  Later.
     
    
</post>
<date>14,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Hey there...hehehehe, threw Summer Gypsy a surprise birthday party, but it wasn't much of a surprise, but she says it was super. Now lets evaluate the super. Super: the guy who maintains the apartment building. Hmmm...Was the party the guy who maintains the apartment building, hmmm...Don't think so. Super: as in to have powers associated with heat vision, flying, and x-ray vision, and of course the super strength , none of which the party had. Super: Great, hmmm...Was the party great? I guess so since all the other choices don't work in context. I still don't see how it was a surprise. I was giving it away, she became suspicious but didn't throw around any accusations till it was too late. Ha Ha Victory!
     
    
</post>
<date>14,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Hmmm.... This is a very strange predictment we have ourselves in isn't it. Oh haven't you heard, It's recently been reported that President Bush commented on the fact that's he is okay with the CIA's reliance on bias, unsupportable evidence about Iraqi "WMD" (Weapons of Mass destruction). You can check out this article at: urlLink New York Times.  I just tried to find out what the exact address was, but couldn't but managed to find that they had another article labeled: "Bush Aides Now Say Claim on Uranium Was Accurate." Don't really know what to believe if they keep doing this kind of shit.  Also in today's NY Times:  Rumsfeld Says Iraq May Need a Larger Force.  Why would Iraq need a larger force, it's been conquered! There isn't anything there expect people with rocks, their nuclear properties extend to boulder technology. Oh my best take of those dangerous Iraqis before they drop a boulder on my dog. Peace Out, I think I'll get me a dog and crush it with a boulder.
     
    
</post>
<date>13,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      If you haven't noticed, there is a new person making posts at this website, and she isn't a drunken monkey, and doesn't usually ramble. This person is Summer Gypsy, my friend who has agreed to help with this crap. Anyway, saw  urlLink The League of Extraordinary Gentlemen . Overall it was a pretty crappy movie. The only thing that made this movie bearable were the characters. The plot was really crappy, the movie is only bearable if you believe:  World War II started in 1899 British special officers pretending to be Siberian Germans started World War II  the stereotypes about Americans and Indians are true.  There were a bunch of Indians guys with guns at one point, but they really didn't do much. It seems that the entire point of their existence, was to die at mongolian/siberian/german/british hands. Why is it that the Indians always get pimped? It was like the Afgani crpyts versus the American Army. Speaking Of Americans, the only American in the movie was the inpatient youngster who shot at everything besides the target. The thing that really pisses me off about his movie is that I ran to see it, literally. My friends and I ran against the win for about three streets and three avenues, trust me that's a long distance. Peace out till later.
     
    
</post>
<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      And I've been on a lot of buses.  And they all smell kind of funny.  But it's a lot better right now - and doesn't smell.  And now graphics are slowly being explained to me and I'm drifting off to sleep. Later.
     
    
</post>
<date>12,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
       This is just a reply to something I saw on the  shout outs   (located on the bottom of this message, check out the old one HaireePhetus is very funny but it's all true, at least in my opinion).I completely agree, commercial are very stupid, I think the people making them are ignorant of the needs of their viewers. For example, a beer commercial has two guys dreaming about women mud wrestling.  What the hell does that have to do with beer?  Usually the actors are so low rate that they've been kicked out of mime school (god damn I hate those mimes). On the matter of Starburst, well...Those people have no life, their commercial resembles the hang over that I have after a night of heavy drinking. It's very sad that people fall for this kind of advertisements, and of course end up as obesity hippos who can't fit through doors. On the other hand if there is ever a food shortage, we can always eat parts of these people due to their fat. Hopefully it won't come to that. Fat people would love to be thin, and still eat like a damn rhino, so they think that if they switch their diet over to slim fast, but 3 gallons of slim fast won't reduce your weight. Fat people are funny. The funniest fat person was the one who had to  crane lifted  out of his house. Magazines are very horrible, its true that everyone is perfect as themselves but if you want to change to better your life span, then go ahead. These magazines though will not help you, in fact they might cause you to drop into depression and gain more weight. 
     
    
</post>
<date>10,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Its been two days since I have had cable internet, and I feel as if I have seen it all, and now I want more. The only problem is that  I have reached the end of the internet.  Yes, as sad and disturbing as it sounds it is true. I have visited almost every single blog, laughed at every single stupid web-comic, well... That I'll leave up to your imagination. I would spent my time online playing games with all the other geeks, but they aren't that friendly plus they hack (damn hackers). I feel as if my computer is sucking my life force out of me. About two minutes ago I updated a sketchy part of the blog template, and discovered since I hadn't used any blog titles, the tag shows up, hmm.... Gotta fix that crap. I think this whole thing would be better if I was wasted. Yesss... Design a website while I am wasted...The good O'l American way. I think I'll try that, peace out (I am going to call my friend up and arrange for the wastage).
     
    
</post>
<date>10,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
       I finally have cable internet.  This is a big step up from my 56k, which sucks my mother's giant gorilla balls. The cable guy came like two hours ago and set it up and he had to replace the cable wiring, not only in my own house, but also in my building's roof. the connection in my house was fried it was like breakfast gone wrong. Anyway I used for the first time like ten minutes ago and it wasn't a slice of Heaven, but the entire cake. Ummm...anyway its Starcraft time, so peace out.
     
    
</post>
<date>09,July,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Funky as in it sucks the balls of a ten year moose whose antlers are only reflective on its small and dagger like cock. Anyway I haven't gotten wasted in such a long time, I think my liver is actually recovering. I could definitely use some Bacardi to put my liver into the dark yet pleasant age. During the time that I have been sober I have noticed some very stupid things, which not only assure me that there is no hope for humanity, but also that I was better off wasted.    The commercial line for Sour Starburst is, and I quote "use responsibly." WHAT THE FUCK IS THAT SUPPOSE TO MEAN? How the hell are you suppose to use candy irresponsibly? Are you stupid enough to choke on a lifesaver? OR are you incredibly depressed and try to strangle yourself with taffy?    Next thing that I noticed that when I was finally sober is that people are getting ass implants! Why the hell would you do that? What, just in case you need a flotation device during the next great flood?   Well...That's enough for now! I am going back to sleep and hoping that everything becomes better.
     
    
</post>
<date>31,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      *Fabulous* day.  Let's start from the beginning.  Went to Borders - now we are *all* going to Borders this week.  You want to know why?  Because they have Pumpkin Spice coffee now!!!!!  It's the best thing ever.  Conrad, Doll, Dead', Sedgie, and hey, Hyperspaz, can you come?  I have Wednesday and Tuesday completely free, but Thursday and Friday before work I can do, too.  C'mon, lazy bums. ^_^  School is starting *very* soon, and we so need one last summer hang out.  *pouts*  I promise not to make anyone do Turkey in the Straw!  Number two - there's an Alexander Hamilton museum!!!!!  I want to go!  Number three - caught the kitten!  It took a freaking lot of effort - not a word out of you, Conrad!  And it's now sitting on my lap purring happily . . .you should all come over and see it.  It's name is Toby Scarmaker . . .Toby for Conrad, Scar was my original name for it, and it scratched me and mom up lots so she suggested I alter it slightly (the name, not the kitten).  Number four, not to be neglected - I went *shop-ping*!  *That was supposed to be trilled*  I spent over a hundred dollars, but I got so much *stuff*.  Clothes, bag, and thirty dollar shoes that are Naturalizers and *soooo* comfortable.  Well, we're going to Borders. . .That's an order.  ^_~  Love you all!
     
    
</post>
<date>30,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Hey! This is the first comic strip. The strip will be weekly, in simpler terms there will be a new comic every Sunday at midnight. This one is my first, please send me any criticism you have. Thank you. I would personally like to thank Deadinside and Dollface for all that they have done and the troubles and nagging they had to suffer because of this comic strip.  
     
    
</post>
<date>30,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Why does Conrad insist we post all the time? It's as if its deadly necessary or like he's getting something for it...I dunno...consipracies...  Anyway, if we're back to songs..well, I have a bunch to choose from, like this one (I got Dollface to like it recently):    Nirvana - Son of a Gun  Up up up and down Turn turn turnaround Round round roundabout And over again Gun gun son of a gun You are the only one Makes any difference what I say  (x2) The sun shines in the bedroom When we play The raining always starts When you go away  Up up up and down Turn turn turnaround Round round roundabout And over again Gun gun son of a gun You are the only one Makes any difference what I say  (x2) The sun shines in the bedroom When we play The raining always starts When you go away  Up up up and down Turn turn turnaround Round round roundabout And over again Gun gun son of a gun You are the only one Makes any difference what I say  (x4) The sun shines in the bedroom When we play The raining always starts When you go away  (Originally by the Vaselines)     Apart from that, I realized, I've lost my mind. I've recently been trying to learn about astrophysics, (specifically regarding orbital bodies eccentricities and other weird crap like that), other stuff about astronomy...and Maltese...I will never make it, and I doubt I'll learn what I remember. I  gotta go back to other stuff I started but never finished learning, like all those languages I though I could learn at the same time. Boy was I wrong, I'll probably try again when I'm not so lazy. P.S.,  Aus Gamers? sounds German. (Out Gamers)  I'm Deadinse...and that'll never happen!  "Me dijo un señor, una vez, un señor de parecido de sabio, pero con vida de portero, que aquellos quienes buscan por un sentido muy profundo en lo que piensan, se torturan, y se atormentan sobre lo que no merece tanto análisis. Cuando le pregunté, 'Señor, ¿cómo es que un anciano, tal como su merced, sepa tanto, de semejante cosa?' Me respondió con, 'Hijo...como crees vos, ¿que terminé yo así?'"
     
    
</post>
<date>29,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      ::IamAEvilMonkey has left the game:: ::IamAEvilMonkey has exited Battlenet:: Eheh... Funny shit. Anyway here is a comic update: I have three comics drawn, one is with Deadinside waiting to return to me in JPEG or PNG format; it might make its way to Dollface though cause she has cable and can send it to me faster. The last couple of attempts to get it to me through email/file transfer by Deadinside have failed. Recently I have drawn up two more, but I think this time I'll find some other way to scan them (hopefully). I have just discovered that most of the PC/X-Box gaming community doesn't reside in either North America or Japan, it actually resides in Austrailia. If you want to join the community or want to see the evidence of this claim just go to:  urlLink AusGamers.  They have almost every single demo for almost evey single PC game out, not to mention reviews and previews which will knock your boots off.  Their servers are kind of slow and so the download time for a demo is kinda long. For example it took me three hours to download the demo for Unreal Tournement 3 (which by the way is about 300 megs). I JUST FOUND OUT THAT PRINCE OF PERSIA IS COMING OUT! Prince of Persia took up most of my time when I was a child and will probably do so again when it is released by Ubi Soft sometime at the end of this year for consoles and GBA.  Well... maybe a little while after that when they release it for PCs. This game looks incredible. The best part of this is that the game will be using the Splinter Cell engine! For those of you who have play/seen Splinter Cell, you know what I am talking about.  Oh my god it looks so good! P.S.why do you guys hate Bill?
     
    
</post>
<date>29,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
        We Are The Champions - Queen  I've paid my dues Time after time I've done my sentence But committed no crime And bad mistakes I've made a few I've had my share of sand Kicked in my face But I've come through  And we mean to go on and on and on and on  We are the champions - my friends And we'll keep on fighting Till the end We are the champions We are the champions No time for losers 'Cause we are the champions of the World  I've taken my bows And my curtain calls You brought me fame and fortune And everything that goes with it I thank you all But it's been no bed of roses No pleasure cruise I consider it a challenge before The whole human race And I ain't gonna lose  And we mean to go on and on and on and on  We are the champions - my friends And we'll keep on fighting Till the end We are the champions We are the champions No time for losers 'Cause we are the champions of the World  We are the champions - my friends And we'll keep on fighting Till the end We are the champions We are the champions No time for losers 'Cause we are the champions    yea....i only remember the "we are the champions part" lol...and by the way..it should be sharifah is the champion lol no jk.  well was listening to that....and was aiming for a bit of optimism lol    hmmm poetry....i remember being interested in this book..that was just ONE POEM..the whole story was a poem but i forgot the title and feeling real sad about that.  o well lol.  well more later lol ciao 
     
    
</post>
<date>29,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      I'll be yelling thought this post, 'less I say otherwise.  Well I'm glad we're all out in the open about this! YES, that's right! It's is very UNpeppy! And do you know WHY?! BECAUSE NONE OF US ARE REALLY FREAKIN' PEPPY! I know I'm sure not! Conrad, you're an idiot, Bill needs to die.  This is GREAT! The last few posts have REALLY said it.  The darkness flooding over the past few days, I love it! I enjoy that kind of thing, when we all realize how things really are! How we all really are! I am demented, insane, an addict, and I hide in corners! That's the world, fear, hatred, deep depression. The General's got it there, with Mr. Poe, everybody knows, that the best poetry is written, when you're horribly depressed...or I guess if you marry your 15-year-old cousin...but whatever.  Tears stream down our enmaksed faces, to show off the best of things, while we tear and burn within, with what we try to deny or forget! But it's always here, there whispering to you from the back of your mind! Haunting you at night just when you're about to sleep, in the darkness, to soak your sadness, and bring you out from the joyus fantasy world you created! Learn to LIVE IN IT, FEED from it! We all need to accept it and grow strong from what tries to get us weak, b/c we survive on "negativity" anyway.  Stop the yelling. I'm Deadinside, and now, another uncredited quote, 'cept this is a very funny comedian's bit. Enjoy...  "...You know recently, I found out something, and it's absolutely true, I just found out but uh...when Coca-cola first came out, it actually contained cocaine...as an ingredient.  Yeah it's true, but then, so did..cocaine sandwiches....seriously, but just for like, the first few weeks, then took it out. Yeah, people were going crazy in the deli's. But no, can you imagine? What it must've been like? People must've said stuff like :: pretends to hold up Coca-Cola bottle:: 'Have you TRIED this stuf?!?!? I LOVE IT!....I've been drinking it for FOUR DAYS IN A ROW! I tarred my roof! My wife left me...I'm alphabetizing EVERYTHING!....Pepsi SUCKS...Pepsi's for LOSERS....all those Pepsi people with their "JOBS"...'"
     
    
</post>
<date>29,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      One of my favorite poems, and so I'll post it so I won't lose it.  The Raven. By (the great) Edgar Allen Poe  Once upon a midnight dreary, while I pondered, weak and weary, Over many a quaint and curious volume of forgotten lore, While I nodded, nearly napping, suddenly there came a tapping, As of some one gently rapping, rapping at my chamber door. "'Tis some visiter," I muttered, "tapping at my chamber door --                                         Only this, and nothing more."  Ah, distinctly I remember it was in the bleak December, And each separate dying ember wrought its ghost upon the floor. Eagerly I wished the morrow; -- vainly I had sought to borrow From my books surcease of sorrow -- sorrow for the lost Lenore -- For the rare and radiant maiden whom the angels name Lenore --                                         Nameless here for evermore.  And the silken sad uncertain rustling of each purple curtain Thrilled me -- filled me with fantastic terrors never felt before; So that now, to still the beating of my heart, I stood repeating "'Tis some visiter entreating entrance at my chamber door -- Some late visiter entreating entrance at my chamber door; --                                         This it is, and nothing more."  Presently my soul grew stronger; hesitating then no longer, "Sir," said I, "or Madam, truly your forgiveness I implore; But the fact is I was napping, and so gently you came rapping, And so faintly you came tapping, tapping at my chamber door, That I scarce was sure I heard you " -- here I opened wide the door; ----                                         Darkness there and nothing more.  Deep into that darkness peering, long I stood there wondering, fearing, Doubting, dreaming dreams no mortal ever dared to dream before; But the silence was unbroken, and the darkness gave no token, And the only word there spoken was the whispered word, "Lenore!" This I whispered, and an echo murmured back the word, "Lenore!" --                                         Merely this, and nothing more.  Back into the chamber turning, all my soul within me burning, Soon I heard again a tapping somewhat louder than before. "Surely," said I, "surely that is something at my window lattice; Let me see, then, what thereat is, and this mystery explore -- Let my heart be still a moment and this mystery explore;--                                         'Tis the wind and nothing more!"  Open here I flung the shutter, when, with many a flirt and flutter, In there stepped a stately raven of the saintly days of yore; Not the least obeisance made he; not an instant stopped or stayed he; But, with mien of lord or lady, perched above my chamber door -- Perched upon a bust of Pallas just above my chamber door --                                         Perched, and sat, and nothing more.  Then this ebony bird beguiling my sad fancy into smiling, By the grave and stern decorum of the countenance it wore, "Though thy crest be shorn and shaven, thou," I said, "art sure no craven, Ghastly grim and ancient raven wandering from the Nightly shore -- Tell me what thy lordly name is on the Night's Plutonian shore!"                                        Quoth the raven "Nevermore."  Much I marvelled this ungainly fowl to hear discourse so plainly, Though its answer little meaning -- little relevancy bore; For we cannot help agreeing that no living human being Ever yet was blessed with seeing bird above his chamber door -- Bird or beast upon the sculptured bust above his chamber door,                                        With such name as "Nevermore."  But the raven, sitting lonely on the placid bust, spoke only That one word, as if his soul in that one word he did outpour. Nothing farther then he uttered -- not a feather then he fluttered -- Till I scarcely more than muttered "Other friends have flown before -- On the morrow he will leave me, as my hopes have flown before."                                        Then the bird said "Nevermore."  Startled at the stillness broken by reply so aptly spoken, "Doubtless," said I, "what it utters is its only stock and store Caught from some unhappy master whom unmerciful Disaster Followed fast and followed faster till his songs one burden bore -- Till the dirges of his Hope that melancholy burden bore                                        Of "Never -- nevermore."  But the raven still beguiling all my sad soul into smiling, Straight I wheeled a cushioned seat in front of bird, and bust and door; Then, upon the velvet sinking, I betook myself to linking Fancy unto fancy, thinking what this ominous bird of yore -- What this grim, ungainly, ghastly, gaunt and ominous bird of yore                                        Meant in croaking "Nevermore."  This I sat engaged in guessing, but no syllable expressing To the fowl whose fiery eyes now burned into my bosom's core; This and more I sat divining, with my head at ease reclining On the cushion's velvet lining that the lamplght gloated o'er, But whose velvet violet lining with the lamplight gloating o'er,                                         She shall press, ah, nevermore!  Then, methought, the air grew denser, perfumed from an unseen censer Swung by Angels whose faint foot-falls tinkled on the tufted floor. "Wretch," I cried, "thy God hath lent thee -- by these angels he hath sent thee Respite -- respite and nepenthe from thy memories of Lenore; Quaff, oh quaff this kind nepenthe and forget this lost Lenore!"                                         Quoth the raven, "Nevermore."  "Prophet!" said I, "thing of evil! -- prophet still, if bird or devil! -- Whether Tempter sent, or whether tempest tossed thee here ashore, Desolate yet all undaunted, on this desert land enchanted -- On this home by Horror haunted -- tell me truly, I implore -- Is there -- is there balm in Gilead? -- tell me -- tell me, I implore!"                                         Quoth the raven, "Nevermore."  "Prophet!" said I, "thing of evil -- prophet still, if bird or devil! By that Heaven that bends above us -- by that God we both adore -- Tell this soul with sorrow laden if, within the distant Aidenn, It shall clasp a sainted maiden whom the angels name Lenore -- Clasp a rare and radiant maiden whom the angels name Lenore."                                         Quoth the raven, "Nevermore."  "Be that word our sign of parting, bird or fiend!" I shrieked, upstarting -- "Get thee back into the tempest and the Night's Plutonian shore! Leave no black plume as a token of that lie thy soul hath spoken! Leave my loneliness unbroken! -- quit the bust above my door! Take thy beak from out my heart, and take thy form from off my door!"                                        Quoth the raven, "Nevermore."  And the raven, never flitting, still is sitting, still is sitting On the pallid bust of Pallas just above my chamber door; And his eyes have all the seeming of a demon's that is dreaming, And the lamp-light o'er him streaming throws his shadow on the floor; And my soul from out that shadow that lies floating on the floor                                         Shall be lifted -- nevermore! 
     
    
</post>
<date>28,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
        Aww man, screw you! You're those computer virsus sent via eMails. We want you to go away because you fill our computers with nougat filled hatred and make them crash. You're even worse than that person who thinks they can curse the world.    urlLink   What kind of eMail are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   I have just been told that I am stupid, and I agree; I am stupid like a fox! This was told to me after I discussed the theory of me not existing with my brother. Yea, much fun. But I am sure that I do not exist, I mean come on, I don't even get any viruses.  Anyway I want to start a cult; a great cult. A cult that has stuff... and they do stuff with the stuff. Stuff my cult will have to believe in and follow these rules because I said so:   Rap music shall be defined as voodoo music.  Alchol shall be consumed.  Names shall not be named.  Mole people shall be hunted till they renew the alliance.  Cult members must have either stealth powers and be refered to as Splinter Cells, or have heat vision and be willing to lay down their lives in order to destroy the conspiracy against Bill the Penguin.  Bill is God.  Believe and ye shall be saveth.
     
    
</post>
<date>28,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Been pretty boring lately, there isn't anything interesting to talk about besides my problems, which I will never again bring up because this is suppose to be a peppy site. The comic that I wanted to start up is being passed around to people with scanners; Deadinside tried, but when I recieved the copy, it looks like french trench during the first few weeks of World War I, in other words it looked like crap. It's like 1:41pm I am reduced to making a post... Concerning posts, I am sorry for two things, 1. not making a post yesterday. 2. for making that really depressed post two days ago. One thing that has humored me lately is that everyone besides me is getting this So.Big virus; I haven't even gotten spam in my mailbox, not even spam concerning how to protect myself from this virus. Maybe this means that one likes me and so I am not in their address book, and that's why the virus hasn't come to me. On the other hand, I am pretty sure that someone out there has to have me in their address book, or I wouldn't exist.  OH NO! I DON'T EXIST! 
     
    
</post>
<date>28,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      I return, Conrad's near ready to kill me (along with other people I'm sure) but he specifically wants me to post, so, here it is a post.  I'm a little lost, a tad void of any clue (hark...a double entendre) so I'll just wing it and see where it takes me.  I hope all are doing fine, as I attempt to integrate myself with the city that I have missed (and the summer I have missed) for the past few days, and ah school rears its head.  Umm....I read a comic book today, it has a few entertainingly worded lines in it (and they say that those things rot your brains) so i suppose I'll share 'em and see where the wind takes it from there.  "...To have my life mean something.  And I think, for the most part, I sucdeeded. I flew high.  I flew well.  It's just that, when I finally failed...I had such a long way to fall.  I go over it and over it and over it.  What was it inside me that shattered?"  and  "...There are some who claim that life on earth is nothing but pain and suffering.  That  people  struggle through brief pitiful lifetimes and die...frightened and alone.  No purpose.  No meaning.  Look at the world one way...and the viewpoint's understandable.  There is terrible suffering.  There is pain and madness that seems inexplicable--if not simply evil.  But there are others who believe our suffering is a doorway to something better.  That our pain helps wear away the masks and lies we've come to identify with...and reveal the radiant authentic selvesthat hide beneath our personalities and egos. ...And I think there's truth in that"  so there ya go...If you took the time to read that, well then, I hope you enjoyed it and I hope you got something out of it as well.  I suppose I'm done for now, talk to you all later, I'm off to go rally the masses (as a General may do...non?)
     
    
</post>
<date>28,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Is it clear we're all getting tired?  We don't normally write like this.  Dollface, you're gorgeous.  My favorite ALMIGHTY!!! ever.  Conrad, I figured it out.  The difference, I mean.  The difference is that I've been trying all along - don't you see?  I know the difference between single parent kids and regular kids now, too - funny how much time work leaves for contemplation.  Single parent kids are always sure - somewhere - that they aren't wanted.  And you know why?  It's cause they aren't.  Funny thing, when grown ups don't know how to grow up.  Funnier, the legacy it leaves.  And if it's all about being wanted and trying and  . . . the universe, maybe, then leave me out of it.  Because it's one of those days where you look down at the receipt you're writing on and realize that tomorrow (today) is your best friend *ever*'s birthday and you haven't gotten her anything.  And then you get home and discover that your sister is a ---- and maybe you are too (maybe we all are) and what is this gaping hole that we are all trying to fill?  And I'm so tired of . . . . all of this.  Reading these is no way to learn about someone's life.  But it doesn't matter anymore.  When I grow up, I want to have a papasan chair to curl up in.  And a down comforter.  And a lot of books.  And coffee.    There is nowhere left to hide There is nothing to be done No people to be saved No pets we've never named Forty miles from the sun  As darkness craves the mind We come undone without our pride No time on earth to come All the pleasures just begun Forty miles from the sun  
     
    
</post>
<date>27,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      I am not an obsessed little freak, just envious. It's not the person; it's their attitude towards life. Their attitude is shit happens; so what, I am always going to be a lil peppy person. Never have I seen something like this. This is exactly what I was looking for, ever since I was lost. It feels like a thick fog surrounds me, the only thing that I can see is her happiness, her peppyness. How the fuck does she manage to do that? Depression comes and leaves for most people, but there are a unlucky few who have it orbiting them. These are the same people who are obsessed, not over the person, but over the peppyness. Why? Could it be that I have lost my ability to be happy? If so it must have been stolen, but by who? Is she like a wormhole, sucking in all the happiness around her. No because I feel happy being near her, makes me feel as if my happiness has come back. No, this can't be envy, but then what is it? The best comparison I can make is to vampires. I feel as if I am the vampire that hungers for blood, soul, something that I lack to fill a part of me that is calling. Yet I also wish that I never had to do such because of the pain. All I want to is to be the one with the blood, the peppyness.
     
    
</post>
<date>26,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Well I hate to say this but... gypsy...your feral. I am only saying this cause all the other post are provoking me and I just had to. School is going to start soon, it already started in some parts of the counrty. I really don't know where I am going with this so bye.
     
    
</post>
<date>26,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Yes sir, step right up and pick up your copy of MTA workers gone wild!  It shows why you should not let three ex-convicts use a hose, bucket, and two brooms in order to clean a Subway station. It can only lead to the worst. They were all wet for god's sake. I tried to pass by politely, but no, one of them had ot spray me in the ass with water. I hate them! After the sexual assault I left to the opposite side of the station and took the train home. I hate the MTA
     
    
</post>
<date>26,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      lol ok i'd like to say that...well...our ms gypsy is SO NOT A FERAL KITTEN...but an ALMIGHTY ...hell yea!  confuddled are u? thats rite thats rite..as u should be...and yes too bad...ya cant be one lol..BESIDES! what have u calling her FERAL ANYWAY??? i should say not...Fiesty? maybe lol....RAAAAAAR  so today i woke up not feelin so great....well left arm feels fantastic..i can move it and its pain-free...but the right...ok i admit it does feel a bit better - either that or i'm just USED TO IT lol  dont u hate it when u REALIZE that u are living...lol...not just alive...but understanding that u are actually standing there..you are actually looking at ppl..seeing...hearing.  i do that often...makes me think...wow....its not even real...like i'm just in a STORY and doing what i think is soo unexpected which is actually expected and wondering am i really SEEING things the way they are.  i dunno...i deja vu a lot too....and if its not the exact same scene...it'll be the same idea....it confuzes the shit out of me.  i think the movies have gotten to me...for i have trained my mind to even ZONE out and hear pple talking...but they'll echo and sound faint and blunt.  it's probably just me....life seems so boring...i would love doing something so 'not me'...but i'll most likely end up not being as amused as i thought i would be.  well i'll save u from my wierd thoughts on life lol...*grin* bye
     
    
</post>
<date>26,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Feral kitten?! What the fuck does that even mean?  There's not much to say, when you lead an empty hell-hole of a life. Band practice today, some good recording, maybe this one will sound better. I'm hating it there a bit more every day. I like having to CREATE my OWN parts, but that's not really possible with Eli. I dunno, maybe it's just me. I'm good at threatening, maybe that'll help me.   Iggy Pop - Your Pretty Face is Goin' to Hell  Awwright! Woooohhhh!  A pretty face and a dirty look I knew right away that i'd have to get my hooks in you Yeah yeah yeah I'm running low on my memories If you wanna make a fuzz, boy, you gotta be a tease, uhuh A-say yeah yeah  I need it all, baby, that's no lie I need a lover with an alibi I wanna fall into a love so sweet Honey baby baby I'm hard to beat  Smell of flesh and I touch alone Smells in the air and I'm feeling so alone, uhuh A-say yeah yeah Hallucination true romance I need a love but I only got a face, uhuh That ain't all  I'll tell ya honey it's a crying shame All the pretty girls really look the same I wanna fall into a love so sweet Honey baby baby I'm hard...hard to beat  Wooooh hey hey Your pretty face is going to hell Your pretty face is going to hell  Honey honey I can tell Your pretty face is going to HELL!!!! HELL!!!  A pretty face and a dirty look I knew right away that i'd have to get my hooks in you A-say yeah yeah I'm running low on my memories If you wanna make a fuzz, boy, you gotta be a tease, uhuh That ain't all  I need it all, honey, that's no lie I need a lover with an alibi I wanna fall into a love that's sweet Honey baby baby I'm hard...hard to beat  Woooh yeah hey Your pretty face is going to hell Honey honey I can tell your pretty face is goin' to hell.....(scatting) etc.  I'm Deadinside, and that's what I've dealt with today  "In fact, the to face the facts, deal with first what you know, to stand up with what you've got"
     
    
</post>
<date>26,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Well... There is no need to agrue about this. We all know that you are a feral kitten, come on admit it. It fits in the scheme of things; makes the picture whole. By the way this whole thing about Mars being so close tonight, well fuck it. I can't even see it when I walk out of my apartment. This just means that Mars does not exist in my universe. You hear that you wannabe-existing-planet-piece-of-crap-hole. For the last time and I am not going to ask Marx! I hate that man, he is like the gay version of the girls gone wild mixed with satan's computer, which is filled with outdated software made by Mircosoft.
     
    
</post>
<date>26,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Song by  Simple Plan .  *Not* what I thought they were singing, but that's okay.  Dead' - all right, what can we do that won't make you wanna go home? ^_^  Doll, you poor girl, next time you're on a roll, take a breather. ^_^  Well, *I* had fun today, and am currently furious with the college board *thing* because it won't let me register.  Ooh ooh, and I watched  Star Trek: Next Generation  tonight!!  *Love* that show - watched Gambit . . .this is pretty much only for those of you who are as dorky about this show as I am, cause no one else will get it.  It's the two part where Picard is Galen and it's smuggling and drama and *sooo* good.  No, I'm *not* a nerd. ^_^  Oh, and Conrad? -  I am not a feral kitten !!!  Hmph.  *Really* ^_~
     
    
</post>
<date>25,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      so today was a nice hang out...sad to hear dead' didnt have fun rollerblading....sad....i dont think any guy really likes doing that with me....it wasnt so much that yozen wasnt having fun that made me feel bad..it was more him wanting to leave us...but i dunno..i guess i understand...sorry i made u go thru that...but i just dont get why most guys i kno feel they're allowed to leave like that.  well after getting home...my mom suggests that maybe a HOT HOT shower will soothe the arms..it did actually..but only in the shower.....once i got out...it was soreness again...so now i'm relying on TIGER BALM....the sports balm!! well it was real hot earlier when i first put it on...really only lasts an hour...came to the conclusion with gypsy that i might have pulled it...so lets hope it goes away by friday.  til later.... 
     
    
</post>
<date>25,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      I hate Bill. In fact, I shot him with the Army's new  urlLink XM8 machine gun , which hasn't even been made yet! Nothin' like a non-exsistant gun to shoot a non exsistant penguin. And while Bill's not home...well...let's just say we know why his kid's half-human.  Anyway, now that I've finished freaking everyone out, comes the self-depreciating section of my post.  I tried to rollerblade today, b/c Dollface and Summer managed to confuse me...and it was the last mistake I will ever make. Couldn't you girls have gone your whole lives without seeing me fall SO many times? I personally would much prefer to keep my incompetence well-hidden, or at least show it, in a not-so-painfully-embarrasing manner. Yeah, complain all you want that you've already trained me to try not to be embarassed in front of girls, but I can't help but,...I fell NINE TIMES...COME ON! I could've gone with out that!...I SUCK!  I'm Deadinside and that's my stupid complaint for today.  "I'm a human being, not a piece of meat! Love me for my MIND!"
     
    
</post>
<date>25,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      No way! Bill is so meant to be. In fact he is sitting next to me right now, and he doesn't appreciate you spreading such vicious lies about him. So what if people sit on him, he still manages to come out of it unruffled. By the way "Toby, go pick me my cotton." For all those of you who indulge in funny shit, check this out (beware it's not meant for the faint of hear/fart or those who have 56k modems [3.07 meg file]):  urlLink The Alien Movie.  It gave a chuckle, kinda like that nerdy kid who had pretended to be a Jedi ( urlLink click here to check it out ) 
     
    
</post>
<date>25,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      For example, Bill the Penguin.  Not only did he *never* exist, he still doesn't.  You can't resurrect an imaginary character. . . especially after he's been sat on. ^_^  All right, kitten still uncaught.  Problem now is that I'm seriously afraid of two things: First, that I won't catch him before he turns feral/gets run over; Second, that if I do catch him he'll somehow end up with the name Toby.  He actually batted at my fingers last night, though, so we're making progress.  I guess.  Later all.
     
    
</post>
<date>25,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Read this and you shall be enlightened on the ways of the world. BtP (Bill the Penguin) is part of this religion. Hear this now, loud and clear: I am now converting to the  urlLink Church of the Great Penguin 
     
    
</post>
<date>24,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Oh yea, then his name would be Bill (the penguin). I am seriously disheartened with life. There is nothing new to do; I would try taking a stab at my mother, but she won't take kindly to it. And so since I had nothing to do I have decided to bring Bill the Penguin (BtP) back from the grave. For those who don't know Bill was my best friend until he was sat on by people and Summer Gypsy decided to kill him. I still don't know how he died, but I am pretty sure it had something to do with bubbles and the lack or air in them. Poor, poor Bill, and so now I have decided to bring him back from the dead. He might even start posting on the web site... but all of you would probably think that it would be me using Bill's name. Nay, I tell you, Nay!  Now I really am starting to go crazy, hoepefully I'll do something tomorrow which will allow me to be saner... Probably not. I've decided to join a MOHAA (Medal Of Honor: Allied Assault) clan, so that I can have something to do on my spare time. In other words I get to live out my fanasty of being an WWII gay guy and shooting people at the same time. Yay!
     
    
</post>
<date>24,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      so today was a productive day....had woken unexpectedly at 8 in the morning...wooooah howd that happen??? lol had BREAKFAST TOO....after eating some pancakes my mom persuades me into jogging with her....from months of enjoying life as a lazy bum i at first did not want to lol but so much boredom led to me agreeing to come along....so there i was wearing some sweats, comfy shirt, bandana and my favorite beaten down black shoes lol....man surprise surprise but i still got energy lol....so we jogged the whole island....entered my home and while going down the stairs i realize...I AM HAVING TROUBLE...lol felt like i couldnt walk.  so after an hour of "recovery" i figure..hey i'm on a roll.........I DID MORE EXERCISE!! AYE AYE AYE...so here i am following an hour and a half aerobics tape...so man my body feels some MUSCLES GROWING lol..but tomorrow..uh-o...man am i gonna feel it tomorrow....but gypsy..do i hear ROLLERBLADES...oooo we should blade together! lol dont know if i still caaaaan but worth a try.  lol so eli changes the solo....just sweet...sweet...sweet....yea just makes sure that doesnt go about happening again lol  ooo THE MUMMY IS ON! lol can never NOT watch it....  well off i go tired limbs and all lol...muahz!
     
    
</post>
<date>23,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      This weekend had just been one huge MOHAA (medal of honor: allied assault) party, unfortunately I have just been informed that yesterday there was a 24 hours Starcraft competition. Drats! Oh, well there will be more. Anyway MOHAA is the most fun online. So many people to kill, almost too many... Maybe not. By the way the comics that i was drawing up will hopefully be up by the end of the week. It all depends on who has a a better scanner, and can get the copies to me the fastest. Peace out x))
     
    
</post>
<date>23,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Random revelation there. ^_^  But yeah, the guy at my work is being good - probably partially 'cause we had the *cool* manager today - so I'm happy with him.  And he's *teaching* me stuff. . . okay, so he's really not, and it's incredibly minor stuff, but that's all right.  I *think* the kitten's a boy . . .I'm not sure.  It's happier, though - now if I could catch it, we'd be set.  Of course, now I'm afraid to try and then to fail and then all the effort I've put in will have gone to waste.  So yeah, I'm panicked and not trying right now.  Tomorrow.  I'll try tomorrow.  *frowns*  Maybe?  Other than that things are going along.  Ooooh!!! I *finally* have rollerblades!!!  I have rollerblades - and they're silver and purple and I have wrist pads and they're so cool!!  I'm just thrilled . . .and probably sounding like an idiot.  I'll leave you now - go look at Mars tonight.  And stupid White Flag song by Dido . . does she have a funny pitched voice, or is it just me?   XOXO 
     
    
</post>
<date>23,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Today was the worst rehearsal ever.  We sounded like crap, the amps sucked, and the room was smaller than mine.  The last version of the recorded song we had was crap, and while the next was louder, it sounds bad and that damn solo's still there.  Oh by the way, thank you Dollface, thanx to your comment about the song, Eli decided to reconsider the solo! (NICE) Dun worry, I failed to mention your name and instead I said about 3 or 4 people hated the solo.  Too bad, it really does suck anyway.  Anyway, yeah it was early today, I got home at like...7? I think...sure, but after my mom started yelling at me as soon as I got in the door, I got to go outside and sleep against the side of a building! Nice! Also saw that Mongol, SovietSmurf, which means I didn't get to live in the street for too long...oh well.  I'm Deadinside, and that's my dream of life.  "She pissed me off, that pissed her off. She yelled, 'Eat me, bastard!' I yell, 'Ok, but I'm still mad!'"
     
    
</post>
<date>23,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      so in my hours of boredom...i decided to play dress up lol..YES DRESS UP...i found a bunch of shirts and pants that i've never worn before or just never considered wearing and found a pair of knee high boots that belonged to my sister...HELL YEA THOSE ARE MINE NOW!! lol.....while this lasted only an hour i was stuck playing on my brothers dreamcast...having finished FROGGER which to me is soo short for a game..i resorted to the race car games...pretty good now but realize regular rules of driving do not apply lol  so conrad..i have a scanner..altho i havent used it in years that i'm not sure if it still works..but hey the next time i see you i can scan ur comic and if anything i can just hand it over to deadinside.  man had the wierdest dream today.....something about the meanest and big ass of a chic who was soooo fucking mean to me...she purposely started a fight....we started fighting....wierd cop looking tour bus??? came along...lol and she still started with me...she was basically a bitch....it reminded me sooo much of junior high that i woke up crying and quiet sobs that wouldnt go away....crazy man....i always wanted to record my dreams in a journal...a pretty journal but i never got around to it lol....hmmm a journal would be nice to have again...lol but yea wiiiierd dream..wonder what it meant.  well thats it for now....love ya babydolls. *wink*
     
    
</post>
<date>23,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Why? Why are people so stupid? Tonight on my way to the Chinese take-out place I saw this kid on the corner. This stupid idiot was taking a piss by a car. At first I didn't think it was possible, I mean who would do something this stupid? Well then for the sake of the human race I thought okay, maybe he lives far away and he had to take the mean leak. Nope, after finishing his leak, he went into a building which was about five feet away (for those who know where I live, I am talking about the building between the bike shop and the pharmacy). Why would you take a leak outside when you just go home and take one at home? If you don't have a bathroom at home, just go to a neighbor; they'll understand.  You must really suck if you have to create a rumor that you are creating the best game system ever, just to get some publicity.  Really can't you think of something else, like a new breakfast special at a nearby Applebee's or maybe the fact that you are lying little crack-heads who work at a strip joint in Florida Keys.  For those who don't know what I am talking about, I am referring to the  urlLink Phantom . I just heard over at  urlLink Penny Arcade  that it's probably a hoax. I agree, it sounded too good to be true; there are too many problems to overcome for them to make a console like this. 
     
    
</post>
<date>22,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Eheheh... Mom's not home and it's fun centeral because I can do whatever I want... Which at this point (sadly enough) is to stay at home and play videogames. Also I wanted to ask is anyone had a scanner? I know Deadinside has one, but I also need someone who I see more often. Need to scan the first and maybe second strip of the comic. Please if you have one, just post or comment. Peace out!
     
    
</post>
<date>22,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Stain*d's  It's Been Awhile  - Look up the lyrics, loves.  Go on, now. . .or *fine*, just listen to the song.  That works, too. ^_^  The kitten's still alive - and by bigger I meant longer, since I can still see it's ribs pretty clearly.  It's getting used to me . . .and by that, I mean that it doesn't take off once every three seconds anymore.  Now it's once every five seconds. ^_^  But tonight it ate til it got full, then looked at me and did this slow, squinty blink thing kittens do - and flopped down (out of reach, of course) and just stared at me. . . .Does this mean I'm making headway?  *shrugs*  Who knows?  But it'd be nice if the people at the gas station would stop asking me what's wrong!!!  And hitting on me, for that matter.
     
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Finally got to convince Conrad to take away my admin. rights.  I proved to him what I could do. I could get real bored and just start taking away all you guys' rights, or even kick you off the site, or just rewrite all ur posts to read stuff like "I-I like jello...jello's cool...I mean, it's good...it's ok. But..baked beans... they just rock.  Ever had like...a can, you roast it...of baked beans...over like a fire, slow roasted over dried cow dung? That's good, beans are like, tasty, like parkas." Obviously that would be bad.  Anyway, now that I have no power, I feel much better about all this.  Things are getting pretty weird for democrats in Texas. Seems that republicans now have the power and are trying to redistrict Texas so as to give the republicans the upper hand. To prevent this, democrats from that state have gone to New Mexico, to avoid being redistricted, a trend that's been goin' on for some time. Let's hope that the democrats get back into power, not just in Texas, but in the federal gov't too.  I'm Deadinside, and it's obvious I had nothing to say for today.  "Register Green, vote democrat!"
     
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink Bush Orders U.S. to Freeze Assets of Hamas Leaders  I agree Hamas has to be stopped, but will just punishing one side will result in a whole lotta crap. It really sucks that the leaders of Hamas are having their assets frozen, while the Israelies are walking away with a little slap on their cheeks. Shouldn't President Bush ask the United Nations to raise some sort of sanctions against Israel; I mean it's understandable if they attack once, but they've been doing it for the last thirteen years.
     
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      The kitten's not dead. . . .Or caught.  It is getting bigger, though.  And cockier.  If I'm at all sarcastic to anyone tonight - I've had a very long evening, and would like to throttle most consumers at the moment.  I might make the suggestion that none of us ever work in retail . . .it's hard enough dealing with the ultimate stupidity of humanity on a daily basis; it's harder to fold their towels and smile while you do it. ^_^   XOXOXO 
     
    
</post>
<date>20,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink MSN Hotmail - Bill Gates Inbox . Hehe...funny shit...
     
    
</post>
<date>20,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Well...Hyperspaz? yeah, you'll get the hang of it...er, hopefully? Oh and is this gonna be your permanent name? Why don't you just leave it at "LadyNeptune" or somethin', Summer and I think Dollface already made references to you by that name.  Yes...I was supposed to come up with some form of hang out, Dollface, but my raging incompetence and lack of recreational knowledge makes coming up with something to do, real difficult.  Conrad...that new"Phantom" thing seems kinda...suspicious...I don't trust the whole thing for some reason.  If it's possible, I think I'm experiencing boredom, or just lots of exasperation, think I might just be loosing my mind. I'f I'm off the grip, realign them according to standardized specs.  We're all just their machines with an oil change. Hey, anyone wanna hang?  I'm Deadinside and that's my subtle hint for today.  "Eating is like, the only disorder that seems to be disgusting. I mean, yeah with drugs and alcohol, women are like, 'Oh yeah, that guy's like, a bad boy, I wanna be with him', or something like that. But with food...you never see a woman say, 'Oh you see that guy with the triple-cheeseburger with drips of grease streaming down his face? I want him.'"
     
    
</post>
<date>20,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      No, this blog isn't about the tiny lines of writing at the bottom of a contract; I am talking about the band. It's pretty small, emerged out of Washinton (the state). The singer (Jerry) is Tycho from  urlLink Penny Arcade.  The only place that I've found with their music is  urlLink MP3.com. Very nice music. Check out some their lyrics:      english    she is not mobile, she just watches me  i am noticable when light catches me  i am illegible any way you look at me  you know my english has deficiencies   and is it any wonder that I  when faced with these odds  would even it with lies  and is it any wonder that i  surrounded by storm  surmounted by swarm  would attempt to obtain the prize   there's a terror to the scenery  a certain fervor to the front of me  and i count them as my enemies  those who mean to be close to me 
     
    
</post>
<date>20,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Still majorly confuzzled on how this thing works.  Let's see it now!
     
    
</post>
<date>20,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      yup...austin powers...BABY! lol just dled it...aint it the shit!! lol *dances with fingers pointing sideways...now THE TWIST!!*  SO WASSUP PPLE....hmmm cant stop dancing lol  so DEADINSIDE is SUPPOSED to create a hang out lol but he thought he told me he gave up..lol so we will try again...wonder when that will happen? we keep postponing.  hehe head keeps dancing to the beat..this is FUN lol....well have nothin else to say....  WHO LOVES YA BABY!! *wink!*
     
    
</post>
<date>20,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Yea, it's my third post; so what? Finally got Linux to work on my comp. It looks great; I think I'll use it for image work, and maybe learn PHP on it too.  Pretty boring day. Just wanted to ask the gang what they are doing tomorrow, cause I'll be downtown and I am wondering if they want to hang out. Oh yea, I now have a catch phrase: " I fight my inner demons everytime I go to the bathroom. " It's copyrighted so don't use it. 
     
    
</post>
<date>20,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      I would like to make a gaming post, in which I'll bring up certain sensitive issues that bother gamers all over. First of all lets discuss the new console that is coming out sometime, they don't really tell you when. All they tell you is that you can register to reserve one when it does come out. For all those who don't know what I am talking about, I would like to introduce you to the  urlLink The Phantom . It looks really great. Maybe that is the problem, that it looks too good to be true. It's supposed to be easy to install, fast ("up to 3Ghz") and even wireless LAN built in. You're supposed to be able to play games with anyone over a wireless network. The funny shit is that there aren't any CDs or cartridges. The games are supposed to be online, and you can rent and download over the game's huge network. Last time someone tried to do this (that crap ass hand-held with 132 games built in) it sucked huge cock. Then there is the fact that you have to download the game, and that will take a while to download the game, even on a cable connection (hell it took me three hours to download the Unreal Tournament III Demo). Then there is the fact that wireless connections suck, they are slower than the norm and they tend to break off during bad weather connections.  The Phantom seems too good to be true, the only way it could seem better is if came with a helper monkey to turn the system on while you are sitting on the couch.  The video card that the Phantom will use isn't top of the line though, it will use the GeForce FX. On the other hand Microsoft is developing X-Box 2, which will have the Raedon built in. So instead of registering for some too good to be pixy gold crap, you could just wait for the new X-Box. Secondly and lastly I would like to say that everyone should buy/borrow/download/steal the new  urlLink Star Wars: Knights of the Old Republic . It got really good reviews and the graphics look awesome (white trash word of the day).
     
    
</post>
<date>20,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      No, we aren't a music posting place thing; atleast I don't think we are. Nice to know that Dollface learned stuff about comps and networking. Not much to say today, sorry. It's pretty early. Oh, Oh, I can now confindently say that I play more games before 9am than most people play all day. If you want to play with me; just email me. I usually play Medal of Honor from 8:30am to about 10am; I am tevren. If you pefer to play *starcraft* (broodwars or normal) than join channel hses anytime between 11:45am to 1pm; I am IamAEvilMonkey. That's all for now, going to go kill people in MOHAA.
     
    
</post>
<date>20,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Are we now a song posting site?  Did I miss something? ^_^  Does that mean instead of posting song quotes now, I have to post the whole thing?  And 'Rifah, didn't you pick up that band from an  unspecified  mini-disc player? ^_~  Sorry I can't be online tonight, peaches, but I'm stranded in Ossining (stupid *job* thing) and won't be home til late tomorrow . . .  if ever. ^_^  So, uh, *Sue*, joined us, have you?  Does this mean you're actually going to be Sue Ann like I originally thought everyone was saying? ^_^  Who else is joining?  'Cause Dead' joined awhile ago - and yes, you dork, we do love you. ^_^  I got to drive around today. . . ah, well, I got to be driven around.  Lots of daydream time . . .we all need to go hiking.  Like I said, daydreaming. ^_^  And work got out early, which was nice.  No song contribution tonight, my apologies.  Hugs.
     
    
</post>
<date>19,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
        Iggy Pop - Gimme Danger    Gimme danger little stranger And I feel with you at ease Gimme danger little stranger And I feel your disease  There's nothing in my dreams Just some ugly memories Kiss me like the ocean breeze  Now if you will be my lover I wish you were insane But if you can't be my master I will do you anything  There's nothing left alive But a pair of glassy eyes Raise my feelings one more time  Find a little stranger, find a little stranger Today you're gonna feel my hate say gotta gimme danger wild little stranger Honey gonna feel my hand Swear you gonna feel my hate Swear you gonna feel my hate  Daaaanger.... Little Straaaanger....(until song ends)    Now that's power right there, awesome song right there, download it now...I'm serious, do it.  Anyways, I'd like to say "hey" to "Sue", new here at posting, so, hey "Sue", how's it goin'?  In other crap, shit's the same as always, I'm getting progressivly pissed with the band leader of Lycanthrope, or however you spell that.  Still, we have a concert coming up in October, a "Battle of the Bands" at some school. As soon as I find out more about it, anyone who wants to go is welcome to.  It's gonna be real fun, and this one will happen...so long as I don't kill Eli first.  I'll put up with him b/c I can put him in his place too, but moreso b/c this is something I wanna do, and I can get on stage, no bull shit.  Even though most of you probably don't care, we also have a website under construction, but I won't give the URL 'till it's up and runing.  Also, I'm about to start mastering our latest recording to try to make the instruments sound out more, b/c we have real bad recording equipment. Once that's done, you can ask me for the mp3 if you wanna hear.   I'm Deadinside, and that's my death threat for today.  "¿Qué horas son, mi corazón?"
     
    
</post>
<date>19,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      What is up all?  Surprise surprise, I'm not dead!  Quite alive and well...maybe not too well, but who's complaining. It's nice to know everyone is doing so nicely for their summer.    I'm quite saddened now.  I've filled out some job applications and haven't gotten a call back from any of them.  I felt rejected and unwanted.......oh well......I'm over it now......that was short.   Since I'm still new at this posting thing, I shall leave you all now.
     
    
</post>
<date>19,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      We have two more people joining our staff, don't quite know what their names are just yet.  
     
    
</post>
<date>19,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      so the brother in law came today to fix the networking lol FINALLY...but guess what happens....well my router is one that most COMPANIES use..ya kno..for like MORE THAN 2 COMPUTERS......u see my brother in law had gotten it for free from his old job...so hey why not use it....and man that was like sooo back in the day when no one really used cable and did networking in their homes so its not like i could get a simple router anyway....well heres what happened...so he comes over....checks it out....has to reconfigure it but we didnt have the software that could do it....he searches AND SEARCHES for it online but its not easy to steal them anymore cuz apparently the company that we got the router from only sells them to companies and you need to create a service contract....so that was a mess....so now he's gonna get me a new router...a simple one that only costs like 50 bucks...he's buying it which is sweeeeeeet lol  man...everytime i talk to that boy he always gets me interested in computers....today he talks about IP Addresses and whatnot..real interesting that IP address thing....and how different routers work and stuff...i still kno shit about computers lol but hey its cool to hear someone talk about it.  and conrad..I LOVE THAT SONG lol i used to sing it allll the time....i'm into lacuna coil rite now...     FALLING   stand, look in my hand talk with this line That's not the answer cry and now I know look in the sky I search an answer  So free, free to be I'm not another liar I just want to be myself... myself  And now the beat inside of me is a sort of a cold breeze and I've never any feeling inside around me... I bring my body carry it into another world I know I live... but like a stone I'm falling down  Damned, looking into the sky I can feel this rain right now it's falling on me fly, I just want to fly life is all mine some day I cry alone, but I know I'm not the only one I see that another day is gone,gone I don't wanna die... Please be here when I'll arrive, don't die... please  
     
    
</post>
<date>19,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Do you have the time To listen to me whine About nothing and everything all at once I am one of those Melodramatic fools Neurotic to the bone no doubt about it  Sometimes I give myself the creeps Sometimes my mind plays tricks on me It all keeps adding up I think I'm cracking up Am I just paranoid Or am I just stoned  I went to a shrink To analyze my dreams She says it's lack of sex That's bringing me down I went to a whore He said my life's a bore So quit my whining cause It's bringing her down  Sometimes I give myself the creeps Sometimes my mind plays tricks on me It all keeps adding up I think I'm cracking up Am I just paranoid Or am I just stoned  Grasping to control So I better hold on  Sometimes I give myself the creeps Sometimes my mind plays tricks on me It all keeps adding up I think I'm cracking up Am I just paranoid Or am I just stoned  --Greenday (Basketcase) I love this song. Anyway couldn't update yesterday cause I came home late and had to go to sleep fast or else people would start yelling at me. The funny thing is that I actually fell alseep at around three in the morning.  During the time when I was staring at the ceiling, I decided to make a web comic (I've made this decision several times). Probably won't do it cause I am too lazy but, I can hope.  Anyway it's true Deadinside does smile, not often, but I've seen it. The  urlLink About The Staff  page is updated; check it out.
     
    
</post>
<date>19,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Hm, now who could that certain someone you're talking about be, hm Dollface? Everyone knows I can't dance and NOR DO I SMILE! Believe me Dollface, you were there with me in fuckin' 217, you know how it was. If I was smiling, must've been my mother yelling at me to do so, so she wouldn't look like a bad parent in front of everyone else. Furthermore...I am not cute, I dun think my smile is either. Disagree all you want, I've made up my mind Summer and Dollface.  Glad to hear it Dollface, considering I might've been responsible for getting you sick n' shit. And WHO? Do you mean Zashid...or whatever...black guy? HEAVY accent of African origin? What are you doin' showin' other people my smile anyway?!?! I can't get over that, better move on to something else.  Helped my sis clean up her school room for the kiddies n' stuff.  Turns out schools are Darwinian nightmares for teachers just as much as they are for students.  All the teachers there seem to be against eachother, tryin' to rub eachother off. How do I know? Some teacher stole one of my sis' school-issue shelves, and had it replaced with a piece of crap (as if we wouldn't notice!) Dude I hate that bitch now! I cleaned out that shelf of rat shit and other crap and she goes and steals it from my sister?!?! What a whore. We recovered it and left all the stuff she put in it all over the floor, scattered..heh heh heh...  I'm Deadinside and there's my crime for today.  "Smiles only brighten up the day of those who have a bright light shining inside."
     
    
</post>
<date>18,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      well today i FINALLY SAW that movie..FINDING NEMO lol how cuuuuute!! saw it with gypsy and conrad...lovely lovely...and guess what...MUSEUM!! MUSEUM!! THEY FINALLY PAID ME!! lol after sending the two home i checked the mail and got a check from them..whoooohooooo....now lets see if they'll call me up BEFORE school starts lol.  scary thing happen too when sending the two to the train station...kid that went to school to me...i think his name was Saddiq....but man i have a feeling that boy was MEAN TO ME or just DIDNT TALK TO ME....and i see him today with paul...and he's talking to paul so i figure..ook he's pauls friend whatever...then he starts talking to me!! ok ok...he's just trying to be nice...but when we finally leave again HE STAYS TALKING TO ME...man o man..this boys got balls lol i sooo remember him being soo shy and such an ass cuz he thought he was a PIMP...aye aye aye..and now that he's grown and in high school i suppose his confidence level shot up.....u kno the more i think about this kid the more i realize I DID HATE HIM and HE WAS MEAN TO ME...bastard bastard bastard. and now he talks to me?!??! like nothing happened?!?!?! 217 succcccccccccccccccccccked.......o btw deadinside.....i showed gypsy and conrad our junior high graduation lol gypsy saw u SMIIIIIILE!! lol how cuuute.  well here's a happy thought...my stuffy nose is clearing!! ahhhhhh i can breath.....better? lol well doesnt that call for some dancing...and i know ALL OF YOU CAN DANCE....*points at a certain someone someone lol*     muahz!!!  
     
    
</post>
<date>18,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Well, sorry Conrad, I didn't see ur post about that independence day thing. 'Sides, Deadinside does things alone...shut up...Anyway, sorry about that Dollface, I think it might have been my fault for your bein' sick and stuff...so yeah sorry...  Yeah, I know you girls love us, can't help but right? Ha ha ha...you're gonna kill me...Bunch of crap goin' on for those people unlucky enough to have chosen to eat a nice juicy stake, filled with E. Coli and other goodies.  Seems people just don't get the idea about THROWING ROTTEN MEAT OUT.  And eating it too? There are better ways to clean out your stomach you know.  Wow, I really have nothing to talk about, since I'm not gonna share my personal life...hm...well I'm just gonna wrap this up with more boring drivel and yet another uncredited quote!  I'm Deadinside, and I've effectively bored you all.  "Republicans need to understand the importance of bondage between mother and child" (If you want freedom from this and other crap destroying the US, go  urlLink here )
     
    
</post>
<date>17,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      I'm not even sure if that's a word, but what the hell; you only live once (I hope). Met Summer Gypsy today, had fun and so on. Nothing really out of the ordinary. Now I've really started to wonder;  is craptacular a word? Can it even function in the viod of slang terms too stupid to ever come out of a person's mouth?  ::Look through many different grammer books:: Guess what!  Craptacular can be a word!  Because of latin syntax, you can join  crap  and  tacular . It's very sad for me to see myself making such an ass of myself on the internet. But hey, What the hell it's not like my name's on the bottom of this post or anything like that... Shit...I fucked! My name is not Conrad,  MY NAME IS KUNTAKINTE! 
     
    
</post>
<date>17,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      blasted rain..GOT ME SICK lol was out yesterday....walked a bit...caught in that stupid thunderstorm of a thing...IT WAS FREEZING LAST NIGHT....my my....didnt work out since i was wearing short sleeves and had drenched jeans....here's the upside....sister, gained some weight from pregnancy...already gave me all of her dress pants...now i have ALL OF HER JEANS hehe....coolness....she says that when she loses the weight she aims to ask for her clothes back...but i doubt she'll fit into a size 1 ever again...hehe...yea i'm hoping the smallest she can ever get is a 2..yea yea i kno..shame on me...BUT FREE CLOTHES lol....only bad side..all her dress pants...ALL DRY CLEAN lol dammit...and her jeans..all boot cut!! hmmm well thats ok...flares i prefer but bootcut i can deal with.  hehe yea independence day was nice wasnt it conrad...and yes gypsy....we do love our guys and hate  THOSE  MEN LOL....yea i want a kitty too and when i once tried catching on...ok ok...telling my mom and sister to get it for me...the lil thing pissed on both of em..whoops.  so at the moment..I CANT BREATHE and i'm told to stay clear of the nephew...awww...but i've acquired a new nickname for him..BAM BAM!! lol just like on the flinestones...hehe   well i should probably go lay down...SCHOOLS ALMOST HERE! aye aye...stuck at home watching back to school commercials! lol   who loves ya baby? I DO! lol muahz!
     
    
</post>
<date>17,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Yay! It's Indian Independence Day, well maybe not only Indian Independence Day. It is Independence Day for most of South Asia, and Southeast Asia and also some of Africa (I think). Just wanted to pop by and say Happy Independence Day to all (I've said that about thrice already). This was the first year I think that I didn't go to the parade, since no one could come with me. Going to a parade is not something you do alone, you always need someone to share the love with and there was no one this time, so I didn't go.    translation: Our India is the best in the World     
     
    
</post>
<date>16,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Brief update: Kitten still there. . .kitten damn fast and still not caught.  Stupid cat.  On the up side, the man running the gas station told me I could have the cat - thanks, thanks a lot.                       I hate men.  Well, okay, I don't.  And no, I don't hate *you* guys, so don't get mad.  I hate. . . .that I'm paranoid that a guy's hitting on me everytime he talks to me.  And I hate brownnosers . . .stupid men.  Anyone see tonight's theme? ^_^   Kisses! 
     
    
</post>
<date>16,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
       Back in black  I hit the sack  I've been too long I'm glad to be back [I bet you know I'm...]  Yes, I'm let loose  From the noose  That's kept me hanging about  I've been looking at the sky  'Cause it's gettin' me high  Forget the hearse 'cause I never die  I got nine lives  Cat's Eyes  Abusin' every one of them and running wild   CHORUS:  'Cause I'm back  Yes, I'm back  Well, I'm back  Yes, I'm back  Well, I'm back, back  (Well) I'm back in black  Yes, I'm back in black   Back in the back  Of a Cadillac  Number one with a bullet, I'm a power pack  Yes, I'm in a bang  With a gang  They've got to catch me if they want me to hang  Cause I'm back on the track  And I'm beatin' the flack  Nobody's gonna get me on another rap  So look at me now  I'm just makin' my play  Don't try to push your luck, just get out of my way   CHORUS   Well, I'm back, Yes I'm back  Well, I'm back, Yes I'm back  Well, I'm back, back  Well I'm back in black  Yes I'm back in black   hooo yeah  Ohh yeah  Yes I am  Oooh yeah, yeah Oh yeah  Back in now  Well I'm back, I'm back  Back, I'm back  Back, I'm back  Back, I'm back  Back, I'm back  Back  Back in black  Yes I'm back in black   Out of the sight    --AC/DC (back in black) Great song! And if you haven't figured it out, well, I am back (in black) in New York City. And my address is... The blackout forced my family to go to New Jersey for two days, and so I am back! I had the worst time there; it was so boring. There was nothing to do; my little cousins were annoying the hell out of me. Now I am back and ready to do stuff. Someone please call me and see if we can do stuff. Summer, are you free tomorrow? Can you come to the parade? What about you Deadinside? Anyone?      HAPPY INDIAN INDEPENDENCE DAY (which is actually tomorrow) 
     
    
</post>
<date>15,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Blackout indeed.  Well, mine wasn't so bad I suppose.  Hung out upstate, didn't go to work, got paid anyway, talked to people on the phone.  Tried to find that kitten . . .someone's been feeding it something besides cat food - I really hope people realize that with kittens this can kill them.  They get diarrhea and die.  It's pretty serious . . .but I guess they have good intentions.  Kitten might still be there.  Who knows?  Interesting thoughts to ponder. . . If this is the fall and decline of the Roman Empire, then as with the last time it's from the inside out.  And if that's true, then the twenties feeling is coming back into the rising generations.  Just an interesting thought, any comments welcome.  All right, *yes*, I admit the whole visitors who don't comment thing is just *odd* to me. ^_^  And I passed by a motion sensor light this evening and when it went dark I thought I had inadvertantly caused *another* black out.  It was kind of funny.
     
    
</post>
<date>15,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      yeaaaaaaaa riiiiiiite....fun?!?! fun?!?! I WAS BORED OUTTA MY MIND! lol man...i could NOT fall asleep...my dad being overly paranoid DID NOT want too many lighted candles....i couldnt walk around my house my goodness...but thats alrite..u kno why?!?! ....cuz i had my good ol' FISHER PRICE FLASHLIGHT lol....yup...took it to raid the fridge....took it to the bathroom...hell....took it to just wander in darkness TRYING ooo so desperately to fall asleep....tried listening to mainstream music....BLASPHEMOUS I TELL u....AYE AYE...i was dying of HEAT too....NO FANS! NO FANS!! had to eat all my ice cream cuz the fridge was DEAD lol but that was a great thing...but nothing to eat considering stupid stove was electric and wouldnt even let a single stream of gas out.  talked to ms neptune and gypsy which helped me live through some of it ^_^ well love to you all! muahz!
     
    
</post>
<date>13,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      I hate posting too much, so bear with me, I know you'd prefer to hear less from me.  I forgot to mention a few things about people I couldn't contact during this whole thing and I wanted to know how they were, that's primarily why I wanted to post.  Dollface, I wanted to call ya and see how you and ur familiy were doing, and Summer, you too, but I couldn't use the phone much, (mom mentioned something about mebbe getting the crap electrocuted out of me, and the phone I was using was expensive) until late at night when she was unconscious. Today I couldn't call b/c I wasn't home and the cell phone was having trouble. Conrad, I only have u cell number and didn't know whether or not it worked.  Well that's all, I'm Deadinside and I'll shut up for the next week.
     
    
</post>
<date>13,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Ha ha ha!!!!! You bastards! Looks like being deadinside payed off. I enjoyed this mini-hell which was widespread through the North-Eastern United States. Damn Canuks, they need to be a little more creative than "lightning", 'sides they were blaming the ConEd station on 14th, when it was only responding to the sudden lack of electricity!  I dunno Conrad dude, I wasn't listening to that 1010, I know better, the shit is, no other station could quite wrap around their heads just how to report, relying on Washington's PR for transmission space.  But I just loved it, it was so dark, it was great.  I insisted on shutting the door in my room and staying in total darkness, from the time the sun set to the time I fell unconsious, only to awaken the next morning in a haphazard position, clothes and hair in disarray. Kinda like a big hangover, 'cept without all the vomiting and the three strange women, all to whom I am now married to... All the while I blasted the greatest music on my mp3 player, having hooked it up to some comp speakers, and maxing out the volume.  I was very eager to go outside though, as soon as I heard about the black out, who knows how many old folks might need some help up dark stairs? Or were dehydrated? How 'bout people stuck in elevators? Or the subways? Man seriously, but my mother wouldn't let me out, said sumthin' about me looting.  That's another thing I wanted to go out and kick some looter ass, I've got no remorse, or regard for my own safety, might as well put my pathetic ass to some good use and help out.  I can handle most handguns, some knifes and such! Let me do SOMETHING, but I could settle for dark solitary confinement with some Iggy Pop blasting...yeah...  I'm Deadinside and that all for today.  "I hope you'll love this song just as much as I do, listening to it in total darkness..."
     
    
</post>
<date>13,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      I have some good news and a whole crap load of bad news. Good news first, People now think I am 21 years old; not to say that I am not twenty-one. Anyway, now the bad news.  I broke my D string and the guy sold me a string. I couldn't tell the difference cause of the lack of lights, and ended up paying too much for it anyway. Almost got arrested for throwing rocks at the highway, only Juan and I didn't "know" that it was "wrong". I personally  couldn't understand a word of what they were saying cause they were speaking like deep mexican spanish (the people who were going to call the cops). Then all the messy shit started. People were setting off fireworks, people were rushing and raping the grocery stores of its supplies in the dark. My family then went to NEW JERSEY for the night. On the way we were listening to the radio; I think it was 1010 Win or something. The worst radio station ever! They speculated that the blackout was the work of terrorists/canadians/lighting or canadian terrorists who had found out how to harness the power of lighting.   You know that there is something really wrong with your country when radio stations start broadcasting the dangers of Canadian terrorists who have mananged to harnessed the power of lighting or made some pact with the devil so that they can destroy their "envious" neighbor down south of the border. 
     
    
</post>
<date>13,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Today I didn't stay home, instead I met new and old friends. The Math regents was today and I decided to go encourage them. Hope that they did well (for all of you you are studing english, the main verb in that sentence was "did"). Anyway met Ali and hung out, played pool and so on. I think Summer Gypsy is a little mad at me. All of you who loves games I have a couple of sites you should go to. The first is  urlLink Insert Credit . You can find video, pictures and other stuff of games that haven't even come out. Yea, the have people on the inside. The next is  urlLink Entdepot . I haven't checked it out yet, but will probably do so tonight. Anyway peace out till the next post.
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      We all need to think a little outside the box now. That quote Dollface posted was GENIUS....GENUIS, you hear me? Good grammer or not, I totally support the idea behind it...I know, I'm anti-patriotic too. Damn vain, stupid, statesmen, patriotic cheerleader girls. (Though "statesmen" and "stupid" is usually synonimous)  God almighty wants to kill me. I say, give it a shot, I dare you.  Anyway, some badass virus has been goin around, its a worm, and it's pretty bad. As is if stuff like tapeworms and other stuff in real life wasn't enough. Anyway, NT based comps are at risk, so if u have any of these (2000, NT, XP..that's all I think) and don't have the patch, go  urlLink here  to save yourself.  And I still hate U.S. patriotism. Thanx Dollface, for bringing such an enlightening quote to our attention.  I'm Deadiside and that's what came out when I pushed all these buttons.  "YOU'RE WASTING GOOD PASTRAMI!!!!"
     
    
</post>
<date>11,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Hey. This is my daily 2 cents, see you're lucky you get 2 more cents than the last dude/dudet (insert name here). Anway that quote makes no sense. I don't get it; so confused. I guess that means that artsy people don't have correct grammer and get lost in their own thoughts. I hope they know that "stupidity" is not a adjective.  Maybe it has some internal meaning within the maze of confudled crap but I don't see it. Anyway if anyone wants to see some really strange/funny art goto:  urlLink Exploding Dog . It's kinda like stick figures/ modern art but with a very "strange" touch to it. Try it out and that was my 2 cents for today P.S. Deadinside can hate blogger as much as he wants as long as he posts.
     
    
</post>
<date>11,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      found this and thought i should share the art!!:   girls that are patriotic and love america girls that are cheerleaders and all american girls that are stupid...i hate stupidity girls that are too self oriented girls that only care about their social status girls that are normal in america   yea got it from this real artsy guy...aint it the truth
     
    
</post>
<date>11,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      so MR. Deadinside...abl...dark? hell? lol so yea YOU...ya posted?!? ya posted?!? lol and whatever happened to bloggers bein complete trash sites contributing to internet pollution huh? i knew it! i knew it!...but i kno why this reaaaaaaaaally happened...its cuz of......~_~ meeee...yup..dollface...I'VE CONVERTED U!! hehe...and yes u'll be negative now...but picture this...not too far from ur future u will see....well...warm fuzzies!! hehe  and to the rest of you guys..how are my lovelies?!? i miss you all...and guess what conrad..i had the same road runner problem...for 3 GODFORSAKEN DAYS!! i went mad! and to top it all...my resolution persisted on staying on safe mode!! took me forever to figure out how to get outta that..but now thats fixed..the math test! ooo the math test....well its in two days...wish me luck!  now i will leave you...but lets leave with a happy moment...FOUND MY NEPHEW'S TICKLE SPOT AND ONLY I CAN DO IT!! hehe not even his own mom can hehe...poor sister...lol ok and now i wish all my lovelies my kisses and hugs...laters!
     
    
</post>
<date>11,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Ahh I can almost taste the massive amounts of raging disappointment coming from Conrad regarding my last post.  Hope regret doesn't set in.  Deciding to post on here came with some massive moral conflicts. Firstly b/c I am against Blog and Xanga and the like. Then again I wouldn't mind an opportunity to try to piss people off or forecfully impose my beliefs on others...to each his own. But seriously, if I kept trashing Blog and the like, I'd look real pompous, and I didn't want anyone to think that I think I'm better than them because I don't post.  That's a lie, I just said that to make you feel better.  Well look forward to being offended or filled with unnhealthy amounts of emptiness, hope I said SOMETHING funny...  I'm Deadinside and that's my rant for today  "I look forward to when we meet again" "Better watch out, you're headed straight for a wall"
     
    
</post>
<date>10,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Well then... I see that Deadinside posted. He really isn't crazy, I swear and yes punk rock rules. I wanted to post some pictures from my starcraft game, but they all came out dark and ugly. It was the best game ever! The General and me versus I think four comps on a money map (I know that it doesn't sound great). After about two minutes the General made a retreat into my base and following him was a mass of AI. After almost dying three times, he came back with Mutalisks (for those unfamiliar with Starcraft, mutalisks are gross flying units). By this time though I had secured my base with lurkers (hidden units that do mass damage) and had already killed two comps with hyralisks (ground range units). Great Game! It wasn't great because we won, well maybe it was, but more so because these comps were actually, kinda, almost good. If you want to download the relplay go ahead and do so  urlLink here.  Be warned you need Starcraft to view it.
     
    
</post>
<date>10,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Look you bastards, I'm Deadinside (I can prove it too), and I'm new around here, and Imma kick ass or chew bubble gum...and I'm all out of bubble gum. In anycase I'll only show up when I feel like it b/c I dun like anyone. Yeah that means you...well nah I'll go easy on   you  .  In anycase, hope u don't mind that I'll say some confusing things that will make you scratch you head. This'll probably be the only time I'll be coherent, so, I'll take this time to say, hey Dollface! and hey Summer! and, Conrad is it? yeah I know no one else's name, so bye.  PUNK ROCK IS FREEDOM. "If you are a sexist, racist, homophobe, or just plain an asshole, don't buy this CD. I don't care if you like me, I hate you."
     
    
</post>
<date>10,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      My cousin likes Carvel . . .it's his birthday tomorrow.  Carvel is a cake, by the way.  It was chocolate, and has crunchy things.  Had work.  Didn't have chocolate cake . . . had carrot cake.  Made me remember my birthday. ^_^  Mine was better.  Guy at work figured out I was only in high school today.  Gotta love the awkward moments, huh Dollface? ^_^  Maybe now he'll stop hitting on me.  Suck if he stops talking to me, though - he's one of the few who does (that speak English).  Kitten (uh, Kitten the Third, I guess?) is still at the gas station.  Haven't caught it yet - Conrad's right, I'm filling a gap.  It's really tiny . . . and likes cat food.
     
    
</post>
<date>09,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Or something like it. I had the worst experience this morning when I woke up... or afternoon when I woke up. My Roadrunner cable internet wasn't working! At first I was scared that the 56k monsters might creep out of my computer's modem and eat me. Then I raced around my apartment checking all the connections to see what might have happened. After completely exhausting myself, I managed to gather the courage and calling Roadrunner Tech Help. It took me about seven minutes of being on hold and three or four crappy "phone-elevator" songs to finally talk to a person, where I heard the worst news of my life.  Their servers were down!  They told me that it would another couple of hours till the service came back. I tried to occupy my time, but it didn't work. Next I tried to talk to my family (worst idea ever) and it ended up with a conversation about me studying bio-tech. in college. Next I tried to read, but I ended up picking out a "How to share your cable internet on you home network" book. In the end I was in a corner shaking back and forth till 2pm at which point my cable came back. Yay!
     
    
</post>
<date>08,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      I don't know who they are or what they are, but I would really like to thank the people at  urlLink Blogger.  They repaired the Archives so fast; it was fucking amazing. They are really fast. Anyway, today I hung out with Summer Gypsy and Zhang. We had fun, I got to be a  massuer , the guy who gives massages. Man I can't spell for the life of me. Also today Summer Gypsy was introduced to Family Guy, the  bset   best freaking show ever! Have a safe and hopefully not so drug free night.
     
    
</post>
<date>08,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Hmph - so I change my titles a lot.  If the people who read this and don't comment have issues with it .. .they could comment.  Hugs and love to Conrad and Dollface - I love you both.   XOXO      Can you look me in the eye and tell me, that you're happy now?    -Michelle Branch,  Are You Happy Now? 
     
    
</post>
<date>07,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      First of all why is Summer Gypsy changing the title of that post so much. Anyway today was fun, started the day with a nice glass of Orange Juice and and hmmm...probably going to end it that way too. I met Ali this afternoon, got him into joining our blog team. Do you want to join? Well that's too bad 'cause the only people who read this are those who already write for it and so you are already a part of us.... Damn it! Anyway as I was saying, I met up with Ali. we went and shot some pool, while we were waiting for Blaine. After pool we went and ate lunch at The Riverdale Diner. Best food ever, just don't rouch the coleslaw. I swear that it attacked me! When lunch was finished we decided to go catch a movie because Blaine was taking too damn long at work. We saw  urlLink 28 days later.  That is such a great freaking movie! The camera work is great, the actors play thier parts wonderfully. The worst part which I considered as a plus was that it wasn't really scary (I hate scary movies). It was more like zombies take over and this is what happens... Kinda like a reality show gone all wrong, but in a good way. The best thing about the movie: alternate ending. I mean how kewl is that, it could be like this or like that. The only thing is that they fucked it up and the movie doesn't end well, like if they added a scene or two it would have been perfect. The action scenes were awesome, but very gruesome as well. I had to look away during one scene when he stuck his fingers in the guy's eyes. Such a great movie; go see it!
     
    
</post>
<date>06,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Yes I have decided to offically change my name to Captain Kaka. When I have done so I will then continue my plan and take over the world with my ray-gun and become Emperor Shitsalot the first. ::Evil laugh::
     
    
</post>
<date>06,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      I have a few things to say . . . First: What the  hell ?  Did you and Sedgwick plan this?  Okay, post me calming down I actually do like it.  You know Dollface said this title as a joke, though, don't you?  It makes us sound like we're tripping on LSD or something.  Not that we don't  want  to sound like that - it just amuses me.  And now that the titles are up there I absolutely love the new layout.  Secondly, work puts you in touch with some fucking *scary* people.  This middle aged guy comes up to this girl I'm working with and says (and I pretty much quote):    They wouldn't have anything for my nephew here.  He's six, and he told me for his birthday he wants an X-rated film.  I asked his mom and dad and they say he caught them watching one and it gave him a mini hard on.  I asked him what he was gonna do with the girls at school and he said he'd rip their panties off.  I told him by ten he'd either be a father or in prison.  He said he wouldn't mind being in prison.  I told him he didn't know the first fucking thing about prison, then.  Now my brother, he's always in prison.  He acts like he likes it.  Once he stole some cigarettes in front of a cop - and the judge said he wasn't gonna throw him in prison.  "What'll you do if I kick you in the balls?" my brother asked.  "What'll you do if I smash your face?" the judge replied.  So my brother tried to kick him in the balls - and the judge told him for that he was sentencing him.  "Thanks," said my brother.  And then one time my sister got a call from a lady who says it's amazing how much better my brother looks with a haircut and how good he is in bed - "Don't worry," says the lady, "I won't return him.  I live in Jersey."  "I'm not worried," my sister says, "He can't come into NY without getting arrested and thrown in jail."    Like I said, scary people.  But that was the most interesting piece of work.  In other news, I'm single.  My life has been summed up at various times in the evening by Jewel's  Dreams  and Blink182's  Dammit .  Of course,  Dammit  kicks ass as a song anyway.  So Dollface, we need to drag Lady out and go guy watching.  Have a fling . . .see how much free stuff we can get from the male cashiers.  Do *something*.  Just don't get me near that guy who came into the store earlier tonight . .or his family. ^_^ 
     
    
</post>
<date>06,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      It would be so awesome to have a terminator as the state's  governor, as long as it's not my state he is governing. For those who feel out of the flow read this  urlLink article  where he annouces his bid for the seat. The only way he would win is 'cause of his fame. I can see the campaign now: Vote for the terminator or be opperessed by mindless robots. Well... It's true, not like he would be lying about it. They are mindless robots. Anyway I just wanted to laugh and so here it is: hahahahahahahaha.
     
    
</post>
<date>05,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Hey everyone! The new site is up. The only "real" problem that I have encountered so far is the July Archives. They are under the old name and so you can't get to them unless you know where they are. To help you out I'll post the address. It's at:  urlLink The Old July 2k3 Archive 
     
    
</post>
<date>05,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      There needs to be three dam posts for this shit to work properly! So this is Post numba uno! I hate this world and am going to kill this computer. Well... I would if it was biotic, but since it isn't well...you know. Fini~
     
    
</post>
<date>05,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Eheheh... This is the new site, same old people, but with a whole new look! It's fresh like a new born puppy. Anyway there were a couple of glitches which I am fixing up right now. The funny thing about this is that the only people who know are well the General and Me. Gypsy and Dollface don't know! Imagine their face when they find out! Ha! This is the end of test number one
     
    
</post>
<date>05,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Not only do monkeys cause damage, but they enjoy doing so. Monkeys have this style of causing damage that is unlike no other. For example: AIDS, thought to be spread to humans by monkeys. We all know that AIDS is a STD, but what we should consider is that AIDS is also the monkey's and nature's way of telling us to get off their ass. Come a normal person would have pulled out a 9mm and filled ya' fulla' lead, but the monkey has style. What does the monkey do? Well the monkey bites your ass for trying to rape it and this bite not only dooms you but stands as a warning to all those other monkey fuckers, damn sick fucks. I colored this really kewl picture, but I don't know if I can post it yet, I'll post it when I can. Y'see there is this comic strip site called  urlLink Penny Arcade  and the guy there drew this great picture of a japanese archer. So there is the picture and a little thing that says color if you want, so I color and I just finished emailing him and asking him if I can post it. Nothing more to say, go away... Far away, all of you!
     
    
</post>
<date>05,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Went to Six Flags yesterday - excellent time, lots of roller coasters.   Spent the day with a bunch of guys - some related to me (sort of), some not.  One of them gave me a stuffed Tazmanian Devil. ^_^  Oh - and this was wonderful! - some girl was wearing a shirt that said, "Guys make  nice  pets".  Suffice to say the boys teased me  . . .about a lot of things, actually, but finally we all managed to agree that  my  girlfriends were cuter than theirs.  (Dollface and LadyN., that one's for you. ^_~  XOXO)  Conrad will like this - the ticket for the safari said, "Monkeys  WILL  Cause Damage".  Other than that, life goes on.  Dollface is absolutely wonderful - my other favorite lesbian lover (I really am saying this too much, one of you is going to hunt me down and kill me eventually. ^_^)  *sighs*  And you know what?  Softball coach was right - men aren't worth it . . .we really all *should* be lesbian.  Stupid propagation of humanity and all that.
     
    
</post>
<date>05,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Well then, another late night Blog. Only thing is it isn't really late night, kinda like 11:26PM Eastern Standard. Anyway today was interesting. Had fun and other stuff. Robbed my best friend of a mini-disc, which I gave back to him later.  My Poem:   T'was a silver moon that night  A hot summer night  A normal city night with crime, despotism and the occasional robbery  The bum in the corner enjoys giving fright to the nearby child named Diggory Out of fright he holds his mother tight Until they are out of the bum's sight  A businessman is returning home He gets on the N train Along with the Pizza Hut guy There is baby who cries The crying drives them all insane Then comes in the bum with the Trombone He sooths the baby to sleep Just figures that he isn't really a freak   Thank you. Thank you; don't try copying this poem for two reasons.   It sucks hot rancid balls of Hellhounds. I'll find you and stick a hot poker so far up your ass that you'll wish that you would have never been born. 
     
    
</post>
<date>04,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Hmm... The world is round and has aliens. Well, at least that's what  urlLink Men In Black  taught me. Truthfully I believe that aliens exist because it would be very arrogant of the human race to say that aliens don't exist. Also if Earth was the only planet with life, then it would be a really waste of space (another movie reference, even though I can't remember which one it is). Aliens living on Earth in human suits, why not. Hell, if they have fat suits then why not human suits. It's kinda like a huge Halloween party. Then there is the other thing they (MIB) ask you to believe in order for this movie to make sense. They ask you to believe that the Earth is round. Now come on... A round Earth is almost as strange as Michael Jackson being straight. The people who live in a place I call "reality" agree with me that Michael Jackson is not straight, but for some odd reason they tend not to believe that the Earth is flat. Who needs reality? Not me. In my world Michael Jackson is not straight and the Earth is not round. I live in a great world.
     
    
</post>
<date>03,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      now doesnt everyone wish that they were this kid::   i kno i do! lol...cutie aint he so conrad helped me put the babe up lol.... yikes...math test comin up..i think i'm prepared.....i should be lol ahh just to get the think over with....well off i go! lol later darlin's!! M*U*A*H*Z!!
     
    
</post>
<date>03,August,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Man, I hate this shit. I tried to get rid of the stupid pop-ups with a javascript but  urlLink Blogger  won't let me. For any of you who want to know what the script is well... Here it is:  SCRIPT LANGUAGE="JavaScript"   !--   function open() {return true;}   //--   /SCRIPT   just plug this in the head. Please don't sue me for this shit. Thank you. By the way i forgot to add the </post></Blog>