<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>28,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
       The Countdown Begins   Well, it's one week until I leave the country...omigod!  I'm totally freakin'!! (Oh, before I forget, I must warn you about something if you are going to read my blog - I love exclamation points!!!  I use them...lots!)   Tonight is my last night at one of my jobs, The Improv Asylum.  Tomorrow is my last night at another one of my jobs, Jeannette Neill Dance Studio.  And Monday is my last day at job number 3, Borders Books.  It's wierd, I haven't been without work since I was 15 and I started washing dishes at the golf club by my house, and now I'm leaving all of my jobs at the same time.  I'm very excited to have all of that extra room in my brain for things that are important to me personally, instead of things like when the RPL (recommended pull list) is due at Borders, which workstudy keeps putting the trash in the wrong place, or the price of a dinner package for two at Mother Anna's.  (It's $100 by the way, plus a $2 service charge if you order over the phone.  A VERY good deal for a 3-course meal and an award-winning comedy show, you should check it out!)  Now I can concentrate on living in Europe and becoming snooty..."wearing black and speaking French for no reason"!  I'll give a dollar to anyone who names that movie quote!    What else??  Nothing really exciting is happening because I'm not there yet.  Right now I'm just dealing with the bagillion last minute things that all of my friends who have travelled warned me about.  I never dreamt it would be this hard to leave the country!!!    So, my first blog entry wasn't that interesting.  What do you expect?  I'm at work right now finishing up my last night!  I had to stop writing a couple times to fix a ticket error, get late people into the show, and fix the flush handle on the toilet in the mens room.  (Wow, I can't WAIT to leave!)  So, no worries, these entries are sure to get more interesting...so stay tuned...     
     

    
</post>
<date>22,August,2003</date>
<post>


       
      This is Liza. Welcome to my blog! Stay tuned. 
     

    
</post>
<date>25,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
       The DAM!!!   Yay!!  I went to Amsterdam last weekend!!  It is gorgeous.    I started to write about it earlier this week, but had to stop in the middle of my post and tried to save it as a draft...no dice, so I have to start over, which sucks because...  Right now, I am going on 3 hours sleep!! (one of my roommates has a slight log-sawing problem)  We are leaving for London at 7:00 am, so this blurb has to happen...please excuse me if I am a little punchy!  First, of course, a little history:  Once upon a time there was a river of Amstel (yes, Amstel, like the beer, except it wat-ter.  It's almost the weekend, people, just stay with me.)  People wanted to live by the Amstel, but the land was below sea level.  This was a bummer.  What do you think they did?  No, Matty T., they didn't drink the river of Amstel!!  They built a DAM!!  Get it?!  Amstel....DAM!  Now, I don't know how many of you have heard Dutch, it's a peculiarly beautiful language, but pronouncing the 'LD' is not so easy...so it evolved to an 'RD'.  Amsterdam!    YAY!  Good story, Liza!  Yes, I know you all oved it.  You have my permission to retell it at parties.  So, Amsterdam, as I said before, is GORgeous!  Along with the dam, the Dutch people, clever as they are, built canals.  Amsterdam consists of 5 (I think) canals which are concentric half circles that move out from Dam Square, the center of the city.  The oldest architecture, in the center circle, dates to the medieval period.  ALL of the architecture in the city is amazing.  So...what did I do there??  Friday we went to the Rijksmuseum, mostly Medieval through Romantic...LOTS of Rembrandt, whose innovative techniques are mindblowing to see in person.  Friday night, they took all 82 of us out for Indonesian food, then the Music History students went to a concert.  Beethoven's 4th and Tchaikovski's 4th, performed by the ConcertGebeouwOrkestra.  Saturday, the Van Gogh museum...wow, I don't even know what to say here.  I don't think I  need  to say anything, I mean, it's Vincent Van Gogh!  Then we walked around...a LOT!  We had great weather and the city is full of quirky little shops.  Walked through the Red Light District...it definitely almost induced reverse paristalsis. (head to dictionary.com if that one threw you for a loop)  My roommate and I then split from our group and headed over to the Anne Frank House.  Wow...I cried...I read that book for the first time when I was in 6th grade or something, and have read it in so many classes since then.  There is a tour through the house where Anne and her family hid for 25 months, and attached to it is a museum and bookstore.     That is my Amsterdam experience in a nutshell.  Amazing!!  Miss you all!!  Wish me luck on my quest to kiss Prince William!!
     

    
</post>
<date>23,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
       And the winner is.......    Michael Kilgore, Ladies and Gentlemen!!!   Michael wins the prize for being the first to send me snail mail, which we all look longingly for every day on our way to dinner!  I know it's expensive, so I completely understand, but it was such a nice surprise!!  Thanks Mike!!  I'm really glad you're enjoying your birthday gift (The L.O.T.R. Two Towers DVD).  That movie kicks lots of bootie!!    Yay for Mike!!
     

    
</post>
<date>18,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Where were we?   So, yes, the movie...see it if you get a chance.  Also, there was a Nike ad played before the movie started.  Are they playing this in the states?  It is a basketball game and they start to play musical chairs.  It was hiLARious!    Anyshmoo...  We woke up at the hostel Saturday morning too late to get the free COFFEE!!!  AAAHHHHHH!!!  Liza - caffeine = NOT PRETTY!!  We start to wonder, stumble accross this little bakery, the man there is my SAVIOR...fresh muffins and a double espresso...I'm ready to go!  We shopped for a while in the shopping district, it was packed, then headed over to see some of the most interesting architecture I've ever seen.  Now, a little bit of background on Rotterdam, in case you're not familiar.  Rotterdam basically got the CRAP bombed out of it during the war.  There was barely anything left.  It's a terrible tragedy, but has yeilded a city FULL of modern architecture, late 40's and early 50's.  We saw the cubic houses...houses literally in the shape of cubes, turned up onto one corner.  People actually live there, and there is one that you can enter, it was amazing.  The cubic houses are right next to the Rotterdam Library, and HUGE building with bright orange tubes running all along the outside.  We continued along the harbor, with a gorgeous view of the Swan Bridge...yup, a bridge, in the modern cubic shape of a swan.  We headed over to the architeutural institute, this was my favorite memory in Rotterdam.  Outside was an exhibit.  It was called "Architects of Air".  It was a huge inflatable complex, climate controlled and filled with spacey Enya-ish music...kind of what you hear while waiting in line at Space Mountain.  Made mostly of opaque grey plastic/rubber.  In each 'room' there were slats of translucent colored plastic/rubber through which the sun would filter, and the 'walls' were molded into different shapes.  It is very hard to describe.  I will have to find a site with great pictures, so that I can put a link in here for you guys, because I really don't know how to describe how interesting Rotterdam is.    That night, there just happened to be a festival going on, so we had a lot of fun just wandering, ducking into a bar or a coffee shop here and there.  There was a lot of art to look at and there were people EVERYWHERE!   Eventually, we wound up back at the hostel...the couple that we shared our room with was already asleep, but we were relieved to see that they were at least fully clothed, unlike the first night when we came home...EEEWWWW!!!!  The next day we headed back to the castle.  It was a bit of a debachle getting back here...I guess Boston is not the only place in the world that has issues with public transportation.  Let's just say that the 2 1/2 hour trip took us about 6 hours.  Oh well, it's all part of the experience, Right?  Rrrriiiiiight!  I say that now.  If you would've said that to me Sunday night when I finally crawled up the stairs to my room, I probably would've introduced your nose to my fist!  Tomorrow morning it's on to Amsterdam!  I hope everyone has a fantabulous weekend!!
     

    
</post>
<date>15,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
       And Finally, Ladies and Gentlemen...Rotterdam   Geez!  Sorry I'm such a slacker about writing about my very first weekend of travelling.  Things are picking up in the homework department, so I'm working on, ya know,  learning  every night...and we stop having access to the internet at 1:00am, so it's taken a few days for me to get in here and write about Rotterdam.  We leave tomorrow for Amsterdam, though, so I've got to do this today.    So....  Last Friday, at about 10:45am, we (Myself, Erin, Emily, Eva, and Ross) walk out of the castle with our packs on our backs and head down to the bus stop! We are all set for our journey, we know when the train comes, we have our Strippenkarts for the bus, we grab some breakfast at the bakery, we are all set.  So...we see the bus coming, before we actually get to the bus stop.  In a state of I-need-to-travel-right-now frenzy, we start to run accross the street...and Ross almost dies!  It's all good though!!!  Everythings alright!  One of us must have had the presense of mind to yell "HEMANDROOOPPAIWAY" (Roughly translated as "Hey Ross, there's a car speeding towards your mortal body, you need to stop moving right now or you will die, please.")  Yay!!  We all got on the bus in one piece!  We got the rest of the way there by train, accidentally sitting in first class on the way...  Conductor: You have to move or you have to PAY!  Embarrassing? NAH!  We just played the 'Dumb American' card...works every time!  Then we changed trains and  got on the wrong one...a minor setback, and we got to see a little more of the Netherlandish countryside...it's beautiful.    So FINALLY we arrive in Rotterdam.  We are in the financial district and are a little lost.  Yours truly forgot to actually print out the Hostel Reservation confirmation with the address of the hostel on it.  On to the internet cafe.  We grab some grup and head to our hostel, for all of us this is our first hostel experiance.  The room is nice, the showers are a little hairy, but hey, what do you expect for 22 euros a night?!  We spent the rest of the day wondering, going into little shops, eating Turkish cuisine (of which there is a LOT in Rotterdam...weird, huh?) and seeing a movie!  We wanted to see a movie in Dutch, but there were none playing, so we saw one that is Icelandic with Dutch subtitles!  It was amazing!!!  We totally got everything!  The performances were great.  It was called Noi Albinoi...if it is playing anywhere in the states, I highly recommend it.    I need to go grab some grub...I'll be back after lunch to talk about the amazing architecture and art we saw on Saturday...
     

    
</post>
<date>15,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Decisions, Decisions...   I can't decide what I want to write about in my next blog.  I'm thinking either Hurricane Izzy...because I think it's really funny that they named a Hurricane after my friend Izzy!!  HAHA  IZZER!!  Or...............  The demise of BENNIFER!!  Wow!  I love America!  Every news site I went to after spending the weekend in a foreign city not knowing what was going on in my motherland had HEADLINING STORIES about J-Lo getting dumped by Ben Affleck.  What the hell?!  Honestly, HONESTLY people, there's nothing better to talk about???
     

    
</post>
<date>11,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
       September 11...is everyone alright?   Two years ago I called my dad in Arizona from my office in Boston.  "Dad, are you watching the news?" "No, honey, I'm just getting ready to leave for the airport."  "Dad, turn on the news." A few seconds later..."Oh my God..."  And then I cried.  I cried for a long time.  It still makes me cry writing about it.  I just woke up this morning and was a long way from home, and just wanted to say that I hope everyone is doing alright today.  I love you all, and by all, I mean every human being who might ever read this.    Peace be with you.
     

    
</post>
<date>09,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
       I'm Like Elmira Gultch   Wow, I just took a bike ride around the town.  So far I had been to the 2 bars, the store Alles Onder Een Dak (All under one roof), and the ATM at the Rabobank.  (I love Dutch!!  When I say I need to go to the Rabobank I picture a bank that was shot to death and then brought back to life using what was left of it, supplemented with mechanical parts of other banks.  And now it's like a big indestructible Rabobank with big guns hidden in it's thighs, but it still has human feelings and memories.  Does anyone else think that when they say Rabobank?  Anyone?  Anyone?)  Anyshmoo, today I took a bike ride around the rest of town.  Didn't take long, Well is about the size of Arthur, North Dakota.  If you don't know how big Arthur, North Dakota is, ask my mom, my grandparents, or one of my cousins.  Everyone who you pass says hello.  There's no litter AT ALL on the streets.  Every house is adorable!!  I just love it, love it, LOVE IT!!  There is a river that runs along the southern Border of the town.  There is a Lake.  There are lots of fields: some with goats, some with corn, and LOTS with HORSES!  Yes mom, HORSES!  And there is a stable where you can ride, which mom and I will most definitely be doing when she comes here!  MOST EXCELLENT!!  Also, I have been to almost all of my classes, French is the only one I haven't had yet.  I love them all.  Once I have been to all of them I will have more info to write descriptions of courses and teachers.    Oh yes, and I figured out what I'm doing this weekend.  We are going to spend the day Friday in Naimagaan (I need to learn how to spell that) and then that night we are going to Rotterdam, until Sunday.  We are going to try to find some live music and/or a Dutch movie house.  YAY!!  First weekend!!!  Oh, and when I say "we" I mean some of the friends I have made here.  There's Erin, one of my roommates, who is Irish and, how awesome is this, does Irish step dancing.  Emily, who plays guitar 'wicked fuckin'good'.  Eva, whose last name is Constantopolis (say that 5 times fast) and who has a RAD singing voice.  And Ross, who is super easy to talk to and officially became my friend when he let me borrow his Aerosmith CD.  A fun little group!!  I will let you know how it goes!!  As for further blog entries, of course I will be writing to tell you all about the different cities I go to, museums that I see, people I meet, all of that.  However, I know that, when friends of mine travel, I always have so many questions.  If you have a specific something that you want to hear about, or want me to check out, email me...YAY!!
     

    
</post>
<date>08,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Oops, I forgot!   I forgot that I don't see and speak to most of you on a daily basis.  I've gotten some emails that go something like..."what are you doing there?"..."Why are you there?"...and..."You're in the F@$#ing Netherlands?!  So, allow me to explain...  I go to Emerson College.  Emerson college owns a castle in the Netherlands, Kasteel Well.  They have an semester exchange program that students can apply for and that I was accepted to, yay me!  Monday through Thursday, we live and take class at the castle.  Mostly art  music history, philosophy...european-centered studies.  The, on the weekends, we get to travel.  There was a travel package we all purchased, it includes 3 weekends that we all so together: Paris, Amsterdam, and Florence (Sorry Suarez!!) And it also includes a Eurail pass, activated at the end of this month, that is good for two months, so we can use our other weekends, along with 2 week-long breaks, to travel and learn more.  Kasteel Well is in the town of Well.  It is a very small town about 5 minutes from the German border.  The closest larger cities, if you are having issues finding me on a map, are Venlo to the south and Naimaagen (I think I spelled that wrong) to the North.    That is the gist!!!  Now we are all on the same page, woo hoo!!!
     

    
</post>
<date>07,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
         Holy drunk fetuses, Batman!!!     Sorry if the fetus reference grosses you out.  It is a pet name for young people, started by Jeremy King...so blame him!!  Well, our first weekend here was full of orientation meetings and 19 year olds feeling awkward ordering their first alcoholic drinks in bars.  It was FUN-NY!!!  "Um, what kind of mixed drinks do you have?" (bartender says something in unintelligible Dutch) "Well, I don't like beer, do you have a list?"  (more unintelligible Dutch)  "A list??" (more Dutch, but then some english "Pick a color.")  "Um, green???"  It looked to me like a Midori sour...but I didn't taste it.  4 Euro for something smaller than my fist?  I'll have a beer please!!  And so it went.    It was very sweet...I make fun, but I have to say, if Matt Terry hadn't been there to get me good and pukey on my 21st, I would have been just as lost.  Tip your hat to Matty T. if you see him.    What else?  What else, what else?? (You have to sing that.  If you don't know what I'm talking about, call Chris or Stephy Pysher, they'll clue you in!!)  We start class tomorrow.  I feel very ready.  I'm all set.  I've got my books, I went to the store in town yesterday and bought shampoo and all that stuff, so I'm clean!  My roommates and I got together and rented a bike, so we can escape campus if we need to, and there is a gorgeous spider outside our window that has caught and punished every renegade bug dumb enough to attempt entry...life is good.  We already, through a scheduling mix up, have a free weekend to travel, next weekend.  Our train passes, however, do not get activated until about a two weeks later.  So, if anyone has any cheap suggestions of what to do, I'm all ears.  I don't plan on spending one weekend on campus.  In fifteen minutes, we have coffe and tea in Sophie's Lounge.  Sophie, if you haven't read the history of the castle, is a...or I should say, WAS A, 13 year old girl who lived in the castle, and died in the castle, and now, as legend has it, Haunts the Castle!!!  Do do do do, do do do do  (If you didn't get that, I was singing the theme from The Twilight Zone.)  Such Wit!  Such Humor!!  Wow, I'm even annoying myself!!  Well, I'm better go get some caffeine in the Ghost room, because we have more meetings all afternoon!!!  YAY!!!  Wish my luck in my first day of classes tomorrow!  I love you all!!!
     

    
</post>
<date>05,September,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Holy crap, I'm here!   I've been awake since Thursday morning at 7:00, Boston time.  I dragged my stuff to school, sat in meetings, ran last minute errands, went to the airport, said goodbye to Chris (cried!!), then our flight was delayed 3 hours, we flew, took a 2 1/2 hour bus ride, and finally arrived here, and then had some of our orientation stuff.  It's now 9:07 Holland time...3:07 Boston time, on Friday afternoon.  I can barely type, let alone be witty, but I had to drop a line to my loyal readers as soon as I could!  It's unbelievably beautiful here!!!  The Castle (whose website I will add a link to later, when I can think straight) is smaller than I expected, but ten times more amazing!! I mean, it's a CASTLE!!!  It's has two moats, black swans, fountains, all that stuff!!  It's gorgeous!!  I'm going to go take a shower now, and then sleep the sleep of the dead until I can sleep no more!!  I love you all!!
     

    
</post>
<date>29,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
       If I eat one more chocolate, I will puke!!   Belgium, I love you!  Brugge is absolutely the cutest little medieval city I've ever seen!!  We got there the afternoon of the 24th, after a six hour journey that was supposed to take 4 hours.  We transferred trains FIVE TIMES...what is up?  The best is when you're standing on a train platform in the freezing cold and your train isn't showing up and then there's an announcement in another language and everyone who understood it starts to walk away.  AAHH!!  Whatever, we got there....  and it was great!  The entire weekend is a blur of shopping, gawking at medieval architecture, munching mussels and, of course...CHOCOLATE!  Our hostel was right in the middle of things...YAY ZOE...so we would just walk until we got cold, then some back to the hostel (right above a bar/restaurant, the room was painted with yellow and blue swirls...trippy!!) and warm up, then head out for some more.  We traveled with a larger group (Ross, Erin, Eva, Emily, Laura, Zoe, Deborah, Jen, and LIZA!) so we jsut kept splitting up and getting back together.  One of my favorite things was that they have an entire Tin Tin store!  If you're not familiar with Tin Tin, click on Chris's link at the top of my blog, he'll school you!    There also, randomly, was a Dali exhibit being held in the building underneath the clock tower (which Zoe and I climbed to the top of on Sunday...Motha of Gawd, that's a hig friggin' towah!!  Umm, that's supposed to be a Boston accent.)  which was amazing.  It was a lot of his later work, 1935-1960's.  There was one series that was based on Alice in Wonderland...it was so scary but I couldn't stop looking at it.  There was also a rendering of the crucifixion that I had never seen before.  I kept thinking of Matt Redder, one of the most gifted artists I have the pleasure of being friends with, and how I'm going to be walking through an enormous exhibit of his work one day.  I love Dali!  So that was Brugge.  Not the most adventurous weekend (except getting there and back...on the way back it took 8 hours, what?!?!) but so much fun!    This weekend we (Myself, Eva, Emily and Dylan) are going to Prague.  My first Eastern Europe experience...I'm so excited!!
     

    
</post>
<date>28,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
       We're all caught up!!   Just to get everything squared away, here's a quick synopsis of what's happened since my solo travel week.  The week that I got back, mom and dad were here from Tuesday until Thursday!  SO MUCH FUN!!  They stayed at the little B that is here in town.  It was really fun having dinner with them and trading stories about European travels.  For those of you that don't know them, they have never been to this side of the pond either.  They started out in London, saw some theatre in the West End (RAD!!) and hit some cool English pubs!  Then they came to Amsterdam, then met me in Well...I'm sure THAT was the highlight of their trip...from London to....(wait for it).........WELL!!!!  Wow, I'm know, it's just so thrilling!  Then they continued on to Paris!  YAY for mom and dad!!    The following weekend, the 17th - 19th, I stayed at the castle.  Almost half of the students did.  Our midterms were the following week, we had just gotten back from a full 10 days of travel, everyone was exhausted!  (I was warned about this before I came, people said that about half-way through the semester, you just need a break, so you don't burn out.)  We took a days trip on Friday up to Arnhem.  There is a national park.  You enter, pay a fee, and rent a bike.  Then you ride through every type of terrain imaginable; tall think forrests, rolling hills of tall wheatgrass, beachy sand dunes, shorter forrests...10 kilometers later, you arrive at the Kroller-Mueller museum.  The museum has an outdoor sculpture garden and a great collection of Van Gogh's work. (Including Cafe de Nuit...SO pretty!!)    The rest of the weekend was nice and relaxing.  We had picnics in our dorm, studied for finals, jammed with Emily on her guitar...it was like a big 3 day long sleepover party!  YAY  The following week is a midterms induced blur, then this past weekend we went to Brugge.  I'll tell you about that in a little bit!!  
     

    
</post>
<date>22,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Horay for the devil kitty!!!   Last night we carved pumpkins...it was perfect!  It was freezing cold and very clear.  The air smelled like cold and fireplaces.  We went to the Barn, a big ...well...BARN that is just outside the castle entrance, and walked in and there was a huge pile of pumpkins!!  YAY!  There were all different kinds: little round ones, huge ones, short fat ones, tall skinny ones, red ones, green ones, orange ones!!!  We all picked one and started carving!  Mine is a little kitty with devil horns...so cute!  This waqs Erin's first time carving one, she carved out a sun!  Ross did a ladybug (lieveheersbeestje in Dutch)!  It was an all around good time!  I took lots of pictures to show you all.  When we were done, we ran back to our rooms (it was SO COLD by then) and put on jammies and made hot chocolate!  It was a  great  night!
     

    
</post>
<date>22,October,2003</date>
<post>


       
       Je rentre au bon Paris!!   So I just hang in Amboise the rest of the night!  There are so many cute little shops, restaurants, creperies!  It's a gorgeous place to just sit around!  Then I went back to my cute little hostel.  The next morning I hung in Amboise some more, did some souvenir shopping.  Traveling alone, I wrote a LOT in my journal, so I needed a new one.  I think the one I bought is my favorite souvenir so far, it's SO pretty, I almost don't want to write in it.    I headed back to Paris, hoping to get an overnight train back to Amsterdam.  Well...didn't happen.  The overnight train only runs in the  summer !  I was wondering what the little 's' in my schedule meant!!  Bad news...I'm stuck in a city with almost no money.  Good news...that city is PARIS!!  I found the cheapest hotel that had an opening and hunkered down for the night.  I walked over to the hotel where I had stayed on Thursday night...the employees there were really cool, about my age, and spoke English.  We hung for a little while, had some dinner, and I went back to my hotel to tackle the task of fitting everything I had purchased during the week into my backpack.  Let me tell you, this was not pretty!!  So, that is the story of my solo travels.  I never thought I would finish!!  I hope that you are all still awake!!  People keep asking me what I thought of traveling alone.  I loved it!  I highly recommend it!  Was it scary and overwhelming at times?  Of course, but think of all the great stuff you've done that is scary and overwhelming at times!  Remember, "Courage is fear that has said it's prayers!" </post></Blog>