<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        12:23 pm and I've finally recieved the other half of my picture.    The picture I speak of features a vividly  rouge  strawberry, witha rasberry (which happens to be just as vibrant) set, unfocused, in the background. However unfortunate it is, the photograph is cut in half for the sole purpose of testing our mailing system in Canada.A close turtlonianperson of mine was told that any mail sent in certain parts of Canada is delivered within three days. For instance, if you send something from Ottawa on the same day that you send something from Toronto, both items will arrive at their destination on thesame day.        Being the wonderfully trying person he is, he decided to find out if thisclaim was true. Thusly, chopping up a perfectly good photograph (for a good cause of course!) and sending one half to my house from Toronto, and the other from Mississauga. As he had suspected the pieces did not arrive on the same day, or even within a two day span. I recieved the first half (sent from Mississauga)on Thursday, July 22nd; and as exciting as that was I finally recieved the second half (from Toronto) today - Monday, July 26th. What a gip, I'd have to say I'm severly disappointed in the system.  
    
</post>
<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
           On another of those dreary days this summer I decided to use my treasured $30 gift certificate at Chapters. Iwas finally ablebuy at least two books instead of drooling atthem on the shelves. It was wonderful. Besides the fact that Chapters is redecorated every time I go there, (they must have acoffee-highredecorator) it's a great place to just  be  in.    On this particular day I happened to be among the best seller/sales section when  The Cheese Monkeys  jumped me.When you glance at the title your mind automatically hurls an array of thoughtsyour way - opens your horizons, gives younew ideas... confuses youto all hell.    "Never judge a book by its cover."  The   Cheese Monkeys , by Chip Kidd, blatantly stomps over this saying and puts it to rest in a lovely little swamp. The cover is what makes this book, or rather, is what bashes the reader over the head and says 'Read me, read me!' At first glance all that is seen is an oh-so-stylish pumpkincoloured front flap featuring the words, "The Cheese Monkeys". On the insideof the flap is an antique looking picture of a baby's head (why a baby's head?) and, of course, a few critiques beside the author's strangely austere picture. Now this was all fairly normalso far, aside from the obviously odd title, buta closerlook revealsan entirely new world.    Upon removing the flapI discovered a lump of Swiss cheese and three monkeys - another fashionable way of displaying the title.AsIsoon discovered, there were countless hidden messages splayed across, around, and throughout the book.In the most unthinkable spots were written random phrases such as:    "Whatever you do... don't think about elephants." (After that what can you do but think about elephants!)    "What do you see?" (A blank page?)    "Good is dead." (Also a quote featured on one of his first pages.)    ...Most of these sayings are repeated in the book, but in different and quite imaginative ways each time.    Not only is the coverwonderfully refreshing, but as well the book itself upholdsits status of highly energetic style. Even the first few pagesmaintaina certainartistic flare by manipulating the placement of the copyright. Normally thought of as one of the mostbasic and boring things a book can contain, Kidd againquestionsthis unmoving notion by spreading thecopyright throughout six pages of the book, on one line directly in the middle. The mere fact that someone would purposely waste pages to make the  copyright  interesting stands out in my mind as something truly ingenious.    AsI continuedmy little  journey  throughthis book there were dozens of extraordinary things keeping my mind up and roaring, and of course glued to the book. That'snot saying thestory itself isn't just as brilliant. Kidd's story featuresa time when Graphic Designing entered and changed his life. It is definitely nota biography, thank goodness; it is more like an assortment of fictional incidents that end in a mass of confusion... quite illuminating and provocative confusion mind you.    Havingthoroughly enjoyed this book I'd have to sayKidd's combination of artistic styleandinsightful probing throughouthis piece dragged me in and gave my mind the workout it had been craving. If you're ever stuck in a rut and in need ofa philosophical or mental boost  The Cheese Monkeys  is most definitely something I'd recommend. A treat for the artist and writer alike.           
    
</post>
</Blog>