<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>31,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      5:30 pm  Mood: Peaceful Music: Norah Jones - Don't Know Why  Iron Maiden and Gamma Ray rocked big time. Bruce Dickinson is probably almost 50 years old but his voice is still amazingly clear and powerful and he can still sing the hight parts, too. He must be in an amazing condition, since he runs around the stage, plays mr. Death or whatever fits into the scene and sings at the same time for 2 hours. Gamma Ray's performance was more modest and the sound was shitty and they also played only for about an hour (like always with the opening acts...), but they really rocked. Man, I really love old school heavy metal! Long live true metal and death to false metal! ;)  Friday... We've been invited to a party. A friend of ours is leaving soon to Australia for 3 months and this is the last night together. We're gonna go to a mexican restaurant to eat and drink. Oh man... It's gonna be a busy weekend. Today to Bern to meet some buddies from IRC and on Sunday Rico has to go to studio to check out some things with some guys. I'm not gonna go with him, wanna stay home or go walking on the hills.  I hate this fucking Halloween fuzz. A good excuse to party. Who the hell needs an excuse to party? Why do people have to support such stupid commercial parties like Halloween... It's all american bullshit. A "Great Tradition"... My ass. Well yeah, you can send your kids (if you have some) to beg for candies and that way irritate your possibly annoying neighbours. That's just about the only good thing about Halloween ;)   Well, gotta go hug and kiss my man. He came home from the office completely pissed off with stupid people there =)  
     
    
</post>
<date>30,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      12:42 pm  Mood: Worn out Music: Norah Jones - Come Away With Me  2-14-03  On love. They say it makes the world go round. Money can't buy it. And it conquers all. They say all is fair in love and war. So make love, not war. They say the first one always has a special place in your heart. They say it's better to have loved and lost than to never have loved at all. They say love is blind. Love is colorblind. Love is a many-colored thing. There's first love, puppy love, platonic love, unrequited love, true love, unconditional love, love at first sight, the love of your life, the one you want your mama to meet, the one that got away... So we ride through the Tunnel of Love. Make out at Lover's Lane. Say our vows at the Chapel of Love. Take a cruise on the Loveboat and reserve the Honeymoon Suite. And sometimes we gotta stay at the Heartbreak Hotel. But hey, love is a battlefield. And I'm a soldier of love.  -T. (Tatsuya Ishida, http://sinfest.net/resistance.htm)  It's a slightly stormy day outside... It's really windy and I think it's gonna rain soon. The autumn here in Switzerland has been so different from the one in Finland. No real colours, not that same feeling. It's already snowing in Finland and here it's still over 0 celsius.  Tonight is the Iron Maiden-gig we've been waiting for long. I'm not really in the mood, since I'm really, really homesick. I got a letter from my dad yesterday and he sent some photos, too. I must say my nieces and my nephew are the most adorable kids in the world... And I miss them like hell. I also miss Finland in general. I know, there would everything be easier, I wouldn't have to do all the paper work and face new things all the time. But then again, I know that I wouldn't be happy there, either. I know, I'm gonna be happier here. Last night, as I cried on Rico's arms (his hug is so secure, so warm and caring...), I once again became more certain that he's the one I want to be with. I don't know if it's for forever, but at least I'm happy now. I love him.  I am so tired after all the crying last night. But I know it's gonna get better. And my baby is coming home earlier today.
     
    
</post>
<date>21,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      4:38 pm  Mood: GRRRRRRR Music: Metallica - Sad but True  Today is an old school heavy metal day. Or at least at the moment. I don't have too much old school with me here (I miss my Iron Maiden and Judas Priest CDs!!), so I have to listen to Rico's Metallica. Actually I decided to do a hard core experiment and listen a whole CD of Linkin Park (so far I've managed to listen to a whole song from them), but I failed. I could listen to one song and then I had to quit. I just can't stand that numetal (no metal) bullshit "so now I'm gonna sing a little, something angsty and then da dude there is gonna rap a little and it's so fucking cool and we're gonna get loadsa money by fooling people to think that this is good music". Brr. Numetal is probably one of the worst things that have ever happened to the humankind. Silly looking angry young men in very large pants bouncing around the stage trying to be credible... YAAAAAAWN. Yep, I can't help it. I just love old school, black, death, progressive... At least in those genres people (in general) can play their instruments and the vocalists can sing or roar or whatever ;) Found some interesting links considering heavy metal and its history:  http://www.hardradio.com/framehistory.html  http://www.allmusic.com/cg/amg.dll  Under allmusic.com there are own categories for all genres of heavy metal, worth reading through. And a couple of radio stations playing hard rock/heavy:  http://64.202.98.75:8100/  http://www.hardradio.com/  Cool.  So, it's time to go again. Take care!
     
    
</post>
<date>20,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      10:21 am  Mood: Awake, Happy Music: Donald Fagen - Trans-Island Skyway  Picked up Donald Fagen for this morning. Easy listening, but not irritatingly simple. And it brings nice memories of the Steely Dan concert on 2000. It was amazing to see the band I've listened to live. I mean, it had its top moments in the 70s, before I was even born. The audience was a mixture of old fans and young people. The meeting of different generations =)  Hmm... The last time I wrote was on Wednesday. Nothing much has happened, the usual. On Saturday we went to Zurich with Rico and Serge (a friend of Rico's), spent some time there and then came home. Then we went to visit Rico's mother shortly, brought her some cake I had baked. Yesterday she sent an sms "thanks, the cake was Delicious!", so I guess I have it easier with her ;) Especially when I told her I can knit :D So far she has been the one to repair Rico's socks and now I'm there to do that. Saves her time =)  Yesterday we were very hard-working =) We slept till one o'clock or so but after that... We cleaned up the whole apartment together etc. Then we went walking on the hills for 90 minutes or so. It was so beautiful up there. You can see the whole Wettingen from the top! It was a little bit misty and the air was so fresh... We also walked through a farm and saw two adorable pigs :D They came to see us and grunted, I think they just came to see, if we have anything to eat ;) When we came home, we made burritos, had a couple of beers and watched Matrix: Reloaded on dvd. It was ok, the special effects were great but otherwise it wasn't really anything special. But it was a perfect Sunday! Relaxing indeed.  With Rico everything seems to get better. We go deeper in our relationship and that feels goddamn good. This morning I was surprised about my feelings getting deeper, too. I haven't experienced the Great Awakening with my feelings and that makes me sure, that I'm on the right way with this thing. You know, the Great Rush won't last long and the risk of the relationship coming to its end is greater. It's also possible that the feelings don't grow to be love at all and that's problematic, too. In my case it has happened slowly but securely. I discover the whole time new things in Rico, that I like and that make me want him to be my man even more. I respect his intelligence, kindness, tenderness, sense of humour etc. But I don't adore him, that wouldn't be healthy any more. I'm just soooooo happy that he's my partner and my friend and I hope we stay together for long.  (My english is getting really, really bad... I already have to check words from a german-english dictionary... :/ )
     
    
</post>
<date>15,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      10:02 pm  Mood: Peace of mind Music: None  We went shopping yesterday, since Rico took half a day off from work. I finally got a coffee machine and a mixer;) Then I got my own blanket and that's a relief, since he always steels the whole blanket in the night and I end up freezing naked beside him... Of course we couldn't leave Media Markt without a heap of dvds! I wanted the Dream Theater live-dvd "Scenes from New York" (awsome... I was completely taken away from this world when watching the concert. Those men are geniuses!), he got Matrix: Reloaded, Animatrix and some other movies, too. I love going shopping dvds with him, since we share the same interests.  I'm also getting used to the idea of living here permanently... It's still incredible, but I'm so happy!  Oops, Monty Python has already begun! Gotta go and laugh my ass off ;)
     
    
</post>
<date>13,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      3:03 pm  Mood: So very happy Music: Pain of Salvation - This Heart of Mine  I lie awake watching your shoulders Move so softly as you breathe With every breathe you're growing older But that is fine if you're with me  I pledge to wake you with a smile I pledge to hold you when you cry I pledge to love you till I die Till I die  The rays of dawn plays on your eyelids A sleeping beauty dressed in sun  I will wake you with a smile I will hold you when you cry I will love you till I die Till I die Till I die  I believe this heart of mine when it tells my eyes That this is beauty I believe this heart of mine when it tells my mind  That this is reason I believe this heart of mine when it cries at time That this is forever I believe this heart of mine when it tells the skies  That this is the face of God  I am so lucky. I am so happy! I actually live together with my man... I mean, we've been living together more or less since may, but today it was said out loud for the first time. I can't believe it's true, it's almost too good to be true! But everything has gone so well, and this is also a reasonable thing to do, since apartments in Switzerland are expensive.  This is, however, not just reasonable... Now I'm sure he's serious about our relationship and really wants to be with me.. Not just now, but also in the future. Now I dare to think about things we can do next winter, spring, summer... I dare to plan. I now have a home...  I think I'm in love.
     
    
</post>
<date>11,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      7:51 pm  Mood: Wonderfully peacefully happy Music: Nada.  We slept this morning somewhat badly, I didn't have enough blanket or space etc. We kept on keeping each other wake;) Then Rico went to lay on the couch, I followed him a little bit later and then we were there together, somehow in each other's arms. Sweet;) We woke up slowly and gently and it was wonderful. Then we went shopping, drove to Glattzentrum to shop in Globus. Globus has the best delicatessen department I've seen here so far. And the service is great! But then again, everything costs "a bit" more than elsewhere. WE bought some fine fish and large shrimps and some good wine and...and... Ooooh yessss... We also popped into the book store to look at some books and I'm still dreaming of buying muse-parfum (joop!) ;)  Hence, this day has mainly been wonderful sex, amazing food and wine... A perfect Saturday! So, gotta go cooking!
     
    
</post>
<date>10,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      1:41 pm  Mood: Surprisingly normal  Music: Dream Theater - Metropolis - Part I "The Miracle and the Sleeper"  Before the leaves have fallen Before we lock the doors There must be the third and last dance This one will last forever Metropolis watches and thoughtfully smiles She's taken you to your home  It can only take place When the struggle between our children has ended Now the Miracle and the Sleeper know that the third is love  Love is the Dance of Eternity (words: Petrucci)  Dream Theater  urlLink   is the band of my life... Like Beatles or Rolling Stones to some people. Our "relationship" began some 3 years ago, thanks to a friend of mine. He played me parts from Scenes from a Memory and that was it. Musically they are almost geniuses, they have total control of their instruments. They are virtuosos, but play extremely well together... In their lyrics they actually have something to say. I've seen them live only 2 times (in Oberhausen, Germany and Provinssirock, Finland) and my third opportunity is next February in Winterthur. I can't wait... But... If I were in Germany, where I used live, I'd be able to see them twice, since they play in Koeln and Dortmund, since the both cities are close to Duesseldorf. Well, better once  than not at all.  Today I'm doing fine, it's weekend! I think I'll manage to do some translation today. My problem is just that the text to be translated SUCKS BIG TIME. So far I've just read old irc logs from #polonhoitoalue, chatted with friends, listened to Dream Theater... I should clean up and I'd like to bake something, before He comes home. Or, I don't HAVE to clean up... I just want to, since he goes to work and I'm at home, although I have work, too... Hmm, complicated;) Well, I just like to make the life of my loved ones a little easier. I know he doesn't like cleaning up.  Well, I'm gonna do something now. Dunno where to start! And WEHEY, the sun is shining! =))
     
    
</post>
<date>09,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      2:00 pm  And now I'm just fucked up. After the crying I usually get fucked up and now I'm in that phase. FUUUUUUUUUCK.
     
    
</post>
<date>07,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Mood: Sedated Music: Muse - Falling Away With You  10:10 am  Didn't have time to write yesterday, but then again nothing much happened yesterday... We went to Zurich with Katja (one of my summerjob mates, who's still here) and walked around and I had to buy some warm clothes. Once again we were amazed of the lack of service oriented people in the shops. I went to pay my stuff in H on the Bahnhofstrasse and I guess she didn't even look at me properly. Instead she concentrated on blabbering with her colleagues and as soon as I had paid and still gathered my stuff together, was she gone. No "Byebye", "Have a nice day" whatsoever. And the same in Manor on Bahnhofstrasse. And I have thought, that service in Finnland is not that good;) But then Katja told me, that there has been researches that have proved that the level of Finnish service is really good in comparison with other countries. \o/ I guess that's why we were so popular waitresses in the labour camp...erm...Hotel Rhodannenberg. The guests said direct to us, that we were so friendly and everything and at least I got personal Trinkgeld more than once.  So, we demand SERVICE!=) It feels so SILLY, if the customers (in this case me and Katja) are friendlier to the clerks than they are to the customer.   Then we went to eat pasta and have a glass of wine. Soon we noticed that it's getting late and I should go shopping (forgot my housewife function completely!;), since the fridge was practically empty. When we came out from Coop and headed towards the main railwaystation, a man looked at us a bit longer. I thought it was just because we're speaking an odd language and not particularly quiet. We're already used to that. But a couple of minutes later two other people looked at us a bit longer and then to our great surprise said "Hello" and "Good Evening" in Finnish! We were quite amazed and I kept on thinking over, what we were talking about;) There are so few finnish people here, that we can normally talk whatever we want;) I wanted to talk more to them, but they just walked on and merely looked at us once again a bit longer. I bet they were tourists! Or just stereotypical finnish people;) I keep on forgetting that I'm NOT a typical finn.  Today...  My father just called me to wish me a happy nameday (today is Ilona's day). I was so happy, that he called and already early in the morning I got an sms from him. But he had also bad news. He has a deadly disease since 1996 and it has been ok and could've been taken care of with medicines. For the last 20 months he had no medication at all. But now it's gone worse (the helper cells are getting weaker and fewer) and he needs an injection and a heap of pills. Shit. I'm so worried about him and here I am, not being able to visit him easily. I just have to hope and pray. THIS is one of the worse things in living abroad...   So, I guess this is not gonna be a good day after all.  I listen to Muse and try to pep myself up, I'd still have to work today. Although all I really hope is that the hours would pass by and my honey would come home and take me into his arms again. At the moment it feels like the best thing in this world...when he holds me and strokes my hair and gives little kisses. In that moment I feel I'm really safe. The warmth he gives is amazing.  Come away with me in the night Come away with me And I will write you a song  Come away with me on a bus Come away with me where they can't tempt us With their lies  I want to walk with you On a cloudy day In fields where the yellow grass grows knee kigh So won't you try to come  Come away with me and we'll kiss On a mountain top Come away with me And I'll never stop loving you  And I want to wake up with the rain Falling on a tin roof While I'm safe there in your arms So all I ask is for you To come away with me in the night Come away with me (Norah Jones)  ---------------------  It's all gonna be alright. 
     
    
</post>
<date>07,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Mood: Rootless Music: Pain of Salvation - Pilgrim  9. Pilgrim  [Music: D.Gildenlow]  'In fire, we can see our past and our coming. For, as with us and our time, these flames are solely born through the complete and utterly consumption of its surroundings. By which, the fire itself is also condemned to be destroyed. Demanding, beautiful and very lethal, it lives itself to death...'   The higher I am reaching - the closer to the sun  The more I learn the less I know for sure  For each machine I'm leaving I find a bigger one  For each step I turn wiser than before  But it's burning me...  Pilgrim, where are you going?  Pilgrim, your roads turning bleak  Pilgrim, true to your knowing  But what will you pay for the Grail that you seek?   Though these roads seem endless  And life seems out of reach  The roads I left were better off unwalked  If I had just been stronger  If I had dared to see  Maybe I would not have had to go this far  But still I won't give in...   Pilgrim, where are you going?  Pilgrim, your roads turning bleak  Pilgrim, This quest is your calling  ...the curtains are falling...  Pilgrim, where are you going?  And who sets the price on the answers you seek?    Today I'm once again the pilgrim who desires to go on, to leave the past behind, to seek for something new and to start again. People say, that's the easy way to live life without taking any responsibility but they just don't know. It's not easy, it's far from easy. You carry the same problems with you that other people can store in their homes, wherever they live. You meet new people, people you can't trust because you don't know them. You live in places you can't trust and which are not your home, you can't let your stuff, the clothes, the cd's, the books whatsoever find their places because you know that you soon have to go again. You grow sick and tired of speaking the foreign language, you get really TIRED of opening your mouth and of trying to find the right words or another way to tell what you want to say, when the words are missing. You get sick and tired of finding the convenient food stuff from the stores... I sometimes want to become simply mute and leave other people guessing what I wanted to say after all. If they even bother. See, the problem with this thing is that, when you don't stay long in one place, you don't make close friends that easily. So basicly the people usually don't give a shit what you're doing or saying. And that's one thing that has kept me going, too. I love being anonymous. But you get very lonely, too. For the very same reason.  Here in Switzerland I'm very lucky. I have my boyfriend, who doesn't let me get mute, if I can't say something immediately using the right words. I have something to hold on and that's very scary, too. I'm living in his apartment at the moment, but it's not my home. Actually, I don't have a home at all. I've rented my flat in Finland till 31.5.04. Ohjeeeee... Rico and I are the kind of people who need their own time, who need to be alone. He more than me. Therefore I'm afraid that if I stay too long here, somethign breaks and can't be mended any more. And I'm afraid that I fall too dearly in love with him and suffer my guts out, if we break up. I don't really wanna think about that but then again I can't help it, these thoughts just enter my mind from time to time. I'm also afraid that I hold on too much to him and that he starts feeling himself cornered and that I end up feeling so, too. Then again, everything's going well at the moment, I'm so happy that I've met him and can be with him, and I hope he feels the same way, too. We share same interests, have a lot to talk about in the linguistic frames given (and german keeps on getting more and more versatile!) and the sex is great. And we both love good food and drinks;)  It's a baffling situation. By going away from Finland I'm searching for happiness that suits me and my lifestyle. I don't want to go away for the rest of my life, since I dream of a family and la vie bourgeoise;) I'm the kind of person who gets restless if not given the opportunity to get away from time to time. It doesn't have to be a trip around the world. Going to Zurich or Luzern or so is enough.   I don't think my mother ever could think of her daughter becoming a "pilgrim" like me... My brother is married and has settled down, has 3 children and a beautiful house in Finland. And he's only 8 years older than I. Oh well, I know I'm gonna get alright. I'm intelligent, social and courageous. This is my lifestyle and despite all the cons I'm happy living my life. Man, I'm so RICH although I don't have much money.  So finally my journey ends  And through this wound my soul can mend  Guilt is my blood  I'm being drained  This is my home, I will stay...  ...inside!  There's always someone inside  Fighting to get outside  The "knowing-right-from-wrong side"  Our home is inside!   I've travelled the world around  In search for some Grail of mine  How could I be so blind?  It was always here:inside  I have only some weeks to give  But at last... I live  [D. Gildenlow]  Life's just a line of situations  A matter of occasions  And mystic correlations  The work of a Machine!  [D.Gildenlow/Hallgren] [Hallgren]  Here in a world split to nations  We fail to see the relations  Between the Wheel and the Machine  And of the scars we're leaving...  ...inside!  I swear there's someone inside  Fighting to get outside  Just give it all an hour  By the Concrete Lake!  [D.Gildenlow/Hallgren]  Take care and love your life and the people in it! I already feel better.  --------------  The time is completely wrong. The time here in Switzerland is 2:34 pm at the moment.
     
    
</post>
<date>06,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Mood: perky  Music: Muse - Bliss   Well, it seems I finally managed to get my own e-diary. It's just a compensation because of the lack of my own homepage *grins*. I just like to do things the easy way, you know.   I'm currently staying in Switzerland and I must say, that it looks like I'm gonna stay here longer... I just love this country and I just love my swiss boyfriend and I could actually study and live and learn and work here! So we'll see, what happens. I had a summer job in the mountains in a hotel and now I'm looking around to find a job here until I get a place in the Zürich university or so.   I'm writing in English, because I thought it would be most convenient for all the people I know. I wanted to write either in Finnish or German, but since I have a lot of international friends, who don't understand Finnish and/or German, I picked up English. And as a former English major student I'm sorry for all the mistakes I make due to my exposure to the german language... The german influences can surely be seen in my words and syntax etc. But hey, my writing isn't that bad, you should here me speaking English these days!;)   Today I'm struggling with my translation dingsda...the word I'm looking for is...Übersetzungsarbeit, verdammt nochmal...translation work/job/something like that. I'm translating an error description list of a machine tool, german-finnish. Blaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa. Highly interesting. But at least I'm getting paid.   It's a very beautiful day here. The sun is shining and the air is fresh. My only problem is that I don't have any warm clothes with me... I wasn't planning to stay this long here! Would it help if I wore 5 summer dresses at the same time?;)   So it's 4:59 pm and I haven't done anything reasonable today. I should get something done before my man Rico comes home from work (he's an engineer), cause I know that after that I won't get anything done. We'll probably cook something and then watch The Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy on dvd. It's just so easy to be with him and do things, our interests are so similar. And we have a lot to talk about, too. Well, I'm very sorry that not every woman can have a man like Rico! ;D   Ok, I'm just gonna go back and show the error dingsda who's the boss! And I'm gonna stop thinking that it's still 24 days left to Iron Maiden concert in Zürich and 44 to Muse here in Wettingen... ;) Besides, I'm already making my IRC friends crazy by asking "how do you say this in English?" ;)   Have a nice day, till later!   ----------------------------------   Whoopee...  It's 5:28 and I still haven't done anything remarkable today. I've been struggling with words like "Wechselvorgang", "Kontrollschalter" and "Wechselgreif-Element". It seems that my dictionaries don't know a shit... Well, Rico is coming home soon. Haha, I told him in IRC that he's not FORCED to use the spacebar after a sentence (he keeps on pressing that after a sentence, before the full stop etc.) and that's what he said:  - ja wart du nur... komme jetzt nach hause und dann geb ich dir spacebar !!!!  Haha;) In english that would be: yeah, you just wait...i'm coming home now and then I'll give you some spacebar!!! :D  I'm hungry.
     
    
</post>
<date>27,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      12:20 pm  Mood: Calm Music: Patricia Kaas - Fatiguee d'attendre  It seems like my e-diary does have some readers, whom my writings touch... =) But I'd appreciate to get the comments myself and not from other people. Hiding behind someone's back is so pathetic.  I went to the library yesterday and borrowed some books and cds and one dvd (The Others). I was so happy to be in a library again, although the library here in Wettingen is very small. I love the atmosphere and the heaps of books. I also managed to find 'The God of Small Things' from Arundhati Roy. I read it when I was in Germany and was completely fascinated by the story, the book's world and atmosphere... Unfortunately it wasn't my own book, I had borrowed it from my friend Radek and I had to give it back to him. Now I borrowed it once again and I think I'll end up buying it. The language in the book is so poetic and mystical that it leaves a lot of responsibility for the reader in making interpretations. One of my favorite passages is this:  As she leaned against the door in the darkness, she felt her dream, her afternoon-mare move inside her like a rib of water rising from the ocean, gathering into a wave. The cheerful one-armed man with salty skin and a shoulder that ended abruptly like a cliff emerged from the shadows of the jagged beach and walked towards her.                   Who was he?                   Who could he have been?                   The God of Loss                   The God of Small Things                   The God of Goose Pumps and Sudden Smiles.                   He could do only one thing at a time.                    If he touched her, he couldn't talk to her, if he loved her he couldn't leave, if he spoke he couldn't listen, if he fought he couldn't win.                   Ammu longed for him. Ached for him with the whole of her biology.                   She returned to the dinner table. (p. 330)  Then I borrowed a book called 'How to Read a Film'. It gives the basics in understanding films more deeply with the help of different theories etc. It's in German, but it's alright. If my German is already so good that I can study in German, I can surely read that book, too.  1:36 pm  np: Kula Shaker - Knight on the Town  I borrowed 'Supposed Former Infatuation Junkie' from Alanis Morissette and couldn't listen to it. It was so full of shit. Wannabe-artistic whining. Mrs. Morissette seems to want to be a fucking emancipated cow, who shouts "fuck all men, nobody's worth me!" on the barricades of feminism... Words are not enough to describe the horror of that album. So, Kula Shaker instead. This is ok, but not really my thing, either. Psychedelic sounds and party feeling. Ok, nice and so on, but nothing worth listening with concentration.  4:27 pm  Hui. Went shopping with Rico's mum and came home a while ago. Now I'm gonna go cooking and baking and stuff. Honey's coming home soon.  
     
    
</post>
<date>09,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      1:27 pm  Mood: More Coffee Music: Dream Theater - As I Am  To those who understand  I extend my hand  To the doubtful I demand  Take me as I am  Not under your command I know where I stand  I won't change to fit your plan  Take me as I am  The new Metallica sounds like Dream Theater...oops...I mean the new Dream Theater sounds like Metallica ;) At least "As I Am". Although this new "metallicastic" Dream Theater is better than Metallica. It's hard to find a band that plays as well as DT's guys.  I gotta buy the album and listen to it carefully. So far I have only three songs downloaded from the new album "Train of Thoughts".  Ok, I changed to "A Change of Seasons" from DT. It's a masterpiece, really. It's one "song", divided into 7 parts, total playing time is 23:06. A Change of Seasons (ACoS) was written 1989 along with "Metropolis - Pt. 1" (probably the best DT song) and it was supposed to be published already 1992 on "Images and Words"-album. For some reason they didn't. Maybe it would've just been too much, since "Metropolis - Pt. 1" was already on the album... Two long masterpieces on one album is not necessarily a good idea. So finally they recorded ACoS as an independent work. Since it's "only" 23:06 minutes long, they filled the rest of the album with a live recording from Ronnie Scott's Jazz Club in London (1995), where they played covers e.g. from Pink Floyd, Deep Purple and Queen. The rest of the album is not that good, at least IMO, but worth listening. They have chosen the songs from the bands they grew up listening to. A great idea, though =) They wanted to have some fun and relax and that can be heard from the tracks.  Yesterday there was a moon eclipse... It was soooo beautiful and strange. The sky was clear and we could see stars really well, too. Although the light pollution disturbs us both. It's just not dark enough, the city lights illuminate the sky so effectively. The eclipse was whole at around 2 am and at least I had trouble staying awake so long... But I'll tell you, making love helps in that sense! =) Although right after making love I just wanted to stay in bed, laying next to my honey. But, we have a lot of time to stay in bed and cuddle, the rest of our lives (or at least till we get children, if we ever get any and that far :D) if all goes this well ;)  I am so happy with my man. I never thought that I'd have my 25th birthday in Switzerland and that I'd celebrate it with the man I love and who loves me. At the moment "ich liebe dich" ("i love you" in German) are the most beautiful and comforting words in this world. I'm safe with him, I can be myself with him, independent and not alone. I've noticed that with him, for the first time I can be what I am. I can be silly, sad, funny, serious, furious... Everything I need to be and I don't feel myself awkward and he doesn't make me feel stupid and he doesn't want me to be something I have to pretend to be. Amazing, how my last two longer relationships seem to have been so much faking and make believe. I made myself believe that this is what I REALLY want. Now with Rico I've been thinking a lot of it and I have been so relieved every time I've noticed that this is not make believe, this is for real. I think that our relationship has the opportunity to live long. I think we could even grow old together. So far all the important things JUST MATCH! =) I am so lucky.  So, I gotta go and call my father. Today's the Father's Day in Finland and I want to say hello to my father...  *edit*  Wow, I just realised that today I've been exactly 6 months in Switzerland and we've been together with Rico that "long", too... Who would've guessed in May that in November we'd be living together! Especially when I had my doubts about this relationship at one point, as one ridiculous femalebeing decided to declare her love for Rico to ME. I talked about it with my friends and had a lot of support from them. They also found the behaviour of this person stupid, selfish and ridiculous. I mean, why tell this thing to me? Fortunately everything turned out just fine and Rico didn't let me down. After all, he said could never even imagine starting a relationship with her. They have never even met in real life! Now I can only laugh about it, it was all so pathetic and ridiculous and I KNOW that Rico loves me. Well, there are a lot of sad creatures in this world and they also deserve to live ;)   Well, time to go and clean up the apartment! Till later!  
     
    
</post>
<date>03,November,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      12:21 pm  Mood: Monday Music: Tehosekoitin - Maailman On Sun (The World Is Yours)  What a weekend! We had lots to do and we also had a lot of fun! Friday was ok, the food was great and the drinks, too. But I was the only one in our group who doesn't speak Schweizerdeutsch (Swiss German) and the other's got carried away with their blabbermouths and I didn't understand much. Well, I now already understand more but for that I need a lot of concentration and I'm not able to say anything, since they're already gone further with their discussion before I could figure out something to say. Well, for once people were able to see me staying quiet for quite a long time ;)  Saturday was great! We took a train to Bern and met our friends Siv and Daniel there. This time the language was not as much a problem, since we talked in English. Siv comes from Norway and her German is not yet that good. Well, it's more like that she doesn't want to speak German although she could. Bern is so beautiful and the sun was shining... We met Siv and Daniel for the first time IRL (so far we've only talked to them in IRC) and found out that we get along really well. We ate lotsa raclette, drank lotsa wine and played games and laughed a lot. I'm so happy that we start to have a common social context here... Rico's friends took me right away to the group and now we have also Siv and Daniel. What I still miss, are my own friends... But in time I'll get some. At least, when I start my studies.   Oh, gotta reboot. Brb.  2:26 pm  On Sunday we did practically nothing. We were just so exhausted and happy to be able to stay in bed till one o'clock and after that lay lazy on the couch. Well, we did visit Rico's mother but that's it.   So, seems like my Ausländerausweis (permission to stay in the country etc.) is waiting for me. Gotta go get it today.  
     
    
</post>
<date>23,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      10:00 PM  Mood: Exhausted Music: Television - Scrubs  Uaahh... Christmas is coming and I've been baking like mad. Today I baked like 5 hours, yesterday a little less. Tomorrow I have to make some Finnish specialities and the day after tomorrow a little bit more. Rico's family is coming to our place on Thursday. After that I can relax ;) I've already been thinking, why I wanna do all this. But I just wanted to do some Finnish things, since I'm not able to go to Finland for Christmas.   I've already had some really bad moments when I've been homesick, but it always goes away. Those moments came, when I got the packages from my parents... I've never been away from Finland on Christmas. And the fact that my parents miss me, too, makes it even worse. On Christmas I am a real family person. I could never go away for Christmas, I mean to live in some hotel somewhere in Spain or whatever. Christmas is not the time for partying or getting pissed, it's time for calming down and so on. On New Year's Eve it's time to party etc. But I guess I'll just leave that, too. I'm getting old, I guess. I don't know, how it's gonna be tomorrow and on Thu but I think I'll be alright. Tomorrow we're gonna go and eat something with our friends Dani and Urs and like I said, on Thu we have Rico's family here. It's always so nice to see Dani and Urs, they're such nice guys.   Rico's mother is an angel, she went shopping with me yesterday, because Rico was ill and she paid at least the half of the things... I don't know, what I'd done without her. Today Rico was healthy again and we could go together to buy some things. I can't wait for Thu evening... Then at last I can relax and enjoy the peace. And do something nice with Rico.  Yeah, everything's like before with Rico. That is, everything's just fine, great I'd say.   So, I'm gonna go and hug that man of mine. 
     
    
</post>
<date>10,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      1:06 pm  Mood: Normal Music: Pain of Salvation - Leaving Entropia  14. Leaving Entropia (Epilogue)  [music  lyrics: daniel gildenlow]  walk with me  and see the world I see  it is our home  it's where we all belong   life is flair  a brittle dress we wear  a fleeting sigh  but though pointless it may seem... live as death were but a dream   you don't have to walk their way  you don't have to watch the show  you don't have to play their game   and you don't have to die to leave entropia   all remains... forgotten smiles in frames  two fleeting lives  cut down to pocket-size   walk with me  and change the world we see  we'll cease to be  just people passing by  home is where we all get by   you don't have to cry for more  you don't have to have it all  you don't have to win a war   if death is but a dream  then don't let me ...fall asleep...  ------  Hmm, what has happened... A lot, I guess. I had my birthday last Thursday and I now am 25 years old. It didn't feel like anything, really. I don't have a crisis, not at least more than I had before I turned 25 ;) I had a nice evening, a couple of friends came to visit us. I had cooked and made a cake and everything was so fine! Seems like I managed to spoil my guests (and of course Rico) with my cookings ;) But I have to say, that I really _can_ cook and bake.  We have decided to have a cat. We don't have it yet, but we'll get it in the following weeks. It kinda feels like getting married, since it's not my cat or Rico's cat, it's Our cat. I can't wait! A cat makes this apartment even more home-like. It'll surely bring warmth to our home.   Well, other commitments we're not planning to make in the near future ;) We've been together for 7 months and that's not much. But I'm so happy for all the time we have ahead of us!  I've also been busy with Christmas cards and stuff... I decided to make most of the cards myself. I took last year a photo, that's good for this purpose. It's not very traditional or typical, but then again, neither am I. I hope people like it. It's just so much work writing over 30 cards and it's not very cheap, either. I wrote a letter for all my relatives, who probably don't know where I am and why and the letter became pretty heavy. Well, next year I won't have that problem, since by that time everyone knows for sure my new homecountry, about my man and all that stuff. I also should still find a couple of presents, for Rico and my brother's family. For me and Rico is the cat the main present and we've agreed not to buy presents. But I have such a great idea and I just have to make it real =)  Ok, now I have to go and finish my christmas card-session so that I can send them today. Furthermore, I gotta go shopping. I got a little birthday and christmas money and I've been spending it generously ;) And then I have to continue looking for a job, it's not as easy as I'd thought it'd be. I'm so frustrated and bored of sitting at home. I mean, that'd be fine, if I could still earn my own money, but no one pays you for staying at home. I really want to be independent with my money. I don't understand the german or swiss women, who stay at home all of their lives and are completely dependent from their husbands. Brr. But, I haven't lost hope yet and so hasn't Rico. He's really supportive.  In any case, till later.  
     
    
</post>
<date>25,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      9:42 AM  Mood: Balanced  Music: Edvard Grieg - Solvejgs Lied, Peer Gynt-Suite Nr.2  I love this classical piece. Very nordic ;) No wonder, since the composer is norwegian. I think I'll listen to some Sibelius after this... Sibelius is very finnish, not only nordic. Amazingly excellent music, I'd say. When a finn listens to Sibelius s/he can really see the forests and the lakes, although s/he'd be a long way from home. And yes, I tend to get a little homesick, when I listen to Sibelius. Ok, I'm gonna listen to this next one, too. It's Pietro Mascagni's Intermezzo from his work Cavalleria Rusticana. Pietro Mascagni (1863-1945) is one of the most important Italian composers of the turn of the 20th century. This piece is really, really beautiful. I'm listening to a collection called "Meditation" which includes some classical master pieces, or parts of the great works. I usually dislike this kind of collections with short excerpts. I like to listen to the complete works so that I can better follow the development and the use of the central themes and can get a better picture of the master work. These excerpts are easy to listen, they represent the pop branch of the classical genre. But all my classical cd's are in Finland and Rico only has these collections.  But! I'm traveling to Finland on 10.2. and will be staying there for a week. I'm gonna fly with Ryanair from Frankfurt-Hahn to Tampere. I'm gonna take the train to Frankfurt and my mom is gonna pick me up in Tampere. Convenient. Although Frankfurt is about a 3-4 hours trip away from here, Tampere is my hometown. Therefore it's not that bad. And most importantly it's cheap. The whole trip will cost about 100 euro, since Rico is so adorably kind and will take two days off from work and pick me up from Frankfurt when I come back. I'm already pretty excited, since I don't know, how it's gonna be... Seeing the familiar places and hearing Finnish all around me can be a heavy experience ;) But it's only a week and then I'll be back home again, with my man and our cats and life can go on again :D Ok, it's great to travel a little again, I need that. And I can get some of my stuff, which I've been missing. Like some clothes, cd's and books. I'm also looking forward to a party and going to the familiar clubs and bars. But we'll see.    Two dear friends of mine are coming here on the weekend before I leave and I can't wait. And what a coincidence! Leena is taking the same flight to Finland with me! If we're lucky, we get to sit next to each other ;) With Ryanair it's not that obvious, since there are no seat numbers given before the flight... But like I said, in return it's cheap.  The cats are doing fine. They are really accurate in waking me up every morning at around eight o'clock... But nothing new, really.  I've been busy arranging an academical career for myself. That means, I'm gonna apply for a place in the university of Zurich for the summer semester ;) I'm gonna get the last certificates from Finland next week and after that it shouldn't be a problem... At least I hope so. If everything goes well, I'm gonna start/go further with my studies, majoring in English and my minors are most likely gonna be journalism and political science or some cultural studies. We'll see. I'm so nervous, but full of hope. I don't know, what I'm gonna do, if I don't get the place... My brain needs challenges again!  Oh, and check out the first version of our cats' homepage (with different kinds of errors and some bad photos ;):   http://www.count-0.com/meow/  Rico made the pages last night and I find the idea really sweet :) The photos are mostly taken by me, except for the Shiva-photos. Only the first two ones are my production. In the mean time we're planning a better site for those adorable creatures :)  So, my love just woke up and his arms are far too inviting for me to sit in front of a computer... Thus, till later!
     
    
</post>
<date>11,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      4:06 PM  Mood: So good! Music: Radio Swiss Jazz  We've had ethno days here. Mostly concerning the food. I've been cooking mostly Thai and Indian food, and a little bit of Italian. Delicious! Today we're going to have canard with noodles and as dessert some banana-chocolate-coconut cheesecake. I used fresh coconut for the cake! It was a show when we were trying to open it :D Well, we did it! With a spike, a little saw and a hammer ;) But it makes a difference and is worth trouble.  Life has been mostly really good. Especially after we finally got rid of one nuisance (that female I told you about before)...for good. It was about time! In summer she's been sending emails like "I wish you were here holding me..." and photos of herself (asking if she looks good enough to be taken home, lol :D). What a no-nice-word-for-that-kind-of-person! But now we've talked it over with Rico and it's ok. And now it's like a new beginning for us and I'm in love again. Or I mean, once again fallen in love ;) My love for Rico never ended, but you know what I mean. I'm pretty sure I wanna spend the rest of my life with Rico ;)   We've had a perfect weekend together... A little bit of shopping, a lot of sleeping, playing with the cats, a lot of good food and enough (not too much) good wine. And own time, too. It's a bit exhausting to be with the same person all the time really tightly. I've been reading and Rico met Dani today; they went to play billiard together.   The cats are adorable! Except when they come before 8 o'clock in the morning beside your bed, meowing and staring at you. You just have to get up ;) But I can't be mad at them, since they are so adorable. Right after they've waked me up and got their food, they come purring and smooching to me. It's a bit like having children ;) But only a little bit, since children don't sleep that much :D They have taken me as their most important slave, since I'm more at home.  Ok, I gotta go. Take care!
     
    
</post>
<date>03,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      3:43 PM  Mood: Tired Music: Nightwish - Stargazers  A grand oasis in the vastness of gloom Child of dew-spangled cobweb, Mother to the Moon Constellations beholders of the 3rd vagrant Theater for the play of life  Tragedienne of heavens Watching the eyes of the night Sailing the virgin oceans A Planetride for Mother and Child  Floating upon the quiet hydrogen lakes In this ambrosial merrry-go-round they will gaze Ephemeral life touched by a billion-year-show Separating the poet from the woe  [Repeat chorus]  Oracle of the Delfian Domine Witness of Adam's frailty Seer of the master prophecy The stellar world her betrothed  Wanderers in cosmic caravan Universal bond - The Starborn  A son in search for the truth Following the pages of Almagest Discovering the origin of dreams Stargazers ride through the ancient realms  [Repeat chorus]   So, I've done it, I bought two Nightwish-CDs... But I really like their music, although it took me some time to start to like them. I do still have some trouble with the lyrics... Especially reading them without laughing ;) But I've always liked their concept and been proud, since they ARE after all from Finland. And they were the first ones to do such a thing, to play epic opera-heavymetal. After that came Within Temptation etc. The singer of the band is a trained opera singer, a soprano. Her voice is really beautiful. The band plays hard melodic heavy metal, with a story on every CD. I once saw them live in Tampere, my hometown, it was probably winter 2000/2001 or something like that. It was ok, since it was a dvd-gig ;) I checked it, the gig was in winter 2000 (December) since the dvd was published 2001. But we spent the whole concert with my buddies in the bar area and played air guitar ;) Well, Nightwish keeps on making music and they're doing well. The singer married a record company chef from Argentina last year and has been studying more singing, for example in Germany.  Hmm, so what's been going on...  Christmas is over and it was ok. On Christmas Eve I had a hard time. I was in stress, homesick etc. I felt horrible and cried a lot and didn't have any trace of Christmas feeling. Thank god Rico was there to comfort me. The next day was much better and we had a great time with Rico's family. After that we've just been relaxing and doing nice things.  We have a family of our own now, too. We got too cats last Tuesday. They are the most gorgeous cats, in my and Rico's opinion of course ;) But they, Minka and Shiva, are really beautiful. Although they have a little overweight, especially Minka. They are about 3 years old and the previous owner hasn't probably looked after what they eat. I mean, they are indoor cats and don't need as much food as cats who go out every day. So, Minka and Shiva are now on a diet. We've been spending the last days just admiring those divine creatures. We have also had a lot of fun with the ladies. Shiva likes to sit in front of the window and look at the birds outside. She makes funny noises and her tail swings like mad. And last night, when we were making love, we suddenly heard a quiet "meow" and looky who there was...Shiva trying to get into the closet ;) Our little peeping tom ;) So we had to get her out of the room and close the door. For a moment she was meowing behind the door and then gave up.   I've been trying to shoot good photos of the ladies, but it's very difficult. I wouldn't want to take merely snapshots of them, since they are so beautiful. But as soon as I manage to take some good photos, we're going to make a site for Shiva and Minka =)  New Year's Eve was peaceful, we went to a concert (Moonspell, Lacuna Coil etc.) and came home pretty early, at about 2 am or so. But was fine, the concert, although we missed Lacuna Coil and saw only Moonspell and Extol. Moonspell was great but Extol was...what should I say...pure shit. A mixture of Evanescence and Linkin Park. I laughed my ass out, as they started playing. As the female singer started to sing, I wanted to say to Rico that all we need now is a rapper and my oh my... Before I managed to say that, he already began :D They played maybe an hour but it felt longer than one hour... I was really suffering. We both found it extremely funny, when the singer announced that "now we're gonna play a really hard song, probably the hardest song we have ever written! you ready for some hard music?!?!" And the song was EXACTLY as lame as the other ones. Fucking idiots.  Today's the last Saturday of Rico's holiday and I'm not that happy about that. On Monday I'm alone again and I have to go on with my job applications. It's so frustrating! I've sent at least 15 applications and received 5 or 6 answers (negative, of course). I mean what's wrong with those people? In Finland one ALWAYS gets an answer, no matter what the result is. But, what I found great, was that a few young people sent an answer. I sent a free application to 3 culture agencies and from 2 of them I was answered. Except for the big boss in reihe13. Fucking idiot. Too arrogant to write a few words? I'm getting desperate with my applications since it seems impossible to get a reasonable job here. Maybe I should just fuck the boss, like some people do. But that's not my style. And I already have the greatest guy to fuck with ;D  We bought the two first LOTR films on dvd and we watched them on Thu. Now we are ready to go to see the last part. Can't wait. We actually wanted to go tonight, but there are no tickets for tonight. Instead of that we're going to go watch Finding Nemo.   Oh, and we have snow! I mean really snow, not just traces of it. It looks amazing ;) The temperature is around -4 and it's kinda sweet. In Finland, in my hometown it's been -24 :D I miss the finnish winter.  But, I gotta go. Till later.
     
    
</post>
<date>22,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      5:39 PM  Mood: Fluffy Music: Sade - Kiss of Life  There must have been an angel by my side Something heavenly led me to you Look at the sky It's the colour of love There must have been an angel by my side Something heavenly came down from above He led me to you He led me to you   A flu is threatening me. I'm not gonna give in! I have so much to do in the next weeks and I can't afford to become ill.  Well, let's get back in time a little...  My holiday in Finland was ok, but I was so glad to get back home again. It was dark and cold and the people weren't very happy. Their facial expressions were really in connection with the weather. They can't help it, though. The weather is what it is and the life has to go on. Furthermore, I didn't sleep too well in other people's houses and I had the feeling of not belonging there any more. I mean the people were like before and with my family I didn't have any problems, but I don't have the social context I used to have and the people were different. I think some of them were jealous or somehow didn't know how to take the fact that I live now here and they are stuck in Finland. My buddies also had some problems with my not being the same party animal any more. I mean I had fun, but had to skip some parties since I got fed up with the old let's-get-pissed-and-look-silly thing. And I was just exhausted. And I was right once again. It was a heavy experience to hear finnish all around me and see the familiar places again. It's just all too small and too familiar. I also missed Rico like hell and he missed me, too. It was so odd to sleep alone, without him there beside me... But he had a good time with the cats, although he says that the cats missed me, too ;)  So. Finally after a week came the day and I could travel back home again. The flight was 25 minutes early in Frankfurt-Hahn and I had to wait for Rico a while. But when he came, I couldn't help the tears. It was so good to be in his arms again, I was safe again. I mean I really had the feeling of being home and safe again, when I hugged and kissed him. But driving through Schwarzwald wasn't too hilarious. Trucks, trucks and trucks on the highway. It was dark and the highway was so boring! Then, when we finally reached the border and got through the id check, I really felt like home. I was suddenly awake (it was about 5 o'clock in the morning) and happy. We came home and the cats were waiting here... Excited, unable to stay in one place for more than a few seconds. Our bed was so warm and lovely and I slept so good.  Now I've been enjoying my days here at home again and Minka has been my lapcat ;) I love it, how here everything's familiar, but in a different way than in Finland.   Nevertheless, we're planning our common trip to Finland in May. Most likely we're gonna stay 2 weeks (17. - 31.5.) but it can also be, that we're going only for a week. Depending on whether I want to stay there that long ;) And in any case we're gonna travel to Finland once again in August, since Laura (my dear friend) is getting married 14. August. In May we have to pack my things and then the removal company is going to bring the stuff here. So, after that my life is also concretely here.   So, I now have heap loads of paper work to do, since I got the place in the university of Zurich. I'm so glad :) I have to do a german test but it's gonna be fine, I'm sure. I'll just read some german grammar to memorize things (maybe I'll finally finish the book we were suppose to read in Finland on one of the german grammar courses at the university, lol... I mean I had it as my minor, but never really put awfully lot of effort on it, cause I survived with my skills) and read some news papers like Die Zeit and so on. I have to fill out forms and make phone calls to Finland in order to get financial support from the Finnish state. I have to fill out some forms for the Uni Zurich, too. But at least I can study again! What amazes me, is the lack of information for foreign students about how it's going to go on from now on. I would want to know how to plan my schedule and how to choose courses and basic things like where to eat and how to pay the meals! In Finland all foreign students have personal tutors (1 tutor/3-4 exchange students) and the information flow is really amazing! If this is not getting any better, I'm gonna have to give some feedback to those who are responsible for international affairs. I think I'm gonna be a nuisance ;) But I want to know about things and I want information! If that makes me a nuisance, I don't care!  Hmm... What else... Yeah, my friends were here. It was so good to see them again and have a good chat with them. It was so wonderful to talk to real friends (Rico is of course my real friend, too, but I need my female friends, too) and spend some time with them. Although two days went so fast... We went to Zurich to do some shopping and in the evening we just laid on the sofa, drank some wine and other spirits and have good conversations. The feeling was so warm and caring!  Hmm, what else. Nothing special, I guess. We have a lot of love in our lives, I and Rico. So it can't be that bad, right? ;) We've had our difficulties and we're gonna have some more of them, but that's only normal. So far we've got over them and if our love stays this strong, we're gonna get over the future problems, too.  So, I'll go and open my sweet grammar book ;) Till later!    
     
    
</post>
<date>27,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      8:47 AM  Mood: Sore Music: Rasmus - F-F-F-Falling  I've had headaches for 3 days now and I'm still a bit sore and afraid of the next wave...  This song brings me memories from the summer of 2001 and my trip to Lappeenranta (http://www.lappeenranta.fi/) a few weeks before I traveled to Germany for a year. We had so much fun in the sun and in the evening with great people... It surely was a legendary trip, we were all single and so free. Now I'm not single any more (thank god!), my friends from Lappeenranta are even getting married and we're all much calmer now, but there are some songs that remind us of our wild past ;) And photos of course, too. Btw, added some new photos in the IRC gallery (www. irc-galleria.net).   It just so amazing how the time flies... I mean, year 2001 was about 3 years ago and in that time has happened so much. We've grown up a little once again, learnt something new etc. There are, however, also things that haven't changed, things that already were there 3 years ago and even before. Like being analytic, critical and so on. There are different forms of being "adult", I guess. I'm not quite sure if there's one right way to be adult, although a lot of people like to measure their being mature with parametres they have set for themselves. Funny. The older I'm getting, the less I know for sure. Even Sokrates said that the only thing he knows for sure is that he doesn't know anything. He understood how little he actually knows and that made him probably the wisest philosopher there is (or was;).   My studies begin on Monday. I'm excited, can't wait. My brain has been waiting for this for so long ;) And I meet new people, too! This means the beginning of studies that last for 6 years and after that I'll goddamn wise, haha. After that I'll be Phil. lic. i.e. MA (I guess) but I won't have a profession... So I'll have to think about that and try to find a job where I'd get practical experience, university IS, after all, pure theory.  I have a purring cat on my laps and I have only one hand free for writing ;) So I think I'll go and concentrate on the sweet Minka.
     
    
</post>
<date>05,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      12:57 PM  Mood: So happy Music: Sonata Arctica - Shy  Lol, i'm listening to this song and I'm laughing my ass out ;) I mean, this is a very sweet song indeed, but the lyrics are so unintentionally funny. Well, the songwriter wrote this song when he was 13 and somehow in love with someone he couldn't reach. Now he's the singer of a melodic heavy band (Sonata Arctica) and they're very popular, particularly in Middle Europe and Far East. His english hasn't got much better though ;) I recommend reading the lyrics of this band, I think you might have some fun with them unless you already know them. I personally don't like this band too much, they are pretty horrible live. For example the drummer is too often a couple of beats too late ;)   I should be cleaning up the apartment, preparing myself for the german test and washing the windows. Instead I've been lazy for the whole morning. But I have an excuse! Minka's been so sweet the whole morning and looking for tenderness...of course I had to give her tenderness! She's spent something like a couple of hours on my laps and also slept on my lap for 30 minutes or so. Now my left arm is almost numb ;) She's not the lightest cat in the world, you know.  It looks like we're gonna have to cancel our trip to Finland for financial reasons. It's a real pity, since everybody's really looking forward to meeting Rico and seeing me again. That means I'll get my stuff then. Shit... I'd really need my dictionaries and all... But in August we're certainly going to travel to Finland and spend a couple of weeks there. I think we'll meet up with Serge and Satu (a friend of Rico's and his girlfriend) in Finland and I think that'll be fun. See, Satu is half finnish and she wants (unlike me) to spend some time in Finland every year. Or has to, I'm not certain. She has to do regularly a finnish test and that's being held in Finland.  Relationship News? Not really, we're still disgustingly happy :) We've talked about the future and it looks rosy for us. But no more about that :)  Ok, I can't postpone my to-dos any longer... I really gotta go. A couple of friends (Siv and Daniel from Bern) are coming to meet us tomorrow and I want this apartment to shine when they come! ;D  Oh, and I'm planning to start a finnish blog since I also have a lot to say to my finnish friends and that happens best of course in Finnish. I also write poems in Finnish and need a place in the internet for those.
     
    
</post>
<date>11,April,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      3:33 PM  Mood: Lazy Music: Dream Theater - Hollow Years  I don't seem to be a very active blogger. Oh well, what the hell. I have a life to live and don't have that much time for being online and going on about my life here ;)   I have studied for a couple of weeks now and it's been good. I have 7 hours on latin per week and that's a LOT of work. But interesting at the same time. Yet, can't wait to get rid of it ;) I have only 3 courses of english and that bothers me a little. I attend the courses in literature and old english. The third course, phonetics and phonology, I try to do independently, I'm already excited what it'll become ;) Phonetics and phonology are interesting, but... We'll see. If I'm lucky I get the literature courses marked down without doing the course work. I namely have already done 4 literature courses in Finland and they also have 4 lit. courses here. I, however, plan to participate on the tuition since it's good preparation for the Zwischenprüfung (intermediate exam, says the dictionary) which will be in two years. But not having to take the literature courses would be so great, cause I could begin with my minors earlier. So maybe I could get my studies done in about 5 years instead of 6.  I've also, of course, met some new people. I really enjoy my university life. And a university like the one in Zurich is just full of traditions and history... The main building alone is mighty.   Things at home are just disgustingly good. The cats are swell and the diet seems to work, at least Minka seems to have lost weight. She's now much more activ, too. They are enjoying the spring days on the balcony and chase the poor bees that are still a bit frozen and not that alert.  With Rico... I'll tell if something new happens ;D On Friday we had our 11-months-day and I actually didn't think about it till Rico came to wake me up and asked where the coffee is :D He wanted to make me espresso, but he didn't find the coffee. So sweet :) He then mentioned that it's really 11 months since we started the relationship... We had Moscato d'asti (a type of prosecco) and different kinds of cheeses and fresh buns for breakfast. The sun was shining and it was just so perfect. In the evening I made a delicious pasta sauce from cream, herbs and smoked salmon. We ate good and talked for hours in the candle light. All the free days we've now had together have been perfect. Being together, doing things, talking, watching movies, eating good food and drinking good wine with the food. We're so in love. The best place in this world is beside Rico. I feel safe and I still have my own life, I'm not too bound to him and I don't live for him only. I mean, I'd die for him, but not give away my life while I'm still alive. You know what I mean.  It's amazing how fast time goes on. In a month it's my and our first anniversary so to say. By then I've spent a year here and we've been that long together. Wow.  But, I gotta go. We're gonna have dinner at Rico's mother. Can't wait :) Happy Easter, every one! 
     
    
</post>
<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      mood: blah music: humming of the computer, rumbling of the washing machine  I haven't done much today and I'm afraid I'm gonna slip into the same apathy concerning my studies as I did in Finland. NO, I won't let that happen! It's just so difficult for me to study in the day time, when there are so many other things to do. In the evening it'd be better, but then Rico is here. He doesn't disturb me but I keep on getting disturbed by him. His presence is enough to keep me from reading.  I missed my friends like hell yesterday. I talked long to Leena, one of my best friends, in MSN Messenger, but that only made my home sickness worse ;) Yesterday was also otherwise such a stupid day again...  Actually, what the fuck am I whining about my doing nothing here instead of DOING something? I'm sometimes such a sad creature ;)
     
    
</post>
<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      1:20 PM  Mood: Asleep Music: Symphony X - Inferno (Unleash the Fire)  Yaaawwwnnn... Woke up about an hour ago and I'm still asleep. Decided to play some heroic heavy metal to really wake up. I don't understand how I managed to sleep this long, the cats didn't bother me, cause Rico gave them food and then came back to bed. I had some cottage cheese and now I'm chewing sugarless blackcurrant candies (I hope this time I'm able to control this, since last time I got diarrhoea from the candies :D), wonderful. I'm looking for some coffee, do I have to make my darn coffee myself? :o Normally Rico makes coffee for me on weekends, so sweet is he :)  I had a really shitty start for a day yesterday... I got mail from the company I'd sent a job application to and they said that I'd be most welcome to the information/interview meeting, if I were Swiss citizen or had a proper residence permit (type C). Well, I'm a Finnish citizen and have a type B residence permit. The reason was that they find it too much financial and temporal trouble to get me a work permit from the kanton I'm living in. Fuck them, I say. Well, I have a couple of other applications I sent, we'll see, if they also are such rotten nationalist firms ;) I was so frustrated and disappointed and cried at for an hour or so. I know people who live here and are not even looking for a job and I get nothing although I've sent about 20 applications. Well, I haven't tried McDonald's or Burger King yet :&gt;   But then I went to meet the literature teacher at the university and it was good. She is such a good teacher and knows what she's speaking of, although she's young. I really like her. Then I came home and it became even better. Rico had wanted to buy me some roses, but he doesnt' like cut flowers since they die so fast. He had then bought me a rose tree! :) A little (ca. 50cm tall), sweet, beautiful rose tree with yellow blooms :) He had also cleaned up the kitchen (I had planned to do that when I come home, since I was reading the whole day)... I LOVE HIM, LOVE HIM, LOVE HIM!   So, we're driving to the Kraftwerk concert to Bern today and before that I'd like to do a couple of things, like re-plant the tomatoes etc. That means, a dieu!
     
    
</post>
<date>10,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      5:20 PM  Mood: Awake Music: Eva Dahlgren - Ängel i Mitt Rum  So, yesterday was our Jahrestag, 1st "Anniversary". That means we've now been a year together with Rico and I've been living in Switzerland that long. He had to work on the weekend on Fri and Sat evenings and I stayed lazy at home. On Sunday we spent some good time together and went then to eat to my mother-in-law-candidate ;) The food was soooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo delicious, I mean really, really good! She had made roastbeef with different kinds of side dishes. She also had managed to find an excellent red wine which just made the dinner even better. Rico's sister with her boyfriend was there, too. It was such a nice evening, we talked a lot and had a lot of fun. I really feel like I'm part of the family and that makes me so happy. Rico's mom is gonna be the best mother-in-law :) Oh, we're not getting married in the near future or anything, but it seems like it's gonna happen inevitably, some day ;) At the moment we're not engaged, but going to that direction.  Today's been a stupid day. I woke up 6:30 AM and thought that I'd start with studying very early. Yeah right. I just surfed the internet, looked for some Old Norse/Old English links for my presentation and then I chatted a little and played a little with the cats, drank coffee, read a little of the book "An Introduction to Old and Middle English" and went to sleep. I slept an hour and woke up about 30 min. ago. So now I'm awake and ready to study more and my honey is coming home ;( See, this is the problem with studying. Rico goes to work and leaves the work there. I go to the lectures and take the work home, since I don't wanna hang around at the university all evening. Sometimes, though, I think it'd be better to do as much of the exercises and reading at the university and then spend time with my family at home. I should just try that. Like go to "work" and come home from "work". Make a plan, a schedule, a framework. Great idea! I could drive to Zurich with Rico when he, too, goes to work and then come home with him. My lectures are in the middle of the day, so I'd have some time after that for working...   I still have no news considering our relationship ;) Everything's going fine. The cats are also fine. Well, ok, Shiva had a little accident on Thursday... She jumped on a hot cooker and burned her paw. Not bad, but enough to make her hiss, growl, hide and eventually groan with pain under the bed. It really did hurt to hear that... I managed to entice Shiva out of her hiding place with a piece of sausage and Rico took her in his arms. We went to the bathroom and held her paw under running, cold water. Well, she didn't hide again and didn't groan whatsoever so I guess it really helped. She was somewhat calmer in the evening and was careful with the burnt paw but the next day already completely normal. She, however, didn't jump again on the stove until today. It seems like the skin on one toe or sole or whatever it's called is a little broken and still healing and that makes Shiva sometimes a bit cautious with it. But it's gonna be just fine. Well, she really is the "jackass" in our family ;) Considering that she already fell down from the balcony and burned her paw... And both incidents happened merely out of curiosity.  The cats have also lost weight, they both almost a kilo! The difference by Minka is tremendous, she is so much more active and mobile. We are so happy that the diet works!  So... Gotta go cooking.
     
    
</post>
<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So umm... We're getting engaged with Rico in August. YAAAAAAAAAAAAHOOOOOOOOOOOOOOO!!! Though it does still feel a little unreal. I think it'll feel unreal till we have the rings and all. In any case our parents know about this and reactions have been delighted. My mom was, however, surprisingly lame about that. Somehow disappointed "oh, you're getting engaged..." Maybe she still thinks I'm going back to Finland to live with her. Brrr. Only the idea of it makes me shiver ;)  But this is just wonderful. We're going to get married maybe 2006, maybe later. We'll see about that later :)  I almost don't believe this is happening to me. This is almost too good to be true!
     
    
</post>
<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So folks, from now on I have titled entries. Great, huh?  I already wrote heaps in Finnish, now I'm tired of this blogging shit again but still something draws me to writing also in English. Oh maaaaaaan.  I also decided NOT to go to IRC but lookylooky, there I am.   Erm, what then... Yeah. I'm gone. Read some Finnish. If you can't, tough. Just ask me, how I'm doing and I'll tell you what you want to know.
     
    
</post>
<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      mood: lazy music: Carmen Fenk - I Love You  I have a family! I really DO have a family! I mean, other than my biological one.  Last night we went to have a dinner at Cindy's (Rico's sister and her boyfriend). Present were: Ilona, Rico, Cindy, Gilbert, Jacqueline (Rico's mom), Gilbert (Gilbert's grandpa), Gilbert's granny and Gilbert's brother Ives.  (It smells like shit, I think I have to go and clean up the cat toilet. Stay tuned, folks.)  So, back. How can one cat produce that much shit? It's amazing.  Yeah, we went to have a dinner at Cindy's (Rico's sister and her boyfriend). ... Yeah. The evening was hilarious! Gilbert is half Swiss, half Spanish. He is lively and sometimes loud. Well, his grandparents are completely Spanish and they are really laidback and nice people :) We others are also not exactly silent or calm... There were really no silent moments. I just loved it :) The feeling there was so warm and comfortable and the food (pasta with various sauces) was Delicious! I really, really felt like a part of the family. Even the grandparents, who met me yesterday for the first time (I think Rico either hasn't met them before...), talked about one family. Like "it's so wonderful to have the family around the same table" etc. During the evening I realised, I'd missed that kinda thing so bad. In Finland we have never had that kind of evening for years now. And when we still did get together for Xmas or so, it wasn't as warmhearted as last evening... A lot because of my mom. Well, I'm not gonna get into this more. I just never had something like last evening and that's why I'm so very happy about it. Can't wait till Thu. Then the whole family is gonna get together again, this time at Rico's mom's.  Otherwise the weekend has been really lazy. We've mostly been sleeping ;) Yesterday, after we'd come home from shopping, I fell asleep with Minka on our most wonderful couch (La Ola by Bretz Brothers) designed for cuddling, naps and generic laziness (http://irc-galleria.net/view.php?nick=sassy_). It was just wonderful! It did so good for me since the day began a bit cranky for me.  Well, being lazy was splendid indeed, but I can't help the bad conscience of not studying at least a bit every day... Well, in about 5 years it's gonna be over and after that I can have bad conscience about other things, haha.   I can't believe I'm tipsy after 3 beers (à 0.33 l).  Me and Rico, we're just fine. We talked yesterday about rings and stuff and last week I think it was Thu he said that he has it all in one woman (meaning me, I HOPE!!!!:D): a friend, a lover and a wife. No dates, no specific plans but now I dare to talk about it in public... We've talked about these things before but I'm careful with these things. I don't want to get hurt again... Now I know, that I won't get hurt with Rico. He's the man for me, he's the love of my life. Well, I think I'm gonna get hurt, since no normal relationship is without problems, but I believe my heart won't be slaughtered again. It took so long to heal the wounds after the last relationship and it still hurts sometimes and it has also made me uncertain and careful. If this thing with Rico goes wrong, I think I'll then rather stay on my own. But, I don't want to think about that option. In fact, it's not even an option for me. Not now. He's my friend, my lover and my husband-to-be. Husband... It's a big word, a good word. It's almost overwhelming.  Ok, I'm gonna go to bed. My SO is already there. It's a warm feeling, to think about pressing my head against his warm chest, feeling his caring arms around me...to fall asleep in his arms. I'll leave it to this image... 
     
    
</post>
<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      mood: peaceful music: Sarah Vaughan - Linger a While  I've had headaches again this week. My back, my neck and the weather... On Thursday evening, as we were lying in bed with Rico, under the same blanket, I said that my head hurts. I didn't take anything chemical, I thought, maybe I could sleep it away. Well, we have this habit of talking about things before we fall asleep (or end up making love ;) and this we did also on Thu. We talked, touched, gave kisses, Rico stroke my hair and my whole skin and after a while he asked, if I still have headaches. They were gone. What I had, instead, was a wonderfully secure feeling, I was comfortable and surrounded by love.   I know I'm marrying the right man.  I took some photos of our beautiful cats yesterday, have a look:   urlLink http://irc-galleria.net/view.php?nick=sassy_=2853984=true    urlLink http://irc-galleria.net/view.php?nick=sassy_=2853976=true   I'm yearning for finnish poetry. Gotta bring my books here in August.   It's raining, I wanna meet my man in our living room.
     
    
</post>
<date>26,toukokuu,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Pitää kyllä myöntää, että tänä aamuna on eniten naurattanut paitsi omat jutut, niin tuo italiankielinen nimi korvatulpille ;) Tuohan voisi olla vaikka jonkun nimi :D "Tappi Auricolari, hyvää päivää"   Shiva tuli herättämään puoli seitsemältä äänekkäästi moukuen "mouuuuu, mauuuuuu, ouuuuuu, mouuuuuUUU". Mietin, että mitvit, Rico antoi jo ruokaa. No, ajattelin, että nousenpa katsomaan, jos vaikka kaktukset olisivat taas lattialla tms. Shiva kuitenkin johdatti mut toiseen kylppäriin, jossa on hiekkalaatikko, hyppäsi lavuaarin reunalle ja halusi juoda hanasta vettä! Totesin myös, että jaaha, kakalla ollaan käyty (Shiva se oli ollut. Usko tai älä, mutta kissojen kakkaamis- ja pissaamistavat oppii tunnistamaan. Jep, järkyttävää ;) ja oli vissiin syytä tyhjentää se hiekkalaatikko. Helkkarin hienohelma. Tosin, en mäkään suostu menemään pöntölle, jossa on edelliset jätökset vielä lillumassa ;) No, tulipahan herättyä ajoissa.  Nyt tässä sitten olisi vielä ihan hyvää aikaa tehdä latinan läksyjä -jos niistä nyt mitään tulee- ennen kuin pitää lähteä luennolle. Masentaa vaan vähän jo etukäteen mennä sinne, kun en tiedä, tajuanko taas yhtään mitään. Eilen käännettiin tekstiä taas ja mä en ymmärtänyt edes sitä käännöstä kunnolla. Mietin, että olenko hypännyt liian suuriin saappaisiin... Mutta en aio antaa periksi!  Tetriksessä on tällä hetkellä pisteitä yli 85 570 000. Aika hurjaa, sano. Kauankohan tuo on tuolla nyt pelautunut, yli viikon joka tapauksessa.  Eilen varasin sitten mulle ja Ricolle lennot Suomeen. Itse matkusta 9.8. ja Rico tulee perässä 14.8. Yhdessä tullaan takaisin sitten 19.8. Ricolla on työkiireitä eikä kissojakaan oikein voi jättää tuota pidemmäksi aikaa muiden armoille. Päädyttiin siihen ratkaisuun, että parasta on jättää ne omaan kotiin, jossa joku käy sitten antamassa ruokaa ja vähän leikkimässä niiden kanssa. Toivottavasti eivät raukat traumatisoidu ihan täysin :/ Huolestuttaa jo etukäteen koko homma... No, eiköhän se ihan hyvin mene.   Lauran ja Tepon häät ovat 14.8. Harmi, ettei Rico tod.näk. ehdi kirkkoon, kun kone on Helsingissä vasta klo 14 ja sitten on vielä ajomatka Lappeenrantaan. No, pääasia, että pääsee edes hääjuhlaan :) Vuokrataan auto viideksi päiväksi ja voidaan sitten vapaammin painella ympäriinsä. Hirveä ruljanssi viidelle päivälle, kun pitää Ricoa viedä näytille ;) Äiti, veljen perhe, Marjamäet, iskä... Kavereitakin olis kiva nähdä Ricon kanssa :) Huhhuh, kiirettä pitää sitten.   Mutta joo, pitää mennä tästä sitten vähän itseään sivistämään. Palaillaan!
     
    
</post>
<date>24,toukokuu,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      mieli: laama musiikki: koneen humina  On taas vähän laama olo. On tää nyt prkl, kun ei saa itestään mitään irti, vaikka tietää, että olis satoja sivuja luettavana eikä aikaa ole enää ihan hirveästi. Stna.  Menen tästä ripottelemaan tuhkaa päälleni. Turha entry tuli tästä :)
     
    
</post>
<date>23,toukokuu,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      11:14  mieli: ärgh musiikki: Eva Dahlgren - Stenmannen  Mä tänä aamuna oon miettinyt, että mitä vittua? Heräsin jossain vaiheessa aikaisin siihen, että Rico tuli kylkeen kiinni ja piti kiinni. Se on yksi niistä isoista onnentunteista, mitä voi parisuhteessa kokea, mun mielestäni. Sitten kaivauduin Ricon kainaloon ja jatkettiin onnellisesti unipilvessä leijailua, huoneessa oli kauniin pehmeä valo, kissat rauhallisia. Mulla oli jotain lämmintä ja karvaista taas jaloissa, Minkahan se siellä. Se tulee aina, kun vaan on tilaa. Jännää huomata, miten ne on meihin kiintyneitä ihan noin pyyteettömästi. Toinen asia on sitten, kun Minka tulee tuijottamaan viiden sentin päästä ihan hiljaa, että "anna ämmä ruokaa". Tosin on sekin aika söpöä. Jotenkin koomista, että kissa tulee aamutuimaan ihan vaan tuijottamaan niin läheltä. Tai pureskelee varpaita, jos niitä liikuttelee.  Tällainen tunne oli aamulla:  När en vild röd ros slår ut doftar hela skogen   När en vild röd ros slår ut  doftar hela skogen   när en vild röd ros slår ut  doftar hela skogen  under ekarnas blad  vilar vindarnas barn  till en sång  om en ros   i en skog  hörs en sång  om en ros   om en vild  en vild röd  vild röd ros   och när en människa  andas  för första gången  i sin älskades famn  vet hon  allt har samma  doft som  den blommans namn   gräver i jord  blomma skön  slår sin rot  runt en annan rot  törnen och blad  det jag sår  växer vilt  i nån annans jord   hela världen runt  mot en husvägg mitt i stan  i dammet på en sliten trottoar  röda rosors blad  hela världen runt  i skarven mellan järnvägsspår   under bron dit inget solsken når  röda rosors blad  hela världen runt  där inget annat orkar gro  finner rosen något och slår rot  hela världen runt   den blomman ger en människa ro  det vilda ger en människa ro  förundrad  och i beundran  står hon vid vägen och ler   jag vill  se min älskade komma från det vilda  jag vill  låta kärleken växa  i det vilda  jag vill   gräver i jord  blomma skön  slår sin rot  runt en annan rot  törnen och blad  det jag sår  växer vilt  i nån annans jord   jag vill  våga ge all min kärlek  i det vilda  jag vill  våga tro på din kärlek  i det vilda  jag vill  jag vill  låta kärleken växa  i det vilda  jag vill   hela världen runt  i öknars torra heta sand  i branten ner mot hav  som river land  röda rosors blad  hela världen runt  där ingen längre vågar tro  finner rosen något och slår rot  hela världen runt   i den blomman finner människan ro  i det vilda finner jag min ro  förundrad  och i beundran  står jag vid vägen och ler   jag vill  se min älskade komma  från det vilda  (Eva Dahlgren)  Rakkaus on niin suurta, etten aina tajua sitä. En voi välillä uskoa sitä todeksi tai että tämä pysyisi minun luonani. Siinä se sitten vaan on ja yliajaa mut. Vieläkin itken toistuvasti, joinain viikkoina joka päivä, onnesta, kun vain ajattelenkin Ricoa. Kai se on myöskin sitä, että täällä meidän suhde voi hengittää vapaasti, ilman ulkopuolisia rasitteita. Ilman tuttuja kuvioita ja liian tuttuja ihmisiä. Minun kannaltani siis. Ricohan nyt on aina ollut täällä.   Kaipaan ihan yllättävän vähän Suomea. Sieltä kaipaan lähinnä ystäviä... En juurikaan muuta. No, rasvatonta kermaviiliä myös :P Ja asioiden helppoutta välillä. Väsyttää ja kyllästyttää välillä puhua joka helvetin päivä vierasta kieltä. Välillä olen vain hiljaa, kun en Jaksa sanoa mitään saksaksi. Onneksi mies ymmärtää. Opiskelu on omiaan väsyttämään vielä lisää. Latinaa opiskellaan tietenkin saksaksi, englantia englanniksi. Suomea käytän vain puhelimessa vanhempien kanssa ja kavereiden kanssa ircissä tai messengerissä tai blogia kirjoittaessani.  No, piti kuitenkin jo ysin aikaan raahautua keittiöön antamaan karvakasoille ruokaa, olivat siitä kovasti onnellisia. Jostain syystä Ricokin sitten heräili samoihin aikoihin. Minun ihana, hyväsydäminen ja kaunissieluinen rakkaani.  np: Norah Jones - Seven Years  Tähän aamuun ei oikein sovi mikään räime, siksi hissimusiikkia.   Yöllä näin taas kummallista unta. Muuta en siitä oikeastaan muista kuin että se oli jostain toisesta miehestä ja tämä mies oli suomalainen. Suhdetta ei ollut, olin sinkku ja ihastunut. Tämä oli siis jo toinen tämän kaltainen uni. Edellisessä unessa olin ihastunut erikoissairaanhoitajaan, siis mieheen. Tunne oli jotenkin molemminpuolista, mutta ei siitä silti mitään tullut. Molemmat unet ovat jättäneet mut ihmettelemään, että mitä vittua? Mikä alitajunnan reaktio tää nyt on? En ole päätäni sen kummemmin unilla vaivannut, mutta vähän silti ihmetyttää. No, tässä on muutenkin ollut vähän kaikkea laimentavaa, mutta WTF? Eihän ikuisesti voi olla hulluna rakastunut, toki tämän tajuan. Onkohan tämä taas sellainen vaihe, kun pelkään jotain suhteessa. Että se päättyy tai että tapaankin sitten vielä sopivamman, kun jo ollaan naimisissa tms. Ehkä tämä ulkomailla oleminen vaikuttaa myös. Mulla ei ole täällä oikeastaan mitään muuta tukikohtaa kuin tämä meidän koti. Vieläkään ei ole muita rutiineja kuin opiskelu ja kotona normaalit arkipäivän rutiinit. Ei ole ystäviä... Välillä hajottaa olla niin paljon Ricon kanssa yhdessä, vaikka samalla haluankin sitä ja nautin siitä. Nyt Rico on äitinsä kanssa hakemassa kissaparkaa eläinlääkäriltä ja musta on ihanaa olla yksin. Tämä on siinä mielessä paradoksaalista, että olenhan mä viikollakin kaikki päivät keskenäni, kun Rico on töissä. Mutta se, miten vapaa-aikansa viettää ja kenen kanssa on tietenkin myös tärkeää. No, uskon kuitenkin, että tämäkin järjestyy ajan myötä. Näihin paikallisiin vain on vähän vaikea tutustua.  Mulle tyypillistä on kyllä saada näitä kriisivaiheita suhteissa. Tai no ainakin noissa kahdessa edellisessä, joita voi suhteeksi kutsua. Jannen kanssa näitä "kriisejä" oli neljän vuoden aikaan monta kertaa, Jussin kanssa alussa (olis silloin kyllä pitänyt luottaa vaistoihinsa ja lopettaa homma ennen kuin poltin näppini)... No, Janne oli sellainen mies, jonka kanssa oli helppoa olla suhteessa. Siinä on nimittäin kärsivällinen ja viisas, pitkänäköinen ihminen. Jussin kanssa taas aloitettiin vuoristoradan huipulta ja kaikkihan tietää, miten nopeasti se vuoristoradan mäki tullaan alas... Tosin normaalissa vuoristoradassa ei putoa kelkasta, kuten nyt kävi. Ricon kanssa aloiteltiin vähän varovaisemmin, vaikka meinasikin käydä hassusti...   Nimittäin Ricolla oli tämä irc-tuttava Malesiasta, joka ei oikein viime kesänä vielä tajunnut työntää omia kuumia tunteitaan Ricoa kohtaan taka-alalle. Ricokaan ei oikein silloin tiennyt, mitä se haluaa ja leikki sen Jasminin kanssa samaa leikkiä. Onneksi kuitenkin vain online. Meillä oli sen takia oikeasti ihan isoja ongelmia ja kun pistin Ricon selkä seinää vasten, niin paljastui asioita. No, niistä ollaan puhuttu ja puhuttu ja olen välillä itkettänytkin Ricoa (itsestäni puhumattakaan ;)... Mietin, että pakkaan kamani ja palaan Suomeen, mutta enhän mä sitä nyt sitten tehnyt, vaikka lähellä oli. Rico katkaisi välit (todellakin vapaaehtoisesti) siihen naiseen, kun totes, että se haluaa mieluummin olla mun kanssani. Jasminkin sitten löysi uuden sveitsiläisen miehen (sillä on joku pakkomielle eurooppalaisiin miehiin) ja on sen kanssa ilmeisesti nyt onnellinen ja me saadaan olla rauhassa. Mutta kyllä vieläkin satuttaa ajatella sitä aikaa ja mitä meinas käydä sen takia, että joku vitun malesialainen oli mun mieheen rakastunut (eivät olleet ikinä nähneet in real life). Ricon tunteet eivät olleet ystävyyttä ja flirttiä kummempia. Tällä hetkellä olen vähän erityistä herkempi, kun se nainen sattuu olemaan sen uuden sveitsiläisensä luona tuossa Zürichissä. Eli esim. ens viikolla, kun meen yliopistolle, saatetaan hyvin kulkea vaikka toistemme ohi, jos paska säkä käy ;)   Mutterilta tuli tänään sähköpostia, sen sunnuntai-aamun mietteitä. Olis tietenkin senkin voinut jättää lukematta, sisältö oli samaa vanhaa paskaa. No, sisältö jääköön tässä referoimatta, mutta ei siitä hyvä mieli tullut. Olin sen luettuani taas onnellinen, että olen täällä suhteellisen kaukana niistä meidän perheen sotkuista ja elän omaa elämääni. Mutta sekin pisti miettimään, että mitä vittua. Onko lapsen tehtävä toimia jonkinlaisena viemärinä, jos vanhemman elämä ei mene niin kuin se on suunnitellut? Onko mun tehtävä olla osallisena sitä katkeruutta, mitä vanhempi kantaa sisällään? Olen meidän perheessä välikappaleen roolissa, kun en ole suostunut valitsemaan puolia (äiti vs. veljen perhe). Se on vähän raskasta toisinaan. Myös se on raskasta, että äidin mielestä mä olen "ehkä" onnellinen täällä. Se ei siis usko, kun sanon sille olevani onnellisempi täällä kuin Suomessa. Ehdottelee vielä vuoden täällä asumisen jälkeen, että voisin muuttaa ihan hyvin kirjani vaikkapa sen luokse, että saisin Suomesta opintotukea ja muita etuja. Sen on vaikea ymmärtää, että mun koti on täällä ja haluan olla omassa kodissani kirjoilla. Toisaalta ymmärrän sen, että se tuntee olonsa tosi yksinäiseksi ja haluais, että asuisin lähempänä ja voisin käydä sen luona useammin. Olen tosin vähän sitä mieltä, että sen pitäisi löytää elämän sisältö jostain muualta, kun lapset ovat lentäneet pesästä. Ja onhan sillä se valokuvaus ja luonto, joiden parissa se on puhtaasti onnellinen, mikä tekee myöskin mut onnelliseksi, koska enhän mä äidilleni mitään pahaa halua. Meidän suhde nyt vaan ei ole ihan yksinkertainen.   Ei tää WTF-olo tästä oikein nyt mennyt mihinkään, vaikka tänne tätä vuodatusta tulikin. No, tartun novelliin ja hukutan itseni sen maailmaan. Ehkä kaikki taas jossain vaiheessa tasapainottuu ja lakkaan näkemästä unia vieraista, tosin anonyymeistä miehistä.
     
    
</post>
<date>22,toukokuu,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      12:57 PM  No niin!  Sain aikaiseksi perustaa tämän suomenkielisenkin blogin. On niin paljon asioita, jotka on vaikea täysipainoisesti ilmaista englanniksi ja jotka kuitenkin haluaisin kertoa ystävilleni, joita on kuitenkin vaikea ja kallistakin tavoittaa esim. puhelimitse. Nyt ne ovat siis luettavissa täällä. Tämän blogin tarkoitus on myöskin ylläpitää Ilona suomen kieltä, joka pikku hiljaa alkaa kärsiä vieraiden kielten dominanssista. Hmm, blogin otsikko on vähän harhaanjohtava ehkä, tästä ei ole todellakaan tarkoitus tulla mikään suomalaiskansallinen paatosblogi ;)  Kirjoittelen tässä vähän nopeasti sillä aikaa, kun Rico imuroi ja mä odotan vuoroani, että pääsen siivoamaan kylppäreitä. Ihan kiva, että niitä on kaksi (nykyään jako menee niin, että toinen kissoille ja toinen meille :D), mutta sitten on myös kaksinkertainen määrä siivottavaa :P No, eivät ole mitään maxi-kylppäreitä, että meneehän tuo nyt vielä. Hillitön mies tuo, imuroi tolleen ihan vapaaehtoisesti ja oma-aloitteisesti :o Ei vieläkään ole varmaan ihan tyypillistä täällä Sveitsissä ;)  1:58 PM  Huh, siivottu on. Kiva homma. Tuntuu, että täällä ei voi koskaan imuroida tarpeeksi, kun on tuo karmea kokolattiamatto. Kissoistakaan ei ihan vähän karvaa lähde, vaikka voisi toisin luulla... Sen takia sitten kylppäritkin ja joka paikka on alta aikayksikön pölyssä. Itsehän olen niin innokas siivoaja, että pieninkin pölyhiukkanen näkyy heti, hehheh.  Rico lähti kuskiksi äidilleen, Jacquelinelle, kun toinen hänen kissoistaan on onnistunut hommaamaan itselleen jonkun haavan silmäkulmaan. Tapellut tietenkin... Kurja kuulla tuommoisista, mutta minkäs teet. Meidän misuille ei ole tapahtunut onneksi Shivan tempauksen jälkeen (poltti tassunsa kuumalla hellanlevyllä) mitään, mutta onhan se meno noiden kanssa vähän kuin lasten kanssa ;) Shivan tassu on parantunut hienosti ja nyt palaneissa kohdissa on suloista vaaleanpunaista uutta nahkaa.  Mulla on ollut menossa jotkut kriisiviikot taas tämän olemisen ja asumisen kanssa. Keskiviikkona vihasin tätä ulkomailla asumista, kun taas tuli kielteinen vastaus, kun hain yhtä työpaikkaa. Tai no, vastaus olisi ollut tietyllä ehdolla myöntävä, mutta mä en sit vaan satu täyttämään sitä. En nimittäin ole Sveitsin kansalainen eikä mulla ole oikeanlaista oleskelulupaa (C-lupaa). C-lupa myönnetään automaattisesti viiden vuoden oleskelun jälkeen tai välittömästi, kun menee naimisiin sveitsiläisen kanssa. Mulla on tällä hetkellä vuoden välein uusittava B-lupa, josta siitäkin jo riemuitsin (ensimmäiset luvat olivat lyhytaikaisia L-lupia kesätyötä ja sen jälkeen työnhakua varten)... Ricoa en halua jonkun oleskeluluvan takia naida. Kyllä naimisiinmenolle pitää mun mielestä olla ihan eri syyt.   Minka tuli taas hellyydenkipeänä kiehnäämään :) Otin sen syliin ja tuossa se tyytyväisenä kehrää. Näppis vaan tulee taas ihan karvaiseksi, niin kuin aina, kun olen tietokoneella Minka sylissä ;) Shiva nukkuu tuossa Ricon LP-levyjen päällä. Ihana rauha täällä.  Lukemassa kai pitäisi olla, mutta onhan tässä tätä päivää vielä ;) Englannin opiskelu ei kyllä eroa oikein mitenkään Tampereen opiskelusta. Täällä vain tulee ylipäätään luettua enemmän, kun osallistuu vähemmän (=ei ollenkaan) muihin opiskelijarientoihin. Latinaa pitää opiskella enemmän kuin Suomessa. Sitä on kahden lukukauden ajan 7h viikossa. Se tuntuu välillä ihan yliampuvalta määrältä, mutta ajattelen sitä sillä tavalla, että ei siitä nyt haittaakaan ole. Jouduin tosin siirtämään yhdelle engl. kurssille osallistumista syksyyn, kun latina ja engl. kirjallisuuskurssi vievät jo niin paljon aikaa ja haluaisin toki viettää vähän vapaa-aikaakin.  Jahas, Rico tuli kotiin ja nyt mennään ostamaan mulle lukulamppua. Siis tää kämppä on täynnä lamppuja, mutta täällä ei silti näe kunnolla lukea kuin työpöydän ja ruokapöydän äärellä. Jotain romaani ei kuitenkaan tee mieli lukea pöydän äärellä, joten vaadin itselleni lukulampun toisen sohvan viereen ;)  Palaillaan taas! 
     
    
</post>
<date>22,toukokuu,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tänään luin vanhasta Eevasta (huhtikuu 03) jutun äidistä ja perheestä, jonka tytär teki itsemurhan "out of the blue" eli kukaan ei osannut aavistaa mitään. Järkyttävää kokonaisuudessaan, mutta kaikista järkyttävintä oli tämä, mitä äiti sanoi:   Hautajaisten jälkeen helluntaiseurakunnan sielunhoitaja soitti ja varoitti minua odottamasta seurakunnasta mitään ymmärrystä. Outoa, mutta tavallaan se auttoi minua, vahvisti hieman, Helinä toteaa.   Minä sen sijaan jäin sanattomaksi. Ikinä en ole helluntaiseurakuntaa (tai myöhemmin sitten oikein muitakaan seurakuntia) oikein minään pitänyt (olen jo ennenkin törmännyt tähän kaksinaamaisuuteen), mutta että näin huonosti ovat asiat. Olen pitkään kyseenalaistanut ja karsastanut kaikenlaisia itsensä pyhiksi ja hurskaiksi luokittelevia uskontokuntia ja erityisesti sellaisia ihmisiä. Tuollaisen lukeminen ei todellakaan paranna tilannetta. Miksi on niin vaikeaa noudattaa korkeimpana uskontona esimerkiksi omaa omatuntoansa? Luulisi, että jokaisella terveellä ihmisellä se reagoisi vääryyksiin ja muihin sellaisiin. Mutta eipä kai sitten. Masentavaa, ei voi muuta sanoa. Tai no sen vielä, että noitien sijasta roviolla pitäisi poltella uskontokuntien ja lahkojen päämiehiä. En osaa tehdä hirveän suurta eroa muinaisten ristiretkien alulle panijoiden ja esim. poliittisten diktaattoreiden välille. Puistattaa ajatella kaikkia niitä korruptoituneita uskonlahkojen johtajia, jotka hyötyvät hätää kärsivien ihmisten avuntarpeesta.  En ole pitkään aikaan uskonut ihmisen perimmäiseen hyvyyteen, niin paljon pahaa tässä maailmassa on. Kuitenkaan en jaksa heittää vielä toivoani, koska olen saanut olla onnekas ja kohdata myös niin paljon hyvää tässä maailmassa. Pelkään, että minut tallotaan ja jätetään elämän ulkopuolelle, jos en halua tai pysty nousemaan samaan menestymisen kelkkaan kuin suuri osa tässä elämässä menestyjistä. Jos kyynärpääni eivät olekaan tarpeeksi vahvat tai kovat. Jos murrun. Miten voi olla mahdollista pärjätä, jos ei ole siihen kykenevä? Ja tuleeko minustakin kyyninen paska, joka ajaa vain omia ja korkeintaa myös oman perheensä etuja. Tähän mennessä olen juossut pakoon kyynisyyttä. Jusa, sinä sen minulle joskus kirjeessäsi sanoit - juokse pakoon kyynisyyttä. Silloin olin 17-vuotias, nyt olen 25. Olen ihan ylpeä tästä pakomatkastani, mutta kuinka kauan jaksan vielä?  Ilpo Tiihonen sen sijaan piristi päivääni tänään. Siinä vasta ihana mies! Tai ainakin ihana kirjoittaja! Lainaan hänen sanojaan:   Tässä ajassa on parasta kieltäytyä hektisestä menosta ja keskittyä yhteen asiaan. Elämän runsaudesta voi valita jotain eikä kaikkea.   Ja taas löysin hänen sanoistaan erään kauneimmista rakkausrunoista. Olen aina rakastanut Tiihosen tuotantoa ja sieltä löytyy paljon muitakin, tämän tasoisia helmiä:    enkä välitä ymmärtää mitä oli rakastua silloin kun jumala meni toisesta korvasta sisään toisesta ulos, ja jätti jäljekseen äänesi käpälän.  (kirjasta Eros)   Näin hän muuttaisi maailman paremmaksi:   Ujoja rakastuneita pareja pitäisi sijoitella tasaisesti ympäri kaupunkia joka aamu. Sosiaali- ja terveysvirasto hoitaisi bussikuljetuksen. Odotushuoneisiin, hautaustoimistoihin, markettien peliautomaateille monenikäisiä suutelijoita ja halaajia. (Parnasso 1/03)   Aivan ihastuttava ajatus! :) Lohduttavaa on myös se, että hänkin myöntää kamppailevansa kyynisyyttä vastaan ja toteaa myös, että se se vasta vaivannäköä vaatiikin. Ja hän on sentään "jo" 52-vuotias, kauan on jaksanut kamppailla, joten enhän minäkään voi luovuttaa vielä. Mutta jos tämä maailma koko ajan tulee vain pahemmaksi kuin se nyt jo on? Ei, minä voin tehdä omasta mikroympäristöstäni hieman paremman, ehkä se pidemmällä aikavälillä vaikuttaa myös makroympäristöön ja sitten koko maailmaan. Hahah, maailmanparantajaksi minusta ei kyllä olisi, jollain pitää ansaita rahaakin ja maailmanparantajuus on kokopäivätyö, josta ei saa palkkaa!  Rakastakaa, kosketelkaa toisianne. Pysähtykää toistenne äärelle!
     
    
</post>
<date>22,toukokuu,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      mieli: liikuttunut tv: RTL - Meine Hochzeit  Päivän kohokohta, katson RTL:ltä Meine Hochzeit-ohjelmaa (Minun hääni) ja nieleskelen liikutuksen kyyneleitä. Onnellisia ihmisiä, pariutumista, kyyneleitä... Snif. Tämän päivän ohjelman ensimmäinen pariskunta ei kyllä ole kaunis ja puhuvatkin junttisaksaa ;) Niinku, jos ihminen sanoo "weider" eikä "weiter", niin se on Aivan Selvä Merkki duunariluokkaan kuulumisesta. Mutta toisaalta, kuka järkevä haluaa jakaa elämänsä onnellisimman (?) päivän juorunnälkäisten keskieurooppalaisten kanssa?! Nyt on tarkastelun alla pariskunta, jonka miehellä on LYHYTHIHAINEN valkoinen paita pukupaitana. Siis mikä MOKA! Mies myös puhuu lapsellisella painotuksella lässyttäen ja tuntuu, että kun hänen silmiinsä katsoo, näkee takaraivon. Ok, hääjuhlissa esitettävä pikku näytelmä parin tarinasta on kyllä erittäin hauska, itseänikin naurattaa :) Ihmeellistä kyllä, miten liikutuksen saa aikaan myös kaikista mauttomimmat bileet. Paitsi nyt joku teini vetää Celine Dionin pahamaineisen vaikean laulun "My Heart Will Go On" värisevällä äänellä, onneksi sitä ei näytetty loppuun asti. Koko ohjelma on ihan tautisen typerä ja karmeaa urkkimista, mutta katson sitä silti mielelläni. Siellä kun harvemmin on kärsiviä ihmisiä tai maailman pahuutta.  Totta kai haaveilen omista häistäni samalla. Millaista tulee olemaan, miten paljon meinaan itkeä, miten sukulaiset reagoivat, miltä näytän, miltä mieheni näyttää, miltä maailma tuntuu. Ajatus on niin ihana! Meidän häät on tosin aikaisintaan parin vuoden päästä. Alustavasti mietittiin 9.5.06, mutta mitään ei olla päätetty. Mennään nyt ensin kihloihin :) Yritän olla innostumatta asioista liian aikaisin, mutta vaikeaa se tässä tapauksessa on.  Tänään ja huomenna pitää vielä lukea tenttiin eläimenä, sitten alkaa kesäloma. Tai no "loma", luen kesälomallakin. Pitää alkaa valmistautua hyvissä ajoin Zwischenprüfungiin, kirjallisuuslista on sen verran vakuuttavan pituinen, että ei tee mieli jättää viime hetkeen...  --------------EDIT------------------------------- "Valtiovierailu" meni ihan hyvin ja leppoisissa tunnelmissa. Äiti huomautti vain kerran läskeistäni ja senkin kerran hyvin hienotunteisesti ;) Itse olin koko ajan sen sijaan hermostunut, koska sompailin kahden kielen välissä. On ihan yllättävän raskasta kommunikoida yhtä aikaa suomeksi ja saksaksi... Näin kokemattomalle. Välillä puhuin äidille ja tämän miesystävälle saksaa, Ricolle ja hänen äidilleen puolestaan suomea. Automatka meiltä Zürichiin oli myös kokemus ;) Rico ajoi sitten takaisin. Kissat reagoivat tyypillisillä tavoillaan. Shiva viihtyi lauantain ja sunnuntai-päivän sängyn alla, mutta ulostautui sitten su-iltana pyydystämään koppakuoriaisia. Ja tietenkin syömään välillä. Minka nautti alkuhämmennyksen jälkeen huomiosta ja valloitti kaikkien sydämet ;)  Oli siis ihan kiva tällä kertaa nähdä äitiä. Kai se teki hänellekin hyvää nähdä, miten minä täällä elän ja keiden kanssa. Maanantaina aamupäivällä he sitten jatkoivat matkaa eteenpäin ja illalla tuli viesti Ranskan puolelta. Jotenkin kuitenkin on nyt taas huojentunut olo. Olen taas vapaa! :) Ja kommunikoin jatkossa simultaanisti vain yhdellä kielellä, vaikka useampia kieliä joudunkin käyttämään. Elokuussa sitten taas...  
     
    
</post>
<date>22,toukokuu,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      mieli: pirteä, stressaantunut musiikki: The InTime Quintet - Soledad  En ole pitkään aikaan kuunnellut Piazzollan tango nuevoa. En kyllä tajua miksi, niin hyvältä tämä kuulostaa. Argentiinalainen tango on ihan omaa luokkaansa verrattuna suomalaiseen paatostangoon. Sir Elwoodin Hiljaisilla Väreillä (rauha Riku Järvisen muistolle) on mielestäni hyvä biisi, joka mielestäni kuvaa hyvin suomalaista tangoa. Biisin nimi on Tango, huikeaa, eikö? ;)   Tango  hän tuntee suolaiset kyyneleet poskillaan  hikinen käsi leninkiä painaa  ja hänen meikin peittämä ihonsa,  väsyneet katseet toisiaan karttaa   se on tanssia ihmisten,  tanssia jumalten,  tanssia välillä taivaan ja maan  suurta ja kaunista,  pientä ja totista  kun ihminen ihmistä  kiusaa   ja kuka tahteja laskee,  kuka rytmiä lyö,  kuka nousee ja kumartaa  ja kuka istuu ja jää,  kuka myöntää ja lähtee ja tangossa toisensa kohtaa   se on tanssia ihmisten,  tanssia jumalten, tanssia välillä taivaan ja maan  mies naistaan vie, sydän tahteja lyö,  kun poskea poskelleen  painaa   yli parketin,  yli savuisen hallin,  poika tyttöään taivuttaa  hetkeks unohtaa,  nuo kaksi kaiken saa  yli parketin,  tytön hiukset oudon kiillon saa  tuoksuu savuinen ilma,  kuin ruusuinen tarha  vain hetken on harha,  mihin kaksi nuo takertuu   ja hänen huulensa huutavat juotavaa,  rasvainen tukka  salin valoissa vain kiiltää,  kengät liukuvat pitkin salin lattiaa, elämän viivoja jauhoon vain piirtää   se on tanssia ihmisten,  tanssia jumalten, tanssia välillä taivaan ja maan  tanssia suurien,  tanssia pienien  kun ihminen ihmistä  kiusaa  se on tanssia ...    sanat: J.Lehti   Argentiinalainen tango on kuumaa, eroottista, tunteiden paloa, intiimiä (melkein punastuttaa katsella toisten tanssivan sitä) ja taidokasta. Argentiinalainen tango ilmaisee tunteita ilman sanoja. Miten viulun, kitaran, haitarin, pianon ja basson voikin niin selvästi saada itkemään, kaipaamaan, rakastamaan ja haluamaan...  Ironista sinänsä nyt on se, että InTime Quintet on suomalainen yhtye :) Joten kyllä sitä intohimoa suomalaisistakin löytyy. He kaikki tosin ovat ammattimuusikkoja. Luulenpa, että Argentiinasta löytyy huikeita amatöörejäkin, joilta tango nuevo sujuu.  Sitten voisinkin kommentoida, että hiukan kosteaa nurmikkoa on aika raskas ajaa. Rakkinekin on niin painava, että käsivoimia tarvitaan kyllä. Olin siis taas anopin nurtsin ajamassa. Pistin vielä vauhtia siihen ajamiseen, kun tuli niin tummia pilviä taivaalle ja pelkäsin, että alkaa sataa ja että pitäisi lopettaa se nurmikon ajaminen kesken. No, ei alkanut sataa, mutta olinpahan tosi tehokas.  Ellei kaverit irkissä koko ajan puhuisi juhannuksesta, unohtaisin sen kokonaan. Täällä kun ei semmoista juhlaa vietetä. Ei ole mikään iso tappio siinä mielessä, että juhannus on aina ollut mun mielestä jopa uutta vuotta vituttavampi juhla. Montakohan ihmistä tänäkin juhannuksena hukkuu taas, kun jotkut pällit ovat joskus keksineet, että juhannuksena pitää ryypätä itsensä ääliö-kuntoon? Kaupat ovat tietenkin kiinni ja kaikki muutkin paikat. Tosin, kaupat nyt saavatkin olla kiinni. Nykyajan uusavuttomat voivat kyllä toisinaan saada käytännön muistutuksen siitä, mitä on esim. ostoslistan tekeminen ja yleinen suunnittelu. Ei ihmiset varmaan vaan viitsi vaivata päätään sillä, että miettisivät, mitä tarvitsevat parin päivän aikana niin, ettei tule sitten tarvetta lähteä sunnuntaina kauppaan. Ihmisillä tietenkin on myös esim. sunnuntaiaukioloaikojen myötä uusia tarpeita. Tai ei välttämättä uusia, mutta enemmän. Lauantaisen bileillan jälkeen pitää päästä ostamaan kaupasta sitä ja tätä. Miksei niitä perkele voi ostaa jo lauantaina valmiiksi, kun se baari-ilta ja seur. päivän krapula tuskin tulee niin suurena yllätyksenä, ettei siihen muka osaisi varautua. Jos ei taas osaa varautua ennakkotietoisuudesta huolimatta tai jos se känni ja krapula todella tulevat yllätyksenä, niin sitten pitää KÄRRRSIÄ. *evil laughter* Itsekin olen kärsinyt ja siitä hengissä selvinnyt.  Mutsi on huomenna perillä. Ahistaa. Saa nähdä, noudattaako vierailu edeltäpelättyä kaavaa. Ristiriitaiset fiilikset tuosta vierailusta. Täällä on saanut olla niin rauhassa ja rakentaa elämää tänne omien mieltymystensä mukaan. Nyt musta tuntuu, että se rauha tullaan rikkomaan, tai ainakin sitä järkytetään. Tiedän, että äiti ei kuitenkaan voi olla tekemättä niitä helvetin elämänkorjausehdotuksia tai olemaan huomauttelematta siitä, mikä täällä on hänen mielestään väärin. Kaiken lisäksi mulla on ensi viikolla kirjallisuustentti, johon on vielä helvetisti luettavaa. Valitsivat siis paskimman mahdollisen ajan vierailulle. Viikon päästä mulla olis jo kesäloma, mutta kun ei niin ei. Mutsin miesystävän loma loppuu jnejne. No, eivät ne viivy kuin pari päivää ja nukkuvatkin anopin luona. Ehkä siitä selviää. Seuraavan kerran pitää kärsiä taas elokuussa, meikäläisen kamat kun on mutsilla varastossa. Olen vähän niin kuin olosuhteiden uhri ;) Tuskin maltan odottaa sitä päivää, että saan roinani pois mutsin hoteista ja voin tulla Suomeen ja asua hyvällä omatunnolla kavereiden tai veljen perheen luona koko ajan. Jotenkin on sellainen fiilis, että niin kauan kuin siellä on jotain mun kamoja, en voi sanoa, ettei tarvii tulla tänne vierailulle, jos meidän aikatauluun ei sovi. Ihan typerää tietenkin. Pitäisi vaan olla huono ja kiittämätön lapsi ja sanoa, että tänä viikonloppuna ei sovi, tulkaa toiste. Argh.  Nyt menen laittamaan ruokaa, ettei olisi siitä sitten viikonloppuna stressiä. Tänään voin sitten stressata siitä ajasta, mikä meni ruuanlaittoon ja jonka olisi voinut käyttää lukemiseen. Saatanansaatana. Perkele.   
     
    
</post>
<date>22,toukokuu,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      mieli: neutraalin tympääntynyt, mutta silti onnellinen musiikki: Carole King - I Feel The Earth Move  Yh, omat tupakat loppu (munhan piti lopettaa sitten, kun nuo loppuvat!) ja pöllin Ricolta yhden Philip Morrisin Super Lightsin ja maistuipa se pahalta, vaikka on hyvää kahvia seurana. Long live the mentholsavukkeet! Porsaanreiäksi tosin mainittakoon se seikka, että anoppikokelaalla on vielä omissa varastoissaan mun tupakoita. Se ostaa aina pari askia itsellensä varastoon, jos vaikka satun unohtamaan tupakat kotiin ;)   Nukuin tänään peräti melkein puoli yhdeksään asti. Minka yritti taas pureskella mun varpaita, mutta tottuneella väistöliikkeellä siirsin varpaat peiton alle ja hyökkäys jäi keskeneräiseksi, sai vain kevyesti tassuilla kiinni jalasta. On se mainio otus :) Shivaa kävin äsken silittämässä pyykkikorilla ja selittämätön onnentunne (tänään menee ehkä yhdyssanat miten menee, mutta menköön; rikkokaa päänne, kielipoliisit *evil laughter*) valtasi minut, kun Shivaa silittäessäni hän tarttui etusormestani hellästi kiinni tassullaan ja kynnet puoliksi ulkona ja kehräsi nautinnollisesti. Tuo tarttumisote oli jotenkin ihmisvauvamainen, mutta toistaiseksi vauvan kosketuksesta ei ole tullut samanlaista onnentunnetta. Ehkä siksi, että ne vauvat eivät ole asuneet meidän luonamme eivätkä ole pitäneet minua äitinään ;) Mutta joo, tokihan näitä selittämättömiä onnentunteita olen kokenut myös veljenlasteni kanssa, kun Valtteri (7v.) aamutuimaan aivan unisena kiipeää syliin ja halaa koko vartalollaan (kädet ja jalat mun ympärilläni) hyvästiksi. Siitä tuli myös iso pala kurkkuun, kun siitä seurasi pitkä ero ja näkemättömyys, joka päättyy elokuussa.  Elokuussa tai joskus niillä main päättynee myös tämä meidän parisuhdekaavamme (tänään luin eräästä blogista, jossa oli lainattu toista blogia tästä 2+1+2-kaavasta) ensimmäinen osa, kun menemme Suomessa katsomaan kihlasormuksia. Hui. Eilen siitä juteltiin taas. Molemmat yhtä hämmentyneinä, kun ei meistä kumpikaan ole näistä asioista vielä kenenkään kanssa jutellut sillä tavalla tosissaan tai onnistumisen mahdollisuus silmissä kiiltäen. Olenhan minä edellisten kanssa näistä puhunut. Ensimmäinen kammoksui ajatusta, vaikkei sitä suoraan sanonutkaan. Partneri nro. kaksi oli ensin innoissaan ja sitten veti hätäjarrut päälle. Sittemmin olen tutkiskellut itseäni ja miettinyt kaikenlaista ja tullut siihen lopputulokseen, että sitoutumisviettini taitaa olla aika vahva :) Se on ollut jo vuosia selvää, että heittäydyn parisuhteeseen pää edellä täysin sokeasti luottaen ja sitten tietenkin joskus putoaa päälleen, kun kukaan ei olekaan tulossa vastaan. No, niistä on selvitty. Nyt tässä suhteessa ei ole vaikea heittäytyä, kun mieskin sanoo, että haluaa viettää kanssani vielä vuosikymmeniä. Ai niin ja perjantaina Metallican konsertista tullessa mies sanoi myöskin, että naimisiin mennään sitten 9.5.2006. Katsotaan tuota päivämäärää ja vuotta sitten uudelleen, kun ollaan päästy edes kihloihin asti ;) Minulla on se etu, että pääsen kaksi kertaa naimisiin, heh. Jos vaan siltä tuntuu. Ensin täällä ja sitten Suomessa. Mietittiin leikillämme, että mennään ensin täällä naimisiin ja sitten, kun olen yliopistosta valmistunut, mennään Suomessa naimisiin. No, ei mikään huono idea tuokaan. En ole ihan varma, mutta tuntuu siltä, että Suomessa avioliitto on voimassa vasta, kun menee myös siellä naimisiin. En tiedä kyllä... Täytyy katsoa nyt.   Niin, perstaina oltiin siellä Metallican keikalla Zürichissä. Oli ihan helevetin hyvä meininki, vaikka ne uudet nu metal-biisit eivät yhtään kolahdakaan. Loppua kohden alkoi tulla sitten niitä vanhoja, hyviä biisejä ja jengi oli ihan pipareina, niin mekin. Oltiin saatu Ricon siskolta liput ja paikat oli katsomossa, lavan lähellä, hyvässä kulmassa, miksauspöydän kanssa samalla kohdalla, wau. Taas nähtiin se, miten kalja yhdistää ihmisiä! Jotain läpänderiä heitin siinä vähän alempana istuvien äijien kanssa kaljan tuomisesta jne. kun olin menossa vessaan ja kaljaa hakemaan siis. Tässä vaiheessa pitää selventää, että päälläni oli tuolloin Dream Theater-paita. Tullessani takaisin toinen miehistä (ikä n. 50v. hiuksien harmaudesta ja muusta päätellen) pysäytti mut ja halus näyttää mulle tatuointinsa. No sillä oli iso Dream Theater-logo olkapäähän hakattuna. No, itsenikin piti sitten lähteä paljastelemaan oma DT-tatskani ja ilmassa oli todellista heavy metal-yhteenkuuluvuuden tunnetta! Olin niin ikionnellinen taas tästä metallikansa-meiningistä. Yksi asia vaivasi päätäni koko konsertin ajan ja vaivaa vieläkin, että mikä hitto on sen no metal-pändin nimi, joka esittää kappaleen "Wish You Were Here"? En vieläkään muista pändin nimeä, vaikka sen levyä kuuntelin joskus. Nytpä meinaan tehdä ratkaisevan askeleen ja päättää piinani ja käyttää kuukelia. Kuukeli ei auttanut, mutta sen yhden vihaamani ihmisen kotisivu sen sijaan auttoi, sieltä löytyi veppikamerakuva sen pändin keikkalipusta. Incubushan se pändi oli.  No, enhän minä sitä söpöä aasialaista vihaa, en vain pidä hänestä. Keskimäärin pidän enemmän miehistä, täytyy myöntää. Naisten joukosta kun löytyy niin käsittämättömiä kanoja ja kieroilijoita, että argh. Tosin, kyllä ne miehetkin kunnostautuvat idiotismissa sun muussa. Esim. perjantaina törmäsin niin pölkkypäiseen mieheen, että sääliksi kävi. Yritimme löytää paikkaa erään baarin terassilta keikan jälkeen ja kysyimme vapaata tuolia eräästä pöydästä, jonka äärellä oli useita istumattomia tuoleja. No, ei irronnut tuolia, mutta yksi pöydässä istuvista katsoi asiakseen kommentoida painoani tyyliin "vain siksi, että olet lihava, ei sun tarvii..." jne. Mielessäni vilisi monia erilaisia napakoita takaisinheittoja (joo, saksan taitoni on jo myös kipakkaan solvaamiseen riittävä;) ja huomasin Riconkin laskevan viiteentoista, mutta ajattelin (ja Rico ajatteli) sitten, että antaa miesparan egoboostata, ehkä hän on seuraavana päivänä krapuloissaan ylpeä itsestään ja pippelikin seisoo paremmin tavaratalon alusvaatekuvaston edessä runkatessa. Sitten siihen tuli vielä kyllästynyt vanhakurppa tarjoilija, joka totesi meille happamesti tilaustamme kysyttyään, että painukaa siitä sisälle sitä kaljaa juomaan, kun selitimme, että kiitos, mutta haimme kaljamme jo sisältä. Ja se, että ylipäätään saatiin kaljaa sieltä sisältäkään ilman käteistä oli niin perkeleen kiven alla, että huhhuh. Tuntui, että olin saapunut johonkin uuteen maailmaan, missä asuu vain ihan helvetin pällejä ihmisiä, jotka eivät yksinkertaisimpia asioita tajua (kuten esim. miten erilaisia maksukortteja höylätään; toisaalta, tämäkin on joku säästötoimenpiteen syy, kun kiireavuksi oli palkattu varmaan jonkun työntekijän isoäiti, joka ei tajunnut pankkikorteista hölkäsen pöläystä ja yritti minunkin pankkikorttiani höylätä ensin väärässä reiässä, kunnes uskoi omaa opastustani, että se tungetaan siihen viereiseen koloon.) ja sitten ollaan vaan epäystävällisiä. Mikä vittu ihmisiä vaivaa oikein? Itse olen sen verran toiminut tarjoilijana, että tiedän kyllä, että vaikka itseä kuinka vituttaisi, niin ei se asiakkaan syy (yleensä, hihih) ole. Tai vaikka olisi asiakkaan syy, niin ei sitä vitutusta näytetä.   Tuosta perjantaisesta kaljanosto/terassiepisodista tuli mieleen taas sellainen ajatus kuin: "saatana, että vihaan tyhmiä ihmisiä". Sanokaa mitä sanotte, mutta omasta mielestäni absoluuttisesta tyhmyydestä ei ole paljon hyötyä tälle yhteiskunnalle. Hmm, pitäisiköhän sitten todeta kuitenkin ilman sukupuolien jaottelua, että keskimäärin en pidä ihmisistä ;) Ei vaan. En ole mikään ihmisvihaaja, mutta mielelläni valitsen kyllä seurani aika tarkkaan ja siksi ystäväpiiriini kuuluu vain ihmiskunnan ehdotonta eliittiä ;) Täällä olen tosin joutunut vähän joustamaan tuosta periaatteestani, koska muuten olisin aina vain Ricon kanssa. Hyi, kirjoitanpa rumia :) Menen ripottelemaan tuhkaa päälleni. Ehkä.  --------------------EDIT----------------------- Olen tässä huvittuneena seuraillut erilaisia blogi-klikkejä, jotka taistelevat toisiaan vastaan. Trio Erektus (http://www.pinseri.com/wiki/wiki.cgi?TrioErektus) vaikuttaa jotenkin erityisen vitsikkäältä, luulen, että sen taustalla on jotain teekkarin höpsyköitä, jotka väittävät dissaavansa humanisteja, mutta päätyvät kuitenkin naimisiin sellaisen kanssa, kun ovat kyllästyneet naisteekkareiden kainalo- ja piNppikarvoja katselemaan. Luulen, että he ovat n. 25-vuotiaita (korkeintaan) ja heillä on kova sukupuolivietti ja he yrittävät jutuillaan saada tytöt punastumaan. Luulen myös, että heillä kasvaa finnejä aivojen pinnalla. Senkin luulen vielä, että he naureskelevat omalle nokkeluudelleen Kultaisessa Vapinassa sähly-treenien jälkeen. Olikohan heidän tarkoituksensa provosoida? Varmaankin ja ilmeisen tehokasta se on, koska toiset provosoituvat. Itseäni lähinnä huvitti, olenhan niin monta kertaa istunut teekkareiden kanssa nakuna saunassa laulamassa hävyttömiä lauluja Rasputinista, vaikka humanisti olenkin :)   Sitten ovat nämä emansipoituneet villakangashametytöt ja vaaleansiniseen ja beigeen pukeutuvat reippaat selviytyjät, jotka taas punaisin kynsin tappelevat miesten sortoa vastaan. BARRIKADEILLE. Esimerkiksi Mintun (http://www.uta.fi/~tlmihap/tarina.html#) sanailu on taidokasta, mutta ei sykähdyttävää. Varmasti sydänverellä kirjoitettuja juttuja, ehkä, mahdollisesti, mutta en minä ainakaan jaksanut liikuttua, provosoitua tms. Jotenkin sanat kolisevat tyhjyyttään. Sitä paitsi minusta tuntuu, että vain hyvin harvoilla ihmisillä on varaa arvostella ehdoitta toisia ihmisiä typeryksiksi. Voinhan olla väärässäkin.   Mutta yksi piirre häiritsee, kuten myös häiritsee www.expatrium.fi:ssä: asioita otetaan niin pirun henkilökohtaisesti. Kirjoitetaan vastineita toisten blogeille, provosoidutaan jne. Itse olen ihan uusi blogi-maailmassa, mutta todella toivon, että näillä ihmisillä on parempaakin tekemistä :) Itse olen irkkaillut vuodesta 1997 ja siellähän nyt otetaan asioita henkilökohtaisesti ja välillä tarkoitetaankin sitä. Mutta kuitenkin siellä on tietynlaiset normit, joiden mukaan toimitaan suurimman osan ajasta. Kyseessähän on kuitenkin reaaliaikainen keskustelufoorumi. Se, mikä irkistä ja blogeista puuttuu, on ruumiin kieli, jota ei pidä vähätellä. Suurin osa ihmisten kommunikoinnista tapahtuu kuitenkin ilmeiden ja eleiden kautta. Raskaasti yleistäen voisi sanoa, että sanat ovat suullisessa viestintätilanteessa vain eleiden ja ilmeiden tukena. Ihmisten eleiden lukutaito vaan on tainnut heikentyä, kun asioita ymmärretään niin usein väärin, vaikka äänessä olisi aivan selvästi havaittavissa sarkasmin vivahteita.  No, tulinpa näin iltasella vielä kirjoittelemaan joitain merkintöjä. Pitää vielä mennä opiskelemaan. Provoisointi on parhaimmillaan loistavaa viihdettä ja täytyy myöntää, että kaikista herkullisinta se on silloin, kun joku todella provosoituu :) Se on sitä egoboostia, jota me kaikki tarvitsemme. Toisen provosoituessa saamme jonkinlaisen todisteen, että olemme ehkä jollain tavalla ansioituneita kirjoittajia ja meillä on valtaa toisiin ihmisiin. Itselleni tosin käy alkuhuuman jälkeen sitten aina niin, että tunnelma lässähtää, kun tajuan, miten helppoa provosointi itse asiassa olikaan... Siksi kannatankin antiikin Rooman kaltaista yhteiskuntaa, jossa ajattelu (se korvattaisiin nyt tietenkin provokaatiolla) jätettiin tietyille henkilöille ja duunareilla ei ollut sitten mitään tarvetta tietää niistä asioista mitään. Höhöhö :D  Sellainen viisaus tuli vielä mieleen, joka meitä kaikkia yhdistää:  Kaikki me synnymme alastomina, kakkaamme pyllystä ja joudumme kuolemaan.  Ja tämäkin tuli vielä mieleen:  Mielipide on kuin persereikä, meillä kaikilla on sellainen.  Kosketelkaa toisianne.  --------------------------EDIT 2-------------------------- Sekin piti vielä sanoa, mutta unohdin, että nyt sitten äitikin tietää kihlautumis-aikomuksistamme. Reaktio oli laimea ja pettyneen kuuloinen "Ai, no onneks olkoon". Juuri aiemmin oli puhetta mun cd-levyistäni, joita se tuo nyt tänne, kun ne tulevat ja se heitti, että "kannattaako niitä nyt sinne raahata, kun sä ne kuitenkin tuot takaisin sitten taas?". Milloin minä ne vien takaisin? Minä sitten sanoin siihen, että "jos me ollaan elokuussa menossa kihloihin, niin en mä perkele niitä seedeitä takaisin sinne ala tuoda." Äiti-parka elää vielä yli vuoden jälkeen siinä harhakuvitelmassa, että tulen täältä ehkä jo ensi syksyksi takaisin Suomeen. "Kyllä sä voit täällä meillä ihan hyvin asua ja käydä täältä opiskelemassa". No tietenkin! Mutta siis, vähän harmittaa, että tuli möläytettyä, kun piti pitää tuo kihlaushomma mutsille yllätyksenä elokuuhun asti. Sehän ei tällaisia blogeja käy lukemassa.    
     
    
</post>
<date>22,toukokuu,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      mieli: pönttö musiikki: ei mitn  Lähdettiin anoppikokelaan kanssa kauppaan jo puoli yhdeksältä, että vältyttäisiin pahimmalta ruuhkalta. Joskus iltapäivällä on ihan tuskaa käydä ruokaostoksilla, kun kotiäidit tulevat kaikkien lastensa kanssa kauppaan. Lapset sitten joko vääntelehtivät tuskastuneina ostoskärryissä, riekkuvat ympäriinsä, saavat raivareita, leikkivät keskenään tai häiritsevät jotenkin muuten. Siis, hyvä, että lapsia otetaan mukaan paikkoihin, että oppivat vähän tätä elämää, mutta onko niitä nyt joka kerta pakko raahata kauppaan? Toisaalta kysyn, onko niiden kotiäitien aina pakko raahata itsensä kauppaan ;) Eikö mies voi tehdä sen vertaa, että vahtisi niitä kersoja kotona sen tunnin verran, mitä kauppareissuun menee (ilman sosiaalista puolta) tai kävisi itse kaupassa? Mies osaa ihan hyvin lukea kauppalistaa, uskokaa pois. Tekee toisinaan oikein pahaa katsella niitä tuskastuneita kotiäitejä, jotka yrittävät pitää viidetsadat narut yhtä aikaa käsissä eli valikoida hyvät tomaatit, kurkut, suklaavanukkaat sun muut. Ei käy kateeksi. Toisaalta tekee pahaa katsella niitä kotiäitejä, jotka unohtavat muksunsa jonnekin riehumaan ja keskittyvät keskustelemaan toisten "kohtalotovereiden" kanssa päivän tapahtumista ja pikku Peterin kakkaamistavoista. Keskellä käytävää tietenkin ostoskärryjen kanssa tukkien koko kulkuväylän. Minä sitten yritän ujuttautua jotenkin anteeksipyydellen siitä välistä, kun en jaksa alkaa selvittää heille, että heidän käytöksensä poikkeaa hyvistä tavoista. Se kun tuntuu olevan ihan päinvastoin. Eli normaalia on tukkia tie niillä kärryillä ja anteeksipyytelevää läpitunkeilijaa katsotaan viileästi ja joskus jopa ärtyneenä.  Toinen laji ovat nämä mummelit. Tänään eräs törmäsi perseeseeni kärryillään, kun olin valitsemassa vihanneksia kalakeittoa varten. Hyvä kun jotain ynähti ja katsoi vielä kaupan päälle inhoavasti, vaikkei mulla ollut edes tatuoinnit näkyvillä. Teki mieli suuttua ja vittuuntua, mutta ajattelin, että se pässi ei ole sen arvoinen. Arvostan ja kunnioita vanhempia ihmisiä, mutta ei ikä oikeuta mielestäni tekemään ihan mitä tahansa. En myöskään haluaisi alentua joka kerta samalle tasolle näiden pällien kanssa ja yritän asettua koko kauppapelleilyn yläpuolelle, hoitaa ostokseni ja mennä kotiin. Mutta joskus ei vaan jaksa, joskus sitä vaan hermostuu. Toistaiseksi en ole avannut sanaista arkkuani, vaikka lähellä on ollut. Varmaan sekin lisäisi pahennusta, koska sveitsinsaksan sijasta (olen siis juntti, kun en osaa puhua kieltä, jota osaa ehkä saman verran ihmisiä kuin suomea :&gt;) suustani tulisikin ulos hochdeutschia. "Mitä tuokin ulkomaalainen tulee tänne MEIDÄN Migrosiin uhittelemaan, painuisi takaisin sinne, mistä on tullutkin!" Ei vaan, eipä mua olla täällä rasistisesti kohdeltu muuten kuin työnhaun yhteydessä ja sekin lähinnä oleskelulupa-asioissa. Ehkä etunani on vaalea iho ja kansallisuutta tunnustamaton tukan väri. Karua, mutta totta. Suomalaiset tosin tuntuvat olevan täällä muutenkin aika suosittuja tai siis ennemminkin ihan hyväksyttyjä.  Joskus toivoisi, että voisi tuollaisen maallisen rituaalin kuin kaupassa käymisen jättää muille, tilata ruuat vaikka netistä. Mutta sehän olisi vähän naurettavaa pelleilyä, kun aikaa mulla kuitenkin nyt on kaupassa käymiseen. Kerran viikossa kaupassa pitää käydä, ei voi mitään.  Ruokakaupan jälkeen mentiin kahville. Ajateltiin, että ei tuu mitään, jos ei saa kahavia koneistoon. Meillä molemmilla on ollut tänään vähän laho latva, ikään kuin pään ympärillä olisi kupu tai ihan kuin olisi oman vartalonsa ulkopuolella, eikä oikein tietäisi, mitä tehdä ja missä nyt mennään; tosi outo fiilis. Kahvi ja jutustelu teki hyvää. Mentiin sitten katsomaan pyörää mulle. Kun on se diili, että mä ajan nurtsin jne. No kuvittelin saavani jonkun 700-800 frangin pyörän, mutta anoppi päätyikin ostamaan n. 1000 frangin pyörän!!! Kypäräkin tuli ostettua. Kohta mennään hakemaan se... Mulla on kyllä maailman paras anoppi, ei voi muuta sanoa. Eikä vain sen takia, että se ostaa mulle pyörän.
     
    
</post>
<date>22,toukokuu,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Kirjoitin pitkät pätkät iskästä ja äidistä aika henkilökohtaisestikin, mutta tuhosin sen kaiken. Tuntui, että se ei kuulu tällaiseen paikkaan.  Iskä, on sua ikävä.   Äiti tulee kylään reilun viikon päästä, juuri pahimpaan tenttiinlukustressi-aikaan. Rico sanoo: Alles kommt auf einmal ja niinhän se on. Prkl.
     
    
</post>
<date>22,toukokuu,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      mieli: harmaa musiikki: Simo Salminen - Rotestilaulu  Olen ottanut jonkun askeleen johonkin suuntaan lähettämällä pinseri.comiin pyynnön, että lisäisivät vaivaisen blogini listalleen. Mitähän tästäkin tulee, myynkö sieluni blog-pirulle?  Taistelen itseni kanssa, että saisin itseni lukemaan J. Conradin Heart of Darknessin huomiseksi. Asiaa mutkistaa se, että olen aloittanut sen lukemisen joskus melkein pari viikkoa sitten junassa väsyneenä ja tiedän, että nyt pitää aloittaa alusta. Lisäksi huomiseksi pitää lukea kasa teoriaa ja MUA EI HUVITA. Koko alkuviikon olen nauttinut ruumiillisesta ja aivovapaasta työskentelystä. Hoidin erästä lasta maanantaina ja ajoin anoppikokelaan nurmikon eilen, sekä kävin kaupassa ja laitoin ruokaa. Nyt on sitten jotenkin vaikeaa suhtautua rakentavasti teoreettiseen maailmaan. Taidan olla vähän hankala, kun opiskelu tuntuu välillä niin väkisin vääntämiseltä, mutta toisaalta en halua hoitaa lapsia ja ajaa nurmikoita loppuelämääni. Enkä myöskään ryhtyä tyytyväiseksi kotiäidiksi. Tiedän, että tulisin hulluksi, jos pitäisi kotona tai lasten kanssa olla kaiket päivät ja pistää joka ilta pesuun paita, joka on täynnä maito- ja räkätahroja.  Maanantaina puistossa näin taas sellaisen Hochdeutschia puhuvan kotiäidin, joka Enzo-poikansa oli pukeutunut täysin samaan vaaleansinisen sävyyn, että alkoi puistattaa. Näin nimittäin liukumäen vieressä ollessani, hoitolastani rappusia ylös saattaessani, tämän kotiäidin t-paidan hihasta sisään (no okeiokei, katsoin ihan tietoisesti sinne, urkkija olen) ja sieltä pilkotti piiiiiiiiiiiiiitkät ja mustat kainalokarvat. Hyi sentään. Aikamoinen järkytys meikäläiselle, joka tykkää karvoista vain päässä... Jouduin myöskin miettimään, että jos se Enzon äiti ei aja edes kainalokarvojaan, niin miten mahtaa olla muiden karvaisten alueiden aika. Yhh. Ok, en minäkään käsivarren hentoisia, vaaleita karvoja ajele tai edes reisieni hentoisia karvoja. Mutta kyllä kainalo-, sääri- ja piNppikarvat pitäisi ajella :/ Onneksi Rico ajelee ihan vapaaehtoisesti karvansa; ajaisi myös rintakarvat, ellen kieltäisi ;) Ja silti on niin miehekäs, että NAM. Pianhan se tuolta töistänsä kotiin tulee, namnam.  np: The Rasmus - Liquid  Hih, tälle laululle tuli joskus porattua kännissä, kun oltiin tyttöin kera Henry's pubissa Tampereella ja oltiin juotu "muutama" Sex on the Beach. En kyllä muista enää, että miksi itketti. Olikohan se juuri ennen kuin olin lähdössä Saksaan tai sieltä tulon jälkeen, kun oli vielä ikävä Saksaan. En muista. Semmoista se on joskus. Joka tapauksessa tätä biisiä kuunneltiin myöskin lappeen Rannalla kesällä 2001, ennen kuin lähdin sinne Saksaan. Tämän vuoden elokuussa tulee taas mentyä lappeen Rannalle, kun ystäväni Laura menee naimisiin ihanan Tepponsa kanssa. Tämän Lauran luona olinkin juuri silloin kesällä 2001. Laura-rakas, on niin kova ikävä...  Olen miettinyt irkkaamiseni dilemmaa. Miksi minä aina toistuvasti menen sinne, vaikka en sitten oikeastaan jaksakaan sitä samaa vanhaa meininkiä. Pitäisi vaihtaa kanavat kokonaan, jos haluaisi jotain uutta. Ja siihen ei taas riitä energia. Siellä kanavilla samat vanhat pellet jatkavat vittuiluaan ja minähän tietenkin vittuilen mukana, niin kuin asiaan kuuluu. Siis ihan hauskaa ja harmitonta, mutta tuntuu, että voisi koko homman lopettaa vaikka ja keskittyä tähän reaalielämään. Toisaalta sitten se on hyvä ja edullinen keino pitää jonkinlaista sosiaalista verkostoa yllä Suomessa. Siis IRC-kaverini ovat myös IRL-tuttaviani, on siellä muutamia ystäviäkin jopa. Toistaiseksi olen löytänyt hyväksi ratkaisun, että käyn irssimässä vain pari kertaa viikossa, joskus saattaa tulla pidempikin tauko. Irc-galleriakin tympii jonkun verran, mutta sekin on toisaalta hyvä tapa kommunikoida näiden tuttavieni kanssa. Mitä mää teen?! Nimim. aktiivista irkkailua vuodesta 1997.  Miksei mies tule jo? Pääsisin rakastavaan syleilyyn.  Tänään luin erästä esimerkki-esseen aloitusta ja siinä esseessä kirjoitetaan Clueless-leffan ja Austenin Emman suhteesta. Siis mitvit? Mä luulin, että Clueless on itsenäinen aivoton pelle-elokuva, mutta että se onkin remake Emmasta. Järkytyin. Emma pitää tässä jossain vaiheessa ottaa lukuun, kun se kuuluu Zwischenprüfungin kirjallisuuslistaan.  Välillä tuntuu, että olisi pitänyt valita ammatillinen koulutus akateemisen sijasta. Välillä kuvittelen oikeasti olevani vähään analysointiin tyytyväinen suurtalouskokki tai joku muu duunari (EN yleistä, tunnen talkkareita, suurtalouskokkeja, keittäjiä ja siivoajia, sekä tyhmiä että fiksuja) ja ahdistun siitäkin. Mietin, miten tylsää työni olisi. Pää meinasi hajota jo kesätöihin laitosapulaisena. Seitsemän kesää seurakunnilla, siksiköhän musta onkin tullut tällainen o_O Hahahahaaa.  Oltiin Heidin (suomalainen kaverini täällä) kanssa maanantaina kaljalla töiden jälkeen. Nauratti oikein se, kun naurettiin sille, että lapsenhoitokeikan jälkeen paitakin saattaa olla paskassa. Mietin, että ollaan mekin niin tyypillisiä, vaikka minäkin olen niin erikoinen ihminen olevinani. Sitten mietin, että mitä se erikoisuus sitten on. En minä mikään kylähullu kuitenkaan ole, josta kaikki tietävät, että hullu se on. Mutta koen olevani kuitenkin erikoisempi kuin nämä Henkka ja Maukka-vosut täällä, joiden ambitiot ovat tasolla "nopea oppisopimuskoulutus vaikka vaatemyyjäksi, naimisiin, lapsia ja kotiäidiksi". Ja taas yllätän itseni arvostelemasta maailman aliarvostetuinta ammattia, kotiäitiyttä. Mutta onhan mulla nyt, perkele, oikeus mielipiteeseen. Jos sanon, että kotiäitiydessä ei ole paljon kunnianhimoa, niin se on mun mielipide, koska omat tavoitteeni ovat jossain muualla. Jos koko ajan yrittää ottaa huomioon jokaisen asian ihan kaikki puolet, niin mä en ainakaan voisi sanoa enää mitään. Lukuunottamatta faktoja kuten "vesi kiehuu +100 asteessa". Aina pitää perustella ja perustella, ettei vaan loukkaa ketään. Paskanmarjat. Tässä elämässä ei voi välttyä loukkaamasta ihmisiä, vaikka olis kuinka pyhimys.  Pitäisi lopettaa tupakanpoltto. Kun oikein mietin koko ilmiötä, niin eihän siinä ole mitään järkeä. Se on epäterveellistä, kallista, haisee pahalta, hapenottokyky heikkenee, ääni kärsii (ainakin mulla), näyttää tyhmältä, savu kirvelee silmiä ja värjää seinät. Tupakoitsijan keuhkot ovat mustat. Voi luoja, minkä sivun mä löysin hakusanoilla "tupakoitsijan keuhkot": http://www.nettilinja.fi/~ilola/kuvasto1.html. Toisella sivulla (http://www.tohtori.fi/tupakka/009.html) sanotaan:    Lopettamisen vaikutus keuhkoihin   Jo vuorokauden kuluttua tupakoinnin lopettamisesta keuhkot alkavat puhdistua limasta ja muista tupakoinnista aiheutuvista jätteistä. Kolmessa vuorokaudessa keuhkojen toiminta paranee ja hengittäminen tulee helpommaksi sekä keuhkoputkien supistustila helpottaa.   Muutamassa kuukaudessa yskä, vinkuva hengitys ja hengitysvaikeudet vähenevät ja keuhkojen toiminta normalisoituu. Keuhkosyövän riski alkaa pienentyä.   Kymmenessä vuodessa tupakoinnin lopettamisesta riski sairastua keuhkosyöpään on pienentynyt 20 %:iin.   Tupakoinnin lopettaminen on tärkein keuhkoahtaumataudin hoito- ja ehkäisykeino.    En mä Suomessa polttanut näin paljon. Lähinnä luentojen välissä ja viihteellä. Täällä tulee poltettua paljon enemmän, siis ihan kotonakin, kun on tuo parveke ja tietokonehuoneessa on vielä lupa sauhutella sisällä. Pitäisi ottaa itseään niskasta kiinni ja laihduttaa ja lopettaa tupakointi. Hyvä yhdistelmä :&gt; Tiedätte kyllä miksi. Kerron tuloksista, jos jotain tapahtuu ;)  Kello on kohta puoli viisi ja suurin saavutukseni tänään on ollut Catullus-nettisivujen selaaminen. Plärgh. Lähinnä aika on kulunut angstailuun ja Minkan silittelyyn. Olen ihan huono opiskelija, mutta sen olen tiennyt jo monta vuotta ;) Oikeutan laiskuuteni sillä, että minulla on eri tahti kuin muilla, enkä sitä paitsi ihan varmasti ole ainoa tällainen!  Menen tästä katsomaan, saisinko jotain aloitettua.   
     
    
</post>
<date>22,toukokuu,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      mieli: nuutunut musiikki: ssad - axel foley hanurilla tosi huonosti  Tulin tänään kotiin päänsärystä kärsien (prkleen helle ja lähestyvä ukkonen :/) ja katsoin postit ja mitämitä?!?! Postilaatikossa ei ollut enää mun itse väsäämääni (jestas, miten suomalainen sana;) nimilappua, vaan ihan oikea sellainen virallinen kyltti, jossa lukee mun ja Ricon nimet. Tai siis etunimen eka kirjan ja sukunimi. En mä tajua, miten se on siihen yhtäkkiä ilmestynyt. Rico on voinut (vihdoinkin...) ottaa yhteyttä talkkariin ja tilata semmosen kyltin. Tai sit talkkari on itse huomannut asian ja hoitanut hommansa. Täytyy tiedustella Ricolta. Meillä on kyllä niin huippu talkkari, etten ihmettelis, vaikka olis omatoimisesti hoitanut kyltin paikoilleen. Meillä on piha aina viimeisen päälle siisti, nurtsi ajettu, kukat ja puskat ja puut rehottaa jne. Se onkin kyllä aina töissä...  Tuli kyl aika hyvä fiilis tuosta kyltistä. Nyt ei tunnu enää yhtään siltä, että asuisin täällä jotenkin väliaikaisesti. Eipä ole tuntunut vähään aikaan siltä, mutta kyllä tuolla pienellä kyltillä kuitenkin on joku vaikutus :)  Mitäs muuten. Eilen tuli 13 kuukautta täyteen seurustelua ja täällä asumista (mulle siis tätä asumista ;). Rico oli ostanut mulle Zürich by Mike-sarjakuvakirjan. Omistuskirjoituksena "Lucky 13   Täällä on ihan hiton kuuma. Koko viikon pidellyt semmosta +30 lämpötiloja ja aurinko porottaa... Eilen onnistuin polttamaan (taas) kevyesti olkapääni, vähän rinnuksia ja niskaa. Ei tarvii olla kuin vartti auringonpaisteessa ilman aurinkorasvaa, niin käy hullusti vaaleaihoiselle ja tottumattomalle pohjoismaalaiselle. Kissatkin on ihan laiskoina. Päivällä ne ei voi ollenkaan mennä kukkapenkkiin käkkimään ja katselemaan lintuja, kun siihen paistaa aurinko. Shivakin yks päivä kulki surkeana sen edessä, katseli ylöspäin ja maukui valittaen ;)  No niin, Rico tuli kotiin. Se kultabeibe oli eilen käynyt teettämässä sen nimikyltin, kun olin yliopistolla :) Menenpä halimaan sitä!  
     
    
</post>
<date>22,toukokuu,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      mieli: laiska musiikki: ei mitn  Viikonloppu on ollut todella laiska. Siis todellakin. Eilen käytiin aamulla kaupassa, jonka jälkeen minä nukahdin sohvalle Minka vierelläni (http://irc-galleria.net/view.php?nick=sassy_). Rico otti sitten salaa kuvia musta ja kisusta ;) Päivä meni jotenkin hengaillessa, en edes muista meidän tehneen siis mitään. Viime viikko oli niin raskas (opiskelua ja töitä), että ei tullut mistään muusta kuin laiskottelusta mitään...   Illalla mentiin syömään Ricon siskon ja sen poikaystävän Gilbertin luo. Siellä oli myös Ricon äiti ja Gilbertin veli sekä isovanhemmat. Gilbert on siis puoliksi sveitsiläinen ja puoliksi espanjalainen, isovanhemmat ovat espanjalaisia. Ilta oli huikea. Ne Gilbertin isovanhemmat oli tosi rentoja tyyppejä ja hiljaista hetkeä ei tullut :) Ruoka oli aivan hillittömän hyvää (siinä tosin kallistuttiin Italian puoleen, pastaa kun syötiin :) ja kaikilla oli hauskaa. Todellinen perheillallinen. Mulla oli niin hyvä fiilis, kun koko ajan puhuttiin "meidän perheestä" ja Ricon äitikin puhuu meistä kaikista (siis myös musta ja Gilbertistä) aina lapsinaan :) Se tunne vaan on niin lämmin ja hyvä... Olla osa isoa perhettä, jossa ei ole niin merkittävää, onko verisukulainen vai perheeseen ulkopuolelta tullut. Ei tällaista perhefiilistä ollut Suomessa exien kanssa ja niiden perheissä ikinä, vaikka hyvin toimeen tultiinkin. Ei voi muuta kuin olla onnellinen :) Tuskin maltan odottaa torstaita, kun koko perhe taas kokoontuu, tällä kertaa Ricon äidin luo. Ja taas on tiedossa hyvää ruokaa, kun tietää Ricon äidin kokkaustaidot :)  Tänäänkin me ollaan vaan nukuttu. Toisaalta, miksei. Täytyy välillä rentoutuakin. Opiskelijana vaan on aina niin huono omatunto, jos ei joka päivä lue jotain. Mutta eipähän tätä huono omatunnon potemista ole enää jäljellä kuin viitisen vuotta, ehhehe. Ja sen jälkeen voi potea huonoa omatuntoa muista asioista :D  Eilen puhuttiin sormuksista (Gilbert ja Gilbertin isoisä ovat molemmat kultaseppiä) ja puhuttiin sitten myös Ricon kanssa meidän kihla- ja vihkisormuksista, vaikka ei edelleenkään olla mitään päiviä päätetty tms. Tuli puhetta Kalevala-sormuksista ja päätettiin Suomessa katsella vähän niitä. Rico totesi, että voihan se mulle sormuksen ihan muutenkin vaan ostaa, joten saa nyt nähdä, mikä sormus siitä tulee vai tuleeko sormusta ollenkaan :D Pitää olla kiltisti siihen saakka ;)  Eipä tässä ole oikein muuten ihmeitä tapahtunut... 
     
    
</post>
<date>22,toukokuu,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      mieli: rauhaisa musiikki: Sarah Vaughan - Black Coffee  Katselin tänään toista kissaamme, Shivaa, kun se istui parvekkeen pöydällä selkä minuun päin. Sillä on niin kauniit muodot, ihastelin. Kissan kaaria tarkastelin. Ensin pää, sitten lapaluut, sitten masu, sitten jäntevät, aina hyppyyn valmiit reidet. Kaiken huipulla keikkuvat korvat, kaiken huomaava tutkalaitteisto ilman tekniikkaa. On vielä yksi kaari, joka ansaitsee huomion: kissan venyttelyasento, selkä kaarella sen noustua makuulta.  Minka herätti minut tänään syleilemällä oikeaa jalkaani pirun terävät kynnet hellästi ihoon painuneina. Ilmeisesti jalkani on toisinaan neidin tiellä, koska sitä pitää myös purra varovasti. Tai sitten hän haluaa vain leikkiä heti aamutuimaan. Joka tapauksessa heräsin naurahtaen, koska mielestäni jalkaa syleilevä kissa on varsin hellyyttävä ja huvittava asia :D  Eilinen aamupäivä oli tämän viikon paras, otin paljon kuvia lepäävistä kissoistamme (taas huomasin, miten hyvä olo valokuvaamisesta tulee). Vaikka itse sanonkin, niistä tuli kovin suloisia... Tässä yksi kuva Minkasta, kahdesta etujalasta ja takajalan tassusta:    urlLink http://irc-galleria.net/view.php?nick=sassy_=2853984=true   Tämä kuva Shivasta on otettu aikaisemmin tällä viikolla:   urlLink http://irc-galleria.net/view.php?nick=sassy_=2853976=true   Uskoisin, että ne omat kissat on aina niitä ihanimpia kissoja :) Silti olen sitä mieltä, että kissoista on pirun vaikea ottaa ainakin meikäläisen taidoilla hyviä kuvia (siis muutenkin kuin vain omasta mielestä hyviä). Shiva ei meinaa ollenkaan jaksaa pysyä paikoillaan kameran edessä. Eilen kävi sitten vartin kuvaamisen jälkeen jo kynsin kameran kimppuun (huom, ei siis kuvaajan :D) :D Pitäisi sille kotisivun rääpäleelle teettää katti-osio, jonne voisi sitten laittaa kuvia. Muutenkin pitäisi saada sinne osasto muita kuvia varten. Voisin sitten vähentää irc-gallerian käytön minimiin. Ennen kaikkea pitäisi opetella itse säätämään sitä kotisivuansa, ettei olisi aina riippuvainen rakkaan taidoista.  Mulla on suunnaton suomalaisten Sanojen nälkä. Luin tänään yhden artikkelin keskustelutilaisuudesta, jossa oli vieraana Ilpo Tiihonen. Huomasin kaipaavani suomalaista runoutta koko sielullani. Pitää tuoda kaikki runokirjat elokuussa tänne, samoin loput cd:t ja muut kirjat. Kaipaan myös päämäärätöntä suomen kielen sanoilla leikittelyä. Sellaista, mitä harrastimme Lexiluolassa, kun olisi pitänyt istua luennolla. Olen sitä mieltä, että sanojen ei aina tarvitse muodostaa koherentteja tai järkeviä kokonaisuuksia. Miksei voisi toisinaan vain nauttia niiden ulkonäöstä, klangista ja johonkin kontekstiin tungettujen sanojen päättömyydestä? Dadaa ei arvosteta ollenkaan niin korkealle kuin sille kunnia kuuluisi!   En ole aikoihin kuunnellut Sarah Vaughania. Tästä tulee ihan sunnuntaiaamuolo ja se ei ole nyt se olotila mitä haen. Vaikka on tämä "Thinking of You" kyllä aivan ihana... Tuolla naisella oli merkittävä ääni. Hän onneksi kuului siihen etuoikeutettuun sakkiin, jonka taidot tunnustettiin jo hänen elinaikanaan. Toista oli klassisen musiikin valtakaudella. Joku Mozart, pyh! Stravinskin Kevätuhrin esitys meni legendan mukaan rettelöinniksi ja päättyi poliisin paikalletuloon. Itse pidän tuota sinänsä merkittävänä merkkinä ihmiskunnan kyvyttömyydestä. Siinä yleisö näytti oman kyvyttömyytensä omien kokemusten ja tunteiden käsittelyyn, kun jotain uutta läväytetään nenän eteen. Kevätuhri oli varmasti tarpeellinen herätys nukkuvalle yleisölle, joka oli tottunut tulemaan oopperaan näyttäytymään ja nauttimaan tutusta ja turvallisesta oopperasta.  Tällä viikolla on taas särkenyt päätä parina päivänä. Pistän sen paitsi jännittyneiden selkä- ja hartialihasten myös vaihtelevan sään piikkiin. Torstai-iltana särki myös päätä. Mutta silloin tuli todistettua, että lievän päänsäryn voi puhua pois. Oltiin Ricon kanssa sängyssä, menossa nukkumaan ja jokailtaiseen tapaan juttelimme yhden peiton alla, minä rakastavassa kainalossa. Makuuhuoneen valo on tällä hetkellä lämpimän violetti, hämärä. Sanoin, että päätä särkee ja Rico silitti hiuksiani ja koko ihoani. Juttelimme niitä näitä, vaihdoimme suukkoja ja kosketuksia. Vähän ajan päästä, minun ollessani onnellisessa puoli-nirvanassa, hän kysyi, vieläkö päätä särkee. Eihän sitä särkenyt. Epämukavan olon tilalle oli tullut vain lämmin, rakkauden voimistama rauha.   Tiedän olevani menossa naimisiin oikean ihmisen kanssa.
     
    
</post>
</Blog>