<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i have this itch. an itch that can't quite be quieted. i suppose it's so unnerving becauseno one hears it but me -- andbecause i know there is nothing morefor me here.   seattle seems to be nothing more than a holding point (he called it that, and he's right)-- for what?ican muster a guess, but my heart doubts the thoughtsthat spin throughmy head. maybei shouldjust crossmy fingers and hope for better -- something thatdoesn't leave me reeling in the "what if's" and the "if onlys."   he left six years ago...and i got to see him yesterday for the first time. as happy as i am that he was here and as happy asi was with him here, i feel so conflicted. and it's becausehe seemed so conflicted.   yethere i sit, doubting his love for me - and thinking of the easiest waytoleave this life behind and move myself to the other end of the pacific. maybe it'sabout time thatone of ustook a chance on "us"-- compromisedour lives -- even ifthere are no guarantees.  
     

    
</post>
<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ididn't tell him when i called that i had did it -- thati had submitted my resume to several international firms...all with offices in tokyo. i had intended to -- that was the reason behind the call. i was excited. and hopeful.    and scared shitless.    and i suppose i had every reason to be. before i could evenbegin to tell him my news, he gave me the "let's just be friends" speech. i shouldn't have been surprised. i've been on the receiving end of this speech of his several times before. but, that's not the point.   i got a call yesterday. it was from one of the firms that i applied to. they wanted me to come in for an interview. in new york -- where they handle all their hr matters for their international offices. it sounded like a great position and it probably would have been a really great experience. needless to say, i declined the interview.more on that maybe later.  
     

    
</post>
<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i've learned a lot over the years about friends and friendships.there's thiscertain breed of friend -- my favorite -- theones you can pick up with right where you left off, even if it's beenseveral months orseveral years.   a few nights ago i found myself clumsily trying to pick up the pieces of whatI thought was my heart. on a whim, i picked up the phone... "7,8,9...when i'm twenty-one, i'll sixty-nine" (howcan you resist aguy who tells you a silly little rhyme to remember his phone number so you'll actually call?). anyway, he was home. i don't remember when we talked last,but it was as if time had stood still (although, i'm sure he'll tell you that it probably had somethingto do with the fact that i was calling to cry about the same guy i had called to cry about last time - right??).   but that's not the point.   momma always said to tell people you love that you love them, to be thankful for what you've got. so, on thatmushy note, i offer you my thanks... for always being that rock that i can rely on to steady myself against... for being thatvoice of reason even when i'm convinced that i couldn't possibly be any more fucked than ialready am.   you are my forever friend. and how i love you.   p.s.for a good time, call: 789-2169 (when i'm twenty-one, i'll...well, you know the rest).   
     

    
</post>
<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       a guy i know told me once to believe in him. better yet, he told meto believe that hewas a good man. a good manwho would never try to hurt me. this, he said, was all that he couldask for.        oh -- that, and another round of beer for his friends.    and i have since learned my lesson.   neverbelieve a man who feels he needs to commend his own nobleness. he hasotherpriorities. and chances are, his buddies and beer will always come first.  
     

    
</post>
<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    see me?? dead center.   i've always secretly wished i could be a mermaid. 
     

    
</post>
<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i am convinced that he feels heneeds to have his life as simple, void of complications and entanglements of the heart as possible. this is the way he likes it, this is the way he needs it. andhere is why (in hisown words):     I have absolutely no idea what I want to do with the rest of my life. Granted I've been aware of this from day one, but I'm glad for it. And now that I've beaten around the bush, here's what I'm trying to get at; I don't want to be responsible for anyone on this trip. I don't think I could live with the burden of wrecking someone else's ride just because I don't have everything mapped out.   yes, he confirmed, this refers to me -- my ride.      he continues:    You know, I think I've made this point elsewhere in this blog, but I don't care. I'll not deal with lost luggage or bad accommodations.   (ah, yes, maybe i should make a recommendation... maybe when you embark on all subsequent adventures/relationshipsyou shouldprovide a handout -- a brochure, if you will. something that highlights the impending loss of luggage, the inadequate accommodations... hell, if i had gotten one, i would've at least packed light.)   he wraps it all up (and quite poignantly, at that) with:   I don't want to compromise myself .  while i could go on and on and on about this little phrase and the egotistical connotes attached whichveil cold feet, i won't. and perhaps this has and always will be one of my shortcomings. it is sufficient for me to simply walk away. they say old dogs can't, after all, be taught new tricks.   but i digress.   so, we wrap up this conversation that we're having... and he asks if we are cool. "are we cool?" as simple andplainas that. now again, remember my shortcomings... will he ever really know just how much he's hurt me? probably not. will i ever tell him? lash out with rage and disparaging remarks? it's not in me, remember? does he need to know thathe'sseduced me withsix years worth of words? no, he knows that already. does he need to knowhe's beenmy crutch -- the calm voice i hear in my head when my ownis panicked?no,i assume he's figured that one out too.   i'm justnot that variety of girl who needs to lay on the guilt to appease her own demons. i sometimes think that maybe i need to be. especially when it seems he skips out with just his handcarry.   butdespite all this, i feel compelled to extend a semi-apology -- because, as he says,he does not have "everything mapped out"and i thinkhe thought that i expected  him to. this was never my intent and i never expectedhim to have answers to questions that had notyet been formed.  and so, i offer up a truce (along with the truth), that if everI hadany expectations, they were onlythese:   one -- that every word out of your mouth and penned by your handbe spoken in truth  andtwo -- thatif you loved me,you'd not give up on me before we got our chance     
     

    
</post>
<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      one in every five women is raped. any which way you arrange it, you sit me down at a table with four other women and i am that statistic.   not many know this and today i added another person to that list. it was someone that i've wanted to tell for years. it's taken as long as it has, not because i didn't think i'd be able to trust him with it, but because well, it doesn't quite makethe best over-the-phone, let's catch up, tell me what's new in your life conversation...   but that's what it came down to.   i've often wondered how that scene wouldplay out. and i half hopedi'd have hisshoulderto cry on -- a physical one. and i've prayedthat he wouldn't be put offby the words thattumbled from my mouth --that he wouldn't think any less of me.   but that's not the point.   i feel better about some things tonight (i think). i've always felt like i've been carrying aroundthis dirty little secret since the night it happened. i suppose it had a lot to do with the fact that everyone who'sclosest to meknew about it but him.   i know i've come a long way since that night. for one, i know it's not my fault. i've learned to stopblaming myselffor something i was on the receiving end of.   i've learned that i'm no better off in my relationships...i still hurt the ones i should probably beholding on to. i still push away the ones whowant to giveme the worldand i still latch on to the ones on the other side of the world...the ones that give me thepretense of a relationship. the comfort of being loved but at a nice safe distance. the ones that provide a skewed semblance of order.   i've learned that certain things will never change -- that no matter how old you grow, people you  trust  will still hurt and break you.  
     

    
</post>
<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink     bird watching at the waterfront.  
     

    
</post>
<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      single man to share a bed.   must be ambitious, able to make me laugh and not mind a view of the ceiling.  no paperwork certifying  higher education is necessary.  in fact, proof of financial stability not required either.    cooking skills not a necessity, just the ability to distinguish lights from darks in the laundry pile.  must be able to voice opinions and more importantly, form opinions.  wit and charm a plus.  knowledge of the workings of a dictionary and the purpose of a thesaurus greatly appreciated.  must be articulate and a captivating storyteller.  metrosexuals and men who tend to think they are prettier than women need not apply.  must be sympathetic (at times) and a compassionate listener (when needed).  must adore your mother.    please call to schedule interview (all applicants subject to rigorous screening process).    
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      he swears he can type 60 wpm.    couldn't resist it, ihad to tease him - how'd you get picked tobe the typing teacher...you evenknow how to type? i mean, really - type??using all ten fingers?! you sure?    he's self taught, he says.    picked it up emailing my ass so often after i moved away. and when his studentsask where he learned to type, hetells them about me.   and i can't help butlove that i am the reason behind it all.    
     

    
</post>
<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      this seems to fit so perfectly these days:    Was it you who spoke the words that things would happen but not to me  Oh things are gonna happen naturally  And i'mtaking your advice I'm looking on the bright side  And balancing the whole thing  But often times those words get tangled up in lines  And the bright lights turn to night  Until the dawn it brings  A little bird who'll sing about the magic that was you and me    Cause you and I both loved  What you and I spoke of  and othersjust readof    Others onlyread of the love that I love    See I'm all about them words  Over numbers, unencumbered numbered words  Hundreds of pages, pages, pages forwards  Are More words then I had ever heard and I feel so alive  Now you and I, you and I  Not so little you and I anymore  And with this silence brings a moral story  more importantly evolving is the glory of a boy    cause you and I both loved what you and I spoke of  and others just read of and if you could see me now, well then i'm almost finally out of...    I'm almost finally, finally free    and it's okay if you have togo away  just remember the telephone works both ways  but if I never ever hear it ring  if nothing else I'll think the bells inside  have finally found you someone else and that's okay  cause I'll remember everything you sang    cause you and I both loved what you and I spoke of  and others just read of and if you could see me now,  well I'malmost finally out of words.    
     

    
</post>
<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      we are standing in the middle of the soda section at the grocery store. i have her convinced that i had them specially made just for her.  she wants them all. every can and every bottle. she can hide them under her bed, she says (with her pet turtle).she insists that if we don't buy them all now they'll run out. besidesauntie mish, she wines, you said it was special and specialmeans not forever.   so we compromise.   i dig out my cell and i make a call:   me: ummm, yes, hello...is this Mr. Sodaman?? it is?? oh good! hi! this is auntie mish. listen, i need a favor. about this special soda deal i made with you... yes, that's right,the Squirt soda. well... you see, i need to make sure that you don't stop making thisstuff. what?? a special?? no, no,i want it made forthe next five years. yes, five!! yes,just for this store, just for TheQFC.   squirt:The Safeway Auntie Mish!! We're not at the QFC!! Auntie Miiiiish!!   me: oh!!!! Mr. Sodaman?? not the QFC!!! it's The Safeway. no, no, not all theSafeways...just  TheSafeway . oh, ok.good. you got all that?? ok. thanks so much. yes, yes,ok. sure, yes. that's fine....just send me the bill.   my little  call  has turned her into thehappiest and giggliestgirl in the world. as she skips through the store, people turn and tell me how beautiful my daughter is, how she looks just like me. squirt and i just laugh, we don't bother to correct them.   she is five now. she insists sheis much tooold to be called neni  anymore.so inamed her squirt. and it just kind of stuck.   her real name isKandace Mae.she tells me she wishes ithad been  Christina   AguilleraPearl Mae Artero  instead.after she saves three more quarters (she already has two), she says she will go to the storeto see about buying herselfa newname.she wants to know if i'll take her --after all, shetells me, i'm a goodpickerofnames.    *Squirt dancing in her halloween costume*   urlLink       
     

    
</post>
<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey brodie. okay. i put all the posts on this one page. most recent is at the top (obviously). so, if you'd like, you can begin with the oldest at the bottom and work your way up. hope this is less confusing. love you. 
     

    
</post>
<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i need a change; i've outgrown seattle.  well, maybe that's a bit much. maybe it's more that seams are being stretched than anything else. seams that are very dangerously close to bursting open. maybe it's that i am now kicking myself in the ass for not going on that interview.  if i could up and leave and make a change, a real change, here is what i'd do: i'd sell my car, i'd use that money to pay off my bills, i'd put my college loan in deferment, sell everything i own and mail home (guam home) anything of real value that i might want again someday (i.e., books, pictures and maybe a vibe). then i'd buy a ticket to somewhere where they don't speak english, where i'd need a calculator to figure out the exchange rate and where i don't know a single soul (okay, one person would be okay, but definitely not more than two). i'd learn their language, eat their food, love their men and then just before the seams started to stretch again, i'd pick a border (or ocean) and cross it.  it just seems so perfect.  i don't know where i'd start. maybe in spain or greece. or london. maybe morocco or even india. or thailand or japan. or even somewhere in the pacific.  it just seems too perfect.  if you could change your life tomorrow, what would you do? 
     

    
</post>
<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i was recently told by a certain man i know that he once suspected me of slapping tuna (so terribly phrased, forgive me).   and since then, i just have not been able to stop slapping, i mean laughing.  i am amused at the preposterousness of it all.  hopefully  she  is too.  as a side note, i think he secretly hoped it was true so he could get in on the action...or at least watch.  this is where i disappoint -- i love the feel of it in my mouth much too much to ever stray. 
     

    
</post>
</Blog>