<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Haha alright, now, I don't know when he'll be reading this, but he'll be very happy when he does. Jaime, I had a dream about YOU last night, but it was soooo random!  We were at school, but it felt like the summer. As if we weren't supposed to be there, but we were for whatever. I was with Jaime, and I think Austin. Jaime, you took us to your house which happened to by right by the school, and it ws a small street that sorta circled at the end (like mine, so you get the picture) but these houses were HUGE, friggin massive. So, we went in your house and there was a very long bench in the middle of the hall and your mom and dad were there. Your mom was standing by a fire, or a cooking pot (i cant remeber) and your dad was holding a classical guitar. Actually, he was playing it. The three of us sat down on the bench and listen to your dad play, I was really impessed beacuse he was good. After a few minutes we had to go, and your mom told me I should come back again at 9:30, when I can hear him play longer. I guess we walked in on him playing, and he had been playing for a while already.. anyway, it was strange. So we leave. It may have been at this point where I woke up. If not, well whatever. Anyway, I did go back at 9:30 and when I went into the house the long bench as filled with guys, and guitars! Each guitar was different though. But it was so cool, all the guys were soo good looking, and I was in heaven. I sat down where there was some room, and I just basically talked to all the guys and asked them about their guitars. I remeber flirting with them to, oh I felt so good in the dream. lol  OK that's basically it. I cant remeber what happened after the guys. Anyway, crazzyness, can't wait to see what dream I have tonight! cheers 
    
</post>
<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night's dream was a little more dark. Although I can't remeber a lot of it. I woke up a number of times, but I remeber the first dream I had, I, uuuhg it was strange, I remeber seing Tom and Ewen going to the movies, that's about it. lol but then the last dream I had was everyone in the class going out to war in the disguise of characters from Warcraft. It was so crazy.  
    
</post>
<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Welcome to my first dream recording! MWAHAHA The dream I had last night was a happy one, and I talked to an old friend. Ok so let's just begin before I forget it.  I was at school, and it was winter. I was starting to walk up the hill but my cell rang. I picked it up, and wtf it was Corum! I haven't talked to him for sooo long, and it was him! I guess the wold I was living in was a lot different then what I live now... sigh. Alright, so I satrt talking to him, butnow I'm walking back towards the school, and random! Mitchell is in a car with a bunch of older guys saying, 'I can't give you a ride!' Okay... dammit. I'm still on the phone with Corum, but then all of a suddon I slip on the ice and my phone flies into the air and wham, on the groud. I reached for it, and I heard someone talking, but it was my dad. I told him I needed a ride and he said sure. I wanted to keep talking to Corum so I tried finding his number in my recent callers. I friend sending him a messagebut then, this picture showed up on my phoneand said I coudn't send him a message because he was out west!! Ok..... but I felt so special that he called me from all the way out west... hehe Then I woke up.  Next time I fell a sleep I can't remeber where I was, I think it had something to do with my previous dream, but I ended up wtih colourful hair and I told my mom not to kill me. heh.  My last dream was a really weird dejavu. I was at Kira's house again like I was on Wednesday. We were swimming and diving for pennies. I remeber when were actually doing it I did so baddly because my goggles kept filly up with water and I really can't holf my breath for that long. Plus Kira is a swimmer. lol Anyway, I remeber the last time we went diving, we didn't really pick up all the pennies. We kept having to dive for them and actually look for them. So, in this dream, I was just at her house diving. I was under water and I actually found some of the pennies we forgot, but as I went to pick them up, more kept appearing! But it was so cool, I could hold my breath for a lot longer.. It's like, omg I was KIRA IN MY DREAM!!! AHHHHHHHHHHHHHH   hokayeverybady, that was last nights dream. Man, I CAN'T wait to fall asleep tonight!!!! 
    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
           Coming Friday, July 23rd   
</post>
</Blog>