<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It was the first time I've seen you since the incident, I must say you've changed in this past month. Your eyes, they look so drowned, you look so exhausted and when you were sleeping, God, I wanted to make it better, because I know something was bothering you, you weren't yourself, did I know you as yourself? All these thoughts cascading through my mind and in an instant everything has and will change again so I know not what to feel. For a split second in my insanity I can almost pick up your scent, I can almost feel you breathing again. Then reality takes hold once again and I am left with these thoughts that I  am  happy now and that I  did  get what I wanted and just to  give up  on hopeless dreams and romances because nothing's the same when you've got it we just throw away.  So I leave you with this. You are in my mind and I care for you always, and I'm a fool for my thoughts and my actions. Pitty...
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       The Examination of Sarah Good    irony of the day:  So, back when the Salem Witch Trials were occuring, everyone was claiming outragous sights of "witchcraft" and blaming them on so called "witches". They believed these "witches" were making deals with the devil so they could have the ability to perform MAGIC. As believable as that sounds, it was recently discovered that in the Salem area, there were crops found with this horrific mold growing on them. Something else was also discovered..it appears that there was a drug in the mold [the same drug found in ACID]. So they most likely weren't seeing witches and magical things...they were  trippin'.. 
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I'm on fire   Inhale. Forget the pain. Exhale. Jealousy withers away. Everything is "little" when we want it to be. Say it just to downsize me. The lackluster of a word when it is like a record. over and over and over you say..
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Jane says: I've never been in love.. I don't know what it means.. I only know they  waaant  mee   Mmm. It's been an all-around terrific day. Plus I ate Chick-fil-A for lunch.  Nothing like winter. Wake up early, go to a set-destination, smokin' ciggarettes and talking about the impossible, livin' the impossible, friends are *new age hippies*, these are the days. Yes, these are the days.  I have this feeling of utter happiness, swallowing me up and I'm floating higher and higher. NoN-Induced High...
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       2 AM Scribbles..   T here is nothing I find more beautiful than these dead hours. Soon before the sun will rise, early morning, but the stars have yet to stop shining. To my eyes, it is still dusk. All the peace, all the tranquility in the world that we have searched for all these years has been hidden in this paradise aglow forgoing dawn.   L ightning. This scene is now chaotic, full of storm and rain, ah, to my ears it is soothing and magnifiscent. A particular dream of mine: to be in love under this inclusive blanket of emptiness that makes us feel so absolute.   O ne day, let everyone witness this perfection.  Heaven is on earth when no one is watching... 
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       No Missouri.  My dad is proud to be my dad because when I found out, I didn't say "YES" as expected, I asked if he was okay. He told me he loved me, it was a "character judging moment" as he said. Sometimes parents aren't cool and you think they just don't understand, like they just don't care..but at that very moment, I knew that my dad does care. And he just wants the best for me. [ although i'll never admit that to them. ]  *All her dreams are falling from the sky right in front of her eyes*  --I LovE yOU ToO ZAcH
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Fucking Missouri. I'm NOT going. NO. I fucking refuse. GOD forbid I stay in one place for more than five fucking years.. I look around, all these people are childhood friends, they've grown up together, but I don't HAVE that because MY dad makes me move around all the country looking for more money. Money this, money that. Is MONEY really the answer? I mean I know we need to pay our bills for the house and cars and all, but can't we get a  smaller  house? do we have to have 9874359873 square feet? i dont WANT to start over. they're like "it'll be hard for Sam too" SAM is EIGHT YEARS OLD...the older you get the stronger bonds you make with people, it's not going to be hard for him, he'll play with anyone. but i already have my place in highschool, in society, in life and i don't want to have to start over..      I love all you guys, I swear to God I do..
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       black-haired flamingo dancer  [show me some of that  spanish  dancing]  hazy skies, all our lies swollen eyes, broken cries these lullabies, as my heart dies the asphault fries say your goodbyes no more tries just watch the *moon rise*  ------------------------------------------------  sedated is my mind. what a  mellow  feeling. nothing to criticize. nothing to be worked up about. ~I used to think I lived for this         NOW I can't be sure I try to shake this lonliness            this pessimist       constant persist  Insist on...everything    I feel happy    and I'm all mixed up WALK...crashing into you    breaking a w a y from me                                from everything  (I lived in you for a moment)
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       An irresponsible kiss on the lips, that's what my mother would say  wondering life's reasoning perhaps we're living in denial days full of hallucinating we've felt this way for a while...
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ..no motivation to write   i just wrote that so you'd all know you stole my motivation.  
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      How perfect would this world be if only  we  determined the error of our own ways. I think we'd all be a little less stressed.     Happy New Years I'm babysitting And making a hundred and so dollars :0
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       "I can't see nothing, nothing 'round here..."   Passed out and forgot my name last night I dont think "it's going to be alright." No, no not at all. "I will fall, I will fall.." "I want to be alive," the man sings Staring at this tattered ring. Time and time again, I ask myself this can't be good for my health. And all I want, is in the pouring rain you to come and act insane Tell me I'm pretty and you made a mistake and that tears rolling down your cheek aren't so fake.  My  impetuous  wishes your 'mean nothing' kisses  watch me fade away...
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay, how about everyone gets off my ass about the things I feel. I'm sorry that I care about someone that I'm "not supposed to", I'm sorry that I messed something up and that I lost someone that was very important to me in my life, I'm sorry that I'm upset and that everyone around me seems to be able to justify feelings otherwise, but for now, I am hurt. And I don't feel like taking anything from anyone, so I'll just curl up into my little 'lonely girl' corner while ya'll bitch about me not having the right to feel this way until I've had my time to get over it...  If you think it's stupid or ridiculous or a waste of my time to feel sorry for myself or complain about my own pain then DoNt read what I write. This is how I vent, this is my escape from the stupid judgemental world we're all so wrapped up in, and I'm not about to let that change.  ::tells herself:: this will go away, this will all go away soon.  
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Stayed up till 6, only to wake at 11 with the news: "I don't think it would work out between us, Bre"   Well, I'm glad that's off your shoulders, I'm pretty sure it was there all along I just hope everything goes as fucking plan. While I lay here, lifeless and float away you'll find me dead in the fucking sand.  Self-medicate till you go away it won't be hard to find a replacement. Just one that means the same, feels the same. And even though I fucking hate you, I'll always love the memories [the ones you fucking stepped on today]  So good luck with your fucking fill-in I hope you find shit I couldn't give and while you suck face and fuck the days away I'll be dying to live..   By the way, I give up on my 'masterpiece' it would've been stupid. 
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Chris is on his way! On his way to my house today! Hey!  good day, bad day. i hate youuuuuuu  boy .
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      All is lost with you, so in the mean time I will do something productive.  I am creating something, for all of you. Because I love you all so much and I want you to know how beautifully I see you. You guys mean the world to me, and I love the things you say.  Friends, leave your responses on my tagboard or send them via AIM. LooOOve Yoouu GUyys.     If you could give me a quote, a meaningful outlook on Life, Love or just Experiences in general,  [you pick which one]  What would it be? 
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This love is a love that branches off, apparently, and I am left at your will. Kiss me and tell me it's over between the two of you or drug me up and leave me crying. At least I'll be floating until I come down. At which time I'll ask you again to tell me what I wanna hear, c'mon baby whisper in my eeeaaar. 	 Straight from my heart to Cory. Via Codine. 
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      PiNK HAiR  semi-permanent. and i loooove it. it's on the tips and i streaked it a little. that's about the highlight of these past few days. i'm waiting for a decision. i'm feeling like second-best. i'm feeling like something i want more than ever is right in front of me and i'm touching it, but it's hands go elsewhere.  Oi. I need a shopping trip. I need some new substance.
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       This stupid JAgGeD PiLL stuck to my throat, polluting my stomach, filling me to the top.   A few minutes, I feel it sinking, into my blood to rot away or whatever makes it feel good.  A few more, the time is really ticking. So desperately obvious, but at least I feel fine. Yeah, I'll be fine in no time at this rate..  Almost an hour, my god what have I done. This fucking substance, does me no good what so ever. Alone and shaking. You couldn't help but crack a smile at this. A stupid girl takes stupid pills cause of one stupid kiss. No, it's more than that. 6 months I'll miss.   "You can't make them want you, they're all just laughing"  --Taking Back Sunday. Oooh how I love those boys. Mmmm, mmm.
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       You kissed me like you meant it.. And I  know , that you meant it..   Love takes its toll, that's for sure. Never wanted this much, you never wanted more. Now all the sudden everything's gone and all we have left are some stupid songs. I can't take this for long.  When you love someone a choice like this shouldn't be so hard A caring person like you, it's difficult But the Fact still stands, if you Wanted to be with ME..and not anyone else..you WouLD.  I think I know your answer, already How else can you explain the tears rolling down your cheeks You want her, you don't want to hurt me.  Understanding, I wish I could be.  Take this fucking gun and  kill me please. 
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       More and more confusion everyday, when will this just  go away ? 
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       It's been  too  long.   My old friend, we've both changed so much. I like your beard and the way you laugh. Thanks for coming to see me, let's not let time get between us again.  Aye. Last evening, I was actually happy for a few hours. Props to:  One Derek. One Sarah. One Meg.  I love you guyssssss   [I don't know what to think of  you . You tell me one thing, you do another. If you don't want to see me, that's fine but don't pretend I'm fucking blind.]
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I love you TBS, you have the perfect words for a bitter little girls heart to relate to..   And I'm not so sure If I'm sure of anything anymore..  You're so guilty it's disgusting She's been sneaking underneath your sheets and your hands have been in places that they probably shouldn't go but don't worry, sweetie 'cause i already know.  Regardless, my pictures, they don't line your mirror. Regardless, you know that I'll still wait for your call.   ::sigh:: 
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ~Look at you, keep smiling~  Merry Christmas. Thank you for calling, though I don't know whether to feel at ease or restless as usual. I do love you. I'm sorry for the hurt I've caused, I knew not of how that felt until now. And I never meant to, I care..so much. If things are over, I promise to remember the great things, there were so many things I loved. I had many firsts with you and I wouldn't of chosen any other person to share them with. You've taught me so much..about my self, about others. If you don't mind, I have so much more to learn. This will either come across as really lame or really caring and sweet, hopefully the latter of the two.   ::playing the fool::   Stole my words and used 'em for profit The things I believe belong to me.
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       A tribute to things lost:  Behind drunken eyes, pursed lips I never thought it'd come to this.  A friends house, or getting high stay up late, the clouds fly by.  You we(a)re my star. A little girl scared to have come so far.  Of all of them, you were my favorite feel. It took something like this to make it real.  And though I can't go back, I hate some things I've done. I still want to be good for you, what light will I have without my sun?  
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have deleted an entry. I do not hate anyone that I have not had the chance to meet. That is obsurd. I do not even hate the other, who I have known for so long, I hate what he did. I hate the way he made me feel. I hate feeling jealous of something I know not of. I hate being clueless to what's going on, and furthermore I hate making myself pull away from the world because I am too hurt and scarred to look anyone in the eye right now and be decent with them. My body is restless with all this envy and hate and betrayed feelings inside of it, I shake at the very thought of you. A dream haunting me over and over. But I do not hate  them . How immature would I be. The fact of the matter is that I'm just a little teenage girl. I don't know how I feel. I just take 'em as they come and I realize that that's just not good enough for the world. But I will not try and change myself. Only time can change all of this, and I am willing to wait.  Oi. What a week. What a Christmas. I love all of my friends. Thank you for the advice and love you've given me. I don't know where I'd be right now without it, but probably not somewhere nice. Merry Christmas. Tell yourself "It could always get worse. If not, then it  has  to get better"
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A little sleepless. I dare not close my eyes, everytime I do so I see this image in my mind you made for me. I thought I was okay to write, but I shouldn't do this. Hateful, spiteful words will spill from these lips once so poisoned by your own.  Dead. Empty. Fin.
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am nothing now. Sitting in white. There is no color, no pigment. The only hint of a sound comes from an unknown faucet. Drip, dripping. Dripping blood from my vains filling this void with what once made my very heart beat. Now I stare blank. I dare not move, the arrows are pointed directly at my chest. I only gaze, blink, barely breathing. An arrow flies at me, pinning my arm to the wall (an apple in my mouth, a target painted on my body). I do not flinch, for I have felt this sting before. The urge, an urge to see the stars is quickly shattered with another pointed blow, this one to my leg. I am seeing a pattern now, they'll kill me slowly, I am their pig. Another arrow is let loose from the bows, then another and another until my body lies limp. This deathe sentense is a beautiful one. Here I am, these things killing me are the only things keeping me held together, as I look at my murderers, their eyes cold and black, my sickened face mirrored in their eyes, these are those I have loved...
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       An infidelity, to say the least..   And as they sat, alone [/ together] under the infinity of stars, she felt  whole , and wondered if he could ever feel it again..
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I feel drained.  I'm happy, but I feel empty, tired, everything is so relentless. I just want a break.  Can't anyone see that all I need is a TIME-OUT. Away from everything? Christmas isn't supposed to feel stressful and be filled with heartache. It doesn't even feel like Christmas time. Where's the spirit and the love?  I used to count the days, how many is it again...
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       You can lose yourself in your courage..  If not now, when?    Wrapping around an old little finger The tree's swaying, this will be a good winter. Everyone is on the go Spending money here and there Anything to show how they truly care. Stress in place of bliss. Well, I'M enjoying the scenery A ciggarette in hand, remembering the good times.  Let's make these Nights we'll never forget...
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm feeling very PINK today. Yes, yes. So pink, infact that my hair is pink. Too bad 'tis only temporary. That could aaall very well change. In due time. In due time.  Going to a skate park in an Abercrombie jacket.      ::thEy loVe yoU::  Kisses. And lots of 'em.
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       "Sweat'n for the Oldies" yes, an  ooooold  one:   Saturday, June 21, 2003 I am hanging suspended in midair. Like a puppet, my arms and legs dangle loosely. Exhaustion drags down my eyebrows and the corners of my mouth. Darkness flows around the contours of my body, avoiding my skin, It seems that nothing wants to touch me. In an instant, my left arm whips out. My right leg kicks at the emptiness. All of a sudden, my arms and legs begin to scramble frantically. My lips and eyebrows turn upward, energized. Around and around I twirl until the darkness begins to whirl with me, losing its round shape, oozing, splashing, jetting me forth. In the soft light of morning, I am born. Dancing through the air, my movements are delicate and graceful. A welcoming sparrow pecks me on the cheek. A butterfly caresses my lips with its wings. Gnats, June bugs, and dragonflies dip down to taste the sweetness of my skin. I am wrapped in wings. It seems that everything longs to be near me.
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You fire your loaded gun. I am lying naked, empty on the cold, cold ground. 
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Tumbling realities.. when all you hoped for lies shattered on the floor when you ask your one-way questions and feel the empty rising. it's not at all surprising to know everything's melting and you can't do a thing and the one you want to breathe for can't give you  any thing.
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       All the lonely people, where do they all come from?...  Yellow Submarine-- watched it today. Muy bueno.  Don't beg, it takes away from your boyish charm. 
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      FREEEEdom of SPeech: She smokes and  announces  it to the room! What a stupid little girl. How dare her say a word! We all know she CrAaAves attention. And the world needs  my  opinion. And the world cares about  my  opinion. And the world sure does give a FUCK about  my  opinion.
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       There's a pain in my stomach, and a hazy rain. And I stumble to get myself up again...  Today, Yesterday. Breathtakingly crude. I don't understand. I don't see why Josh had to go. I want him to stay here, we had so much fun, he was always there. Smoking, talking about our crazy things. Sitting on Derek's backporch sharing a ciggarette enjoying life and all at the same time hating it. But it was cool, cause we all did together. It was in unison, a joint effort.  A good friend.  "CH". "You  would  say that." Love you, kid.
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       The look on your face as you threw our addictions at me  Screaming through your eyes, and I knew that you hate me. Begging for a reply, locked myself away calmly. Try and bring me down, I feel this is the right way. You don't know how difficult it was today.  I'm sick of fucking rhyming and everything is out of tune. So go to hell, you fucking jerk..and blah blah blah...um, June.      Blasted poets.
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       The nightingales are coming out..  What a way to celebrate Christmas. Alone. At least I'm with friends and I haven't ruined absolutely  everything , I love you guys. I love you Zachy. I love you Sarah and Ally and Meg. I love you Cory and Steven and ...and well everyone else along the way. You guys make me so happy and ..And I don't ever want that to change, no matter what else happens [or doesn't happen]. I don't ever want my friends to be sad, or down, and just..you all mean the world to me. [Even those of you that aren't supposed to.]  THank you, and goodnight.
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      just going through a few old journal entries from a few months ago..  I can honestly say i was happy for a while. Something about you makes thoughts rage through my head and I can't stop hearing beautiful words. Damnitt, I'm falling into a pit again. Somebody pull me out..wait..no I want to stay for a while  this is totally one-sided and I'm wasting my time..
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       "hello beautiful"  (i need this)   but she said not a word, just smiled. and she thought he knew just what that smile meant, when she leaned back on him (a night well spent) but i think it was the moment and nothing more at all shes still thinking over and over: "I will FALL. I will FALL."
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        TOOL   So familiar and overwhelmingly warm This one, this form I hold now. Embracing you, this reality here, This one, this form I hold now, so Wide eyed and hopeful. Wide eyed and hopefully wild.  We barely remember what came before this precious moment, Choosing to be here right now. Hold on, stay inside... This body holding me, reminding me that I am not alone in This body makes me feel eternal. All this pain is an illusion. 
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I like your face  So, everything's a daze I've been here before I promised not to look back  [but I like it]  I hope I do well at this secret game I play Keeping the pieces seperated ...or trying anyway  ::sigh:: Never wanting you to leave..
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Play it again, Love.  this web you're spinning Subconcious Devil. with your sweet eyes rough hands  Teach me immunity from this poison lethal to me. Make me oblivious to this connection of we. Lead me not toward the darkness of you I know I will FALL    *      I know I will FALL [when I cannot see]  Yes, toxicity and everyone loves the stars. It's something unoriginal, a feeling so far. And as I reach for them, you laugh in my face 'cause I'll never make it make it away from this place.  But you, you have touched them many, many a time. And what once was a beauty seems not so devine. Still you discard his romance holding me to the ground singing, your pretty voice such a pretty sound..  But you weren't singing for me that, I see clear. For we'll never relive our old affairs, my dear. 
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       A Kade.  He's losing faith in the stars what has this world fallen to? A beautiful boy with a beautiful heart. How dare you, hot sun, corrupt his fine eyes. Don't you know the moonlight is his heaven in disguise.
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Is this a bad night or am I just dying? We got in a fight cause he got caught lying. And all this time we gave up trying. For what? Who's to say, who's denying that what we had is multiplying? What are these curious thoughts signifying? And how much time is worth your buying when all she does is sit while crying? Things would be fine, yes, things would be flying. And here I sit, "sighs" and "why" ing..  [Late and no one is awake. Why am I so wired? 'Tis another NoNiNdUcED high I have not felt in a while, not the same as the others, no. I dislike(/enjoy) these omens. I do not wish(/ I beg) for things to happen. What a shady girl, what a shady facade. That is, if everyone didn't expect just that(+ a little more) of her..
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       These grass stains on my knees, they won't mean a thing..  True, young boys must grow into big boys, but not through corruption, I don't think so anyway. It's getting late and I need some sleep, I just thought I'd put my two cents in before bed.  Oh, and I was  so  happy to see you two. Oh, and jealousy is  stupid , concentrate on the bliss.
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      IF I'M JUST BAD NEWS..THEN YOU'RE A LIAR!!  urlLink    urlLink audio post  powered by  urlLink audblog 
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      When I smell you I think of midnight where things are done that nobody knows cause if they did they'd die to forget
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       how's  that  for controversy?   I LOVE people's petty minds. The way we think amuses me oh so dearly. Our train of thought goes as follows: 1- We see a boy and girl, linked arms walking down the hallway. 2- The boy walks the girl to her classroom and they stand outside for a while chatting before the bell. 3- We immediatly invent this supposed relationship between the two of them. [I mean, c'mon. What members of the opposite sex link arms and walk eachother to class if they aren't dating!] 4- We proceed to go as far as to  ask  if they are dating.  ::whistles::...
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Tell me your secrets Ask me your questions You don't know how  lovely  you are...    ::sigh:: Love. Love is a many, splendid thing. Waiting, it seems as if we're always waiting for Love to come to our door in the pouring rain and kiss us on the lips and explain where it's been all our lives. But that's not how it is, society has created this ideality of what we are supposed to feel, how Love is supposed to be. This is the very thing that is so confusing about Love. It comes in many ways, many forms. It's not like the movies or storytales. Love continues to change for everyone that endures it. Sometimes it's cold. Sometimes you're left alone without them. It is never all smiles all the time, and what makes it that much more splendid, the ones that can make it, the ones that can live through the bad and learn to focus on the laughter, well, I believe that that is the most beautiful accomplishment in the world. Maybe all we need is not love. Maybe two people cannot live off of eachother's air, and if there is no ideal lifestyle in place, there can be no successful Love. But this is not my way of thinking. I'd like to believe that two in love can live somewhere far, far away. Living only for their other's smile, only for their voice, only to make their other's life worth.   Mmm, picture it. We're under the sun, on a towel on the beach somewhere in Cali. The water's beautiful, just look how everyone's smiling. I look over and so are you, and I wouldn't rather be anywhere else in the world.  That's how it feels everytime. That's how I always want it to feel. Sincerely,  the Hopeless Romantic. 
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Where is the kid with the chemicals? I've got a hunger that I can't seem to get full I need some meaning I can memorize   And the phone's ringing and the band's leaving Let's just keep touching, let's just keep, keep singing. But you, but you write such pretty words But life's no storybook Love's an excuse to get hurt And to hurt, do you like to hurt? I do, I do, then hurt me.  Hm. Around 12 days left. As much as I hate to say this  [it's exactly what they want me to say]  Don't skip school, it isn't worth it.  Oh, and apparently, I am a little girl because I don't like authority. I like to make my own decisions and I don't believe in anyone looking down on me, telling me what I should and shouldn't do. I have common sense, I have human decency, I know what's right and wrong and it should be my prerogative to decide whether I wish to 'conform' or not. See, these are the thoughts that get me in trouble. 'Cause when I'm in a bad mood, it's me against the world and I could give a fuck about any other person that came along. So how do you change your beliefs if you still believe them? ALL I know is that I cannot be grounded anymore. Not only is it affecting my home life and my friendships..it's affecting my relationship and that just won't fly.   All your love, all your love is gone, so sing a lonely song.. 
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I drove my two favorite [drunken] boys home this evening. 'Twas a jolly good time, I love them so very very much. Hopefully tomorrow will be as great as today.  "It's a perfect kind of love"   Dear Cuteboy Cory, (via Brand New)  I'm sinking like a stone in the sea. I'm burning like a bridge for your body.   Dear Zachy-poop,  No dirty girls!!!!!   Love, Bree. 
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       bitches will be bitches hooooes will be hooooes  like you.   [thank you, that is all :)] 
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       She was a sour girl the day that I met her..   Tears on my cheek 'cause I think I love you too much And she tries to explain to me how it happened Stabbing, slit all my veins open, I'm right here bleeding infront of e v e r y o n e Don't you think this is fun?  Did you say this to her? Did you touch her like this?  I swear to God this is eating me alive. I try not to dwell on what they say but it's EVERY DAY.  [I love you..]
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       THE MARS VOLTA!   Is it unhealthy to sit in the same place for over 4 hours straight? Like a computer? Or for that matter, a home? No, no I don't think so, sounds to me like a waste of a perfectly good Saturday. Yes, yes indeed.  Waiting for that boy to come over, seems like I'm constantly waiting for something or another. Blah blah blah wait wait wait. You'd think with the amount of waiting I endure that I'd acquire some sort of patience, ah, but this is not the case! No patience what-so-ever. And we are out of Coke so I am forced upon Sprite. Boo Sprite. I think if Sarah was here she'd throw a fit.  In any case, this was my day, slow, boring, yada. Tomorrow will be filled with church, ciggarettes, [i like those words next to eachother, muaha] the boys, and fun fun fun!   Sing me something pretty I'll watch your lips part in the dark I want a sunset serenade come steal my heart.. 
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I can't imagine all the people that you know and the places that you go when the lights are turned down low..   Two little names on a wall and I fall to pieces. I hate to be rational, but it was just a reality-check. I mean, right there in front of everyone, everyone fucking saw me when I saw it, and I could feel him holding his breath wishing I didn't, but I did. And I wonder if it will ever go away? Will this be in my head forever? Always looking over my shoulder, always feeling 2nd best...   It's to dying in another's arms and why I had to try it.. 
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Mmmm. Taken.
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       YOUR AURA IS PURPLE!   With you one look, just one look and  everything  is s  ha   TT  e r ed..  Mmm. I realize I don't explain things much. That's not a very good habit to be forming, now is it? Parents can be ruthless, completely unbarable for no apparent reason whatsoever other than to aggrivate you. Spending about 5 hours on worthless cleaning is not the way to go, I wouldn't recommend it at all, at all.  Aaand then there's something I've been meaning to write. Lately I've been slightly..okay a little more than slight..insecure about a few things. This feeling is completely rubbish and I do not condone it! But in any case, it is still there and I would ask of you not to frown upon it as much due to the circumstances. *Speaking of those circumstances, it's just difficult, okay? Being with you..which is spectacular..and knowing that you have done some of the same things with her, said some of the same things.. it's just literally heartbreaking, maybe it'll feel that way forever..it's just not a comfortable situation and I do not want to think about it. So in the mean time I shall force it out of my head as best as possible and try and avoid conversation about such things.  That is all for now.  --She kissed as if she, alone, could forge the signature of the sun-- And I love you..
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       "I'm gonna make your toes curl"   Amazingly fantabulous. And that's THAT! I love yoooou   We live in a beautiful world... 
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I guess I'm going to be the jealous one, standing aside... Just so scared this isn't going to work..
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      There's talk that in the future, every U.S. resident will have a National ID Card with an individual National ID Number, which will have all your personal information stored on it.   A way to crack down on terrorism or an excuse to put Big Brother in office? You decide.   Operator : "Thank you for calling Pizza Hut. May I have your national ID number?" Customer: "Hi, I'd like to place an order."  Operator : "May I have your NIDN first, sir?" Customer: "My National ID Number, yeah, hold on, eh, it's 6102049998-4554610."  Operator : "Thank you, Mr. Sheehan, 1742 Meadowland Drive, phone number 494-2366. Your office number over at Midtown Insurance is 745-2302 and your cell number's 266-2566 . That's you?" Customer: "Where d'ya get all this information?"  Operator : "We're wired into the system, sir." Customer: (Sighs) "Oh, well, I'd like to order a couple of your All-Meat Special pizzas."  Operator : "I don't think that's a good idea, sir." Customer: "Whaddya mean?"  Operator : "Sir, your medical records indicate that you've got very high blood pressure and extremely high cholesterol. Your Private Health Care provider won't allow such an unhealthy choice." Customer: "Damn. What do you recommend, then?"  Operator : "You might try our low-fat Soybean Pizza. I'm sure you'll like it." Customer: "What makes you think I'd like something like that?"  Operator : "Well, you checked out 'Gourmet Soybean Recipes' from your local library last week, sir. That's why I made the suggestion." Customer: "All right, all right. Give me two family-sized ones, then."  Operator : "That 's quite a bit for a family of six, sir, especially with your daughter's thyroid problem; but your total is $49.99." Customer: "Lemme give you my credit card number."  Operator : "I'm sorry sir, but I'm afraid you'll have to pay in cash. Your credit card balance is over its limit." Customer: "I'll run over to the ATM and get some cash before your driver gets here."  Operator : "That won't work either, sir. Your checking account's overdrawn." Customer: " Look, I'll borrow the money. Just send the pizzas. I'll have the cash ready. How long will it take?"  Operator : "We're running a little behind, sir. It'll be about 45 minutes, sir. If you're in a hurry you might want to pick 'em up while you're out getting the cash, but carrying pizzas on a motorcycle can be a little awkward." Customer: "How the hell do you know I'm riding a bike?"  Operator : "It says here you're in arrears on your car payments, so your car got repo'd. But your Harley's still paid up. Customer: "@#%/$@?#!"  Operator : "I'd advise watching your language, sir. You've already got a July 2006 conviction for cussing out a cop." Customer: (Speechless)  Operator : "Will there be anything else, sir?" Customer: "Yes, I have a coupon for a free 2 liter of Coke".  Operator : "I'm sorry sir, but our ad's exclusionary clause prevents us from offering free pop to diabetics." 
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       The crowd gasps as they round the corner...   bad actors with bad habits. some sad singers, they just play tragic and the phone's ringing. and the band's leaving let's just keep touching. let's just keep, keep singing. I NEED SOME MEANING I CAN MEMORIZE   The sun is out today. Without the breeze, you'd think it Summer. I feel accomplished, we saved some lives [with our little petty charm]. And lately I've been in love with the day, so I can be with you and stay awake..But when I dream you seem to fade.  Funny how tables turn, can we ever learn to not be afraid? A promise not to lie, not to hurt... sincere as ever.  I have to close my eyes, this isn't real Can you believe how  good  it feels?   L  A     G  L  O  I  R  E    S  E    F  A  N  E   ? 
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       And the race begins..   I  was just guessing on numbers and fingers pulling the puzzle apart questions of science, science and progress would not speak as loud as my heart come tell me you love me come back and haunt me oh, what a rush to the start..   Maybe we have changed. Maybe nothing is ever the same. Maybe this will never work and we'll prove them all right. But I know how I feel, I know how I feel with you, and I know that hasn't changed. And even though we may be two different people now, and might have forgotten all the things we once knew, maybe there is such a thing as 'meant to be'. Maybe there is such a thing as You and Me..
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      WHERE ARE YOU GOING? *Where to begin? WHAT ARE YOU DOING? *Breaking me in? Missing my skin?  I couldn't move all day, You are killing me aren't you? The knife is inching towards my back Yet I smile and close my eyes And continue breathing you in, precious poison.  See, this thing will leave me face down. Like a sick puppy following you around. If I've never played the fool, I don't know what this is. Why should I fall for one stolen kiss?  I need to not dwell *swimming a month in hell* and I'm terrified of reoccurring infidelities. Why are you even here with me? 		[if that's what we call it]  Well I love you so I'm playing the charade. I'm getting what I wished for [right?] So why complain?
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        ::deep breath::    Ohh. I forgot how it felt to smile like this..
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       A beautiful world , indeed . . . [ You don ' t recover from a night like this . ]   What are you DOING? I swear I won't get my hopes up but if YOU bring them up and push them down again I will pull away forever. I hope you know how vulnerable you're setting me up to be. And I don't like it at all, I hate being the terrified girl. It's not me. This has happened once [which is one too many] and I hope to God it does not happen again [I don't know if I could bring myself up again..]  Lov e  and Hat e  end the same, remember that.  (DIE YOUNG AND SAVE YOURSELF)
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       *This is the end my beautiful friend                           my only friend, the end.    Roaring, rumbling, the accidental extinguish turned out inneffective, or so they say..
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       SHE'S BREATHING QUIET AND SMOOTH </post></Blog>