<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I know I just posted but I am posting again. I wish this was like a xanga, where you could play music. I would be playing tiny vessels by DCFC. So just hum it as you read this.   Pat pisses me off, day after day. I know he plays me. I know he has a temper. I know he is wrong for me.   WHY CAN'T I GET THAT THROUGH MY HEAD???!   God damnit. I need him, and I hate that. I want to be with Chris, or Ryan. But I can't seem to detatch myself from Patrick. We have the most intimate moments, and it makes me forget all of the things he has done to me.  I needto remember the pain he's caused me, and not allow myself to be reeled back in. I need to be done with him. I need to be with him. I need a change.   The way I am living now isn't satisfying me. At all. I need a guy who is TRUE and HONEST and will love me for who and what I am. I am sick of all this suffering, andcan't allow this to go on.    RANDOM WORDS, THE FIRST TO COME TO MIND AT THE MOMENT: deceit, lie,trust, played, unreliable,fucker, jerk,fake, passion, and hate.   wow, that was kinda weird. Don't know whyyyy I did that.   Right now, the thing that is making memost mad, is that he told me heloved me. Thenafterwords he told me that he really did mean that. If he loved me, would it fade that quickly? If he loved me,wouldhe be able to do this to me? If he loved my, WHY IS HE LETTING ME GO SO SOON?  I justtalked to Scott (the awesome dude) about all this, and he said I should let Pat go. I should search for someone who will make me truely happy. Andif Patrick returns to me,thenso itis meant to be. ANd if he doesn't.... then I am better off with out him.     F A T E . . . . think about it.   
    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       i think this is the end of Megan and Patrick. Not like there was ever a begining. Just thinking right now, he hates me.   I know it.    Fuck you all. I want to be a differnent person.   
    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Miranda's birthday was yesterday. I didn't get to talk to her. Kristen's birthday is today. I haven't talked to her yet today.  My number of friends is decreasing rapidly.Miranda andKristen are stillmy friends still. At least Iknow Miranda is. I don't think Kristen likes me anymore.  She's got her pom friends. I am not very pom-ish. At all.Maybe inhigh school I will meet some people.    I hope.   That sucks.I am such a loser.  Maybe if I wasen't so emo people would like me. too fucking bad for them      
    
</post>
<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Deanna's journal says that they still kiss. Everytime they depart, they kiss.  I can't believe him. I can't believe he would do this to me. Or her even. He can't be with us both.  He needs to make up his mind. I refuse to be played. I can't belive he thought he could get away with it too. How ignorant could he be?  I need someone to talk to about all this.  Miranda is in Utah. Miranda is the one that I would feel best about talking to.  Laurren is out with her mom. I'm not going to call her mom's cell to talk about this.   Chris.. Chris. Chris is a good friend. He in understanding, sweet and never gets angry with me.   I need ot talk to Chris, before I do something that I will regret. I don't want to cut. Ever again.   But I need it. So bad.   I hope Chris is home.    
    
</post>
<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I just got back from a walk. It was a long walk. I walked alone.  During this walk, I passed a man.I bet he was about 25. He appeared a mess. He was crying when I passed him. I asked if he was okay, and he said "No one is okay, ever."  Now, where as most people would have quickly walked away, thinking he was insane, I took what he said to heart. I replied to him, "You are right. I know that noone is ever okay." He looked at me with this intense look, and continued walking. i stood there for a while, thinking. I don't want to be in pain forever. Life is slowly killing us all.    No one is ever okay.    
    
</post>
<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I am getting frustrated with this. I just want to know if I am being lied to, led on, or cheated. By reading Deanna's journal it sure seems that way. I wish he couldn't lie. Ever. If he couldn't I think that everything would be better. Deanna would know the truth about me and him, and I would know the truth about him and Deanna. Doesn't he have any morals? God, I love him even though I am suspicious. He is the greatest kisser ever. He is so sweet, and I love how I feel when I am around him. Like the rest of the world doesn't matter, and will never again. Out for now, more later.     
    
</post>
<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Ah, Patrick and Deanna are going out again.   Andy is incredably sick.  My best friend is    acting strange.  I have given up on my dad.   I feel so  a l o n e .  
    
</post>
</Blog>