<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        counting down to nxt month... 16min52s... im home.. tmr having choir... dad n i went tm just now.. had a pleasant evening.. he bought some accesories,  bought me a shirt... hMm.. andrew must be reaching home already.. yeap bought my converse school shoe also... yayeE.. hahax.. gotta sell ard 6 pieces of mobius items for art tmr.. hope i can get ppl to buy frm me, i'lll target art freaks den aunties =) heE.. kkz sleEpy slEepy...  better get going... goodbye july~ nxt month 8 august ish mums bdae...        misS my baby*    
    
</post>
<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       phew*   im  urlLink home  sweet  urlLink home ...   went to  urlLink school  @ 10... ppl were already there.. so we did  urlLink art  until lunch  urlLink time .. went opposite to uncle kenneth's... me, clar,mel n nat..  hahax... we laughed so hard when calarion called out to tt guy, " haAAy, yr  urlLink underwear  can be seen, pull it up ".. and alot of other crap like" so long already.. u cannot feel meh?  "  hahax... hes gf also didnt notice.. man~ it showed his butt okay~ so funNy..  the jc gurls next table were all red in the face too.. hahaha...   well we went back n met Ju @2... we have this project to do, starting with the  urlLink art  exhibition.. it'll be brought ard  urlLink schools  n eventually hospitals to teach patients who suffers frm  urlLink cancer  to use colours to brighten up their day.. more towards kids n outreach to community...   haha think im gonna get involed in it... its gonna be a long term thingie.. probably 4 yrs to establish everything..a dream to dream =] then our grp would be the pioneers.. so cool aye.. haha.. not forgetting my choir.. *  hmM clarion and i started on a pottery.. both of us.. hahax.. nt sure can finish or not but we'll try..     i moulded two pieces of heart, one with 'drew', the other with "jas"...  =) gonna post it on  urlLink http://tabulas.com/~starstarx  for ppl to go view it =] hehe... waiting for daddy to be back  urlLink home  now.. later bring me buy sch  urlLink shoes ... *yaWn.z.. kinda tired already.. lol.. ahh theres bread in kitchen.. ciao~ go munch...   
    
</post>
<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      [[http://www.tabulas.com/~starstarx]] my images page =) created for andrew also actually =) tgif *heE.. watched I.robots wif mel,nat,clar,fiq,dil... its quite nice.. haha.." aaRRHhhCCheeEwW!! uhh im sorry but im allergic to bullshit" said willsmith.. hahax.. s o funny... i realise im really kinda short of cash.. haiz.. need buy bus pass, converse  urlLink school   urlLink shoes , we're planning to go  urlLink shopping  one day too.. but no  urlLink money .. hai..only can start saving after i buy my  urlLink shoes .. ahah its ok.. i'll survive thru though... juz cut down on  urlLink movies  n all =/ hope i can lar.. anyway tmr going to  urlLink school  @ 9am to complete  urlLink art .. den theres a  urlLink art  meeting with Mr.Zul @2pm.. probably gonna try new stuff or go to OBS for  urlLink art  again.. xD anyway dad juz came back.. hez nagging at me lyk hell.. gosh.. i hate this so much... sigh*... i wont let him bring me down.. im gonna stay nice.. yesh.. cuz i dont want ndrew 2 worry bout me.. just wanna enjoy the moment with him... hmMm how nice if i get a warm hug righ now n everything unpleasant would go away... (*_*~) 
    
</post>
<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      long day... impact gave me a call to ask me to reschedule my audition.. i dont feel like going anymore.. haiz... class time was alright.. miss andrew here n there..lost debate to 3b but we're nt exactly the losers.. tey won cuz they did mre homework thats all.. yupp... looked for clarion in art room.. mr. lau gimme a chocolate sweet.. hahax.. den i went home with my grp of malay friends from class..arifa followed n she suddenly pull me down to convenient store n treated me peach yougurht drink.. haha.. so i walked with her ard n listened to her story...saw zenn @ park doing stunns.. hes good..=) went blading ard8.. was pouring outside.. so i came back @ 830.. khairul asked me for a favour, sadly i cunt find any info on net... today mast absent.. tmr she'll be alright i guess.. hmMm den bro louis is kinda sad.. feels sad too... failed to notice my godbro's emptiness.. or maybe he's just too happy-go-lucky in front of schmates.. hmmM hope tt i can manage to comfort him thru words.... drew msged me i miss you baby.. haha.. probably hes reached home by now cuz its 10 mins already.. wanna say gd night to him b4 i sleep later.. yea... think tts abt all today.. feeling quite tired now.. n the bunch of bad news i received today kinda 'depressed' me.. lol.. nt tt serious... n i realise... im so lucky to haf andrew too.. juz lyk hes said to me.. actually its vice versa =]... imu* goodnight everybody... if only i could fill up emptiness in every singel person on earth.. i'll start with my beloved friends n family n den everyone else... before myself.. cuz by then, the satisfaction of ppls joy n ma baby's love would have filled mine up alread...nights.. starry land time*
    
</post>
<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       A Telephone Call that Changed my Life       The night was cold and I was sitting in my bedroom, reading my once favourite book by Nicholas Sparks. I have read it for more than three times already. It was not as if I have a choice to do whatever I want after having a heated argument with my father.     Suddenly the telephone rang and to my immense relief, it was a call from mother. I asked her if she had a good day and then complained to her about father’s unreasonable attitude, however I could sense that she was not really interested in my conversation so I asked her if she was alright. “Daughter, I have decided to leave the family and I’ve already booked a one way ticket to Europe. I shall be staying at a friends house. Please inform dad about this and take care of the family for me dear.” With these words from my mother, I found myself at a complete loss for worlds as I felt as though my whole world had just collapsed. I was filled with remorse and the fact that I was totally unprepared for such a situation made me scared. I could not hold down the sorrow and a scorching stream of tears began to flow down my cheeks. I went into the bathroom and locked myself inside for the next half an hour. When I regained my composure, I began to question myself what had affected mother so badly that she had to leave our family. Minutes drift pass and eventually the answers shot at me like bullets. Our family consists of father, me, and my two brothers. We lived in a big house but have never hired a maid, mum had to clean the house everyday and she never fail to cook us our favourite meals every evening. Father was a workaholic who comes home from business trips only for sixty five days in a year. Mother must be lonely and tired of nagging at us without our least efforts to change for the better. Occasionally she even received cold shuns from my brothers. My heart palpitated wildly as I thought of the consequences without mum around the house, taking care of our needs. My brothers are always quarrelling with each other over minor things and they never got along well. Father did not have a close relationship with us due to his constant business trips, he was absent from all our major graduations or birthday celebrations, unlike mother.  I stared at my distraught face in the mirror and wished that it was all a terrible nightmare. The telephone call on that fateful night indeed changed my life. The beginning of my misery.  
    
</post>
<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      manage to complete my first layer for batik.. its so off the traditional form of art but i still like it =) its made of 3 butterflys n a face, lips, hair, hand... haha ratehr abstract... today after school went tm with lu, shron , n kanna...bought her stuff...den came back.. kannan treated me free ice cream.. lol.. wasnt exactly a good day.. not that bad either.. just feel tired now.. *tmr debate dae... we haven done anything much.. hope that by luck n our intelligence we can win =) andrew gotta recover... missing him alot alot... today we did art in artroom n jy was there also.. haha had a lil talk wit him.. hes still the same.. den andy was at workshop... lamed ard for a sec also.. &gt;. .</post></Blog>