<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>22,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      FREEZING!!!! Tonight we ascend upon the  urlLink St. Paul Winter Carnival Ice Palace ... both very exciting for me and admittedly in these economic times of budget cuts and layoffs a huge waste of money... I've never seen an ice palace before and this is the first one in 12 years. I remember being a little girl living in North Dakota and my parents had a brand new calendar up on the wall... January - the first month of the year - was adorned with a huge sparkling picture of the Ice Palace in St. Paul. I was enthralled - I thought it was the coolest thing I had ever seen. Tonight I'll be standing out in the cold - bitter bitter January cold - volunteering at the Ice Palace.   And for those crazy for Friends spoilers... the  urlLink best  happen to be over at  urlLink The Morning News ...    urlLink Happy Year of the Monkey ! I was born in a year of the monkey.... i guess that means i'm special or something right?  This Sunday we're having a little Johnny-Depp-A-Thon at Maria's (i haven't seen Pirates of the Caribbean yet)... another fabulous reason to watch that movie...  urlLink Orlando Bloom   Also...   ITS REALLY FREAKING COLD HERE!!! (did i mention 5 layers of clothes and i'm still inside???)
     
    
</post>
<date>21,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink here . this is an incredibly interesting email interview with David Eggars. I will admit that I did not read much of the first part of the questions/interview (i scanned) because I was directed to it through  urlLink rex  through someone else on the topic of selling out... the rant on selling out is so right on though... right on.   also there is a new pizza place we should check out soon...  urlLink SPOKES ... its located in the seward cafe and only open on thursday and friday evenings from 6pm-1am. and i guess they do delivery too - on bike... must have felt that the new seward location of pizza luce needed a little  urlLink coop competition ...   and this  urlLink phone thing ... just bizarre... 
     
    
</post>
<date>20,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      New Job News:::&gt;  Day 2 was shorter and seemed more frantic than Day 1.  Had to run  out of my first site manager meeting to plug the parking meter, but wasn't the only one to do so.   I feel so overwhelmed trying to digest all the information and protocol, but moreover, incredibly overjoyed that my supervisor is actually cool.  And not just cool in comparison to previous awful bosses, but legitimately a wonderful person.  She's completely scattered and disorganized, which for now makes me chuckle--but will it drive me nuts after a week?  I'm hoping A, that it won't, and B, that after a week or two of my assistance she will be far better organized.  ((And let's note that it is A and B, not A and 2.  Or 1 and B for that matter)).    Sad Things:::&gt;  Finally watched Whale Rider---it's been sitting in the apartment for weeks---and enjoyed it.  Though some parts I feel could have been explained further, but that little Keisha Castle-Hughes was darned compelling.  I almost cried.  Following the movie-watching, spent the latter part of yesterday evening yelling at the radio with the Dean-atic roommate.  She probably did some crying herself later on, but hopefully the hour we spent ranting and shouting obscenities at the voices of Kerry, Edwards, and Gephardt (goodbye little Dicky) allowed her sufficient venting opportunities.  
     
    
</post>
<date>15,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      big news...  urlLink Katherine Lanpher  stepped down today as host of MPR's Midmorning. I guess I missed the announcement - I was late to work this morning and was therefore able to listen to the first half of midmorning... still no word from our insider on her behavior at recent annual work party...   in more personal related (and admittedly somewhat boring) news:  Ifinished  urlLink Dune  last night. The last third of the book was actually quite good, and overall I enjoyed the concept - innovative ways of coping with/transforming your surroundings, prophesies, advanced body/mind control, and rebellion. However Frank Herbert needed an editor so bad that I was forced to take frequent breaks from reading. Now I want to rent the movie and see if that clears anything up for me (don't get me wrong - the book wasn't confusing) but I'd like to see some sort of condensed version.   Also started  urlLink Life of Pi , interesting so far. Learning a lot about zoos.   Watched Average Joe last night... i really like that tattooed ocd boy... so cute! the new hunks seem just obnoxious... its making me nervous.   Sunday night was  urlLink Heiruspecs  at  urlLink rockrockrock  and next week is  urlLink Coach Said Not To  at the Kellar Bar...
     
    
</post>
<date>15,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      forget magnets... we need to pick up some more marbles and start doing  urlLink necklaces ... genius!   urlLink this site  is also pretty cool... i've been wanting to learn how to stencil for a while... i figure its something that could enhance the sewing and other projects i do already...    also...  urlLink go Brazil!  i don't see why U.S. world travelers shouldn't be treated the same as our government is treating our world guests... did you forget the golden rule? 
     
    
</post>
<date>14,January,2004</date>
<post>

     
      if you are one of the masses that does in fact watch tv - although a lot of us claim to be above its hypnotic stare - i hope to god that you did not watch the simple life reunion show. that’s all i have to say about it. i also cannot tell you how many hours of television i watched last night because a) it was quite a lot and 2) it is quite embarrassing.  i did finish reading a christmas present as well though - Bachelor Girl by Betsy Isreal - a look at single women through the twentieth century - very interesting at some points, a bit repetitive at others...   in other news... 50cent cans of tomato soup make for a damn fine lunch. as do walking past the cute auditor who i am hoping takes another week after this to finish all the work audit stuff or whatever it is they do. as for things that do not - filling out one's college alumni registration, and chatting with a certain coworker.
     
    
</post>
<date>19,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      a) the triple rock has redesigned their  urlLink website  to include food, photos, and more great info  2) i was at the triple rock last night for the greatest show i almost missed. Dre Day 2004. The second annual celebration of the life of Andre Young - yesterday was his 39th birthday. This great celebration was put on by the crazy skater boys at  urlLink life sucks die magazine  and had incredible music sets by  urlLink heiruspecs  and the entire  urlLink rhymesayers  crew. It also featured the return of the $20 sack pyramid. Heiruspecs took the stage to do some great Dre and Snoop Dogg covers. Muad'ib sounding especially impressive with the Snoop vocals. After a short break Heiruspecs band got back on stage and was shortly joined by Eyedea, Felipe from Los Nav, Brother Ali, Slug, I-Self, Musab and probably some others that I really shouldn't be forgetting right now, for some great freestyle to the back beat of Dre produced tunes. It was a great time. We were dancing, there were 40s, and there was some camera guy who edged himself right in front of me for much of the freestyle. For me giving up a little bit of my front and center I better be seeing those photos in a full page glossy national magazine spread...  As for now... the ink isn't washing off the back of my hand, I hung my little Dre Day poster (that I took off the entrance to the 3rock) proudly in my cube (i've gotten quite a few positive comments on it already), I'm daydreaming of the most beautiful guy in Minneapolis who was also snapping quite a few photos at the show last night, and I should probably get some more sleep. Next year I'm taking the morning after Dre Day off. 
     
    
</post>
<date>18,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      When I was in elementary school in North Dakota a friend of mine and I made up alternate words to this song in the hopes of making some sort of small fortune off of the sales to other fourth and fifth graders…  Unfortunately our genius was not nearly that of  urlLink billy joel’s … thanks to  urlLink useful noise  for the link
     
    
</post>
<date>16,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I keep hearing about electability and this frightens me.  Why are we so focused on who the other guy would vote for? Don’t people realize that now, especially in the primaries and caucuses that are occurring, now is your chance much more than in the nationwide election to make your voice be heard. This is about you and your choice and picking the right candidate to represent you and your issues rather than voting based upon what your neighbor thinks is right and following suite. Am I missing something here? Granted my politics are much more radical than the people that I have chosen to support and so you may in fact call me somewhat of a hypocrite. I do believe that it is important to choose someone to bridge the gap between us all. However, don’t just give up and pick the guy everyone else is. This isn’t high school. It does remind me of it though. When I was a senior at my rather small school in northern Minnesota I decided that I wanted to be chosen as queen of our winter school festival called SnoBall. Since the decision was made rather democratically (we nominated people in our class and then those names were given to the student body to be voted on) I thought I had a rather good chance. All I had to do was get a nomination and then get my name out there to the rest of the student body on voting day. Most of the underclassman would not be familiar with the senior student names and with the help of some homemade posters and a handy catch phrase “Vote Christine for SnoQueen!” I had a fairly good chance at it. This was the route that we (a couple of my friends and I) undertook. My friend Maren even made up the two little posters to go up on the voting day. After the voting was in I found out that I had not been chosen as SnoQueen. This I could live with – evidently our tactics had not been effective as we had thought. What threw me the most however was that my dear friend Maren had decided not to vote for me on the basis that she didn’t think that I would win.  What?! This is how our country is working. I just don’t get it. 
     
    
</post>
<date>06,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink thats it ... i'm moving to france. americans are just to freaking prudish! not to mention lawsuit happy!
     
    
</post>
<date>03,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      the absentee bloggert.  it's like my mom used to say: if you don't have anything interesting to blog, don't blog anything at all.    the one single guy in the office--who, don't worry, probably doesn't like girls anyway--filled me in on ms. jackson's little halftime oopsie.  ((you see, the coworker is a devout J.T. idolizer.)) don't ask how i missed it, of course i sat through the whole boring first half of the game, then missed the janet nipshot.  i haven't tried to download any nips, er...clips, yet, but word is there is a vertiable deluge.  i am currently addicted to postal service: "give up".  i borrowed it from a friend, and am hoping i can make sure she forgets that i have it before she leaves the state in a few weeks.  if only i were as cold-hearted a friend as that.  i had track one (the district sleeps alone tonight) stuck in my head for all of Monday--probably means i'm addicted in a bad way.  as soon as i figure out how to add links (yes, i'm dense) my posts may gain a little more spice.
     
    
</post>
<date>03,February,2004</date>
<post>

     
      local kids do good.  when i was a teenager living in northern minnesota my family got the  urlLink fargo forum  delivered to my house. i was never terribly interested in the local news that was happening in the fargo/moorhead area as it were - but would skip ahead to the local movie reviews and read them with reckless abandon. the local reviewers would tell me what to expect, what to avoid, and of course what books the movies were based on so i could be sure to either read them first or read them instead of seeing the movie (because books are always better). my absolute favorite reviewer though was chuck klosterman. i would value his advice above all others... especially above tammy swift whom i couldn't trust at all with her puffy blond hair and super done up northwestern pretty mom face. since i'm super excitable about reminiscent stuff and my roots and all... i you know... feel happy when i hear that my favorite little reviewer is currently an editor for spin magazine and that  urlLink this little interview  was linked on  urlLink gawker . that makes me happy as well.   oh and i also can't forget to use my barnes and noble gift card to pick up the newest issue of spin which is evidently featuring  urlLink slug  on some article about emo-rap... whatever that is. he also was drinking at the cc club saturday night. i was also harassed by one of the wait staff, who when i emerged from the bathroom stall insisted that i "should leave" and that she "had been watching me". i'm not entirely sure why she was so insistent that i should leave. my slightly intoxicated behavior was - i assure you - not inappropriate or anything else that would require me to leave. we stayed for quite a while anyway. our server didn't seem to have any issues with me or my posse. 
     
    
</post>
<date>29,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      the  urlLink funniest thing ever  via  urlLink New Yorkish  it makes me even more sorry that i missed the showing of tron at  urlLink sound unseen  this past fall... ahhh tron.... i get a little misty eyed when i see the simpsons version... pure genius...   this  urlLink nifty little device  would be so handy to have... there are many a show that i've come home from wishing i could have a copy of the songs that night. especially since i've been forced to listen to so many crappy recordings from cell phones and i'm not technologically inclined enough to think up my own way to do it... 
     
    
</post>
<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Its Thursday today. All week I’ve been one day ahead. Not usually a good thing but this week it has been. Especially since I’m calling in sick tomorrow… so today is kind of like Friday, I have to get all my work done today.   Anyway. Been staying at the new place. I love it. Last night I was supposed to take my last trip of stuff over from the old place – well I moved my kitchen table and chairs (was going to leave them in my car last night, but there were other people out moving as well so I just hauled them in at 11pm). Tonight I have to get all my stuff out of the fridge and freezer – which really isn’t much at all and I have a basket of dirty clothes (which I’m throwing in my car to take home Friday night, I guess I still have a couple things in the bathroom drawer and a picture on the kitchen wall, and a couple things in downstairs storage… oh man and my bike. Will this never end!? Well, it will have to. I’ll go out to the old place after work and load up all that random stuff (try and get my bike in my car (eek) and take it back to the new apt. I’m also going to stay over at the old place tonight because we’re moving roommate out at 7am tomorrow morning. That’s a little early for my taste, but at least most of her stuff is all ready to go. We have been packing her for the last couple of nights (interspersed with my moving.)   I’m so excited for next week. I just want to be able to know that there is nothing left to move and then I can sit down and start putting things up and organizing. I have three sacks of dry groceries sitting on my kitchen counter. I need to get things put away. Amazingly enough I already have plans for Monday, Wednesday and Thursday with friends. And  urlLink Swiss Army is playing on Friday at the Entry  which we might try and see. Also I have a wedding to attend on Saturday. Oh boy. I’m just going to collapse from exhaustion pretty soon here.   Oh – and I love my new place. It’s tiny, with good sunlight, hardwood floors, and quiet. There are dogs in my building which are just adorable – I saw this young great dane leaving the other night as I was hauling stuff in… so cute. And since the weather has been nice I see them walking all over the place.  I think its going to be really good – this living on my own. Quite good. 
     
    
</post>
<date>23,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Wow... thanks to  urlLink CP Babelogue  for noticing us and for the birthday wishes.... 
     
    
</post>
<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      ITS MY BIRTHDAY!!!   urlLink TAURUS (April 20-May 20):  Your most important accomplishment this year has been to deepen your capacity for love. That alone should inspire you to leap up and sing a song of joy. More and more, you understand that in order to get the passionate affection you want, you simply have to give the passionate affection you want. If you continue to expand your generosity in the coming months, you will receive a flood of evidence about how beautiful you really are. That, in turn, will ensure that the influences you want to bring into your life will also be good for you.   
     
    
</post>
<date>19,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      edited... for now...    
     
    
</post>
<date>14,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Birthday Week has commenced!  Sunday  - Force college girl friends to eat delicious breakfast in my company at SunnySideUp Cafe. Accomplished! Jes, Katie, Kat, and Jill accompanied me for breakfast/lunch to open up my birthday week. I had my usual 5A (which will feed me for the next week) with scrambled eggs, whole wheat toast, veggies, potatoes and a whole lot of gooey cheese. Delicious! I do believe the winner of the meal though was Katie, who in her indecisive prime, made our server choose which meal she should order. The choice was the Cowboy Tort which almost everyone tried and decided they would certainly order next time.  Monday  - Coffee. This shows how crazy I am. I had penciled in coffee for Monday which meant that I was to go to a coffee shop and write and drink coffee, because as it is something I enjoy doing - it is something that I rarely make time for. So tonight I'll be having some sort of caffeinated beverage on Lyndale while being interviewed by a friend of mine from college about an article he's writing for some online magazine. You must remain flexible in the plans you make.  Tuesday  - 3Rock two-fers My favorite place for a cheap drink.   Wednesday  - (actual birthday) Nachos and muchos friends at Little T's  Thursday  - Skateboard shopping (unfortunately i won't be actually purchasing the skateboard yet... just doing my research). Also  urlLink Dining Out for Life  and book club. (I'm half way through the book - don't tell)  Friday  - Was going to be girls night has now been delegated to "Pack the Kitchen with my roommate" night  Saturday  - Moving day - that’s right. moving. Filling up an empty 15 passanger van with all my belongings and moving across town. I'm excited. Will most likely be celebrated that evening with cold Premium. 
     
    
</post>
<date>14,April,2004</date>
<post>

     
      So last night we didn’t make it to the 3Rock until much later than planned. It was still good to be there. D is freshly back from Italy and I have so much missed hanging out with her. She’s crazy and funny and the boys tend to hover around her (or maybe they were just trying to get through to the video games we were leaning against – whatever) and she continues to talk about how she just needs to find either some random to date or some good Christian boy to settle down with that will understand her restrictions etc. I told her good luck, because as far as I’ve seen, what she’s looking for is purely a myth propagated by parents and church leaders, no boys are ever that pure or understanding. Well we kept getting in the way of the people who wanted to play golden tee or the root beer game but that was mainly because we refuse to go into the new addition (granted I’ve been over there for shows and that’s about all its good for, in fact its great for that… but for a bar – no). We complained about the lack of old regulars, the twins – two boys that some how look so similar in their gorgeousness and yet completely different (one of whom I’ve renamed the most beautiful man in Minneapolis, he wanders around uptown with a camera and a skateboard… so lovely) the other that we were missing was Mr. Intriguing. Mr. Intriguing is this crazy eyed curly haired man who we always used to run into (not talk with) exchange crazy glances and raised eyebrows with at the old triple rock patio. Last night we had the realization that we have been going to the triple rock for four years now (some Tuesdays more regularly than others).  He is one of whom it cannot be said is either attractive or not – he transcends all the normal classifications of our people watching. We hadn’t seen him in quite a while – granted D has been out of the country and its harder to go there in the winter or even if I start to think about the loss of the patio and all the new faces that are there – but he arrived last night at 1:30, just as we were leaving. We almost turned around and went back in, but really, we both had an early morning to look forward to, and we’ll be back next week. I mean next Tuesday after all is the night before my birthday… where else would I be? Oh and next week, I’m taking Wednesday morning off. 
     
    
</post>
<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I think the nicest thing Dana said to me last night when visiting the new place was "It looks like you."
     
    
</post>
<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      "oh these creatures and their love"  It's good to be a twenty-four year old uncommitted girl. Uncommitted to anything besides my apartment anyway. For the love of the apartment (with the hardwood floors, big windows, huge bathtub, in the lovely neighborhood) I have committed to at least a year of habitation. Which means that in a couple of months I must find something to support my committment - a job. I work now, but not in the actually getting paid for my forty hours a week sort of sense. This I'll worry about more later. But while my friends are considering cohabitation and engagements I am still trying to figure out whether or not I can drill into my walls to affix shelving, if I should really get a step stool to reach the top shelves in my kitchen, what art/picture I could hang over my bed, whether my neighbors are aware/bothered by all the noises coming out of my apartment, and if that guy with the black lab down the hall is actually attractive or if he's just really old and I only see him in the not well lit hallway and because he has a dog with him I've imagined that he's hot. Oh I don't know how I get through my days and nights with these pressing issues.   For now I will worry about kickball. What night of the week it should change to - the responses seem to be leaning towards Mondays and Wednesdays.   Oh, and I've been dreaming about puppies again. It's at least comforting to me to be dreaming about puppies instead of babies. I know that I'm not either responsible or ready for either of them, but I'd rather be having the puppy dreams.   In real news: *This weekend jilianlove will be down from the great boring north for a little book clubbing and general hanging out in the cities.  *I'm looking forward to attending the  urlLink U.S. Conference on Democratic Workplaces  next Monday and Wednesday. (unfortunately I am unable to attend on Tuesday because of a training that we're hosting at the Hill House) *I'm having happy hour at  urlLink rock rock rock  tonight with some of my girl type friends. $5 for a beer and a burger... (veg burgers included!!) *Next Tuesday evening is  urlLink Voltage: Fashion Amplified  at First Ave featuring my favorite new band  urlLink Coach Said Not To !
     
    
</post>
<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Maybe I’m in love with myself and that’s what keeps me from finding someone to share my love with.     Before it explodes.    The love that is.
     
    
</post>
<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Why am I not inspired to be writing?  It’s the laziness.  I felt it last night. No I didn’t.  I was going to call people that I hadn’t talked to in a while… but then decided not to waste more of my daytime minutes and wait until 9. By nine I figured most people didn’t want to be called? I read instead.  It’s a book – paper back novel – by  urlLink Agatha Christie  – one of my favorite writers, featuring the splendid little Belgian detective Hercule Poirot. There is a murder to be solved. I’m half way through the book. Will most likely finish the second half tonight. The host of a party who liked to dress as Mephistopheles was killed while his guests were playing bridge. Who did it!? Can she write the word Mephistopheles one more time? Or make one more reference to what a character the host was? He lived dangerously, was a collector, of many things… including… murderers. Dun Dun Duhnnnnn! Oh and I baked cookies too. Not too complicated since they came from a box (which I might add is very unusual for me.) I brought them to work today and labeled the clear plastic container "Cookies are for sharing!" They'll most likely be gone by the time I leave work today.  Now here I am at work. Just finished my latest project. Waiting for lunch and walking. Wondering where last evening went and why I didn’t do more. Why haven’t I been doing more while I’m at home. I have all this time, this space, this freedom and I just want to lie around in bed. Dreaming.  
     
    
</post>
<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      This morning I'm early to work and listening to Dancing Queen on Radio K.  Last night I was terrified. Just a little while after my parents left(They stopped by on their way to their hotel out by the airport. They're going to Rochester today for my Dad's appointment.), around 11pm, I started hearing noises like people pounding on something and then breaking glass. I had never heard this noise before, but from what I could decifer it sounded like people breaking car windows. So I sat there in the middle of my bed. Then I went to the windows to try and see if I could figure out if I was just freaking myself out or if this was really happening. I couldn't see anything. Although I feel very safe for my person in the new apartment I'm always a little n</post></Blog>