<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Apparently assistant is short for “the one who does all the dirty tasks”, like washing the dishes. Great! I’m a dishwasher with a higher education!  Assistant apparently is also short for a person who has no needs of his or her own. If she were to print a copy of the last week’s meeting’s minutes and this meeting’s agenda in order to prepare for a meeting where she has to take minutes in – it’s ok to take these papers from her desk while she’s in the toilet and never return them. It is also acceptable to spread one’s papers and personal belongings all over her personal working area, to move, and mess around with her neatly stacked pile of papers and, to steel her pencils and pens from her desk, so that she has to reach into her purse and find something of personal origin to write with. It’s ok it seems. But forgive me, if I at some point during today lose my cool. I’m truly sorry if I’m going to make someone uncomfortable by raising my voice and unleashing the truth about the true boundaries that should exist in a working place, at least in my working place.  
     

        
</post>
<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Today has been a good day. A problem that has already for long waited for some kind of a solution has finally been resolved. I’m not saying there won’t be any aftermath, but there’s at least some light in the end of the tunnel. So I’m happy, and a little proud of myself for making the first move. If you know me, you should realize it has not been easy.  Now that I’ve gotten rid of the first issue, I have lots of negative feelings available waiting to be re-channeled. I’ve chosen my boss. How dare he chase me away from my working place! I remember one case study during University about some kind of a company where work was re-arranged so that no one had their own computer or working place any more. You’d come in the morning, take your pencil and stack of paper from your locker, grab a laptop from the secretary’s table and find a suitable place to sit, and they were not allowed to sit in the same place for two days in a row. I vaguely remember that this system proved to be not so good. If I remember correctly, it was discontinued quite soon after it was first introduced. So why doesn’t it work like that? Out of all people I should be the one who would not mind a change of scenery (three jobs within 12 months, think about it, and in the middle of it I took quite some time off to graduate from Uni), but I hate it as much as anyone would.  Take for instance the polar-person sitting next to me today. She has a habit of keeping the window wide open even during sub-zero temperatures (luckily today it’s +8, I imagine it makes quite a difference). Last time I was here I tried to find some kind of a reasonable explanation for this phenomenon. Turns out she lives in an apartment where there’s no central heating, and be it for whatever reason, she only heats it herself every other day, even during winter. For those who are not familiar with the matter, some people heat theirs’ twice a day. Go figure then. The only consolation once again is what we northern people keep telling ourselves on the crispiest of winter days – oh no, it’s not unbelievably “freeze your ass off” cold outside, it’s simply refreshing, and it helps to keep us young for a longer time.  Here’s to youth then!  
     

        
</post>
<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Inspireerituna oma hea sõbra  urlLink Riksti  meeldivast kombest endast aeg-ajalt on-line päeviku kujul endast ka virtuaalseid jälgi maha jätta, olen nüüd vaevlemas luulude küüsis, et ka mul võiks vahel midagi öelda olla. Teine põhjus on ka tegelikult - minu töökoht pakub mulle enamustel nädalatel kõigest umbes 10 tunni eest tööülesandeid (optimistlikult öeldes ja mitte väga kiirustades), kuid "rõõmu" siin oma tagumikku laiaks istuda on mul siiski 40 tunni eest. Niisiis, let the fun begin!!!   Igavesti Teie,   ell  
     

        
</post>
<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Must… write… something…  Olen eelmise nädala keskpaigast peale haige olnud – läkanohu nagu ma seda ise nimetan. Kurguvalu, nohu, pidev aevastamine, nüüd pisut köha ja peaaegu tundmatuseni muutunud hääl, mis küll õnneks päris ära pole läinud.  Õnneks on täna juba märksa parem, kell juba lõuna, aga ma pole isegi ühte taskurätikut suutnud ära kasutada veel. Ilm on ka imeilus, niisiis olen üle pika aja täis energiat, siin töö juures on seda aga võimalik ainult kirjutamisse suunata.  Seda silmas pidades koristasin ennist oma mailbox’i, ja avastasin, nagu tavaliselt, et võlgnen paljudele toredatele inimestele kirja oma viimase aja käekäigu kohta. Hakkasin siis ühte kohe otsast kirjutama, see on üks nendest kirjadest mis tavaliselt suhteliselt pikad ja enese-analüüsiga täidetud välja kukuvad – ja jõudsin järeldusele, et mul on vaja mingisugust muutust.
     

        
</post>
<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I was about to write something bad about my boss once again in today’s entry, but then I had to ask him for two favors – more specifically time off on two different occasions, and he agreed to both of them, so I’m feeling rather fond of him at the moment.  Another good thing is, that one of those occasions concerned already today’s afternoon, which means, that in about 15 minutes I will gracefully get up, put on my overcoat and leave, even before it becomes dark outside. Add to that the fact that tomorrow is already Friday, and the things are definitely starting to look up.  Today has actually been an extraordinary day already from the very beginning – first surprise – I managed to get up in the morning almost immediately after my alarm rang, an even more surprisingly – I managed to stay up. Consequently today was the first day over a rather long period of time when I actually got to work on time, which was a nice change.  But right now, I have just about 3 minutes left to post this entry an be on my way, so farewell, for now.
     

        
</post>
<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I’m having a tiny little headache today. We’ll see if the ever so popular mixture of coffee and sweets I just had during my lunch break will make any kind of difference in that frontier.  Other than that, today is a bit thoughtful day. Last night, I received the news that  urlLink Michael Kamen  had died early that morning. I was not a great fan of his, but it is nevertheless true that all of  urlLink Bryan’s  greatest hits from movie soundtracks have been written in co-operation with him, and Bryan considered this sad event to be significant enough to address his fans and share his sorrow. So I’m a little bit thoughtful, definitely not as upset as I was in 1997 when  urlLink Michael Hutchence  died (which I think still is among the 10 most significant moments of my life, because it made me think and realize so much about life…), but rather more reflective than my usual self nonetheless.  It’s strange really that I seem to be more thoroughly affected by someone’s death that I did not personally know at all, and seem almost utterly insensitive when some of my own elderly relatives are concerned. Many of you would think that I’m cold and heartless, but I view death as a natural part of life, and when it comes after a life that could be considered lengthy, or at least reasonably long, I feel that in a way it’s a relief… I’m not sure to whom though. You shouldn’t worry about my mental health though, I do miss the people who have passed away, I do sometimes think about them, but I would never go as far as wishing they would still be alive, as this desire would be selfish and routed purely in my ego. Maybe they welcomed death; maybe they’re better off now?  When someone relatively young dies though, no matter how well I knew him or her or almost if I knew him or her at all, it’s a tragedy. Perhaps I’m being naive here, but young people are supposed to have good lives, they’re supposed to have a lot of things still to anticipate, and they’re supposed to stick around for many more years and try to make a difference… they’re supposed to want to live. So it’s sad, when for one reason or another, this thread is cut short and others are left behind wondering what could have been…
     

        
</post>
<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      So I moved my homepage from Yahoo to Zone.ee… Last night Riksti asked me why, and I couldn’t give her a straightforward answer, but it has been getting clearer by the minute.  First of all, for development purposes having FTP access is way much better than not having it; FTP access and actually moving physically closer mean that it’s now way faster to get my files on or off the server.  Secondly, I’ve been thinking about adding some more sophisticated features besides HTML and an occasional Javascript or two… that was definitely not possible in Yahoo! – We’ll have to see what will happen here though.  Thirdly, I’m a patriot – why keep my files somewhere in US, and have them beg money from some weird company on my account, when it’s 99,99% clear I’m not ever going to buy anything they advertise to me ALL THE TIME. In fact, in the long run and ideal case scenario I would like to get rid of my Yahoo! account altogether. It’s too bad though, that they have an e-mail interface that I like (not the amount of spam and lack of POP3 access, however). Until I figure that one out though, I’m happy to get rid of at least the annoying little pop-up’s that you get in Yahoo! web pages on almost every click. Here, at least, you get only one in the very beginning, and once you’re done with that, you can feel free to browse and surf as much as your heart desires.  So, here I am, this me for the very first time in my new Internet environment, and I must say I’m subsequently pretty glad it only took a few hours to get the files off the Yahoo! server and then a minute or so to get them here.
     

        
</post>
<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Amazing really, I’m sitting here, it’s rather early Monday morning, and quite many of my thoughts are focused on that when Saturday comes, I’ll finally be able to sleep as long as I want.  Before that comes though, there’s still around 40 hours to spend here, so I was happy to find at least something worthwhile reading in my mailbox this morning. Currently I’m browsing through a chat transcript, where Darren Hayes talks about his upcoming new album and life in general. There was a thought in there in reply to a question what would Darren do if he weren’t a singer/songwriter that I would like to share with you: “I'd work at Starbucks… I'd work for George Lucas or I'd be a writer for film... something artistic (and yes I believe there is a lot of artistry in a good latte)”. I think if you would have tried to observe me when I first read this paragraph that you would have found me adding a subconscious nod to this everlasting grin I’m reading the rest of the e-mail with. I do agree that latte is not just plain old coffee. And if D were serving lattes somewhere around where I live, I’d probably spend most of my free time there absorbing the art of coffee making. :)
     

        
</post>
<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Õnneks läks kõik lõppkokkuvõttes ikkagi hästi… Terve nädalavahetuse ja ka täna hommikul ma absoluutselt totaalselt vihkasin mõtet sellest, et pean täna jälle tööle tulema, jälle siia, ja jälle selle sama inimesega üheksa tundi järjest ninapidi koos veetma. Aga hetkel see ei tundugi nii hull. Võib-olla tuleneb see osalt ka sellest, et ma täna suhteliselt palju tööd teinud olen, mis on omakorda vastandiks päev läbi mängimisele, aeg-ajalt sellega vahele jäämisele, ja siis seetõttu ennast süüdi tundmisele. Sellise mõtteviisiga võib äkki hoopis selguda, et ma ei vihkagi oma bossi ja tööd vaid hoopis ise-ennast. Mõtle kui huvitav mõte!  Igal juhul, eilne isadepäeva lõuna läks kenasti, kõik olid kangesti sillas et meil üldse õega pähe tuli midagi sellist korraldada, ja toit oli ka söödav. Suurimad probleemid olid, nagu arvata võiski, meie korteri puhtaks küürimine aastate (või aasta vähemalt) jooksul sinna kogunenud saastast, ja üheksale inimesele toidunõude leidmine. Põhimõtteliselt, nagu juba mainitud, võis aga kõigega lõppkokkuvõttes rahule jääda. Kui kõik teised jalga lasksid, siis panin ma kõik tuled kustu et mardisante vältida (õnnestus, ei peagi nüüd ennast süüdi tundma selle pärast et mõne neist ukse taha oleks jätnud), ja jõin “Felicity” vaatamise kõrvale ära veel järgi jäänud pool pudelit veini. Laualt musti nõusid kokku korjata muidugi ei saanud, sest pimedas on pisut riskantne kergesti purunevate asjadega jännata.  Pärast õhtul leiutasin mõnda aega kuidas nurgas kasti peal seisvat arvutit jälle käima saada. Asi oli kahtlane, sest kõik teised osad peale monitori vilgutasid oma tulesid tavalise innuga… too aga ei kõssagi… vaatasin lausa mitu korda üle, et kõik juhtmed ikka sees oleksid… kolmandal korral monitori taha vaatamisel selgus aga, et mitte kaugel juhtme august on tal ka ON/OFF lüliti, mis, nagu te ehk isegi oskate arvata, ei olnud parasjagu ON’i peal. Ma olin juba suht lähedal kapist vana arvuti monitori välja otsimisele… Hea et niigi läks.
     

        
</post>
<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Kõht on tühi. Juba eile õhtul oli, aga ma ignoreerisin seda ja läksin magama. Oleks siis veel, et mul oleks mingi õudne dieet ja enesenäljutamine käsil, aga ei ole ju.  Öösel ei juhtunud ka midagi põnevat, unesid ei mäleta ega midagi. Ma olin küll õhtul natuke mures selle pärast, et mis öösel saab, sest enne magama minekut sirvis mu õde netis pilte arstitudengite esimestest jõupingutustest päris inimkehaga tutvumisel (kel uudishimu ja külma närvi jagub, võib ka vaadata  urlLink siit ).  Igal juhul kui ma mäletaks oma täna-öiseid unenägusid, ja kui neis oleks samal määral peegeldunud eelneva päeva sündmuste järelkaja kui eile, siis ei oleks mul ilmselt kõige meeldivamad unenäod olnud. Nüüd ei saa me seda aga kunagi teada.  Kuulsin hommikul raadiost ka juba esimese vastukajasid eilsele Matrix’i kolmanda osa esilinastusele. Räägitakse, et ei pidanud eriti hea film olema, aga ega ma selle pärast seda ilmselt vaatamata ikka ka ei jäta (kus see loogika on siin?).  Siis veel üks asi, mida ma juba mõnda aega olen mõelnud tõestada on, et  urlLink wordi dokumentide  web'i ülesse panemine on lihtsamast lihtsam. Sama kehtib muide ka  urlLink exceli  kohta. Tarvitseb vaid ülesse laadida ja töötab nagu muiste, ilma igasuguste trikkideta!  Ok, tegelikult ma saan aru küll kui katkendlik ja kehv mu tänane sissekanne olnud on. Kui ikka inspiratsiooni pole, siis ei tasuks teine kord ilmselt üldse kirjutama hakatagi... 
     

        
</post>
<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Ma nägin öösel unes Mr. S’i. See oli kohe pärast seda kui mu akna taga keeristorm möllanud olid, unes muidugi.  Igal juhul ta üritas mulle midagi öelda. Rääkis midagi, et oli mulle sõnumi saatnud, ja miks ma ei vastanud, aga kui ma vaatasin et kas ma tõesti olen vahepeal sõnumeid saanud ilma seda ise teadmata, siis ei olnud. Selleni aga, et mulle öelda mis ta öelda oli tahtnud, ta ei jõudnudki.  Inspiratsioon selle teemalisteks unedeks tuli ilmselt eile õhtusest kohtumisest temaga. Ok, me küll päris ei kohtunud, aga just siis kui ma koju jõudsin jõudis ka tema, ainult et ma põgenesin koridori kaitsvasse rüppe juba enne kui ta autost välja sai. Kui ainult seda naisterahvast poleks tulnud… siis oleks mul võimalus olnud veel kauem oma koti kallal kohmitseda ja aega viita võtmeid otsides… mine tea, äkki oleksin talle isegi tere öelnud.  Põhjuse paanikaks leidsin aga alles mõni aeg hiljem, juba kodus olles, kui avastasin et Mr. S endiselt midagi oma auto juures kohmitseb, ja sellele järgnevalt, et ta kohmitseb seal midagi seoses mingi mööblitükiga! Oh õudust! Ainuüksi mõte sellest et ta võiks ära kolida, ja jätta mind ilma minu elu ainukesest rõõmust – stalkimisest, oli kohutav. Samas oli päris meeldiv teda seal taguots püsti ukerdamas näha – minu kullakallis nagu ta on, every last inch of him.
     

        
</post>
<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Noh, kingade ostmisest ei tulnud nagu tavaliselt mitte midagi välja. Ju mu jalad on siis nii värdjad, et pole ette nähtud. Peale vaadates nagu ei arvakski, aga kui mingit asja jalga proovima hakkad, siis selgub, et mu jalakesed on umbes poole laiemad, ja poole kõrgemad kui ette nähtud, ja kui juhuslikult peaks tekkima soov osta midagi millel ka mingisugune sääre osa on, siis võib selle mõtte juba eos maha matta, sest mu jalake on ka sellest küljest nii palju ülemõõduline, et eile ühe saapakese lukku oli ainult alumise 2 cm ulatuses võimalik sulgeda, kui sedagi.  Ühesõnaga, jääb mulje, nagu ma oleksin troll kuskilt maagilisest metsast, kes on enda teadmata sattunud elama sirejalgsete (nr. 36 kingi kandvate) haldjate juurde.  Koti ma vähemalt sain. Ma ei ütle kust. Te hakkaksite naerma. Ma ei ütle palju maksis ka – te arvaksite tast märksa halvemini kui tal tegelikult välja nägemist on.  Ja kingapoodide kammimisest alati (või vähemalt nendel enamustel kordadel kui asi lootusetult ja tulutult lõppeb) tekkivast masendusest sain ka tänu kahele tassile kohvile, Riksti ema kohupiima-õuna koogile ja tõelise armastuse võidule (Great Expectations TV3s) üle.  Täna leiutan tööl igasugu asendeid kuidas oma riideid võimalikult vähe kortsu ajada, sest mul pole enne vastuvõtule minemist enam aega koju riideid vahetama minna. Ei oska nagu ette kujutadagi mis seal toimuma hakkab. Kui hästi läheb, siis tunnen ma seal veel ühte inimest, loomulikult peale oma bossi, keda ma võimalikult palju vältida sooviksin. Ma nägin eile õhtul juba soomekeelseid unenägusid, peale selle ei ole tema läheduses viibimine eriti söömisega seotud hetkedel kuigivõrd meeldiv – tal nimelt pole eriti lauakombeid. Ma pean ainult meeles pidama, et ma automaadist raha võtaksin, et kui asi hakkab juba liiga ebameeldivaks minema, siis takso tellida, kuigi enne seda võib muidugi ka veel kiirelt paar-kolm drinki teha, et kodus kõige maha jääva hea ja parema pärast kurvastama ei peaks.   P.S. kas teile hakkab ka tunduma selle jutu järgi, et mul on mingid alkoholiprobleemid? 
     

        
</post>
<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Last Friday was Halloween. Halloween is by no means a traditional Estonian holiday, in fact, only for the past few years some youngsters have been using it as an excuse to dress up and get drunk. Not my kind of thing really, especially dressing up.  So, despite of actually thinking that someday I do want to carve at least one pumpkin just to see if it’s fun and what it’s really like, my celebrations this year were limited to purchasing a can of pumpkin-apricot juice on the day after Halloween. It was surprisingly good actually (especially when mixed with sweetened condensed milk and Cointreau), but not my favorite juice of all times.  In an hour, when I’ll be finally able to leave this place, after doing absolutely nothing for the entire day (not that there wouldn’t be anything to do, but I had more interesting things on my mind like the release of The Sims 2 in March next year, and the half-price day in  urlLink Neopia ). Anyways, when I’ll finally be able to leave, I’m going to have to deal with one of my least favorite things of all – purchasing footwear. I mean, I don’t 100% necessarily have to do it, but it’s either that or wearing flip-flops tomorrow. So I’ve been thinking if I will find anything that’s even remotely ok, I’ll probably have to relieve my bank account accordingly. I also need a new purse actually. If I were at least a somewhat classy person I’d probably think it’s important that the shoes and the bag match somehow, but this is really not the case here. It’s more like a combination of an “interesting” monetary situation (AKA not having any) that I have encountered during the past year, and my general tendency to be a bit of a cheapskate (especially when clothing and footwear is concerned), which has left me with nothing to wear to an official buffet-dinner in the EC delegation tomorrow.
     

        
</post>
<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I feel it’s time to write again.  Yesterday was such a wonderful day. The 30 m/s wind along with heavy snowfall and blizzards didn’t really bother me at all. Sure I had to make my way on foot for a few kilometers just to reach a street where there was still at least some kind of traffic movement, and thus a possibility to use public transportation for the rest of the way, but I’m not complaining. I was almost appropriately dressed (it must have been a divine intervention which made me wore pantyhose and some rather adequate footwear in the morning, the only thing missing was a hat, but I can’t have it all, can I?), and I made the right decision in deciding to keep moving and not to spend at least half an hour or more standing in the trolley stop where probably no trolley had been seen for hours already. In the end, it was nothing that a hot cup of tea and a bath could not have cured quite easily. At least we will have a white Christmas, maybe a bit wet to actually move about outside, but pleasant enough to look at through the window.  But there are things besides feeling empowered (pedestrians over the cars thing probably, cause the cars were really going nowhere for hours) that made yesterday a lovely day. First of all – Mr. A might be coming to Estonia, and more specifically to Tallinn for the New Year. If that in fact were the case, this might become my most memorable new year’s eve to date. I still have to figure out something to do though. I doubt he would actually have any plans.  Second little reason for rejoicing is that I found out that one my favorite PÖFF films – “Buddy” will be shown in Estonian cinemas sometime next year – I can’t wait to see it again, and maybe again, and again…  Third one – Bryan Adams keeps adding dates and locations to his next year’s  urlLink European tour . I’m thinking maybe he will just happen to come here as well. At least there’s hope.  That’s about it too. I could maybe find something more, but something really annoying has just come to my attention, and I’ve lost the positive vibes…
     

        
</post>
<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Tagasi vanasse rutiini. Kurnav ja masendav oli kui vahepeal tõepoolest tööd oli, aga õnneks läks see nüüd jälle hetkeks mööda – ma tean et pisut tuleb homme ja järgmisel nädalal veel tegutseda, aga pärast seda… kes seda oskab ette arvata… õigemini mina oskan – vaevalt et mul midagi olulist peale  urlLink Neopetsi  lahti oleks.  Osa pingeid taandus taas kord seoses ilma soojenemisega. Ma oleks nädalavahetusel peaaegu juba arvama hakanud, et Eestimaa talved on piisavalt külmad et endale talvesaapad ostma peaks – samas ei ole ma üldse kurb et mu hetkeline meeltesegadus valeks osutus. Võib-olla peaks muidugi ikka ostma, mitte just otseselt praktilistest kaalutlustest lähtudes, vaid pigem et mõne nädala pärast kui ma väga suure tõenäosusega oma noorepõlve armastust taas kohtan vähem linnabimbolik mulje jätta. Kingakestega lumevallide vahel ja jääkonarustel komberdamine ei aita sinna vist väga kaasa. Teisest küljest, ma ei ole ka kindel kas ainult jalanõud ka aitavad…  Seda teemat jätkates, eelmise nädalavahetuse uued perspektiivid panid mind mõtlema selle võimaluse üle, et kuigi ma olen pealinnas sündinud ja kogu oma elu erinevates suurtes linnades elanud – kas oleks siiski võimalik et ma võiksin kunagi elama kolida mõnda väiksemasse linna või lausa maale. Välistada seda ju ei saa. Praegu aga, kui ma ei ole kunagi kuskil mujal elanudki, siis on raske endale aru anda kui palju mulle päriselt tähendab mõni linna mugavustest. Armastuse pärast? – selle nimel olen ma paljuks võimeline, kuigi loodetavasti mitte enda ambitsioonide ja mina täielikuks kaotamiseks, tegelikult olen ma suhteliselt kindel et nii hulluks see ei lähe, kuigi oma energiat ümber suunata annab oludele vastavalt kindlasti.
     

        
</post>
<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Can you imagine that – I was actually working almost non-stop from last Friday afternoon until now, that is Wednesday lunchtime. Even did a few hours worth of overtime. If I had any guts I’d go ahead and ask Christmas Eve off work next week, because it is supposed to be a shorter working day anyways, and with them almost three hours of overtime – I’m thinking I deserve it. Most probably there won’t be anything to do here anyways… but we’ll see. I can’t actually imagine working on Christmas Eve – last few years I’ve had quite many last minute shopping obligations, but overall, Christmas Eve in Estonia is basically the most important day of Christmas, so the perspective of getting up before 7 on that special day to do something I’d rather not be doing is not a pleasant one.  Other than that – I should really be thinking about Christmas presents – I have a few ideas, which is surprising, but many of them are rather expensive and I’m not quite sure – maybe too expensive. Perhaps I should look for collaborators as I have done during previous years; just because I can’t really afford a good gift is also not a good enough reason to give someone a crappy one.
     

        
</post>
<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I had so forgotten how good it feels to flirt, and how great it feels the next day when your mind is filled with a thousand scenarios of how things might develop in the future.  I'm in this state now - discovering new perspectives, trying to figure out if there is any chance of finding common ground with this person in the future. Unfortunately I don't know him too well, thus I'm also having trouble making up my mind about how I would prefer things to go. What I do know, though, is that we have quite different backgrounds, so I can't even use my own reasoning in order to mimic his mind.  But it is all so much more complicated than it has ever been… I've had crushes on this guy since I was like 10 or 12 or something, and now...
     

        
</post>
<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      PÖFF on läbi, ja ma igatsen teda juba taga. 10 filmi 10 päeva jooksul oli küll pisut palju, aga seda Hollywoody junki tahan ma nüüd veel vähem näha kui enne. Jäin oma senise filmivalikuga lõpuks üpris rahule. Üritasin oma list’i koostada nii et see oleks võimalikult mitmekesine nii žanrite kui ka filmide päritolumaade järgi ning lõpptulemus oli selline:   -  urlLink "Jah, õde, ei, õde"  (“JA ZUSTER, NEE ZUSTER”), rež.: Pieter Kramer, Holland, 2002 - muusikal  -  urlLink "Rohelised lihunikud"  ("DE GRØNNE SLAGTERE"), rež.: Anders Thomas Jensen, Taani, 2003 - must komöödia  - "Äkki" ("TAN DE REPENTE"), rež.: Diego Lerman, Argentiina, 2002 - road movie  -  urlLink "Semu"  ("BUDDY"), rež.: Morten Tyldum, Norra, 2003 - noortefilm  - "Kivid" ("PIEDRAS"), rež.: Ramón Salazar, Hispaania, 2002 - draama  -  urlLink "Oaas"  ("OASIS"), rež.: Lee Chang-dong, Lõuna-Korea, 2002 - draama  - "Dogville'i pihtimused" ("DOGVILLE CONFESSIONS"), rež.: Sami Martin Saif, Taani, 2003 - dokfilm  - "Läbi ja lõhki" ("GANZ UND GAR"), rež.: Marco Kreuzpaintner, Saksamaa, 2003 - noortefilm  - "Rändurid ja võlurid" ("TRAVELLERS AND MAGICIANS"), rež.: Khyentse Norbu, Bhutan, 2003 - muinasjutufilm  -  urlLink "Dogville"  ("DOGVILLE"), rež.: Lars von Trier, Taani, Rootsi, Suurbritannia, Prantsusmaa, Saksamaa, 2003) - draama 
     

        
</post>
<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Asju mida võiks meeles pidada kui on tahtmine hommikul õigeks ajaks tööle jõuda:   - Hommikune äratuskella helin on ilmselt ikkagi pigem sulle suunatud kui su õele, kes niikuinii nii vara tõusma ei pidanud  - Valguse ja helide varjamiseks pea teki alla pistmine ei ole maailma kindlaim viis mitte sisse magamiseks  - Veel 5 minutit magamist ei lõppe MITTE KUNAGI 5 minuti pärast  - Kui väljas hakkab juba koitma, ja see tundub kummaline, siis oled ilmselt tööle juba lootusetult hiljaks jäänud  - Teatavast unepuuduse astmest alates ei aita tõesti enam unisuse vastu midagi muud peale magamise  … kõike seda arvesse võttes võikski ju aeg-ajalt normaalsel ajal magama minna, eriti kui juba mitmendat päeva ärkamisega raskusi, ainult et täna on mul ju veel linnas, asja (PÖFF, ikka PÖFF…), ning siis tuleb koju jõudmise puhul äkki veel ka pisut telekat vaadata, et õigesse meeleolusse saada enne kui lõpuks saab voodisse poetud nii umbes kesköö paiku, mis tähendab, et ööuned jäävad jälle pisut napiks…
     

        
</post>
<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      It wasn’t a bad movie, really, it wasn’t… but still maybe I shouldn’t have gone to see it – especially when I had the not so frequent possibility of being in love with the world and life as such before that. And of course it’s gone now. It’s weird really – all the characters in the movie ended up being better off in the end, but the journey there was so difficult and depressing at times, it ended up overshadowing the happy end. I didn’t leave the theater filled with hope and looking forward to a better future – my life is definitely not screwed enough for it to work out like that at this point. 
     

        
</post>
<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Oh, oleks ometi kõik päevad sellised - täis ilusaid mehi, lootus ja armastust… Praegu käib PÖFF, ja mina, kui enese poolt tituleeritud filmispets ja muidu tore inimene, otsustasin sel aastal korralikult osaleda - iga päev üks film, mis teeb siis kokku ei vähem ega rohkem kui 10!  Täna, neljandal päeval, nägi minu filmikava ette Norra noortekomöödia, millel inglise keelseks nimeks "Buddy". Nii tore film oli! Midagi muud on hetkel isegi raske öelda… Selline ütlemata armas, aga samas realistlik (või olen mina jälle eriliselt naiivne?), igal juhul lahkusin ainult positiivsete elamustega, millest ei võtnud grammigi vähemaks filmile järgnenud küsimuste ja vastuste sessioon, kus oli kohal peategelase Kristofferi osatäitja Nicolai Cleve Broch, kes vähemalt filmis äärmiselt nauditav oli (päriselus küll pisut liiga lühike ja hetkel väheste juustega:().  Mul oli juba laupäeval pärast esimest ülimeeldivat elamust selline tunne, et kas tasubki enam oma õnnega mängima hakata ning muid filme vaadata, mine tea äkki rikub veel üldmulje ära, aga õnneks pole seda veel siiani juhtunud. :) Loodetavasti läheb mul sama hästi võiduka lõpuni! 
     

        
</post>
<date>16,Jaanuar,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I'm thinking I'm tired of html. There has got to be some kind of a solution for a server such as this, which supports PHP, but doesn't have access to any databases... and I'm hoping this is it now.  20.04.04 - täna on see päev kus ma siis selle asja tegelikult kasutusele võtsin. Miks täpselt võib lugeda tänast kuupäeva kandvast post'ist. Kõik teised post'id mille siit enne tänast leida võite olid algselt teises formaadis ühe teise koha peal, aga mulle meeldib kui kõik asjad ilusti koos on, nii et...
     

        
</post>
<date>09,Jaanuar,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Lot’s of fun coming up this time… Let’s start from an audit scheduled to start next week where special attention is devoted to the project I’m working for. Unfortunately those poor people are going to find out that the financial accounts for that project are kept in Finland, and are not a concern of the Estonian party at all… well… I don’t know what will happen then.  Secondly, I was faced with an interesting dilemma – which would be more pleasant – an audit or a visit to dentist? A difficult one, don’t you think? I think at the moment I’d choose the dentist, perhaps because it’s been such a long time since my last visit that I can’t really recall all the ways in which it can be unpleasant, or maybe because at the dentist’s I can’t be blamed for much (maybe only not exercising sufficient care in brushing and flossing), while the result of the audit could be more directly tied to my self-esteem and well-being.
     

        
</post>
<date>09,Jaanuar,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Ma ei tea, kas see on minu paranoilisusest tingitud, aga miski tuli väga tuttav ette kui üks vana tuttav palus mul saata talle oma kehtivad isikuandmed selleks et ta saaks oma vastavasisulist andmebaasi täiendada. Mul tekkis tahtmine öelda, et kuna mina olin see kes selle triki kunagi kuus aastat tagasi välja mõtles samalt inimeselt minu jaoks tollal elulise tähtsusega informatsiooni (sünnipäev ehk siis tähtkuju jms.) hankimiseks, siis nii loll ma ju ometi poleks, et teiste poolt üles seatud lõksu langeks, aga järgmisel hetkel viskusin ometi ilmse sisemise naudinguga sellesama orgi otsa… Ma võin ju ometi veidikenegi mõelda et see lõks ehitati minu jaoks, et tal tegelikult ei olnud kogu aeg plaanis selle aasta algul midagi ette võtta oma tuttavate elust parema ülevaate saamiseks.
     

        
</post>
<date>09,Jaanuar,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Täna on jälle üks neist “sõima oma bossi” päevadest. Ta paneb ikka sellist segast vahepeal, et ma tõesti ei imesta enam kuskilt otsast miks ma eile järeldusele jõudsin, et ma teda karvavõrdki ei usalda – ma ei usalda teda siis kui ta mulle räägib mida keegi teine öelnud oli – elu on näidanud, pahatihti tema arusaam ei ühti tegelikkusega. Ma ei usalda teda võimeline olema kaasa võtma ja mitte ära kaotama vajalikke pabereid, kirjutusvahendeid jne. Ma ei usalda isegi tema statistilist asjatundlikkust, sest senini pole ta seda vähemalt adekvaatselt väljendada osanud, ta ei tea tegelikult isegi milline see nende Soome süsteem on, mida heaks eeskujuks võttes Eesti oma üles ehitatama peaks, sest ta on seal juba nii kaua ülemuseks olnud, ja ülemused teatavasti, ei tea töö tegemisest suurt midagi.
     

        
</post>
<date>09,Jaanuar,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Soon I will start counting the days left until the end of my employment contract. It gives me nothing (except money) to sit here. From one side I could be learning about statistics, but then again, what would be the point – I’ve always hated it, and if should ever need it I can always learn it then - God knows I’ve studied all these things already three times, and each time forgotten them so completely afterwards I have to start all over again.  What will become of me when this sitting strike is over, though, I don’t know? I know I could raise the 40000EEK to start a business of my own, and I even have one business idea… But I’ll have to give it some careful consideration before I jump into anything. It wouldn’t exactly be wise to through my money away just like that either, there has to be at least a fair chance of success before I’ll get myself involved in anything like that. I’d love the benefits though, being able to work whenever I want to, from wherever I want to etc. I’m really not the person who can be productive every day from 8 to 5. Some days, I’m not productive at all, and the rest of them I’m usually the most productive at some point late in the evening, so honestly, why torture myself by having to sit still from as early on as when I’d rather be having my wildest dreams until the end of all daylight and thus the only possibility of accomplishing something without major discomfort outdoors. Maybe I should venture out on my own into the wilderness of the business world?
     

        
</post>
<date>09,Jaanuar,2004</date>
<post>


           
      “If God wanted those ducks around they wouldn’t be an endangered species.”  I’ve started the year off with an inspiring quote from one of the episodes of “Dharma and Greg” that I watched for a second last night. Makes you think, doesn’t it? In my case the effect is more of an affirming my disbelief, for some others it might raise some serious questions.  Looking back now, Christmas was true to its name. The good thing about it was this year, that me and two of my sisters managed to come up with pretty good gift ideas, regardless of the cost (although I do feel a bit guilty now asking my sisters for their share of the expenses, when I know they have so much less money than I do). When the gifts had been bought and wrapped the eating started – pork straight up for three days in a row is not a laughing matter… and all that chocolate, I think I should add a clause to my next year’s letter to Santa saying that please don’t bring me any chocolate, honestly, I can afford to buy some when I really feel like I can’t do without. Having half a kilo lying around is just not healthy. I’d maybe even go ahead and start with a diet or something, if I didn’t have to eat all that chocolate before I can even start…  Anyways, the new year has arrived – 2004 – the first time I’ve had to write it so far. It will probably take some time to get used to, as it always does. It came actually pretty well. Mr. A was here and I did see him, but that was not at all the best part of it. By the time we met it was pretty late (and I was getting tired having had quite a little sleep for the past two nights), and I think we were a bit off sync as well, so although it was good to see him, I was also disappointed in that he just doesn’t do it for me any more.  The best part though, was before midnight, when we were sitting with Ms. M, a dear friend of mine, in a bar watching the bartender go out of his way to entertain us. He was pretty relentless in his effort to through around each bottle and glass and slice of lemon before it reached its final destination in a drink. He only managed to break two glasses as far as I know – two in a row actually. :) He was fun, and strangely intriguing, and at some point he gave us a refill on the red wine for free when no one else was looking, so my heart was spoken for in an instant.  For the actual moment of the arrival of the New Year we went to outside to Vabaduse Väljak, where the fireworks could best be seen. I make a point of seeing the fireworks, at least when I’m in town. It just isn’t the same without them. They were also pretty enough this time to fulfill my expectations.  On the evening of the 1st of January was the Estonian Premiere of the “Return of the King” – the last of the Lord of the Rings movies. My sisters,  urlLink the official fans , were of course all psyched out about it. They made themselves elf-like dresses and participated in the dressed parade of Estonian LotR fans that took place before the Premiere. I was too much in the mood of the 1st of January (sleepy and lazy that is) to get to town early enough to go and see them. I went to see the movie though, and I must say it was pretty good. I realized it at that point when the troops from Rohan arrived in the battle, and I was moved by the speech and the devotion of fighting for what you believe in although you’re greatly outnumbered. I though to myself that if going to war (which I don’t believe in) can move me, then it must be an excellent movie.  Of course there were a few minor things, which I thought were not so well presented. The scene where Pippin looks into the ball… that didn’t do it for me, it was just so strange. The musical score in the scene where Frodo leaves Sam in the mountains was particularly cheerful, and therefore inappropriate in my mind. Denethor in flames falling off the cliff in Minas Tirith was comical – probably unintended... but overall, as I already said, a great movie indeed.  Which now just about brings me into the present moment – the two weeks of just minor visits to work are over and I’m sitting here once again ready to face the last six months of my work tasks here (the current perspective). The problem is, though, that my boss is at home and sick today, so the task of deciding whether to stay at work till five o’clock or sneak out early is upon me once again. I think I’ll sneak out early – just how early is another matter.
     

        
</post>
<date>09,Jaanuar,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Day light saving time took about two days to get used to it seems, or maybe it’s the sunshine that boosts my energy levels so high that I no longer feel like just tipping over my desk every other moment.  I also wanna be in love. It’s spring, and I’m unbelievably bored, and all I can think of to do is to fall head over heals for someone who could keep my mind occupied in these never-ending three months that separate me from the end of this job a.k.a. summer vacation. I’ve tried browsing through the always-gorgeous celebrities, but no buzz there this time. Could it be that as an almost 24-yearold my mind is finally grasping the concept that although they in fact are real people, for me, who lives thousands of miles away from Hollywood, they might as well be fictional characters? Maybe the fact that the purpose of our pre-programmed affection towards the opposite sex is not to obtain yet another imaginary friend is finally sinking in? I’m afraid it doesn’t make much of a difference what I think, though. There is just no one who would actually be willing to tattoo my name to his forearm – a gesture that I in general regard as stupid, but I believe I’d be impressed as hell if someone did it for me.
     

        
</post>
<date>09,Jaanuar,2004</date>
<post>


           
      My dreams just keep getting weirder and weirder… last night there was a war going on in my head and my mother was dead for a while, I think there was even a funeral, but then afterwards she miraculously showed up alive again from some place.  Maybe that’s what happens when I watch horror movies – “What Lies Beneath” was on TV last night, and although I decided not to watch it after being rather bored for the first half an hour, it still managed to creep me out in some sense. I actually thought it hadn’t reached that point yet, but I guess it had… The thing with horror movies for me is that there is a certain snapping point when I know that although it is terrible I now have to watch it until the conclusion to receive at least some kind of an explanation – for what, I don’t know, maybe it is some kind of preparation for the not so real chance of the same ordeal ever happening to me. Realistically I know it never will, but sometimes not so realistic things happen, don’t they?
     

        
</post>
<date>09,Jaanuar,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I slept too well tonight, in fact so well that the second half of the night I spent in a state of balancing between consciousness and sleep. In that state I had another one of my Mr. S dreams.  I think the venue must have been Paris, for the building I lived in looked like something from “Amelie”.  It all started with him wanting to explain to me about the unresolved issues between us, but I’m thinking we never got to the talking part. ;) I know he wanted to explain to me something about being happy with his current girlfriend, but then we kissed instead and next thing I remember was he showing up behind my door to pick me up for some sort of official party, but he acted all weird and stuff so I decided to ditch him instead.  Actually, it is starting to seam surreal that I ever knew him at all in real life.
     

        
</post>
<date>09,Jaanuar,2004</date>
<post>


           
      First I'd like to sleep it off, and then I'd really want to go to the movies... Last night was THE night of the year - the Oscars - I ended up not getting any decent sleep at all, I might have dozed off a few times before the red carpet reception started, but not for more than 5 to 15 minutes at a time, and I'm not quite sure actually I did at all... I almost fell asleep during the wee hours when I decided to use the commercial breaks for getting some down time, don't think I actually missed anything though, and when it all ended it was very appropriately time to take a quick shower and head to work.  So... This year wasn't a particularly good year for the Oscars. I do agree that LotR deserved a few golden dudes, for it was an enormous effort, but it sort of felt like they over-did a little - holding back the last two years, and now feeling guilty because of it? It was dead boring for it to win in every category it was nominated in. The one that I don't agree with the most was actually the Original Song category, one of the very few where I had a personal favourite, and my choice would have been Sting's "You Will Be My Ain True Love" from "Cold Mountain". I only saw "Cold Mountain" on Thursday last week, and I can't seem to be able to get it out of my head. It's not only Jude Law's ravishing blue eyes, Nicole Kidman as an ultimate personification of beauty and talent, and Renee Zellweger with her great performance (although I'm not much of a fan of hers in general), but also the song... And I'm not really the type of person who would fall for music from a motion picture. Take for instance that Bryan Adams is someone for whom I have a great deal of respect, but those sappy movie ballads of his - NO WAY!  I also thought that Johnny Depp is someone who should finally receive the recognition he deserves. I've seen him in a number of roles one weirder than the other, and he has not once failed to live up to his characters. I'm quite sure his choice of a place of residence and his general wariness in dealing with all things American has had its toll on his likeability in Hollywood. I really hope that he will consider being nominated as a reward in itself, for it was already something rather unlike the Academy we (or at least I) have come to know.  Sadly, not even Billy Crystal seemed to be in his best shape, I have distant memories of him being genuinely funny, but this time it didn’t get any further than an automatic involuntary burst every now and then, which then faded into me thinking what on earth could I have been thinking to laugh at a joke like that… sad, quite sad really…  In general all there is left is to hope that next year will be better, that there will be movies made worth considering, that the Academy will make a sufficiently diverse choice of nominees, and that all expectations will be crowned in a ceremony that has pace, wits, charm and unexpected moments to remember for years to come, for at the moment I’m not really sure what will happen when there’s not even Adrian Brody to save the day for those 15 seconds of his encapturing appearance.
     

        
</post>
<date>02,Aprill,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I discovered a major dislike - toilet tanks that take forever to fill up again once you've flushed them. In addition to increasing water pressure, cleaning the pipelines and valves, I could also recommend introducing see-through water tanks in toilets. If I knew there was only 3 centimetres in the tank I would probably be less anxious to flush it over and over again without much result. It seems every day comes with its own great ideas. When will I ever carry any of them out in real life? Wouldn't you like a colourful plastic water tank in your toilet? Reminds me of the Mac computers that come in a variety of colors... Let me know if you'd like to get one, maybe it's my destiny to be the queen of toilets?
     

        
</post>
<date>02,Aprill,2004</date>
<post>


           
      There is a preliminary proposal to hold an Estonian grown-up  urlLink Neopets  players convention this summer. I thought the idea was interesting. In fact I thought it was surreal enough to participate. :) Which brings us to the next issue - people are making plans for the summer! I have also known since Christmas that certain weekends are "booked", and actually I even tried making some other plans about a month ago, but then I got caught up in the monetary issues, and decided to ditch the idea of going to London, and for some reason making other plans didn't seem significant at the time... I'm not saying there's cause for any alarm. It's still April for gods sake! But the heat is bound to arrive some day, and as we all know, in Estonia, you never know how long it's gonna stay, so one should definitely try to make the most of it. Which means I will gladly take some of my remaining 44,5 working days and spend it going through the calendar making future plans for the summer.
     

        
</post>
<date>02,Aprill,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Sünnipäevaga selleks korraks vist ühel pool. Läks täitsa talutavalt, ei jäänud arme tulevasteks aastateks. :) Ainuke asi mida kõrva taha panna on see, et mu korter on liiga väike, või siis liiga ebafunktsionaalne. Kurb oli see, et vanaisa tulla ei saanud. Ta on küll jälle haiglast väljas, aga tunneb ennast tihti nii kehvasti, et ei taha kodust kaugele minna, lihtsalt juhuks kui tekib möödapääsmatu tahtmine pikali visata. Osalt ei julge teda vaatama ka minna – eelmine kord kui käisime sai ta pärast mingi viiruse ja siis oli tal veel kehvem olla. Aga näha teda ju ometi tahaks, seni kuni veel võimalust on. Positiivsed uudised – ei ühtegi nõmedat kingitust. Aitäh kõigile! Kui nüüd veel vannitoa remondi ära lõpetatud saaks võiks hooga uute ilustusprojektide kallale asuda. Järgmine, ma arvan, on köök. Tegelikult peaks ennast kokku võtma ja köögi ja toa vahelise seina maha võtma. Kui palju selline töö ikka maksta saab? Segasem on see, et ma tean et mul on selleks mingit luba vaja, kui mitte rohkemat, siis vähemalt korteriühistult. Enamuse muuga peale lõhkumise peaks omapäi hakkama saama, aeg mille jooksul see toimuma saab on muidugi iseasi. Vannituba on vist juba kaks aastat töös. :p 
     

        
</post>
<date>02,Aprill,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Tänane päev ei ole mõeldud töö tegemiseks. Kodus magamiseks oleks ta muidugi enam kui sobilik, ei mingit ohtu et päike silma paistaks ning ühtlaselt uinutav vee tilkumise hääl akna taga. Mul vajuvad silmad kinni juba lihtsalt selle peale mõeldes... :) Üleeile oli mul sünnipäev, kuigi mässasin siis pool päeva oma vanade kirjutuste siia ümber tõstmisega (ja teise poole päeva peo organiseerimisega, sest tööd ju ometi teha ei või) ei jätnud ma tookord maha jälge sellest, et see päev ka kuidagi muud moodi oluline oleks olnud. Ilmselt oli mul niigi hea olla, ja tegelikult oligi.  Mis aga puutub sünnipäeva tähistamisse, siis olen seda sel aastal võimalikult palju edasi lükanud, esialgu alateadlikult igasugu vabandusi tuues, aga eile jõudis mulle kohale, et lükkaksin seda veel hea meelega indefinitely edasi... Õnneks ei ole tegemist kartusega vanaks saada, pigem lihtsalt - noh, oma kõige nõmedama sünnipäevapeo pidasin ma juba ära - töö juures, ja see oli ikka nõme küll, nii et ma olen pigem natuke ettevaatlik, ei tahaks nagu rohkem negatiivseid emotsioone seoses millegagi mis peaks ju ikka pigem positiivne olema. Kui mitte kunagi valmis saav toa koristamise operatsioon välja arvata, siis on mul loodetavasti ainult veel üks veidi ebameeldiv tegevus seoses oma sünnipäevaga - helistada oma vanaemale ja ka tema endale külla kutsuda. Te mõtlete muidugi et kuidas saab see olla minu ebameeldivate asjade TOP 10's? Tegelikult pole me kunagi väga lähedased olnud, ja kuigi kunagi veetsin ma siiski päris tihti nädalavahetusel tema juures aega, sai see millalgi sel ajal läbi kui ma piisavalt suureks sain et mitte lasta endale pähe istuda. Aga lootus sureb viimasena, äkki möödub seekordne sünnipäev ilma piinlike momentideta ja alati kohal oleva ebamugavustundeta?
     

        
</post>
<date>02,Aprill,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Idiots, I knew there must have been a catch when they said they’d renew the firewall software and afterwards I could get access to some not work related things I couldn’t get to before. Well, as it turns out, they’ve killed FTP in the process. Which do you think is actually more harmful, me watching streaming video off the Internet for hours (which I now can do), or me uploading a few k’s of personal web page files every now and then? Only two months plus ten days to go any more before the end of this ordeal. Must survive...
     

        
</post>
<date>02,Aprill,2004</date>
<post>


           
      A guy who looked quite like Joseph Fiennes stared at me in the trolley last night.  Decided to take it as a compliment. Went home and checked myself out in the mirror just to be sure – still nothing wrong.
     

        
</post>
<date>21,Mai,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Täna hommikul, umbes kell 8.20, varitses meie maja ees keegi tütarlaps ja kinkis kõikidele tööle saabujatele ilmselgel reklaami eesmärgil ühe pakkikese Post-it’i  kleepjärjehoidjaid, mille teisele küljele on ära mahutatud ka reklaam paljude teiste samasse sarja kuuluvate toodete kohta. Õnneks on sellel ühel küljel joonlaud ka. Joonlauast olen ma juba mõnda aega puudust tundnud.
     

        
</post>
<date>21,Mai,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Right now I'm left wondering why is it that I'm supposed to think for everybody else? Why is it, that when I make a tiny mistake, or not even a mistake actually, maybe just I'm a little less careful, I don't spell everything out 100% and repeat and repeat and repeat all over again... Why is it that I feel like the world is crumbling down after that? Why is that if a person receives a paper that she doesn't know what to do with, she doesn't start wondering that if she didn't request it, maybe someone else did? I can sit here and sigh as much as I want to, but the truth is, I sent out requests for submitting IT training tenders 6 weeks ago. The date for submitting the tenders was 5 weeks ago, and today I find out that the one tender I received by e-mail wasn't actually the only one after all... there was another one that the personnel manager has graciously sat on until this very moment, I only found out about it from a third party. What else is there to do really, but sigh...
     

        
</post>
<date>21,Mai,2004</date>
<post>


           
      The first thing I did today was to find out that if I were a John Cusack character, I'd be      urlLink Which John Cusack Are You?    Cool! Being a hitman could turn out to be a little difficult at times, so I'll settle for Rob Gordon gladly.
     

        
</post>
<date>21,Mai,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Went to see The Butterfly Effect last night. It was one hell of a heavy movie, especially considering that I also have experienced things in my childhood I'd undo if I could. But then again, who would I even be in that case? Could the difference between the current me and the potential me without the dramatic childhood events be as vast as it was in the movie? Is it that everybody has some kind of an experience that has really traumatized them? Or is just me and I should really seek counselling? I actually considered it a few years ago, quite seriously. It was probably that I was finally realizing what had happened all those years ago, and of course as so much time has passed already, it is time for acceptance, for coming to terms with things... Maybe I have managed on my own. After all, the therapist can't undo any of it anyways, I'll always have my past and childhood as a part of me... and I've turned out ok more or less, I think. I'm sorry to have been so mysterious. I think you must be quite puzzled. I've only actually ever told the whole story to one person in real life, a friend with whom I've never been too close, and now we haven't caught up for years already. I think that at that point I just needed to say it out loud to someone, someone who wouldn't hold it against me, nor use it to analyze each and every step I do through that information. It's not that I wouldn't trust my current friends, but whatever happened back then does not define the majority of what I am today, so if it doesn't define me, why should I manifest it to the world? Actually some part of me would like to speak out on the Internet right here and right now, but I think I should tell my parents first, and I'm not ready to do that, or is it that I don't want to burden them? What could they possibly do now after all these years? They'd cry, and I'd cry, and it'd come down to accepting the past and moving on.
     

        
</post>
<date>14,Mai,2004</date>
<post>


           
      The thing I hate about any kind of job is when there's a problem, and I have to solve it, and I don't know how, and neither does anyone else. This time - I wasn't even the one who created the problem! The thing is, EU funding rules say that no money shall be allocated towards national taxes. We do have to buy some services and goods however, and the companies do tend to add VAT to those expenses. The clearest way (although time consuming and frustrating) would have been to apply for a 0% VAT from the Tax Board for all expenses occurred in this project (each one separately, though), but I was told the new Tax Law no longer enables that - all you can do now is to apply for a refund later... Which brought me right back to the original issue - if we can only ask for a refund later - who will initially pay for it? There are two parties in this project - a foreign party, who has custody of the EU money and is paying at least the non-tax part of the invoices, and the local beneficiary. It simply can't be paid from the project money, because that's still not allowed. I managed to somehow agree with the accounting department of the beneficiary organization, that they have funds that could be used, and as refunds are expected to occur - they actually didn't mind too much in the end... Procedure-wise I was still not quite sure though how it would work. If a company issues an invoice to the project (i.e. the foreign party), could I just make a copy of it to the beneficiary and would that be ok? Turns out - no. Fair enough actually, I also wouldn't want to be paying for stuff when the invoice is addressed to someone else. Solution - ask each company to submit two invoices, both containing the same numbers, and each addressed to a different party of the project... We purchased quite many things over the last two weeks already, however, and as I was not the one communicating with the companies, I was deprived of the "pleasure" of introducing this clever little schema to them. So now I have a bunch of regular invoices that are merely partially acceptable, which means I have had to tell a bunch of companies, that in order to see the entire amount that is due to them they'd have to come up with another invoice which would enable us to pay the VAT amount. And now I'm sitting here hearing them complain to me over the phone about how that would be just downright impossible for them. So you see - now they have a problem, and I still have a problem... and I'm just hoping they do something about their problem, because for them, at least some money is involved. And if they solve their problem, also mine will be solved... eventually.
     

        
</post>
<date>14,Mai,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I'm going to see "Troy" today. It was a decision that took quite a long time to make. I don't find any of the lead actors irresistible... The tag line about "the greatest battle ever fought" doesn't attract me at all... I've heard they've really been a bit too "creative" in the script writing department... but then I remembered that once upon a time the stories of the ancient world seemed very fascinating to me, and being the ever so naive and optimistic type that I am, a tiny little light started to shine at the end of the tunnel. "Maybe they haven't totally screwed it up", I thought. My friends all wanted to go anyway, so I'll go and see it too. Lets hope for the best.
     

        
</post>
<date>14,Mai,2004</date>
<post>


           
      So we didn't get to the finals... I'm not very upset about it - after all we finished in the better half of the semi-final, I think all I needed was proof that our song is not a total failure, and it wasn't. What I'm a little suspicious of, is the voting system. Once you never see the votes, and despite of their constant assurance that everything is being monitored, etc. Don't you still wonder if they're not manipulating the results just a little? Especially after the news surfaced that there actually were some errors in the initial vote counting... software errors to be specific... Or maybe it's just me... Ever the mathematician who just watches a song contest for the shear fun of seeing the numbers in the end. :)
     

        
</post>
<date>14,Mai,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Today is Eurovision semi finals. Occasionally I still manage to forget about it, but in general I think it's starting to sink in. There's no other night in a year that would have equal bashing potential, and this year we have two of them in one week. :p As usual, there are a few principal questions besides the position of the Estonian song "Tii" that need to be answered: How bad will the Finns do? (Note to self: Remeber to add a link here to a joke about Finns and Eurovision once you get round to it!) How horrible is the Lithuanian singer/song? The thing that comes to my mind about their past performance is a colourful knitted Jamaican style cap one of their performers wore a few years ago... and, well, I guess he couldn't sing either... can't actually remember any good songs from them so far. Unfortunately the Greeks have gone a little less kitsch this year, not that it would make me change my opinion of them, after all, they're the ones who came to Tallinn in 2002 singing the, to my mind infamous, "Sagapo". More on that tomorrow, though, and hopefully with good news from the first round.
     

        
</post>
<date>14,Mai,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I have done my duty, and more... for about 60 lifetimes to come. In Estonia there's a saying that each person should plant at least one tree during their lifetime, and we in our party of five planted about 300 birches on Sunday. It's not all that pretty though, I've been spending half the day today trying to look up on the Internet how to classify this bizarre rash and tiny blisters that are tormenting me on my hands, and feet, and most recently I found one on my lip too. Hopefully it will go away soon, it's been almost 5 years since I visited a doctor, and then also I only had to go to get a paper that proves there's nothing wrong with me. Dentists don't count here, must see one of those too by the way.
     

        
</post>
<date>14,Mai,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Kui mu töökokkuleppel ei tõotaks olla erakordselt magus lõpp, siis oleks praegu see hetk kui ma asju pakkima hakkaks ja minema jalutaks siit.  Ei, ok, ma olen ennast ühe eelmise töökohaga seoses ka hullemini tundnud. Tol korral muutus see mõte nõmedast tööpäevast nii valdavaks, et mul ööpäevas praktiliselt sellist aega enam polnudki mil ma selle peale mõelnud poleks. Eile avastasin ma, et hetkel olen ma siiski veel seisukorras mil paar esimest tundi pärast tööpäeva lõppu valdab mind kergendus, alles hiljem õhtul hakkan ma mõtlema, et pagan, homme peab jälle tööle minema, ja see tants aurukatla ümber läheb taaskord edasi...
     

        
</post>
<date>11,Juuni,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I went away from work for a couple of days, and when I came back I discovered that the IT guys have kept busy in the mean time blocking the Internet sites' functions (clicking any buttons such as 'log on' or 'delete mail' results in '111 - Connection refused') and MSN doesn't work, and maybe something else as well. The good news is, next week I'll go on a vacation, and after that I will continue only part-time, which means I'll be sitting behind other computers for the remainder of the hours in a day, and I can live my personal life from wherever these computers should happen to be. And when I re-configure my blogger account from some free-access computer, I'll be able to submit to it using regular e-mail, so that's how far your sophisticated cleverness takes you! I bet if I really wanted to I could possibly get around all the restrictions, but it's not worth it. Let the little people do they're job and be proud of it. :p 
     

        
</post>
<date>11,Juuni,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Olen tagasi online, ainult kaks ja pool päeva võttis pärast e-maili ja võrgu süsteemi vahetamist aega vana süsteemi tagasi installeerimine, sest uus, nagu valusalt näha oli esmaspäeva hommikul, ei töödanud (tegelikult ikka päris vanasse situatsiooni tagasi ei läinud). Õnneks pole see tegelikult minu probleem. Eile lugesin pool päeva ettenägelikult kaasa võetud raamatut Marilyn Monroe mõrva kohta ning mõtlesin et mida kõike ma võiksin teha kui kasvõi ainult Interneti-ühenduski oleks. Tühja sellest e-mailist ega ma seda tööd nii paaniliselt teha ei tahagi. Aga natuke kasulikku oli sellest arvutikuttide sebimisest ka. Võtsin eile inspireerituna tööl toimuvast oma koduse vanema arvuti ette (me kutsume teda hellitavalt Turbolehmaks) ja otsustasin teda veel kord parandada üritada enne kui ta lõplikult maha kannan. Temaga juhtus ükskord umbes kaks kuud tagasi selline asi, et teda tabas CMOS Setup Failure ja siis ma panin talle vist et Use Default Values, aga pärast seda väitis ta täie tõsidusega et ta üldse ei tea et tal kunagi sellised asjad nagu kõvaketas ja floppy drive oleks olemas olnud, ning ma ei suutnud muidugi ka avastada mis nuppu mida ma paaniliselt taguma peaksin et uuesti CMOS Setup'isse saada. Proovisin igasuguseid F-nuppe, aga kasu ei miskit. Eile aga, olid jumalad minuga, ja mul õnnestus silmanurgast tabada vihjet Del klahvile, mis, oh imet, mind ka soovitud tulemuseni viis. Õnneks vedas mul veel paar korda - kui ma olin umbes 5 minutit välja mõelda üritanud et millised kõvaketta parameetrid Turbolehmal olid, siis avastasin kaks rida allpoolt ka variandi 'Auto Detect'... ja pärast seda, ei uskunud ma isegi õieti oma silmi kui ta tõepoolest ennast üles bootis, ei mölisenud asjatult, ja isegi oma Win 95ga hakkama sai. Tal tundus lausa teine noorus olevat. Vähemalt vana hea CIV, mille tarvis ta meil seal nurgas üldse ongi oli ka märksa kiirem kui enne selle katsumuse algust, umbes nagu siis kui seda kunagi veel DOS'ist mängitud sai.
     

        
</post>
<date>11,Juuni,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Veetsin kaks päeva tööasjus Soomes. Just saabusin tagasi. Kummaline kuidas vahel on nii vähe vaja selleks et nii palju asju hakata hoopis teises valguses nägema. Esiteks, ma vabandan Helsingi linna ees, sest ma läksin sinna mingi iidvana aimdusega et Helsingi on üks igav koht. Tuli välja, et pole ta nii hull ühti, eriti kui parasjagu on piisavalt raha et ennast vabalt tunda. Seal on palju häid asju, mida Tallinnast kuskilt ei leia, kasvõi Magnumi jäätised ja  urlLink H 'i riidepoed. Teiseks pean tõdema, et mulle hakkas Helsingis olles tunduma, et eestlastel kui rahvusel on mingi lapsepõlvetrauma mis kandub põlvest põlve edasi (sest traumeeritud inimesed kipuvad ikka teisi edasi terroriseerima kui võimalus avaneb jne.) ja takistab meil normaalselt käitumast. See oli nii kummaline kuidas seal tänaval kõndides ei tule seda mõtetki et sa peaksid vabandama oma olemasolu pärast, püüdma kõigest väest kõigile meeldida ja mitte millegi erilisega silma paistma, ühesõnaga vabadus olla see kes sa tahad. Ma isegi ei oska öelda milles see väljendus, aga see tõdemus tabas mind nagu välk selgest taevast. Muidugi on sellel ka teine pool, kindlasti on teist enamus kuulnud räägitavat eestlaste kenast väljanägemisest, ja heast maitsest riietumise vallas. Mulle hakkas tunduma, et ainuke põhjus miks see nii on ühiskonna surve - kui sa ikka oled 120 kilo ja kablutad avalikult linnatänaval retuuside või miniseelikuga ringi, siis keegi kohe kindlasti vähemalt vaatab sinu poole halvustavalt kui mitte kõva häälega välja ei ütle. Samas ühte sellist tädi nägin ma Soomes töö juures liibukate pükstega mis väga hästi üleval ei paistnud püsivat, ja see tundus ok olevat. Mine nüüd võta siis kinni kumb parem on. Endale meeldiks kindlasti vabadus teha mida tahad, aga silmadele on ilus vaadata ikka ainult mingi piirini.
     

        
</post>
<date>04,Juuni,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Kõndisin täna pärast tööd ringi mööda Helsingi tänavaid. Selle suve kohta oli ilm soe (umbes 16C). Selline kummaline lapsepõlvetunne. Olin täpselt 7 aastat tagasi samal ajal Helsingis Bryan Adamsi kontserdil nr. 2 oma elus. Olin siis 17 aastat vana ja me sõbrannaga, vaesed nagu me olime, otsustasime et öömaja jaoks meil raha pole, niisiis ostsime tagasisõidupiletid esimesele hommikusele laevale ning veetsime öö mööda linna jalutades ja lobisedes ning lõpuks viimased tunnid niisama sadamakai peal istudes sest jalad olid juba liiga väsinud ja villides. Praegu sellele tagasi mõeldes tundub, et lapsevanem olla võib ikka päris kole olla. Vaevalt et nad eriti hästi magasid tollel ööl. Siis polnud ka veel mobiile, et teada anda et meiega kõik korras on. Igal juhul oli korras. Öö oli väga soe, võimalik et alla 20C ei langenudki, pimedaks ju ka sel ajal ei lähe ja keegi tülitama ka ei tulnud. Ja mida mäletada jagub veel tükiks ajaks. Kontserdi elamusedki ilmselt ainult võimendusid nende mitmekordsest läbielamisest ja arutamisest selle öö jooksul. Äkki aitab see kunagi isegi oma lapsi natuke paremini mõista.
     

        
</post>
<date>04,Juuni,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Tasuta meelelahutus täna hommikul kell kaheksa trollipeatuses. Hr. Europarlamendikandidaat Tunne Kelam oli tulnud valijatega kohtuma. Näitsikud pakkusid kohvi ja küpsiseid ja parteilehti. Hämmastav milleks need poliitikud valmis on. Mina keerasin neile selja ja naersin. Enamus teisi inimesi ignoreeris teda sama moodi, aga sellest hoolimata seisis ta seal keep-smilin' naeratus näol, siis tuli keegi keskealine naisterahvas temaga mesijuttu puhuma ja kätt suruma. Küll tal oli ilmselt hea päev. Naljakas oli igal juhul. Keda ise valin ei tea ma ikka veel.
     

        
</post>
<date>04,Juuni,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Took the first swim of the season in the Baltic Sea today. Water temperature - I believe about 15C. It was extremely nice to have a quick dip in after a hot summer day. I can't remember ever doing it in the beginning of June. Usually it's around mid-summer's day that there is a reason to go and have a look at the water temperature. And even then its possible to get cramps and stuff when it's only 12-13C.
     

        
</post>
<date>04,Juuni,2004</date>
<post>


           
      A girl I knew was killed tragically in a car crash this morning. She was a few years younger than I am. A nice girl by all accounts, full of energy and willing to direct it towards community causes. Now she's gone and it might never be known what caused her to hit a huge truck head on. Life is not fair. She, if anyone, deserved to live. 
     

        
</post>
<date>09,Juuli,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I'm half way through the no obligations period otherwise known as a vacation. So far so good. Being at home is nice, stalking up on neighbours etc., I had so lost track of what was going around me, really needed to brush it up a little. :)  For instance, I had noticed it a while ago already actually, in front of my house the guy with the coolest/biggest/most expencivecar gets the best parking space. Living proof of the car being the extension of you know what. It's funny though, that this solution is in a way also maximizing the welfare of the society. The best places are lit at night and through that, I suppose, safer from all kinds of unwanted criminal activities. What is it that makes people act unselfishly in this aspect? Some kindof packmentality of subjecting oneself to the dominant male?Is it purely a guy thing or will I get to play the game too when I get a car someday? So many questions, so little time...  
     

        
</post>
<date>09,Juuli,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Oh, I just love all those wonderful opportunities provided by the modern technology... what I actually wanted to say, though, was that Mr. S has bought a new car once again. Show-off! :p No actual proof of that yet, though, just a gut feeling, but it was right with the last car. :) 
     

        
</post>
<date>09,Juuli,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I'm thinking I don't want to know how much they must be smoking in the apartment next door for the smoke to infiltrate my apartment from the electrical socket next to my computer. And before you ask, yes, it's definitely tobacco smoke, not the wires melting away inside the wall as they also could be doing theoretically. And another comment, it's not coming from the apartment I have "forgot" to build up the walls between with either.
     

        
</post>
<date>09,Juuli,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Tahaksin midagi kirjutada, aga kust küll pihta hakata. Täna, ilmselt reede puhul, ei tunne ma kurbust selle üle, et mu mõtteline puhkus sel aastal ilmselt väga ebakonkreetseks jääb. Loodetavasti on järgneva kolme nädala jooksul siiski lõppkokkuvõttes piisavalt päevi mil ma tööle tulema ei pea. Esmaspäev samas, ei ole ilmselt üks nendest päevadest. Käisin eile Õllesummeril – see traditsiooniline üks päev – lahe oli, lõppkokkuvõttes, hoolimata sellest et ma vahepeal täiesti lapsikult käitusin (ja sellest endale aru andsin) sain ma ju siiski lõpuks seda mida tahtsingi nii et lõpp hea kõik hea. Ja  urlLink Smilers  on ka vahepealsete aastate jooksul mil ma neil live’ina näinud poole paremaks läinud, just mitteverbaalse publikusuhtluse, inimestel kaasa laulmise võimaldamise jms. poolest. Natuke rohkem sarkastilisi märkusi ja olekski juba meie oma kohalik  urlLink BA  valmis. Võib-olla paremgi, sest nii palju kui ma ka  urlLink Keithist  lugu pean, näeb  urlLink Martin  neil hetkedel kui tal suitsu hambus pole oma kelmika naeratusega temast märksa parem välja. Martin oli hea üllatus, ma ei teadnudki et nad kitarristi vahetanud on. Õllekalt koju saamine oli muidugi omaette kogemus. Nagu selgus ei ole sellisel ööl Tallinna kesklinnas võimalik mitte ühtegi taksot saada. Kõik tellimisnumbrid olid kas kinni või vabandasid nad et neil ühtegi vaba autot pole. Kuskil kella 2 paiku jala Kristiinesse jõudnutena õnnestus meil siiski ühe peale hääletada, nii et viimased paar kilomeetrit jalavaeva sellega säästsime. Magama sain pisut enne kolme. See on see koht kus flex-time on jumala kingitus. Tööle jõudsin kuskil 11-paiku. Ja nüüd, (ja ma olen täna olnud märksa produktiivsem kui eilsel täiesti mõttetul tööpäeval,) on aeg koju minna! 
     

        
</post>
<date>09,Juuli,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Ma olen suht veendunud, et enamus inimesi ei vaata paneelmaju selle pilguga et millisest paneelivahest peaks joone läbi tõmbama et saada kaks ühesuurust maja. Või siis et huvitav kus asub mu korteri keskpunkt ja et peaks selle välja uurimiseks kaks diagonaalset joont läbi korteri tõmbama ning nende ristumiskoha ära märkima. Nüüd te siis teate, ja kui ma kunagi seda peaksin kõva häälega tegema hakkama, ja isegi kui mitte väga kõva häälega, peaasi et kuuldavalt, siis te teate et mu tõeline mina on paljastunud ja on aeg kiirelt abi kutsuda.
     

        
</post>
<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Sometimes you see someone who is so much less fortunate than you are and it makes you realize just how lucky you are yourself. I became familiar with a very tragic story involving a co-worker of mine the other day. She is an older woman, very close to retirement already. It turns out that one of her two sons, her personal favourite was killed seven years ago, killed by someone to be specific, and to this date she's unable to let go and believes truly that some kind of nonsense about re-creation of bodies and calling back the souls from the other side can help her literally bring her son back from the dead. It really amazes me how much people are able and willing to hurt themselves.  It's quite clear that no one else can persuade her to let go as every member of her family and every co-worker has probably already tried. It has to come from within, but if it hasn't so far, will it ever? And how much of it are the people close to her, like her new companion, willing to take? 
     

        
</post>
<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      I stayed up until 4 something last night just to be able to catch a quarter of an hour interview with Darren Hayes on the  urlLink Metro radio  of UK. Luckily it did finally come before I fell over, and I managed to get my stream rip software up and running before that too. :)  I also caught the new single “Popular” in that show. It’s a pretty good song, with an even better  urlLink video , as I found out today. I’m very much looking forward to its release on the 23rd of August. Hopefully the whole album called " urlLink The Tension and the Spark " will be equally good, but I think I’ll have wait and see until mid September something. It’s funny though, I’ve been waiting for new releases from both Darren and Bryan Adams for years, more actively the past 12 months, and when they finally do get around to releasing their new material they do it basically at the same time. Bryan’s new single “Open Road” should be getting some airplay already now, as it was released yesterday, and his album “Room Service” should be available in the second half of September sometime. I’m not so sure about the musical value of this release though, I wouldn’t go recommending it to anyone at this point. 
     

        
</post>
<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>


           
      Things like that don't happen every day, in fact I've lived here for 2,5 years and it's the first time it's ever happened so far, anyway, what I'm talking about is that the little girl from the apartment opposite of mine, with whom I haven't had any contact so far, knocked on my door earlier today and explained something about their own vacuum cleaner starting to emit smoke or something, and asked if she could borrow ours. At first I was like, should I trust her? After all, the cleaner cost several hundreds of kroons, but then I thought to myself, that the request is odd enough not to be any kind of trick, and honestly, if someone wants to clean, who am I to stand in their way? She returned it not more than 20 minutes later and gave me a little chocolate as a thank you. It would have been more useful if she'd come to clean my apartment too while she was at it, but it's too much of a mess here for me to want her wandering about anyway, so I'll just linger on the sweetness for a while more, and think to myself how odd and unexpected it is that I actually live here so close to other people I know nothing about, but occasionally, in very unexpected ways, we can be useful to each other. Maybe I should stock up on sugar? Isn't that the most popular request to go to your neighbors for? 
     

        
</post>
</Blog>