<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just, y'know, so I could say I work at the Quikie Mart. Not that I think it's a great career choice or anything, it'd just be cool, someone says,  "I'm an industrial engineer"   And then you say "Oh, that's great, I work at the Quikie Mart for $6.50 an hour, I used to only make minimum wage, but I've been workin' for quite a while now. The boss says I could even get up to $7.00 if I work on my catfood displaying skills.."   The look un their face...priceless no?
    
</post>
<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Lindsey recently posted this to her journal...thing. "I think, day by day, life gets progessively worse. And sometimes I wonder, "Y'know...maybe it's just the little depression stage all teenagers get...It's not my fault I'm so fucked up..." But what if it is my fault? I think I drive people away so I can be alone. I don't mean to. I don't WANT to; who likes to be alone? I don't know...It is so hard to live when you feel completely isolated. I can't think of anyone I know that feels like this...Maybe I do and they just didn't care enough to say anything. Right now, I think the only thing that keeps me from "giving in" would be Adi. It sounds weird, I know. My life depending on someone who lives hundreds of miles away. But I think, no, I know, she's the only person I told everything. My bestest friend, and I promised her that we'd meet up and get drunk together, have a hella fun time. I don't want to break my promise, but if shit doesn't improve, what can I do?" Yeah, there's more after that, but this is the part about ME, damnit. Now that my bout of selfishness is over...I must say... .....I love you too Lindzeh. I am so looking forward to holding eachother's hair up whilst we barf up everything we've eaten from the past decade. Or something like that.                              
    
</post>
<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Lord have mercy..such a good mood. If like, my way of life, did not completely outlaw dancing, I'd be dancing around right now. Aaaaall is right with the world. Meh friend Lindzeh is back from exile and oooh, I'm so happy. Yayness.
    
</post>
<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      You don't want to hear me sing. Trust me. Heather nearly dies at the sound of me lalaing. Anyway, on with what I'd intended to talk about. Today, I had a rather good day. Got up around 6 pm, talked to Simon without fighting, had steak. All around fulfilling day.  I can't wait until I have money. I have soo many albums I want to buy: Franz Ferdinand Incubus-A Crow Left of the Murder Avril Lavigne-Under My Skin Blink-182...I don't really know the name, it's the one with Down on it.  So yeah, tha's about it for now.
    
</post>
<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've considered everything, and right now the only thing that seems acheivable is crying... That friend, the one that put me on ignore, I got on a friend of mine's e-mail and sent him a message, here was his reply:  Tha's low...tricking me into reading an email from you..well I was gonna take you off ignore today..but I don't think I will. Hope you're having as much fun as I am. toodles...  He's..having fun..without me... I screw up everything, I really do. I don't want or deserve to walk this earth anymore.
    
</post>
<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Learn How to do Self-Hypnosis  Hot damn! I do a google to find the calories in an orange, and this is what comes up! Well...a site with a link to a site with a link to this site, anyway. The audio part of it I thought was a bunch of crap, but that spinny wheel was one hell of an acid trip....quite a treat if you're not epileptic.
    
</post>
<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Shit I Like: Pudding, pens, blank books, black, Heather, Laura, Simon, Shayla, Lindsey, Yahoo, condoms, the music of Franz Ferdinand, ditto System of a Down and Evanescence, White Oleander, the Georgia Nicolson Series, boiled chicken, England, air conditioning, irritating my parental unit, Amy Lee (lesbotronic moment), Scorpios, Juila Roberts (totally innocent), the art of Ursula Vernon, male hands.  Things That Should Be Obliterated Or Are Otherwise Disliked: Said parental unit, spanish rice or anything remotely casseroley, blonde hair, shaving bumps, stretch marks, pit hair, shedding of the hair, Jessica Orlikowski, Dale Swafford, R, Usher, Usher's nose, black men in white high tops, people who refuse to accept that they are white, people who tan, when your pubic hair bunches up and makes you look like you have a penis...tbc.
    
</post>
<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well that's fine and dandy for the bird, but I have bigger problems. My best friend has me on ignore (on yahoo). It is, mostly, my fault. But it's also his because he just didn't  get it.  Then again, I'm not entirely sure what it was I wanted him to get. Perhaps it's for the best...but in the meantime...I'm bored and I miss my monkey...
    
</post>
<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My freezer/fridge...thing...it's haunted. I'm not kidding. .... .... IT BREATHES LIKE DARTH VADER!! What if it's been in the food? Oh god...spectral hands fondling my food...
    
</post>
<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok, so maybe they haven't been stolen. Maybe I'm just out of clean ones. But still, it sucks big style. I have no underwear! .......  .......  ......Ok so maybe I do have the white granny panties at the bottom of the dresser...but I'm SO not going to wear them...really...really really..I mean it. o.o
    
</post>
<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Since when has it been the Fourth of July?! Why wasn't I informed?!?! Gah&gt;</post></Blog>