<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>27,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Springtime.  It may be on the way...  Today on the weather channel I saw that it is going to be 50 degrees and Sunny! I don't know about anyone else but I am feeling a Springtime itch. The wintertime blues hit me a little hard on Tuesday of this week, so I am looking forward to a nice weekend to liven my spirit a bit.  Speaking of the weekend...  I am pretty psyched for it because I am traveling to Bowling Green. I LOVE Bowling Green. It's always to hard to leave when I go back for a weekend. Sometimes I can't believe that I feel this way because as a Freshman, I hated BG. I went home (Clyde, Ohio) every weekend. Slowly and surely, however, it began to grow on me. The summer between my Junior and Senior year, I stayed in BG for summer classes and after that summer, BG became my home.  I can't express in words how hard it has been to move away from everything that I have know for 4 1/2 years of my life. It chokes me up just thinking about it.  I miss walking around campus. For anyone that is thinking about attending BG, I will tell you know that our campus in so beautiful in the Fall. There is nothing that I would love more that to be able to take a walk around campus every evening when all the trees are changing, and the sidewalks are full with students. Even though there is life and excitement, it's also really peaceful. I also miss the Student Recreation Center. I taught aerobic there for 3 years. The REC is where I lived. I LOVE that place. The smell, the people...and on a quick sidenote. BG has the best Group Exercise program in Ohio. I know this because I have taught at Kent State, Twinsburg and now Bedford Ohio and the level of teaching and the level and competence of instructors is unsurpassed.   I also am a big fan of BW 3's and even though Jon and I have found that the one in Kent is pretty good, BG's rocks out. On the weekends they have this guy playing acoustic and singing. He is freakin amazing! It is SO much fun to go out in BG. Two places (Nate and Wally's and Howards) have awesome Live Music...and that's something I haven't come across in Kent. Well, Jon and I did see one band, but they were horrible.  I could go on and on and on. I look forward to each time I go home to soak up everything that I love about Bowling Green.  Thank God it's Friday and I'm going home.
       
    
    
</post>
<date>25,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today I want to talk about the Atkins Diet.  As a fitness professional, you can imagine the questions I get about diets and dietary habits. First and foremost I will tell you that my position is and will always side with the Food Guide Pyramid and moderation. Secondly, let me tell you a little bit of my personal background with diets.  A long, long time ago (great beginning to an awesome song) I use to be overweight. In Junior High I stood at a mere 5'1" and weighed 200lbs. Yeah, I was an apple. I was also a cheerleader. Not to be egotistical or anything, but even though I was fat, I had the best jumps on the squad. Anyways, let's fast forward to my Freshman year in High School. For Homecoming all of the squads (Frosh, JV and Varsity) cheer together for that game. So, I'm cheering my heart out, per usual, when I hear a cheer coming from a small crowd of boys..."You're fat, clap clap, Lose Weight." I can tell you that I cried. I can also tell you, that very moment in my life lead to a dramatic change and I started starving myself. So long story short, I became so thin that I suffered from amenorrhea for over 6 months. What that means to me is that I have a higher risk of osteoporosis and I may not be able to ever have children, even if I wanted any. I also have to take birth control pills in order to regulate my hormones and have my periods monthly (Sorry if that was too graphic for any of you). Additionally, it has taken me a long time to get back to normal. I screwed my mind and body up. This is why I hate Diets.   So let's talk about Atkins. The hype is so huge that restaurants are now offering "Atkins Friendly" items to their menus. Cozwallop to boot, if you ask me (and Rubuis Hagrid). You may be asking, what's your point. This is my problem with Atkins. Ketosis, and what it does to your body. Having your body messed up, in anyways, totally sucks. As I explained above. You want my reason for hating Atkins? Well here it is:   "Ketosis is the presence in the blood of abnormally high levels of acidic substances called ketones. The normal body fuel is glucose. Ketones are produced when there isn't enough glucose in the bloodstream, and fats have to be used. When fats are used excessively as fuels, they are eventually converted to ketones. The real danger in ketosis is that ketones are acidic, and high levels of ketones make the blood abnormally acid" (NHS Direct Online).  You may be asking, so what? Um, do you know what acid is? The stuff that can eat holes through metal? You know, acid? Do you really think you want that in your blood? I think not. Additionally, high protein diets cause halitosis and kidney stones. I am thinking that all this stuff does not sound like fun.  Can I also point out that after any diet, when you go back to "normal," you are going to gain back everything you lost! Fitness is not just a quick fix with Atkins or some other diet. Fitness is a Lifestyle. This is why I love the Food Guide Pyramid. This is why I am an advocate for the Dole-5-A-Day Program and regular exercise. The way you live needs to be something you can live with! Moderation people! Ice cream is not your enemy! Nothing is! Before you can decide to make Fitness your lifestyle, you have to be ready to accept who you are. Not an easy task. So please! Get off the Atkins, the South Beach Diet, the Metabolife WHATEVER! Do me a favor and give yourself a big hug and make a promise to yourself to make a healthier lifestyle.
       
    
    
</post>
<date>24,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Thank God it's no longer Manic Monday.  Yesterday I experienced what may be the busiest day at a YMCA, ever. A new session started yesterday, which meant parents scrambling to get their kids signed up for programs. This also meant that all of the staff members would need their best fake smiles and patience to deal with rudeness.  Let me ask you a question.  Have you ever yelled at a Customer Service Representative because you couldn't find a place to park? This happened to me yesterday. I was helping out at the Front Desk and what do I get for my good deed? A lady telling me off because she couldn't find a place to park. I had to look down at my name tag to make sure it didn't say "parking officer." Nope. Sure didn't. Just my name. I really wonder what this lady wanted be to say to her. Maybe,          "I'm so sorry that you couldn't find a place to park. It's entirely my fault. Let me give you a parking space with you name on it. No, I don't have a space with my name on it and most likely due to your whiney ass I am going to have to park across the street. Is this acceptable with me? No. I work so that I can give all my privileges as an employee to you. Thank you very much, fucker."  Of course I wouldn't say that, but trust me, that's is exactly what I was thinking.  Why has the general public become so angry? I think people forget that certain places they go to be "served," those service people are there to serve them because, here's the punch line. Wait for it...IT"S THEIR JOB! Take fast food restaurants for example:  Customer: "Yeah, I want a...a...Big Mac.  Fast Food Employee: Would you like fries with that?  Customer: No  Fast Food Employee: Would you like anything else today?  Customer: No  Fast Food Employee: Okay, your total will be (cost of Big Mac here).  Customer: I told you I wanted that in a combo! (obviously pissed)  Okay...what is wrong with the scenario? In no shape or form did the Customer tell the Employee they wanted a combo. But this happens all the TIME! (Trust me I have worked at McDonald's AND Wendy's) Where was a thank you? Where was, I'm sorry...could I have that in a combo please? This doesn't happen just at Fast Food Restaurants. It happens EVERYWHERE! (No wonder people hate their jobs so much!)  WAKE UP AMERICA! (Shout to Bernie Mac right there)  So next time your pissed about something unrelated to the person who is dealing WITH YOU, remember, they want to like their job, so be nice! Say Thank You! Maybe even smile (a shocker!). I bet you'll even feel better about yourself. 
       
    
    
</post>
<date>23,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It Starts...  You think you know someone...  This is a little piece of my world.  I am currently 22 years old. On June 22nd, I will yet turn another year older. My birthdate being the date that it is, has rendered me a Cancer/Gemini Cusp. Which will most undoubtedly prove to all of you that yes, I do have three personalities. I think you'll find this quite an amusing aspect to my entries. Of course, my sense of humor is a little off so maybe (hopefully) you'll find this amusing as well.  I work at a YMCA as a Fitness Coordinator. So you can say, the a 4-year degree and 4 years experience in the Fitness Industry qualfies myself as a mid-level Fitness Guru. Work and my days at my Alma Mater, Bowling Green State University, has brought to my attention that my idea of health (which I do believe to me correct) and society's (undoubtedly due to the Media) views of health do not coincide. So, I decided to start this Blog to shoot some of my opinions out to all of you (and because my boyfriend has one and I just think it's pretty darn neat).   Mostly you'll find that I will rant and rave about how I think the Media screws us all up and to talk about my life, of course. I hope to write often, but most likely it won't be as often as I would like. I currently do not have the internet at home (shocking, I know). But, check back regularly. Hopefully you'll walk away NOT wanting to even think about the Atkins Diet and other forms of bodily torture again.  That said...  Thanks for stopping by and enjoy your day here at...No, it's not Cedar Point, but do have a nice ride!
       
    
    
</post>
<date>05,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I was sitting here trying to think of something that fires me up to talk about today. Lucky for you, I remembered something I really would like to talk about.  Safety.  First, I have been an AFAA (Aerobics and Fitness Association of American) for five years now. I have put my certification into practice and have upheld the integrity of the world-renowned certification. I am very proud of this. With each class I teach, I follow the guidelines of the AFAA 5 Questions. (read more about AFAA at http://www.afaa.com)  These 5 Questions are VITAL for the safety of any aerobics class. As a refresher, they are:  1. What muscle are you trying to lengthen and/or strengthen?  2. Are you doing that?  3. Is the back protected? Are there any other stress points?  4. Who is this exercise appropriate for?  5. Can you complete the exercise for 8 repetitions and maintain proper form and alignment?  Pretty good, right? Something that you would hope every aerobics instructor thinks about when putting together his or her class.   So why am I so fired up? Because various magazine fitness editors disregard any sense of safety. I read Shape, Fitness and Self magazine pretty regularly. I have written to each of their fitness editors about safety concerns (some more than once) with a certain exercise they insist on including in their magazines. Mountain Climbers.          (*Mountain Climbers are performed in the up position of a push-up. You hold that position and then bring your knees up one at a time like you are running.)  I hate mountain climbers.  Here's why: 1. What muscle are you trying to lengthen and/or strengthen?      I guess you could say the legs.   2. Are you doing that?      Are you adding resistance? No, so really, what are you doing?  3. Is the back protected? Are there any other stress points?      NO! DANGER! Also, major joint stress on the wrists and shoulder joints.  4. Who is this exercise appropriate for?      A competitive athlete, maybe. An aerobics class or fitness magazine? NO!  5. Can you complete the exercise for 8 repetitions and maintain proper form and alignment?      I don't think this is possible. If you are trying to "run," how many people do you think are trying to do this motion correctly?  I am just APPALLED that any magazine's Editor would let something like this be printed. If you have a basic fitness magazine, where you KNOW beginners are going to picking it up and saying, "Hey, I'm going to try this," safety MUST be your first priority. Here's something I would like to know:  Who is the heck are these fitness editors, what are their credentials and why don't I have their job?  UHG!  Lastly I would like to give props to the Editor-in-Chief at Self Magazine for her response to my concern, is as follows:  " Dear Brandi:  Thank you for your comments concerning our December 2003 Body Bonus  article. We've forwarded your e-mail to the appropriate editors, so you can be  sure that your voice has been heard.  We appreciate your interest in SELF and your taking the time to write."  Dear Self, Fitness and Shape,  I'm watching you.    
       
    
    
</post>
<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Turning Signals.  Everybody has them, not everyone uses them. This, drives me crazy.   This may be my only and biggest pet peeve. Not only is it irritating, it's dangerous. Currently I live outside of Akron and a hop, skip and a jump from Cleveland. People drive like assholes anyway. My most favorite thing in the world is when I am driving on I-480 and someone decides to change lanes in front of me. All I ask for is a little brake check and a quick snap of the wrist to flip on the turning signal. Unfortunately, I usually just feel like I might have a heart attack and die.  This might bother me even more. When Cops don't use their turning signals.  So, yes we all (everyone that drives) know that the lack of turning signal use happens all the time. But why? We all had to go to drivers education and last time I checked, turning signals are not an optional accessory.   What else bothers me? Why have some drivers forgotten how a 4-way stop works? I'm not even going to explain it because it makes me so disgusted.  Turning signals. Another time it really sucks when someone forgets to use theirs is when you're out on a run. With the weather getting warmer, I have been known to go for a run from time to time outside. I have been running for about 8 years now, so I would say I have a little experience with it. I love it when I'm getting ready to cross the street and I stop because a car is coming and then they all of a sudden turn. That pisses me off. Thanks for getting me out of the zone. haha...did I say love...I meant loathe.  Road rage...Running rage...maybe this would all disappear if turning signals because less of an option to drivers. I ALWAYS use my turning signal...it's way fun!  Everyone should try it.
       
    
    
</post>
<date>02,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Now you cab take a magic pill each day to keep you slim, trim, beautiful and happy!  Now, just read that first sentence again. Doesn't it sound a little too good to be true? Yet, millions of American's would sell their most prized possession to get a monthly supply. Even if the name Anna Nicole is attached to it. So here comes the real question...why are we always looking for a quick fix?  Everything this day in age is all about quicker, faster, better. Fast food restaurants, DSL internet connections, driving...I could go on and on. Sadly dieting is no expection here. Why is this sad you may ask? The faster I lose weight the better. But let me ask you...for what cost?  "Magic Pills" (a.k.a Diet Pills) are bought by millions of American's, leaving the weight loss industry with millions of dollars. Maybe I should just buy a bunch of wholesale vitamins, put them in a new bottle that says "Flubber Flush" and collect my cash. I bet people would by it. All I have to do is put some false little pictures of heads that don't belong to the  body they're on with their touching testimonial. Leaving consumers with the impression that this pill will make them look like a brick shithouse.   MISCONCEPTION!  Diet pills can be very dangerous to your health. Not only can they be addictive, but sometimes the bottle isn't all that clear about it's ingredients. (You may of heard this about Dexatrim) Ma huang, also know as ephedrine, has been linked to serious side effects such as; heart attack, stoke and even death (to read more about Ma huang and it's dangers visit: http://www.yourlawyer.com/practice/overview.htm?topic=Ma%20Huang).  Let me just say that use of such aides is basically an afterthought to a weight loss plan that is going to work in the long-term. Without eating healthy and adding exercise to your daily life, you are just spinning your wheels in a never-ending roller coaster of weight lost and gained back (Being a yo-you must really suck).  If you are even THINKING about taking diet pills or any other weight loss supplement, please do your research. Better yet, just go take a walk outside and enjoy being able to just take a walk. There a many American's that can't even get out of bed.   Lastly, remember...those last 5 pounds never hurt anyone. Besides, I look at them as a blessing that you have enough to eat.  
       
    
    
</post>
<date>01,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I hate growing up.  I once thought that once I graduated with a college degree that I would be making $30,000 a year and my life would fall perfectly in place with what I wanted. Then I graduated. None this happened.  It's been pretty hard being smacked with "the real world." The state of the economy doesn't help either. Jobs are few and far between and the ones that are out there require worldly experience. In the past 10 months, I have moved twice and had three different jobs.   First I graduated and had NO idea what I wanted to do, as most college graduates do, and freaked out. I decided to go back to school. So I moved in with my friend Cricket in BG and started to work at Wendy's. I hated everyday of my life that I went to work at Wendy's. Somedays, I just didn't go. To make a long story short, I decided against going back to schoolthat found a job in Twinsburg, Ohio. A part-time fitness position I could make a little more money with and use my major. So in August, I moved to Stow, Ohio to pursue "career dreams." I worked in Twinsburg to the end of 2003 due to an accepted position at a YMCA as a Fitness Coordinator. A step up, full-time AND benefits. Don't get me wrong, I like my job. What I don't like is being away from Bowling Green, away from home and away from my friends. This sucks my ass.  So what comes along to throw Plan A out the window? This:  Jon and I took a wonderful walk through campus and downtown on the beautiful afternoon we had on Sunday. As we walked on campus I just became so sad. Thoughts, memories and feelings just overflowed inside of me. I missed my home. I missed my friends. I missed my family.   Being a nice day, tons of people were out and about and I miss that. Stow is ok, but I've only seen my next door neighbor about 5 times, he never leaves his apartment, and the people above me seem to never leave and never sleep. I miss people. I miss being in a place that is alive. I miss being close to my family and friends. Where I live now, I have nothing, no one. I sit alone at night and try not to think about how lonely I am.  Walking around campus and through town made me realize how much I wanted to be back home. I just keep thinking about it, all evening. I finally cracked when Jon and I were driving to see "50 First Dates" (Great movie, by the way). All I could tell him is that I don't know exactly what I want to do, but I do know that I want to move back to Bowling Green in August. I think he's really, really excited about this because he loves BG more that I do, and I love BG a whole lot. So right now, all I can think about is, how am I going to make this ok? How are my parents going to react when I leave a full-time job with benefits behind to come home? For the most part, I think I should be ok to find a job. I'm interested in working with Seniors and special needs and people who are interested in that are hard to come by. There are lots of YMCA's in the area as well that I can always start off part-time at working at the Front Desk or anything like that. Graduate school is also an option for the Spring.  I'm so impatient that I just want this all solved now. I just want to know what is going to happen. I want to move and find a new job. I want this but I know I can't have it until August, which sucks. Thank God Jon is my polar opposite in this arena, so he'll be a big help.  I just hate all this change and the stress that comes with it. I have been a big stress ship these past 10 months. I know this because when I come home, it goes away. By the end of the weekend, my jaw stops popping and I feel so happy I want to cry. Every time I come home, I never want to leave.   I hate being a lost twenty-something.  So, how does it end? "I don't know...it's a mystery" (Shakespeare in Love).
       
    
    
</post>
<date>12,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yeah. I want to talk about food.  I love food. Food is good. If you've read my archives you'll see that for a period of time I didn't eat very much food at all. However, now that I am over that period in my life, I enjoy food without guilt and hatred.   I don't understand people when they come to me and we start talking about their diets and they drop this bomb on me, " I don't eat bread." This angers me. Why, you ask?   Well, there's this process called digestion that breaks down what one eats so that it can be absorbed into the blood stream (read more about the digestion process at: http://digestive.niddk.nih.gov/ddiseases/pubs/yrdd/index.htm). Just as people are picky in what they like to eat, so are the cells that absorb nutrients from the food in our blood stream. Especially when it comes to brain tissue and muscles. The cells that comprise these organs and tissues love glucose. Glucose is a digestion by-product of carbohydrates. Carbohyrdrates are foods such as vegetables, bread, rice, pasta and potatoes (read more about carbohydrates at: http://www-library.net/sites/framer?/sites/carbohydrates_in_nutritionist). So in order it get the needed glucose that everyone needs, you have to eat carbohydrates.  Why would you deny yourself needed nutrients that your body NEEDS to function properly.  What some people may be confused about are the different types of carbohydrates. There are complex carps and simple carbs, or sugars. The type of carbohydrates one eats is of high importance. Complex carbohydrate foods like bread, noodles, rice and veggies take longer to be digested than simple carbohydrates do. Simple carbohydrates, sugars, are digested quickly and easily. Simple carbs are food such as cake, candy and soda. Fruits are also sources of simple carbohydrates.   The best type of carbohydrates to incorporate into a diet plan are the complex carbohydrates. It's not that you can't eat fruit or treat yourself or that you should only eat carbohydrates. Everything in life should be taken in moderation, food, drink, etc. The people that claim to not be able to eat bread or pasta are denying themselves a vital life nutrient. Everyone can eat bread, everyday. One has to be smart and use moderation. This is hard for some people and this is where a big lesson is self-control comes into play. I mean come on, do you really want to avoid bread and pasta and everything that is yummy for the rest of your life? That's not even living!  What people have to understand is the body can only use so much glucose at one time. So when the cells have extra they save it. Then it's stored in the "fridge," the liver and muscles, and is called glycogen. Glycogen hangs out and when exercise is performed, or go when there are long periods without eating, it is used to produce energy. But, if one sits on your butt all day the glycogen becomes impatient and turns into fat (by the way, this can happen no matter what you eat, carbohydrates, proteins or fat).  What does this teach us? Carbohydrates don't make us fat. Sitting on our butts and eating too much of ANYTHING makes us fat.  The only diet that American's need to learn in the self-control diet! Come on people, let's get real!
       
    
    
</post>
<date>24,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Last week I got into my first car accident.  It sucked.  Where I live, in lovely Stow Ohio, it snows ALL the time. I really was hoping no more snow would fall, but when I woke up last Tuesday, there was ten inches of snow outside.   Needless to say, the roads were a mess and I had to go to work.  So...out I went and right when I got onto route 8, boom.  It was crazy. First a huge red 4x4 truck started to do a 360 in the left lane. Then a U-Haul ( I hate U-Haul by the way) started to slide from the middle lane to the right lane (lane I was in). So the driver in front of me started to try to get out the way, followed by myself...but I hit a big patch of ice and instead of avoiding the car in front of me, I rear-ended it.  A little background about my car.  It's a 1996 Ford Contour that my parents got at a repo auction. It also had a huge dent on my passange side back seat door...due to a former accident. My car also had over 155,000 miles on it. So...this accident did not fair too well for it. Long story short, I now drive a sweet 99 pontiac sunfire.  Did I mention I have the best parents in the world? Yeah, they totally helped me get this car.  I hate snow.
       
    
    
</post>
<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Health: 1. The freedom from disease or abnormality 2. The conditioning of optimal well-being, concerning ecological areas of health  I thought I would open with the definition of health to introduce today's topic of choice. How the media affects the images of the ideal body in society.  If you flip through popular magazines such as Cosmo, Glamour and Redbook, you'll find many advertisements depicting females in a very different light than when you would just walking down the street. Bone thin models posed in often times vunerable, provocative positions. Very lean and muscular young men in position of superiority to women. Psychologists are concerned with the exposure of these images to society. Studies from various University's have found that after looking at a fashion magazine, where pictures of these thin young men and women are advertised, test subjects reported less satisfaction with their own bodies. Thus, many young teenagers are pre-empt to develop eating disorders and poor body image.   Think about it, when only 10% of the population looks like the images we see everyday, everywhere, it's no wonder so many people fall prey to such disorders.   This is where I have the biggest problem with the images that are displayed to society. 10%, not 90%, not even 50% of people in our society look like these models, actors and actresses.  Yet, everyday, we are judged upon and compared to these unrealistic "norms" of "society." The media is trying to define health. But if you scroll back up to the top and read the two definitions of health I have listed, are these bone thin people healthy? Should we as a society accept these images as a definition of health? NO! But still, every single one of us falls victim to this "definition." How? Abnormality. This is their loop hole. The reason the media allows us to believe their definition as fact is that word. Everyone else who does not look like these people (10% of the population, mind you) are "abnormal." Fat, is abnormal? Curves are abnormal? Being healthy, is abnormal?   BUT WHY?  Why do we want to look like this? Is this sexy? Is this normal? (Can I please say again that only 10% of our population looks like this) When and why did the size of our body, clothes, nose etc. start to define WHO we are as a PERSON! I think some of the ugliest people I have met have been extremely thin. Why? Because they have very thin or just a horrid personality. Is that how we are all suppose to be? Angry, bitching thin people that just need to go eat a hamburger? I don't know about anyone else, but I like to go eat a hamburger when ever I want.   Personally, I would like to lose about 5 pounds, but then I think why? These 5 measly pounds just mean that I have enough to eat. That I'm happy. That I like to live a little. One day, I hope that everyone in the world can think like this. Variety is the spice of life. Everyone has different genetics. That means no ones booty is suppose to be the same!  I could go on and on about this, but I think I'll just wait till I write my book.  I hate the media.
       
    
    
</post>
<date>05,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      BG.  I just had a GREAT weekend home.   After work on Friday I drove to BG for the first weekend home in I can't remember how long. The sun was shining, I had a good day at work...life was good. That evening, Jon and I met up with Cricket (old roomie and dear friend) for dinner at SamB's. It was so nice to see her and get to chat about what has been going on in life since I'm never around anymore. We had very nice meals and drinks and then parted our separate ways. Jon and I then ventured to BW's where I ran into a guy I had almost every class with at BG.   This is where it gets really good.  He works at the private club up in Toledo and gave me his card...long story short:  He is going to make sure my resume goes to the right people.  Boo-Yah.  On to Saturday...  On Saturday I had dinner with my other very good friend Rachel. We were roommates our Freshman year, we actually went to High School together. But then she got married, so we couldn't live together anymore. Thank God that's over for her though. She's much happier without that crazy dude.  Sunday was the day I got to spend the most time with Jon...and it was very nice. I'd actually like to take a moment to send a shout-out to him. See, I have the BEST boyfriend in the world. It's crazy...I really don't deserve a guy like him and I don't know who I scored points with to actually be with him, but whoever it is...I love you man.  Jon makes every weekend together special and memorable. There's never a moment that passes by that I don't know how glad he is to have me here with him, how much he loves me or how special I am. There are not too many people like this in the world...so Jon, I hope you know how much you mean to me. I love you with all of my heart and I hope you do keep me forever. I love you.  Whew, need to wipe some tears!  Anywho.  On Sunday, Cricket had her senior recital. It was lovely. She conducted and sang about 20 pieces. The whole experience really choked me up. See, I was suppose to be in music school right now...and if I would have been, I would have been singing in her chamber group. I almost cried because I can't believe how stupid I was to not go through with it. Music has been something I have wanted to do since High School. I just have never gotten around to it due to: 1. The money 2. The money 3. I don't have enough confidence in my voice. However, you never know that the future will bring. I know there is further schooling ahead of me and what that might be, it's a mystery as of yet. But, I do know that last night had a big effect on me. There are a lot of decisions that I made last May that currently I am not to happy with myself about. There were other people involved in some of them and I hope they know how truly sorry I am for all the stupid shit I did.  On to Checkers...the townie bar.  Karoke :)  Yeah...I saw so many people that I love and miss and it was SO great.   I don't want to leave home today, at all.  Life sucks.
       
    
    
</post>
<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Job searching.  I feel like this all I have done for the past year. Right now I am job searching because I hate my current job and I live 2 hours away from everyone that I want to be around. Not that 2 hours is too far, but it is when none of your friends and family come to see you. The only person I see regulary is Jon. If it weren't for him, I would of shot myself by now.  Did I mention I hate my job?  I actually don't hate my job, I have my boss. He's the stupidest man I've ever met in my life. Everyday, it becomes more relevant to me when I talk to people if they went to college or not. I'm not saying just because you go to college you are above everyone. However, while at college the majority of students learn how to communicate and function as a normal piece of society. You can have a good conversation with a well-education person. This is the biggest gap I see. I'll start talking to some people and it's like they have no freaking clue what I'm or they are saying. They just stare at you with glazed over eyes. I get this from my boss all the time. I just look at him and wonder how in the hell did he get his job. It really pisses me off that I went to college for 4 years and there are people with no education out there holding jobs that people like me should have. I'm not saying that not everyone like this does a shit house job. I know there are people out there with no education that do awesome. What I don't understand is when people quit because of you, when programs are failing and unorganized and it keeps happening over and over again...how do these people keep their jobs? If I was the head hauncho...they would be so out of there.   You know what else bothers me...people with no empathy.  My senior group exercise class was talking about me (where I could hear) about how I do everything different from their last instructor. That really hurt. I have been comparted to this lady since I've got to the Y and that sucks my ass. You know, I know my shit. What we do in class we do for a reason. All they want to do is work on there chest muscles (for breathing problems). That's not how you get in shape! I work the entire body with them and they can't understand why. It just fustrates me that people do not TRUST my knowledge. For God's Sake I studied exercise for 4 years! I think I might know some stuff about it! This made me break down yesterday. I just want to say that I am not happy (have you noticed this is a vent blog?). I'm not happy with my boss, I'm not happy with my classes, I'm not happy living in Stow, I'm not happy being alone. I'm fucking not happy. And yet I bust my ass EVERYDAY to make other people happy. When is something going to happen to make me happy?!?!?!?  Sorry...I needed that.  Anyways. Next time you decide to talk about someone, I don't care if you do it. Just don't do it where the person might hear. Make sure they are gone for the day. And, if you have an employee that knows there shit, respect them for that and get off there asses. Help them grow instead.  Geez.
       
    
    
</post>
<date>26,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I know someone famous!  All the way from the little town of Clyde, Ohio my fellow Clyde High School graduate, Tim Anderson, is now a professional football player for the Buffalo Bills.  I think that is way freaking cool.  Tim and I spent 2 years in the same math class with Mr. Moiser. From that experience I can tell you that we learned great math, learned a lot about football and had a lot of fun. I use to get teased a lot in that class (one time I asked for it because I told Mr. Moiser I saw a UFO). Tim also picked me up with one arm in that class...he's a big dude if you didn't notice.  Tim was always a nice, down-to-earth guy. He was friends with just about everyone in high school. He really deserves this and I am so happy for him.  One thing is for sure, everyone in Clyde is now a Buffalo Bills fan!  Timmaytahoe, I'm thinking about you buddy, congratulations!   
       
    
    
</post>
<date>07,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Poop  Fuck  Dude  Sweet  DickHole  Fucking-A  Penis  Fart  Kitty  Ass  Neat  Ooh  Yucka  Yummah  What  No  God?  Buzz  You Crazy  Bonjour  Merde!  Pardon (with French Accent)  Taco  Money  You Win  Blurple  Yaowzah  Cool  Nox  Jon :)
       
    
    
</post>
<date>03,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I went home to BG this weekend...I love going home!  This weekend was spectacular, so I had to write about it!  Friday was great because I got to see my step-mom for lunch (and her sweet new car) and my mom. I haven't seen my mom in a while. I also was able to get my hair done where I always do back home, which made me feel great. Then Jon took me to EasyStreet, my favorite place to eat in BG...which was so awesome. We got in a game of pool and some word/trivia games before we ate. It was just such a fun, low-key evening.  On Saturday, we went to see the Detroit Red Wings play. This was my first hockey game and it kicked ass. I  now like hockey a whole bunch. My favorite part is when they start fighting...that's way fun. I definitely want to go to another game next year...whether to be a BG game or a Toledo Storm have...good stuff.  However, the best part of the weekend came on Sunday. Jon took me to try on engagement rings. This, was WAY exciting for me! I found two rings I really liked and didn't want to take off...lol...it was a good time. Jon knew that I had been dreaming about doing this...he always makes my dreams come true.  Sunday evening Jon and I went for a walk around campus that I LOVE when we do that. I love being home so much and I can't wait till I am here to stay, with my baby!   
       
    
    
</post>
<date>12,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today I listened to an archived broadcast of Dave DePew's Fitness and Nutrition hour. A friend/co-worker of mine from my days at BG, Doug Jackson, and now co-author of a new fitness book, "The Power of Champions," sent me the link to enjoy this broadcast. What I would like to write about are the top training secrets of fitness professionals. This list was given on the show, but I would like to expand a little bit more for anyone who might read this blog.  #1. Periodization.     Periodization is a fancy fitness word for planning. If you plan out your workouts for a week, you are planning what is called a microcycle of a periodization schedule. This is where we find our training splits: Back and biceps, chest and triceps, shoulders, legs, abdominals all trained on different days.  It is a wonderful thing to plan out weekly workouts to have efficiency and moreover active recovery in your workouts. However, while some people might plan out their weekly workouts, they do not look at a bigger picture.  The bigger picture in periodization is called a meso or macrocycle. Depending on the length. A mesocycle might last a few weeks to a month or so, while a macrocycle might last 6 month to a year. Why it's so important to look at the bigger picture is due to our next item on the list:  #2. Goals.     More importantly to have S.M.A.R.T goals. A lot of people come to me and say, hey Brandi I want to lose 20 pounds in about six weeks and have abs like Britney Spears. I think then my eyes bug out of my head. Sure, they have a goal, but it's a goal that they won't achieve and will most likely make them give up on exercise. So let's make this a S.M.A.R.T goal.  S=specific: This is our what, when, where, why and how. First off understand that 1-2 pounds of weight loss a week is considered safe. Next, you have to set up a workout plan that you can stick with. For most people working out six days a week is not going to happen. Lastly, have a good reason why you want to do this...hint, it shouldn't be just to look good in a bikini. So, to make this goal specific let's stick with the 20 pounds. But instead of 6 weeks, let's aim for 12 weeks, or 3 months. Then the person needs to set up a workout plan that's finds them in the gym 3 times a week working on cardiovascular exercise for 30 minutes every session, and strength training exercises for at least 20 minutes every other session.  M=measurable: This is easy enough. You can surely measure 20 pounds on a scale and moreover, any weight loss can be measured on how your clothes fit.  A=attainable: Can you do this...safely? This is why it's important to plan for a weight loss of 1-2 pound a week. It's also important to look at your body type. There are three body types: ectomorph(willowly), mesomorph(muscular), and endomorph(curvy). If your body type is something like a meso-endo combination, you are never going to look like a supermodel because your body is just not built that way. It's so important to know what you and your body is capable of.  R=reasonable: This means you can't possibly work out 7 days a week for 3 hours a day. It  means you can lose 20 pounds in 6 weeks. You have to be reasonable with yourself and not look for a quick fix.  T=timely: set a time goal...that again meet the rest of our acronym.  So, our goal before is to lose 20 pounds in 6 week and have abs like Britney.  After? To lose 20 pounds in 12 weeks by planning and doing a workouts that contain cardiovascular and strength training exercises for a combined time of 50 minutes 3 days a week.  Note, I didn't mention Britney because you do not ever want to compare yourself to someone else. You always want to be in the best shape for YOU!  #3. Find out what works and DO IT!     So if you do not like to run, don't do it. Do what you like, do what works for you and drop all other ideas.  #4. Eat like a champion     My favorite little story goes a little something like this:     Picture yourself as a pile of firewood. When you diet by restricting calories or not eating, fad diets, overexercising etc., you put water on your firelogs. Everyone knows you can't burn a fire with wet logs. Which means you can't burn fat and keep your motor running. When start doing to right things like eating right, exercising regularly and getting enough fluids, you start to dry out your firelogs. When you dry them out, that's the only time your fire will burn and you will get permanent results.  #5. Don't ignore the red flags.     If it hurts, don't do it. If you are feeling to tired, you need more rest. You have to know your own body, it's telling you something...LISTEN to it!  #6. Have a team approach.     Get a trainer, work out with a friend, go visit a nutritionist. Find out all the information you can to make it work for you!  Now go get to it!     
       
    
    
</post>
<date>11,May,2004</date>
<post>
</post></Blog>