<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>31,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I am still having Spring Break. Nothing too exciting about that really. Carolynn’s school is having a book fair and tomorrow she is going. She had her eye on a couple of books I guess. Catherine is still being Catherine. She polished off a little machine with M’s in it early this morning. It’s not like we don’t feed the kid. She ate a nice bowl of Mud and Bugs for breakfast. (Mud and Bugs is Lion King cereal.) She had peanut butter and jelly for lunch and we went to the Taco Bell for dinner. So we aren’t starving her, yet she feels the need to get up before everyone else and eat as much junk as she can find as quickly as she can.   So Amy Adams got kicked off of American Idol today. I can’t believe that. Carolynn is just shocked. None of those girls deserved to go this week. I liked all of the girls in the bottom three; Amy Adams, Jennifer Hudson, and Latoya London. I thought John Stevens was worse than any of those girls. I thought Camile Velasco needed to go and she wasn’t even in the bottom three. I thought she was the worst one this whole time, as you may have known by reading this. But like Simon said, this is what happens when you let America vote. Of course, the votes are a bit off because of people like my sister. She has said she is voting for Jon Peter Lewis no matter if he is the best or the worst singer, but just because he is cute.  Teenage girls are so weird!!!  I thought that even when I was a teenage girl.   I have been reading this book for my history class. It is a collection of 100 stories from the Middle Ages. I have to write a 6 page paper by using these stories to show how life must have been like during this time. So far all I have learned is that there was a lot of sexual stuff going on and I have only read 9 of the stories. Well, that is all for now.   !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!  Trivial Question   What is the name of the black stone discovered in Egypt in 1799 that was inscribed in three different scripts, which, after deciphering it, allowed us to understand ancient Egyptian hieroglyphics?   Answer-   The Rosetta Stone 
     
    
</post>
<date>30,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today I ran a few errands. I went to the bank, stopped by the NEX to pick up  Brother Bear  on DVD. I went over to the Barnes and Noble and got a few new books, thanks to my friend Trish. I went to the Best Buy and got some printer ink and the movie  How To Lose A Guy In 10 Days . I stopped and got milk on the way home. We had frozen pizza for dinner. It is Motown night on American Idol. I voted Fantasia Barrino, Carolynn voted for Jennifer Hudson, and I predicted that Phillip would have voted for Diana Degarmo. He was at work, as usual. He will watch it in the morning when he gets home. I think Camile Velasco is going to get voted off. Of course, I thought that she’d go the last three weeks and it hasn’t happened yet. So we’ll see.   -/-/-/-/-/-/-/-/-/-/-/-/-/-/-/-/-/-/-/-/-/-/-/-/-/-/-/-/-/-/-/-/-/  Take My Advice   Men: Save your breath for your inflatable dolls. 
     
    
</post>
<date>29,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I didn’t have to go to school today! Cari and Glenn left this morning. I took a nap. I raked some of the garden. The crocuses have bloomed. I have been doing some studying. Carolynn said she had a bad day at school. Catherine refuses to learn to ride her bike. She can ride just fine, but as soon as she realizes you’ve let go, she just falls off. So there isn’t really anything exciting today.  *^*^*^*^*^*^*^*^*^*^*^*^*^*^*^*^*^*^*^*^*^*  Wise Words   Kids in the front seat cause accidents. Accidents in the back seat cause kids. 
     
    
</post>
<date>28,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Being that is Sunday, I am not doing anything today. I am making spaghetti for dinner. Friends are still visiting. I stayed up late playing Pong and Pac-Man. It was like 1982. That’s about it for now.   Just Something To Think About   Depression is merely anger without enthusiasm. 
     
    
</post>
<date>27,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So, it is a bit cooler today than it has been all week. Only into the 40’s today so far and not expected to past 52. Still better than snow. Well, now that school is out for Spring Break, all I have been doing is studying. I have written an essay for my politics class. I have taken notes for another one. I still have so much more I want to do before school starts back up again. My friend Cari is visiting today. Phillip and her husband Glenn have been talking cars and running to the Krispy Kreame. Carolynn and Paige are bringing down the house. Scott is doing what Scott does which is playing video games. Not much else going on. It’s Saturday so there isn’t even anything on TV.   +=+=+=+=+=+=+=+=+=+=+=+=+=+=+=+=+  Mythology For You   What is the name of the legendary bird that sets fire to it self and then rises from the ashes to live again?   Answer-   The Phoenix 
     
    
</post>
<date>26,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So it’s Friday. Last nights Friends was a good one. I had my last history class before Spring break today. My teacher has assigned a book report for over the break. That kind of sucks. The weather is getting better. It has been raining for days, but in the 60’s. I have been getting the house cleaned. I got the floors all mopped. I painted my toenails blue since it is going to be sandals season soon. What an exciting life I lead!  In other news, I saw that Richard Simmons was charged with assault after he slapped a guy in an airport for making fun of his Sweatin’ To The Oldies videos. I saw that there was a four eared cat in Germany who finally found a family to adopt it. That was kind of creepy and weird.   I am sure you have heard that there is currently a case in the Supreme Court that will decide whether the words “under God” belong in the Pledge Of Allegiance. As the case goes, a man took a school district in California to court because he didn’t think his child saying those words was constitutional. He is an atheist and feels that every time his daughter said the pledge it was like a slap in the face to him. What I find odd about the whole situation is that he does not have custody of the child, the mother does. And what is even odder is that the mother is raising the daughter as a Christian, as she is one herself. Also, as it turns out, the daughter doesn’t really care either way. The way I see it, when you say the pledge, you are pledging to the country and the words “Under God” do not necessarily mean anything religious, but something said out of respect for the men who founded this country, who were Christian. It is traditional, like the words “In God We Trust” printed on our money or the prayers that are offered before sessions of Congress or the Supreme Court. However, the reason that they put those words in, in 1954, was to show how we were better than those godless communists. So that in it self may be unconstitutional. I don’t know. It all seems kind of like a waste of the courts time to me. There is no law saying that the little girl has to say the pledge at all. So why bother taking all this time and money to decide it. People really have gone kind of sue-happy. I saw on the news that most Americans think the pledge should stay how it is. (Also for those who can't remember the words: I pledge allegiance to the flag of the United States Of America, and to the rupublic for which it stands, one nation, under God, indivisible, with liberty and justice for all.)  So that is all the news for today. Tomorrow is my last class before Spring Break. I am just one biology class away from freedom for a whole week. And my friend Cari is coming over tomorrow. Sounds like it’s going to be a good weekend. And the best part, today I saw my tulips and things shooting up.  SPRING IS HERE!!!!!!   ================================================  Just Out Of Curiosity……………..   In what city was the trial of Nazi leaders conducted after World War II?   Answer:   Nuremburg  
     
    
</post>
<date>25,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last nights Survivor was just a recap episode. That must mean there’s a merge coming, even though they hinted that there was going to be some major twist instead. I still think Boston Rob is an a—hole. I think women are going to be his downfall. He thinks he is just such a stud muffin. The only person I know who is any kind of baked good is my own Sweetie Pie. I also think Jerri has to go. I hate her.   Then on American Idol, I thought it would be Camile Velasco to be the one to go. I have never really liked her. I liked Matt Rodgers. He wasn’t the greatest on Tuesday, but I thought Camile was worse. We saw my mom and dad and my sister in the audience. They were sitting behind the judges so they were on TV a bunch of times. Carolynn was so excited. It was so funny to see them on her favorite show. She is just having an exciting week; Clay and Kelly in concert and then Grandma and Grandpa on American Idol. Also, Kimberly Locke sang her song. Her album comes out May 4. We heard Clay sing one of the songs off her album on Monday night. They sing it together on her new album.   Today, I went to my politics class. Last one, because next week is Spring break. WOO HOO!!! NO SCHOOL FOR A WHOLE WEEK!!!! And we got out early, and didn’t have to do any work. That’s always a plus. Tonight is also the number 3 pick of best Friends episodes. I haven’t seen my favorite yet. But they are all good so I guess it doesn’t matter. Also, today is Phillip’s Aunt Sherri’s birthday, so happy birthday to her. Tomorrow is Friday. My friend Cari is coming to visit this weekend. Carolynn is excited to see her friend Paige. That is all for today.  ()()()()()()()()()()()()()()()()()()()()()()()()()()()()()()()()  Here’s A Puzzler:   Why do psychics have to ask for your name? 
     
    
</post>
<date>24,March,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, today not much happened. I went to my history class. I made pork chops for dinner. I was going to make them on Sunday, but Phillip had duty so I didn’t. Carolynn went to school. Phillip went to school. I got a certificate in the mail from my school saying that I made the college honor list. Tonight is both Survivor and American Idol. My mom, dad, and sister are seeing American Idol in person today, so we will be looking for them on TV tonight.  Phillip wants me to add that his mom is coming to visit. She is flying out here on June 9th and staying until the 15th. We are going to take the tour of Chicago, go to the Jelly Belly factory, and maybe we’ll go take the brewery tour. I am sure we will do some barbecuing and hanging out. Phillip is pretty happy about it.   </post></Blog>