<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>31,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      please.. let me write some more in this blog to tell you about my oh-so-interesting life. i could run through the bathroom and get rachel's diary out from between her matresses on the left side of the bed if you were facing the window and tell you about her life instead. But she'd get upset if she knew i knew where it was. Which i don't. So have you ever looked @ a bubble? I mean really looked at one. To the point that you thought  hey i'd like to get in there..  well i haven't. but yo i'll put it on my to-do list. So i have a rough draft in english due friday along with a final report in espanol. I have a chemistry home work sheet due tomorrow and a geometry pre-test to do, even though i've already taken the test. How much sense does that make. And go on.. ask me how much of that i have done. Why no go ahead and ask me how much of it i've even started? You would think with all this free time on my hands i would have time for my homework but between eating and napping and tv and talking to my wonderful sister on the www.. and then the just plain sitting.. time gets away from me.. and my homework just kind of sits there. Maybe that's why it haunts me at 5 am. But i'll get it done. I aint skurred. I always end up getting it done and its always okay. And you would think with me being the totally rad girl that i am that i would have something better to write about.. guess again..... or you could think about it this way: maybe i DO have wicked awesome stuff to write about.. but maybe it's just stuff that the whole world doesn't need to have access to.. there's food for thought. so we have this dog named maggie.. she poops a lot and pees all over the place and mom get real upset.. dad loves her and takes naps with her and i think he loves her more than he does my mother.. and mom gets real upset.. and this dog happens to be the dog that i begged for for years upon years and promised repeatedly that i'd take care of.. and i dont.. and mom gets real upset. having said that i suppose i'll tend to my duties as an 11th grade student and go stare at my huck finn book.. u know how it is.
      
</post>
<date>30,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So i wake up at like 5 in the morning.. and i can't go back to sleep, so i think hey.. why not do some homework? then i used my better judgement and went back to sleep. and then the usual routine goes about with mother beckoning at my door at 7 am when she knows good and well that i never roll out of bed until about 7:20.. so yada yada i get up, get dressed, eat some apple cinnomin (spelling?) oatmeal and go to school. nothing interesting happened today except i ate a hot dog for lunch. my friend Alise is coming over to go to church with me tonight so she can meet this boy that goes there. I'd hate to embarrass her so i'll give him the code name of Lucas Womacus. Which is really his name except for the last 'us'. And so the story goes. Yeah.. but uh.. word to tha roomdawgs since you are the only cool girls that read this :D 
      
</post>
<date>30,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      blog blog blog... this is fun. i wish some self-contradicting non-Christian would tell what what a terrible person i am so i would have something to write about. Just kidding! :D okay but i did rip my toenail off today, well not really off but it kinda got bent back and it didn't feel too good. here's the story since in know you're all so interested. so i was walking behing this guy and i kicked his heel accidently. yeah it happens. and that's all the news for today. holler.
      
</post>
<date>22,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I hate school. All highschool is is busy work. You learn to read write and draw pretty rainbows in the third grade.. so buy you a calculator and you're set for life. I tested this reasoning on mother-bear but she wouldn't have it. Things got a little crunk and disorderly up in this muther. I stayed with hailey last night. We stayed up til 2:30 and tried to re-hook her up with her former boo cause we're just BA's like that. Fer real tho. I think we made quite a bit of progress. Aw snap. If there's one thing i've learned from watching other people's relationships (because i HAVE had so many of my own)... it's just that guys are idiots. I dont know why i've developed such a strong hatred towards the average male specimen. But i have so get over it. I'm sure it's just a passing phase. It'll be over by tomorrow around 8 or 9 cause hailey's comin over and so is her ex boo and my former/potential boo. And lemma tell ya... thangs are gonna get a lil crunk and disorderly up in this muther! I think rach will be coming home. I hope she doesnt wanna chill with us. that would make things orderly and uncrunk. And with having said that, i'm gonna go because i needa straightin my hurr b-fo full hizouse cums on. Life is ghetto fabolous. Because when my mom came to tell me goodnight tonite.. she said "nite dirty"... and i swear she did. And that makes me want to inflict large amounts of phsyical pain upon my dog. Whom i got in trouble for kicking today. whatever.
      
</post>
<date>20,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      My internet's been messed up so i haven't "blogged it" lately.. haven't had a lot to say anyway. mainly because i hate guys.. i guess it's because i have this thing about people lying to me.. call me crazy but i don't like it. But everything usually works out (usually) and stuff happens but it all comes together in the end. no worries. i'm going to the prom with robby trammel. that's who i escorted on homecoming court. my sis is coming home from college soon. maybe she'll fight with me, maybe she wont. this is the moment of truth. i dont know where i come up with this senseless babble. for those of you that are wondering, reguardless of all my pointless attempts to cease the life of maggie, she lives. Long live the dog. hooty hoo. whatever. and that's all i have to say about that. besides the fact that i made a D in espanol. i guess i should have done that report.....i'm thinking of taking up yoga as a hobby. my soul could use a little clensing. holler. 
      
</post>
<date>06,April,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      so my sis got all emotional in here blooger today and it put me in a blogging mood. hailey stayed with me last night so that we could do our homework together, and we watched texas chainsaw and baked a chocolate cake. and no, the icing does not come in the box (thanks rach).. and there was actually a point that we did consider doing our homework.. but it was a long walk out to the car. and there's just no sense in walking out there to get it just to come inside and look at it. i dont care a whole lot for my dog maggie. dad really likes her and wont let me lock her outside for a long time. he wont let me feed her chocolate either.. so i just slip her some pizza rolls here and there. get her good and fat for the next dog eating buzzard that flies by. sometimes i really miss my sister. then there are times that she tells me she doesn't want to fight with be but yells at me for "getting smart" when i look at her the wrong way. talk about a weirdo.. ok so maybe i didn't have as much to say today as i thought. i miss will. William Burley Cooley. that used to chill @ da crib wen RaCh*bAbY was his boo. that's over and done with. GO TWC BASEBALL! AND MCMINN SOCCER </post></Blog>