<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      hmmm... okay... i saw a very shocking news.. okay? i checked my friend's friendster to see if he has approved my testimonial for him... accidentally, i knew from one of his testimonials, actually from Eldric, that, this friend of mine, once loved me... this is the testimonial:  c payat... grabe yan... adik ... parang ako.lgi kmi magkasama, sa ragnarok,sa lakwatsa,pero d ko sya kasama sa pangbababae..d joke lng.. mabait yan. tpos parang DAO MING ZI.. makulit na pangasar..sarap kasama.. kaya lng dapat mo siyang hawakan kpag humahangin..hahahahaha.. joke.. idol ko sa ragnarok yan kce scammer at hacker..looter pa.. malakas kce charac niya.. ano p b? mahal na mahal niya si jhamie,c roan,c may,and  dati c Ms.Raya .. huhuhu.. pero happy nako ngaun.. pag pumupunta yan d2 sa bahay.. lgi ako binubuking sa mommy ko.. kaya lgi ko siya niyayaya sa labas para maglaro.. highest jumper yan. abot niya kce ung ring sa school e.. pag 2matalon nga yan ung tuhod niya nasa leeg ko na.. hahaha.. un lng... [his name] un lng...   well, that's really shocking for me.. because, i never thought of that....    sadly, my sister likes this guy.. and now, she's kinda angry and of course, also shocked with this... heeeeelllllppppp!!!!!     
      
</post>
<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      i'm feeling kinda happy today...   this morning, i went to school to meet Adel because we're gonna get our physics book.. after that, we stayed at the hs benches and we talked and talked and talked... haaay... i really missed that.. it's been a long long time since we had our last chikahan... we should have been to the mall, but we have something to do.. so, we ended up eating at mcdo and we talked again.. we really missed each other....  haaay.... i feel great because, we had our bonding together today.... ;)
      
</post>
<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      well, we've got lots of things to say hello to and lots of thing to say goodbye to.. especially this end of summer...    hello school, goodbye summer...   obviously, the opening of the next school year is coming and most of us hate it.. who hates summer anyway??? hmm.. whether we like it or not, we have to go to school and face our responsibilities like doing all those "nakakaiyak na" assignments, projects.. and we have to attend those practices wherein we don't really practice at all, we just make "kwentuhan, chikahan and bili-bili ng food sa may co-op, jollibee, mcdo at sa lahat na ng food chain sa dapitan.. and for the guys, ang walang katapusang pagraragnarok o di kaya'y billiards na may kasamang piyaya..".. hehehe.. actually, that's kinda our life in saturdays... but, we still get to finish our tasks and end with a great project...     hello freehands, goodbye working hands.. ;)   hmmm.. since the classes are starting, i will not have time anymore to wash loads of dishes everylunch! and i don't have to do the laundry anymore... ;)... sounds, lazy huh???     hello books, assignments, projects,.. goodbye overtime in internet, over-telebabad and over-texting (from the moment you wake up till the moment you sleep)..   well, i guess, it's kinda obvious... i have to spend most of my time reading my books, doing my assignments and projects... simply, i have to study really hard!!!... i can't have time for the internet that much (which i really enjoyed this summer), spending lots of time on the phone (just making chika about my kilig summer), and most of all, texting.. i have to hide it cuz u know... ;)   last,  hello, cute guys and goodbye to boredom and searching here in my place even if i know, there's none! hahaha   the most enjoyable part of being in school, of course, the cute guys! every girl in the campus is looking for them! i will get to see again my crush, Kenneth, Alvin, Paolo, Peter and other guys... hahaha... well, they're just my crush.. i'm not planning to be close to them.. okay?   hahaha.. it's really nice being in school because i know, that wherever i may look, there'll be a cutie.. compared here, there's obviously none! maybe they're not just my type?? no, i don't feel them.. no offense.. peace!!   there's a lot of things we'll miss after summer... but, we can still do these things once in a while.. ;)
      
</post>
<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      uh, well, i can't think of any title for this post... so, i decided to entitle it like that...  as you can see in my previous post which has the title, "shut up!".. i'm kinda bad-tripped   because of my sisters.. you know, they are calling me a "snatcher" because they think/feel/or whatever i am snatching other peep's "guy".. the proof, they're kinda giving more time to me than other girls.. well, it's not my problem! it's not my fault if guys are getting close to me.. plus, they're not courting me anyway.. they're just being nice and they want to make friends with me... and i'm not flirting with them anyway esp. when i know that they're already taken or whatever it may be...  uhm, just wanna make it clear to them.. ;)  
      
</post>
<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      my sisters are bugging me.. and i don't like it.. hellur?!??? 
      
</post>
<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      well, i'm feeling kinda okay now... he texted me last night saying sorry.. and he's gonna call later... that's what he said.. hahaha  
      
</post>
<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      yesterday, we discussed about that... i realized that the words  pagmamahal  and  pag-ibig  are really different from each other even if they only mean one thing in english...  so here's their differences:   pagmamahal:  galing sa word na  mahal ... of course, if you love a person, u are going to take care of them  , u are willing to sacrifice for them and  mahalaga  sila para sayo. ngayon, sa word na mahalaga, makukuha natin ang words na  mahal, alaga at halaga . there's no reason behind loving a person kasi minahal mo siya dahil mahal mo siya.. di ba?  next,   pag-ibig:  ang ibig sabihin ng  ibig, gusto, like, want .. it's  more of just liking not really love.. example, u like that person because of his nice body.. but, what if naaksidente siya? eh di wala na ang nice body nya.. magugustuhan mo pa ba siya? hindi na diba? kasi un lang naman gusto mo sa kanya eh.. right?   now, kapag sinabihan ka ng  iiniibig  kita, wag kang maniniwala kasi  gusto lang yon .. pero pag sinabihan ka ng  mahal  kita,  totoo un ..     buti na lang, ang sinasabi nila sa akin, "mahal kita..;)" 
      
</post>
<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Every  start  has it's own  ending ... it is true.. right?!??  Today,  the seminar  that i attended since Tuesday is done... I shall come back there on June 4 for the Recollection... Actually, that seminar is like a review on what i have learned in my freshman and sophomore year in Catechetics... i've been  "making sisi"   to myself for throwing away my Catechetics notebook.. all of the subjects in the said seminar was written in my lectures!!! arrgggghhhh!!!   the lesson:   you should not throw away some things in the past because you can still use it in the future....   Next,  the summer vacation  or the so called,  the sarap buhay time ... one week and it's finished! i have to go back to the very cold classroom and meet back my soooo kulit, energetic and weird classmates.. well, i will meet another set of them too.. i also have to meet again my teachers and all those  "mountain high loads"  of school work... plus, i'll be having my CAT..   to look at it at the brighter side, i love going to school.. staying at home looks unusual for me. especially on saturdays wherein i usually spend the rest of the day in the campus practicing or doing my group project... this new and final year in highschool,  i'll be having new friends, i'll have my allowance and this time, i can save some of it so that i will not be poor.. ;)... since there will be classes, my time will be organized.. and the best reason why i love school: i'll get to see my crushes in the campus again and i'll be having new crushes!!! hahahaha... ;)   And last,   the thing between Eldric and me... .. WE ARE NOT! okay??!? yes.. i've been asking myself a long time ago, "what if, this thing between us   ends???" and "how is it going to end??".. "when?".. "what would be the reason?".. you see, i've got lots of questions in my head and i haven't asked him this question yet.. another thing, i wanna know kung "ano na ba kami?".. of course! i wanna know that... he might think that we are but for me, we're not... and for other people too.. i want it to be clear..  now, the thing that scares me is his uhm, not actually attitude, but the way he's talking to me.. he's not like what he was before.. you know, he seems to be cold to me.. he did not text me yesterday... plus, what if, this is how our thing ends? like, this is it! you're until here... the thing between you doesn't seem to work... first, you were just textmates.. friends, okay... but it's not personally.. you do not know him that much... next, we haven't seen each other yet...   ohhhh my!!! why is this happening?!??? you let me know this person and fell inlove with him and you're gonna end this thing just like this? =C   well, i should be ready for what's gonna happen later, tomorrow and on the next days...   in all of the endings i'll be facing, some of them may be a happy ending or unfortunately, i'll be ending everything with a tear.. whatever it will may be, i know.. after all that when i'm through with an end, i'll be having another start.. ;)
      
</post>
<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      well, this morning, we had this seminar for the sacrament of confirmation.. it will be until friday... hmm.. walang cute! meron kanina kaso, di siya kasama sa seminar.. hmmp!!!  
      
</post>
<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      last night, i watched Mel Tiangco's "magpakailanman"... well, it's about the life of a comedian, Mike Nacua, also known as "pekto".. it's about how he surpassed his problems together with his wife.. it's an inspirational story.. ;)
      
</post>
<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      last night i dreamed of Jeff Anthony.. because of that, memories came in my head.. uhm, he's my classmate in elementary and actually, he's my crush.. well, we're not close friends.. it's just that he was my crush and he was crushing me back.. he's not that nice.. you know, he embarrassed me in front of his friends.. he's really bad!!! and i hate him for that! well, on the other side, whenever he sees me having fun with others, he's giving a sign that he's jealous.. yes, i'm flattered about that cuz even if he's doing those embarrasing blah blah, he's still kinda affected.. ;)  another "ghost".. he's Cyrus.. well, he's always like that.. he's always on my mind even if i don't like it anymore.. i admit it that once, i've been addicted to him... but, it's not like that anymore... and i hate it now!!!
      
</post>
<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      uh, well, actually, i decided to make a new blog because i find my old blog too inlove.. well, i always talk about him.. it's him today, it's him yesterday and it's him again tomorrow.. it's not that he's out of my life.. it's just that i don't want by blog to be like that always..   next, the color: pink.. actually, i planned to change the color.. but it seems like i really love the color pink that's why i ended up, choosing a template with that color...
      
</post>
<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      i answered this survey last thursday [i think]... and mostly, my answers were  "multo"  or  "eldric.."   Message: WHO/WHAT do you remember when you hear  these songs?   1. More than you'll ever know by Michael Ruff --&gt; c Opin.. eh kanta nila yan eh!  2. Fallin by Nsync --&gt; c multo/su tian nu... [bawal sabihin ung  name.. kasi delikado na.. mabubuko na naman ako!  baka di ko na siya maharap! nakakahiya!! gosh!]  3. It might be you by Stephen Bishop --&gt; elem days...  4. I'll Be by Edwin McCain --&gt; c bestfriend Carla... atchaka ung endless  love.. heheh  5. Because of You by Keith Martin --&gt; uhm, si multo atchaka si eldric... [o yan..  may pangalan na! eh baka kasi maguluhan ung  magbabasa... ;)]  6. Cry me a river by justin timberlake --&gt; britney spears daw.. ;)  7. Let me be the one by Jimmy Bondoc --&gt; c eldric.. ewan ko.. basta, siya naalala ko  eh..  8. Maybe by King --&gt; c multo ulit!!! eh akmang akma ang lyrics for  him eh...  9. Jealous by Nina --&gt; c multo pa rin... kanta ko yan sa kanya nung  nalaman kong may girlfriend na sha.. hmm..  nakakalungkot...  10. Rainbow by Southborder --&gt; c multo [kinakanta kasi nya yan eh,,,]  atchaka si eldric ulit...  11. Kahit kailan by Southborder --&gt; si eldric ulit.. :)  12. Angel of mine by Monica --&gt; c frederick... ;)  13. A Little Bit by MYMP --&gt; kapatid ko..  14. Why by Avril Lavigne --&gt; hay nako! si multo na naman!  15. Moonlight over Paris by Paolo Santos --&gt; wahhaaha!! si jc!!! dudududududuyduduy... [sa  freebreak! hahaha!] bad trip ako nung araw na un  eh!  16. Miss you by Aaliyah --&gt; cellphone ng sister ko.. [ang layo noh?]  17. On bended knee by Boyz II Men --&gt; hmm... ate ko... [naks! naalala ko ung mga  kapatid ko! heheh]  18. You Were There by Regine V. --&gt; hmm... ung friends ko....  19. Dreaming of you by Selena --&gt; si frederick...  20. You've made me stronger by Regine V. --&gt; di ko lam yang song na yan.. pero sa title,  si eldric naalala ko.. :)  21. Before i let you go by Freestyle --&gt; c eldric pa rin... ;) [hay!! anu ba ito?!??]  22. Paki sabi nalang by Aiza S. --&gt; c multo!!!  23. I've fallen for you by Freshmen --&gt; ahhhh!! ayoko sanang sabihin pero si company  ang naisip ko dyan.. well, muntikan lang naman eh!  24. I'll still say yes by Freestyle --&gt; hmm...  25. Bakit nga ba mahal kita by Roselle N. --&gt; ahaha!! si dan carey!! kasi kinanta niya ung  isa pang song ni Roselle N.. eh! back in grade 5!  26. Sa'yo lamang (unknown singer) --&gt; kapatid ko...   27. Never had a dream come true by S Club 7 --&gt; c multo!   28. If You're Not The One by Daniel Beddingfield? --&gt; ate ko! kanta nya yan para kay labs nya eh...  29. The way you look at me by Christian Bautista --&gt; c multo... [anu ba yan! nagmumulto talaga!!!]  30. If You Come Back by Blue --&gt; wala...  31. Shape of my heart by Backstreet Boys --&gt; c Carla at si Joem atchaka si frederick...  32. Toxic by Britney Spears --&gt; c multo pa rin...  33. From This Moment on By Shania Twain --&gt; si opin.. kinanta nya yan sa videoke eh.. hehe  34. 6, 8, 12 by Brian McKnight? --&gt; si multo pa rin.. eh multo nga eh! shempre!  naiisip ko.. :)  35. Selfish by N SYnc? --&gt; wala.. :)  36. Burn by Usher? --&gt; si Glessie...  37. Torn by Natalie Imbruglia? --&gt; friends ko nung elem..  38. Get Busy by Sean Paul? --&gt; cm8s ko last year!  39. In Da Club by 50 Cent? --&gt; cm8s ko last year ulit!  40. Swear It All Over Again by Westlife? --&gt; si opin din.. ;)
      
</post>
<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      normal lang naman ang nangyayari sa akin nitong mga nakaraang araw   june 21 -   wala lang... si multo, nagtetext lang at nagmimiss call... hay naku!!! loko talaga yun! nakakaloko na naman.. pakiramdam ko si Still, may gusto pa rin sa kaibigan ko.. hellur??? eh ano ngayon?!? at nung gabi na, tinext ako ng aking first love na si Frederick Cruz... medyo nag-iba ang pakiramdam ko nang mabasa ko ang text nyang:  "hindi mo pa ba ako kilala?? matagal mo na akong nakasama bago ka pa umalis..."    june 22 -  kaarawan ng aking kaibigang si John Antolin.. o, dabuh??? friend siya ni Eldric... ;) kakaiba tong araw na to kasi ung mga kaibigan ko, inaasar akong may gusto sa akin si Still... so what??? kinakantahan pa nila ako ng "muling ibalik ang tamis ng pag-ibig"... nyeh!! korni!! kakilakilabot!   june 23 -  tinext ako ni multo ... eion, tapos feeling ko, balik na naman ako sa dati... eto ang linya sa kanta na naglalarawan ng nararamdaman ko: ".. and i'm back in the game i can't seem to win.. love's knockin on the door..." ashoooo!!! as if!    june 24 -  walang pasok!!! araw ng maynila... eion, nung bandan tanghali, naisipan kong magparamdam kay Eldric.. aba! shemperds, miss ko na ata siya kahit nalilito na ako... eion, di ko siya mashadong maintindihan kasi parang meron siyang gustong sabihin o itanong kaso ayaw niya... nag-aalala na nga ako eh...  anu kaya un???    june 25 -   ang araw ngayon... hindi masyadong maganda ang araw..  una:  dahil kay eldric.. di ko pa rin alam...  pangalawa:  tinawag ko si Still kanina kase pinapatawag siya ng kanyang ewan na kaibigan...  pangatlo:  nagkaroon kami ng isang napakahirap na pagsusulit sa pisika [physics...].. nakakabaliw!  at ang huli:  si "Jessica".. pakiramdam ko, naikwento na nila ng kaibigan niyang si "Lila" ang tungkol sa nakaraan ko.. ang kasaysayan na nangyari sa amin ni Still..ung kadramahan ko.. ay nako! tapos ang flirt!! ehhhh!! nakakainis!! sa katunayan, kaibigan ko siya.. kaso simula nung may nangyari noong kami ay nasa ikadalawang taon pa lamang sa mataas na paaralan [naks! tagalog!], nagbago ang lahat... parang pakiramdam ko na hindi ko na siya ganoon na pwedeng pagkatiwalaan.. haaay!!! mawawala rin to!!!             dumako naman tayo kay eldric... eto... sa tingin ko, mahal ko pa rin siya... haaayyyy!!! kaso, may tumutubo na namang kakaibang damdamin sa puso ko... panu ko ba pipigilan to? si multo kasi eh!!! panu na yan?!?? magmamahal ako ng dalawa?!?? ... nyeh!!!         
      
</post>
<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      wahhhaaa!!! kinikilig ako!!! promise!!! kasi si Multo!!! atchaka si Still!!! basta... nakakakilig!!! mangyayari din un!! i know!! sayang kasi eh!! ang shongak shongak niya!! hmmmp!!! basta, dapat mas maaga pa para natuloy... hmmp!!! basta! nakakakilig talaga...   &gt;&gt;for more infos ask me nalang... ;)</post></Blog>