<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Baka: I'm the one who started this whole thing. I guess I should say that a lot of this material is copyrighted, so  DON'T COPY IT !!      ***   Koda Nikeli walked into the doorway that lead into the bar. There were many people sitting around, most of them are just blurs and didn't really matter to him. There was only one person he wanted to see.   He looked back to a shadowed corner where he could see a woman sitting alone, reclining.    Same old Jinix.  Nikeli walked to the back and sat down in front of Jinix.   "Carjulé, you never change do you?" he asked her.   She looked up, her yellow cat eyes meeting his directly, and gave her classic Corellian smirk. "Your life wouldn't be as exciting if I changed." 
     
    
</post>
<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Khala groaned. According to Thellas, after the energy weapon's shot bored into her leg, she had fallen, hitting her head on the hard top of the wall.  Now, the Fremen cracked open her eyes to find her vision blurred by some sort of gel. Air appeared to be administered to her via a tube and mask from the surface, and she noticed her clothing to be a bit on the revealing end of things. Unhappy with this situation, she swam (so to speak) to the top of the tank, where she found very little life.  She groped by her side, where she found that her beloved crysknife was missing, as was her zatn'katel. That certainly would not do.  After quickly checking the nearby side of the large tank for life, Khala broke through the wires connected to what little preserved her decency, grabbed a towel, and rid herself of the strange coverings. Once this was done, she climbed down a ladder that led to the top of the odd tank, where she found her Tok'ra garb.  Finally comfortable enough to settle down a bit, she gave the room a more thorough look-over. Small beds with white coverings, each with a set of curtains ready to surround it, lined two long walls. Khala estimated that there were twenty altogether. Another strange tank towered beside hers with two more on the opposing wall. In the center of the wall to her left was a glass door, which led into a seemingly featureless hallway.  Three of the beds on the far half of the room were occupied, but on her side of the room sat only one person: a human (she did not sense any naquada). This woman sat on one of the beds, facing Khala's tank. Her head was down, and she stared at her hands.  The Tok'ra approached, cautiously watching the stranger, noting that her weaponry lay undistrubed on the sheets beside her. After slipping around the tall woman, she replaced the knife and zat on her person. "What have you done to me?" Khala asked.  Jinix looked up, her yellow, cat-like eyes catching the Tok'ra's attention. "I saved your life, for one."  "My life was not in danger."  "Well, you had a pretty bad wound."  "It would have healed shortly."  "And how would I know that?"  "My clothing."  "Why would your clothes give that away?"  "Do many species here dress as I do?" Khala asked, indicating the brown leather garb typical of Tok'ra.  "Only on Tatooine."  "And do these Tatooinians heal quickly or not?"  "I don't think they do."  "Oh." Khala's eyes widened as Thellas reminded her of her trouble with the planetary authorities. Such matters seemed so foreign to Tok'ra. "The locals. Are they still looking for me?"  "We pretty much took care of them."  "Good. We did not want to completely incapacitate them as we did customs."  
     
    
</post>
<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Jin watched as the girl dashed out of the bar.   What the hell?   "Koda...," Jinix was interrupted by her companion.  "I already know.  Let's go see what we can do."  Koda put some credits on the table for the ale and followed the half-breed out of the establishment.  He stayed at her heels directly, knowing that she might pull her lightsaber before knowing the whole story.  The two of them came to where the two guards were trying to climb the wall clumsily.  "Oi!  Dumb-ass duo!" she yelled to the two.  They turned their heads to see a tall, slender woman all in shadow except for the neon iridescence of a silvery green laser blade.  The guards, having not gotten far up the wall, jumped down and began walking towards Koda and Jinix.  The two Corellians remained unfased by the approaching sentinels, even when they pulled their blasters from the holsters.  "Why the hell were you chasing an innocent?" Jinix asked ferociously.  "It's none of your business.  We'll let you live if you just walk away now," responded one of them.  "No, if you bastards 'just walk away' then  we'll  let you live," Koda said.  "Fine."  One of the guards held the blaster level with Nikeli's head.  He never had the time to pull the trigger.  Jinix had suddenly turned up behind him and had shoved her saber through the guards torso.  The other guard turned to face the woman.  He had paled to a terrified milky white and, though it was dark in the alley, his pupils had reduced to the size of pinpoints.  Jinix, in an almost arrogant gesture, turned off her blade, clipped it to her side, and punched the guard in the face.  The guard was knocked out and he fell limply to the floor.  "All of that build up and that's all the action we get," she shook her hand.  "Hard jaw, though.  Nearly popped a blood vessel."  "Where'd you suppose that woman got to?" Koda asked.  "She's unconscious on the top of the wall."  "Never cease to amaze me."  Jin shrugged and leapt agily to the roof.  Nikeli followed her.  Jinix was examining the wound on the woman's leg.  "It's not bad, but not good either.  Probably should take her to the Alliance base here."  Koda lifted the light woman in his arms without a response.
     
    
</post>
<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Khala finished her ale as two security gaurds came in to the bar.    We should leave now before they spot us  "You are right Aldwin," Khala headed for the door and as she did one of the gaurds recognized her and told the other gaurd," Hey you stop where you are."  Run, do not fight them just run we do not want confrontation  Khala heeded Aldwins advice and made a dash for the door all the while dodging a laser shot in the process,"HALT!" The gaurds pursued her out of the bar and down the street. Khala made a right turn down a street, then made a left with laser shot missing her by nanoinches.  She takes another left and comes apon a dead end, "Now what Aldwin, any great ideas now."  Yes climb the wall behind you and you will come out in a main street where you can lose them, I hope "That's reasurring, what the hell," she turns around and starts to scale the wall.   The gaurds round the corner and let out a barrage of shots at the wall almost nocking Khala off.  Khala makes it to the top of the wall and jumps off, but takes a shot in the right leg.  She falls towards the ground and hits and is nocked unconscience.
     
    
</post>
<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      As she reclined slightly in her own booth, Khala listened in on the conversation of those in the booth ahead of her. She wondered briefly if these people might provide the sense of adventure she missed since the Goa'uld had been destroyed. The Stargate had been buried on her homeworld of Arrakis, so returning home was not an option, either, even if she was certain to have a home to return to. Whatever this galaxy was that she had happened into, so far, it hadn't proved anything more interesting than helping the other Tok'ra to build their own civilization.   But these people, whoever they were, sounded as if they might help quell her thirst for adventure.    We should return to our own,   her symbiote reminded her.   They need us to help build a world that might be seen as acceptible to the Tau'ri so that the people of their world can learn of us and we can have relations with them.    Khala rolled her eyes. "When the Tau'ri first met you--us," she whispered back, her low tones blending into the din from the other customers, "they could barely accept us for who we are. What makes you think that the general population of the Tau'ri can take it? They have not seen as many strange things as the first group had."    It can be introduced to them more slowly. Also, with the Goa'uld threat gone, they will not initially believe us to be those hideous beings,   insisted Aldwin.  "The Tau'ri are no less superstitious than my own people. When  I  first met you, I wanted you to undergo the Test of Abomination or at the very least, the Test-Mashad. The Tau'ri will not accept us any easier than I accepted you. It will be as if we had to pay the Taqwa again."  While she said this, the human seated facing her in the next booth caught Khala staring at her, so the Tok'ra diverted her eyes; it would do no good to have any new suspicions here. Already, she had upset the security force guarding this world. If they found her here, both Khala and Aldwin knew that they might have to defend themselves, and that would involve physically harming or incapacitating the unfortunate souls sent to capture them. Too many years avoiding Harkonnens and Jaffa at any cost could not benefit the well-being of anyone the Tok'ra saw as an opponent.     You have too little faith in them, Khala,   Aldwin concluded.   Even if they do not initially assist a friendship between us, they will not condemn us, even as Colonel O'Neill does not.   Now, we should return and do what we can for our kind.    The Fremen nodded, again watching the other booth. "I know. We'll leave when I finish my drink." With that, she picked up the glass in front of her and took a cautious sip of the ale, carefully noting her symbiote's impressions of it. 
     
    
</post>
<date>22,April,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Many elves and humans were walking up and down the avenue.  They had their own intents and so did Briar Letalas.  Andolin was supposed to meet him at this avenue, yet she wasn't here.  His short nerves were breaking.  He had been stood up before, by women he thought he loved, but Andy was his partner in crime and a fellow elf.  So what if she were a thief, she still had an honor code that she upheld.  He folded his arms across his chest and closed his eyes.  Elves had very sharp eyes, but they were very delicate.  Many elves prowled around at night, and did not enjoy the bright sun as the humans seemed to.  Suddenly Briar was pulled into the alley behind him by his collar.  The force threw him off balance and he fell onto the dirt ground.  It took only half a second for his vision to clear, and to see the shadowy form staring out into the crowded street.  He blinked a few times.  The figure was dressed in the clothing of Escalace, the Western Kingdom.  The character wore a black Veil to hide its face except for the eyes, with dark colored clothing.  The Westerners were often distant to outsiders, and weren't very sociable amongst themselves.  It was rather unnerving to be in the presence of one.  Of course, Andolin came from Escalace, so Briar was used to the prowess she held.  "Who are you?"  Briar stared at the Westerner. 

						
</post>
<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   The only company she had, besides Hood's hourly visists, was a decomposed skeleton that was chained to the wall.  She sighed and dropped down onto the floor with her back against the wall.  The dungeon wasn't the worst part of her capture; it was the fact that she had been caught by the invariably stupidest law enforcer in the land, it was an awful scar on her pride.  She gave another sigh, drew her knees up to her chest, wrapped her arms around them, and stared blankly across the room.  ***  Sheriff Thomas Hood sat straining over arrest papers.  He muttered about the difficult words and how he should be wandering about the village catching other pieces of  filth.  Old Tom, as the village called him, had had his moment of grandeur and boasting when he had caught the blasted elf, but it was soon to wear off with the hard leaf that lie before him.  He scratched at his balding scalp and rapped on the wooden table with an old featherless quill.  He scratched his head again twice before he placed his quill into the ink well and began to sloppily draw out the arrest record.  ***  Andolin had moved from her drawn up position and was throwing loose stones at the ugly, cracked masonary wall.  If only she had a quill and paper, her bored mind would have something to do.  What was worse, claustrophobia was beginning to settle in, and the shadows seemed to be crawling closer and closer to the young elf.  *Letalas, you'd better get her soon.*  She stood and walked to the small, barred window that didn't give much light into the dungeon.  She stood just outside the dim square on the floor.  This offered her the best view without temporarily blinding her.  ***   

						
</post>
<date>21,April,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Baka: Hey, guys. I'm here too. Please don't copy this idea. I hold it dear.      ***   The Code of the Dragon   Chapter One: Sentinel Village, Lockhana (Eastern Kingdom), Cirenhem   Andolin Dragonrider, most hunted elf in Cirenhem, was pacing in a dark, dank, reeking dungeon. She had had no food for several hours, but the sheriff would bring her a bowl of water. Not that shw was drinking it, she had no trust in the old man.  

						
</post>
<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   He opened the door that led down a flight of dark, crumbling stairs.  Saltar began his descent, his black cape drifting lightly after him.  The dungeon was not a place even he would want to stay too long.  It was damp and smelled faintly of rotting carrion.  The walls were also deteriorating, ready to fall to pieces taking the rest of the building with it.  Water could be heard dripping in from the soil, and, no matter what the temperature out side, it was always cold.  Even the lightest footsteps echoed off the old walls along with that eerie drip.  ***  Andolin could hear the door open with a creak.  All doors blocking out these conditions would.  She could hear the loose stones fall from the stair or crunch underneath the slightly faint steps that were coming closer and closer. 

						
</post>
<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   "Are you questioning my expertise?" the voice asked with a devious ferocity.  Hood got a panicked look on his face.  "No, S...Saltar.  I...I was just...," he managed to stutter as a black gloved hand grabbed his huge neck and began to squeeze.  The speaker had stepped close to the fat sheriff.  Saltar lifted him from his wooden seat by the neck and was dangling him a good few inches in the air.  Saltar was an evil sorcerer that used magic to manipulate anything he couldn't naturally.  His appearance also suggested of his power.  He had thick, short, black hair that was slicked back away from his brow.  He was dressed in all black which brought out his pale skin.  Perhaps his most dominate feature, however, was his bright red eyes that always shined with a demonical light, making him even more sinister looking.  His voice was not too deep, his colleagues said it was more spritish.  Thomas hacked violently, trying to catch a breath even though it was impossible with the pressure that the evil wizard was putting on his neck.  "Don't ever doubt my magic," Saltar said slowly while squeezing harder and harder with every word.  He got a look of disgust on his face and dropped the sheriff on the floor in a gasping, wretching heap.  Hood's face was like a huge face beet from the lack of air he had suffered.  "Humans, so fragile," Saltar commented as he kicked the sheriff hard in the side.  Hood coughed, spattering some blood from his mouth.  "Do not forget who is in control here.  Without me, you'd be nothing more than a simple peasant," the sorcerer stated angrily.  Hood didn't respond, too scared to.  "I'll go check on our guest." 

						
</post>
<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   ***  About two hours after he had started on the arrest records, Hood was still scrawling on the paper.  This should have really only taken him a few minutes, but, of course, he hadn't recieved the best education.  Perhaps he should just hire someone to write these damned things.  "Why waste your time writing those stupid things?" a dark and sadistic sounding voice sounded from behind him.  "You know the deal.  She will be erased from all memory soon enough."  "This is just in case your little hex don't work.  Never trusted those damn things." 

						
</post>
<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   "You'll soon find out.  You, however, need to have more caution."  The stranger unraveled the  wrappings from his face and ruffled his short cropped hair.  "You won't be able to save Andolin if you're caught as well."  "Andolin was caught," he rose to his feet and swiped off the dirt, "by who?  The sheriff here's an idiot."  "Believe it or not, it was the sheriff.  However, he wasn't using normal tactics."  "Huh...?"  Briar didn't get the hidden meaning.  "He used dark magic, a very powerful type."  "Okay, now I know you're lying.  Hood couldn't cast a spell let alone a line."  "I would have said the same thing, if I was just a human by-stander, but I'm an elf with a keen eye for magic. He was muttering a curse under his breath."  "Why am I listening to this crap?  I don't know you, nor do I care to know you.  I'll be going now."  He started walking out of the alley, but was stopped by a blonde female.  "Don't you want to save your friend?  I know Pathen does," she said.  The first thing Briar noticed about this girl was that she was not an elf, but a human.  She had golden hair that hung tied behind her ears.  "Who are you and why are you in my way?"  "I'm Kiri, Pathen's partner."  "Who's Pathen?"  "You were just talking to him," she gave a general gesture to the direction of the Westerner.  "Why are you two so interested in my partner?"  "He has his personal reason, don't you Pathen?  I don't really know, but I'll go along."  "Personal reason, what did she take something from you and you want your own revenge?"  Briar sneered.  "She's my fiance,"  Pathen responded frankly.  "Andolin's got a fiance?!" Briar yelled.  "Yes."  "She never told me," he pointed out.  "Our engagement isn't in the approval of The Guild.  That is the only reason she is your accomplice," Andy's fiance responed.  "Now you've got my attention.  So, how are we supposed to save her." 

						
</post>
<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   "So this is the great dragon summoner; captured by a pathetic old man living on borrowed time, sitting, waiting her sentence.  How could such a powerful elf such as yourself allow this to happen?" the owner of the footsteps mocked.    "Well, stranger, perhaps you shouldn't be talking, if you had to rely on 'a pathetic old man living on borrowed time' to capture me," Andolin paused to smile.  "I can sense your prowess.  You're aura is so dark; why didn't you use that awesome power to capture me yourself?"  "You are a sly one, aren't you?  Then again, your whole family is like that, Dragonrider."  "As if you even know my family," Andolin commented bitterly.  "Your whole clan was slaughtered, except you.  They had power to control dragons, but a dragon wouldn't even let you come within a five meter radius of it.  Your mother's last words were, "Don't forget your lineage," which she uttered while you were trying your best to save the last member of your family.  "What a sad ending to such an exciting story."  Andolin stood and walked over to the bars.  "How do you know that, wizard?" she asked with a slight hint of anger seeping through.  "Your mother died in the depths of the forest, did she not?  Trees rarely forget such morbid occasions, especially when a maiden as fair as yourself is crying."  Andolin's face paled slightly.  How could this wizard know?  They were alone when her mother's life energy faded.  Andolin sunk down to her knees.  "Brings back memories, doesn't it?"  "No!  I won't believe you!"  Andolin covered her head, trying feebly to block the sorcerer's voice.  "Lost your confidence?  Most do in the face of Death."  "I'm not dying!" the elf screamed.  "Not yet, but once I drain you of your soul, your life energy, than you will only wish for Death.  You will always see the Reaper close to you, but far away, hungry for a soul.  You will have immortality, but you will be a shell."  Andolin shook violently. 

						
</post>
<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   "I do so enjoy seeing an elf squirm," Saltar commented. He ascended the stone steps with a wicked grin on his lips.   Andolin remained in a crunched up position. Voices from memories echoed through her head; a wizard's trick.   The door clicked shut and agonizing screams echoed down from the upper part of the building.   ***   "Hey! Pathen! Why are we heading out of town if Andy's being held in the prison?" Briar asked haughtily.   "There's a dark aura surrounding the entire building. I fear the sorcerer has already taken control," Pathen responded in a soft voice.   "Uh... Which sorcerer are we talking about?"   "Saltar."   "That's a stupid name," he commented.   "Well, Briar is kind of girlish. Luckily we don't judge by names," Kiri said cheerily.   "Hey! My name's not girlish!"   "It isn't?" Kiri teased.   Pathen shook his head.  Andolin, I hope you're alright. I can't even laugh at simple things knowing you're in danger.  He clutched his heart; the pain was great.  

						
</post>
<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Baka: You guys sick of me yet? Well, you pretty much know the drill, so I don't have to repeat myself. But I will.      Don't copy anyone's work. It is wrong and illegal.      ***   Kurama stalked through the forest angrily. Why did Kuwabara have to wave his spirit sword around like an imbecile?   He continued through the woods.   Suddenly a huge, ugly, monstrous demon walked through. The other demon looked as though he was pieced together from the parts of other demons. It had ugly bluish-gray skin and sickly yellow hair. The demon had a small horn on its head. Small, white, feathered wings were barely visible over its gigantic shoulders. Its finger and toe nails were green and yellow and all jagged. Kurama didn't even want to dwell on its swelled, bulbous face.   "Show me to the nearest human flesh depository and I will devour you quickly and not so painfully," it roared.   Kurama took the rose tucked behind his ear and it immediately turned into the long, green, thorny, and elegant Rose Whip.   Suddenly, there was a streak of red glowing energy that pierced the demons ugly face. The grotesque demon exploded in a bright white light and was disintegrated.   After the carnage had cleared he looked up into the trees to see a demon holding a bow made entirely out of red demon energy. She had dark brown hair that was split into two short braids that hung just a bit below her shoulder line and two black tails tipped with white could be seen swishing behind her. She had black cat-like ears with a magenta interior and blue glasses over her deep brown eyes. The demon wore a hooded sweatshirt that was ragged and too large for her. It had gray sleeves attached to the maroon body with two gray dragons flanking a yin-yang sign a little bit under the neck. She also wore tattered blue jeans and blue and white tenis shoes that were on their last legs.   She jumped from her branch and landed shakily on the ground, lacking the grace that normally accompanied demons of her nature, but on her feet.   "That's the second one I've had to kill today. Name's Baka, by the way," she said in a clear alto voice. "And you are?"   "Kurama," Kurama responded.   "You know, you have the same name as that famous, dead thief, Yoko Kurama," she pointed out.   "He's not dead. I am him."   "But he had white hair."   "I had to escape into the human world."   "Oh, I feel stupid now."   "That's not surprising."   "What's that s'pose to mean?" she asked angrily.   "Your name is Baka..." He never finished his sentence. Baka hit him over the head. "Hey!"   "No one makes puns on my name," Baka warned. 
     

    
</post>
<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      ***  After the fire incident they had set out again.  "Why are we walking around aimlessly anyway?" Baka asked as she bandaged her poor tail.  They all turned to her with looks that said, "That's the smartest thing we've heard you say so far, but we have no idea.  This is just how The Creators want this story to go."  "Okay, I get the point, you guys are as clueless as I am," Baka pointed out.  "I don't think we're as stupid as you," Kuwabara commented.  "Oi, Numbskull, who's the one who got a  seven  one a  multiple choice test ?" Baka snapped back.  "Geh!  How do you know about that!?" he shouted at the bitailed demon.  "I'll never tell," she responded in a eerie sing-song voice as she shook her finger slowly like a metronome in front of Kuwabara's square face.  Baka walked on ahead of him.  Kuwabara stuffed his hands in his pockets and with a slouch of his shoulders he mumbled, "Creepy little prick."  "I heard that."  Suddenly a woman with light blue hair and a pink kimono flying on an oar landed in front of the group.  "Yusuke," she said in an annoying British accent.  "Oh, who are you?"  "I'm Baka."  "I'm Hito."  "And we're demons who are presently helping these idiots out," Baka said.  "Speak for yourself," Kuwabara commented under his breath.  "I heard that."  "Gyy!"  "Alright.  Well, anyway, Yusuke, an extremely powerful demon is heading towards Mushiori City.  He's going to kill everyone and devour them."  "Let me guess, Botan, Koenma wants me to kill him off, right?"  "Bingo!" Botan responded cheerily.  ***  They came to a point directly in the demon's path, weapons ready.  Every foot step the demon took, he shook the ground.  The demon was huge, but even that would be an understatement.  They had to tilt their heads all the way back to see the guys face.  All of them attacked at once.  Kurama wielding his signature Rose Whip, Hiei with his katana, Kuwabara with the spirit sword (*cough* lightsaber rip off *cough*), while Yusuke, Baka, and Hito used their projectile attacks.  None of them worked, he swatted them away with a simple motion of his hand.  "You can't defeat me with those pathetic attacks, you fools."  "Gah!  Bad breath!" Baka stated as she covered her sensitive nose.  With his abnormally large hand, the demon swept them all away, sending them into trees.  "Damn!" Hiei spat as he picked himself off the ground.  "Such insanely strong power!  How will we defeat him?" Kuwabara paniced.  "Drama prince.  This calls for my infamous tear-jerking jaw-breaker."  Baka pulled a fist-sized red orb out of thin air.  "What the hell is that?" Hiei asked.  "I just told you.  This is guaranteed to cause instant paralysis to whoever eats it."  She walked up to the large demon, only about the height of the demon's big toe.  "Hey, mister big, powerful demon dude.  Um, I've got something you might want to try," she shouted up to him.  The demon looked down.  "What is it?"  "Just a really tastey piece of human food."  "Fine."   What an idiot.   Baka climbed nimbly up a tree till she was eyelevel with the demon.  She handed him the small orb and he popped it in his mouth.  Almost instantly he froze up.  "Now!" she shouted.  Hiei took this opportunity.  He sliced through the demon like he was soft butter.  The demon disappeared instantly.  After Hiei and Baka had reached the ground, Yusuke asked, "What did you put in those?!"  "Special secret recipe."
     

    
</post>
<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
         After at least another good hour, Hito finally awoke, she stood stretching for a moment then sat again her legs cross as her eyes then seemed to reflect a fire that wasn't there. Baka awoke as Hito began her meditation, She looked at the flamed eyes that were compleatly detached from everything around. Then teh tip of one of Baka's tails sparked and set on fire.      "AAAAAAH! Ow ow ow!" Baka yelled putting the fire out quickly.      "How'd ya think that could've happened?" Kuwabara asked watching Baka nurse her crispy tail      "I wish I could say, the fire died a long time ago" Kurama said as confused as everyone.      An evil smile crossed Hito's lips as the dead fire began to crackle again. They all looked at her irritated as Kurama hit her in the head knocking her out of meditation but still smiling and laughing as she said innocently,      "What? I didn't do anything!" She sat up as Yuske walked up and muttered      "So, You mean to say we spent an hour getting a fire started when you're a walking LIGHTER?!?!"     She thought for a moment blinking rapidly as she then cheerfully spouted, "Yep-a yep-a!"     Yuske then hit her in the head as well, followed by a kick from Baka. Hiei simply raised an eyebrow as the beating commenced, Kuwabara asked confused,      "So you can like, Create fire and stuff?"      Hito looked at him irritated rubbing her head, "No Numb-Nuts, I create sparkly little fariys that explode in beautiful patterns bringing joy to all of the children of the world!"      "when did you learn how to do that?" Baka asked her tilting her head      Hito tripped her with a swift sweep of her leg as she stood poking the fire with a stick the end of the stick lighting as she then stared at the flame it thenk forming the shape of a small cat.     "Owie!" baka Cried then seeing the shaped flame marvled, "Ooooh! Kitty!"      The flame froze and shaped into a ruby as Hito tossed it into the air kicking it quickly as baka yelled     "NOOOOOOO! Poor kitty..." as the sparkling shards fell to the ground
     

    
</post>
<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Baka, sniffing in the air, responded, "Are your other guys two humans who use extreme amounts of hair gel?"  "Yes."  Kurama turned to the slightly shorter demon, "You can tell that just by smelling the air?"  "What I lack in sight, I make up for in hearing and smell.  I have to admit, you guys have the oddest combination of smells."  "How do you mean?"  Hiei asked.  "For instance, you smell like blood and death, Kurama, here, smells like plants, Hito, for some reason, smells like fries, and your friends, that happen to be lost about a mile that-a-way," she pointed to the left, "smell clearly of hair gel."  "Yep, that's Baka.  She'd be able to smell the smallest molecule of scent from two miles off," Hito commented.  Baka grinned with pride, and her two tails twitched wildly with amour-propre (Don't ask the translation, just know it's a synonym for pride).  "That's right, besterest buddy."  They then set off in the direction of the others and met up with them.  After they had all had another chorus of laughter at Baka's namesake they set up camp, which was them propped up against trees or sprawled on the ground (By the way, that was only Baka, because she enjoys fighting the darkness, not that she knows she's doing it).  ***  Finally, after a long night of crickets chirping, the sun began filtering through the trees, waking the birds of various natures.  One, singing particularly  beautifully , was very close to where the six where still fast asleep, Baka in a completely different position from two minutes ago.  Everyone was starting to wake up, with the exceptions of Baka and Hito who were becoming increasingly annoyed.  Suddenly an arrow and a blast of red energy pierced the bird, and it exploded with a final croaking noise.  Hito and Baka were on their feet, but obviously only half awake.  The crossbow was in Hito's hands while the spirit bow faded quickly from Baka's.  "I hate birds," they mumbled simultaneously.  They then collasped on the ground completely asleep.  "What strange demons," Kurama commented.  The others agreed heartilly.
     

    
</post>
<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      "waaaaaait!" Hito said standing thinking for a moment, "Did you go to 'The High School for Demonic Creatures and Various Other Creatures not Able to be Classified as Humans, Tokyo Branch?"  "Yep yep!!" Baka said cheerily, "And my bestest friend went there to Saki-"  Hito covered her mouth shaking her head depressed, "I don't go by that name anymore, I dropped that name...125 years ago. don't ask"  "Saki!! IT'S REEEEEEEEEALLY YOU?" Baka said praticly jumping up and down  "DON'T CALL ME SAKI!! and yeah, It's me" she said dropping her head as baka hugged her Hito tapping her arm  "What is it my Best-y-est Friend?' She asked smiling  "air!" Hito said weakly   Hiei walked up to Hito as Baka released her, "You went to high school?"  "Yep, in college i majored in pyrotecnichs and explosives and weapons I miss those days."  "The good old days when we worshiped Baccius...how i miss them. I'll be fine" Baka said mock holding back tears  "Baccius, Who's Baccius, you?" Kurama said pointing to Baka  "No!! Baccius is the Greek god of Drunkeness and WILD PARTYING!!" Hito said excited, then quickly returning the nearly emotionless normal state  "we should really try and find the others, it's getting dark. We need to set up a camp or something" Hiei said, turning and dissapearing  "What's going on?" Baka asked as Hiei dissapeared  "The rest of our group, a few friends of ours. He's right we should try to find them. Keep your eyes out for anything." Kurama said walking on down the path the two odd demons catching up with him quickly.
     

    
</post>
<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      "Cool," Baka said like a wide-eyed child playing a friends awesome new game system.  "My name's Baka."  Everyone began laughing in their own way.  Kurama was politely snickering, trying to cover it with his hand while Hito flat out laughed her head off, and Hiei just raised his eyebrow with the always angry expression.  (Hey, that's as close to laughing that you can get from the shadow apparition.)  "Why is it always a pun?!" Baka shouted furiously.  "Maybe...," Hito stopped to try and catch her breath, but it was a hopeless cause, "maybe it's because your name is Idiot!"  Another round of laughter pierced the normal serene silence of the forest.  "My name is not Idiot!  It's Baka!"   "Same difference!" Hito continued to laugh.  "Errr..."  Baka shook her tight-clenched fist.  "Don't take it personally, Baka.  It's just you have to admit that it is pretty funny," Kurama tried as a comforting remark.  "Jeez...  That makes me feel a whole lot better," she rolled her eyes with the sarcastic remark.  She then hit Kurama in the head, followed by Hito, with a fan that just seemed to appear out of thin air.  "Ow!" they said together.  "I'm feelin' better now," Baka commented with a satisfied smile on her face while she gave them all the peace sign.  "Where'd that come from?" Hito asked, rubbing her head where Baka had wacked her.  "I'll never tell," Baka responded in an eerie sing-song voice.
     

    
</post>
<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      The girl then followed the path of where the large demon had recently passed. The demon in black jumped down, the white in his spiked hair standing out, he drew his word and prepared to attack. She stopped as his sword was nearing her head, one of her katanas hovered over her eyes as she turned to face her assailant. But all she saw was a black blur, she held her sword ready as she walked on slowly. Hiei was crouching on a tree branch watching this girl curiously. Her walk was slow and paced, she came to the path where Baka stood with Kurama. Hiei made his attack as she turned to look at the path she had just walked on. her sword just blocked his but her still knocked her down. She dragged on the harsh path for a moment before standing, her long black finger nails that looked like they had been sharpened into points, wrapped around the hilt of her sword as she poised for the next attack. Baka and Kurama watched as the two headed off on another attack.   The Girl held her ground as Hiei again became a blur, she looked around the leaned back her sword shielding her heart, Hiei knocked the word from her hand, she performed a quick back flip and stood, She froze hearing the voice of Kurama, her other katana half out of it's sheath.  "Stop NOW!" he said sternly as she looked out of the corner of her eye at him  "Oh! COME on!!!" her sword slid back into the sheath, "You're like the annoying older brother I never wanted but got ANYWAY!"  Kurama walked up to her hitting her in the head, "None of that anger now...Sak...saki, How do you pronounce your name?"  "The human and demonic tongues could never properly pronounce my name for the fact that it takes at least 20 years, starting from birth, to even grasp the simple pronunciation of the language of my home...Call me Hitogoroshi, Or Hito actually" she smiled picking up and sheathing her sword  "Doesn't that mean Murderer?" Baka asked curiously  "yup..." Hito said smiling
     

    
</post>
<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      "DAMN IT!", a girl yelled out walking through the dark forest mumbling, "I don't get paid enough for this, HONESTLY. I'm their best assassin and they send me to kill some high ranking demon!I want to slaughter entire villages not singular demons...Damn it all."  She was seen through a break in the light, long black hair streaked with bright blue, she wore knee high combat boots and a short black kilt that met an inch above her knee. She had on a long black cloak with a few odd symbols on the back embroidered in metallic blood red thread. She had on a black tee-shirt with the word 'FUCT' imprinted on it. Her left ear was pierced 5 times, her right ear 6 times, when she yawned a black 10 gauge barbell ran through her tongue. She had two swords strapped to her back forming an X, in the center of the X was a crossbow. Two katanas lay sheathed on her seat-belt buckle style belt. Her eyes were a deep blood red mixed with a hint of silver, when she raised her right arm to brush back her hair, a tattoo of a scythe on a chain wrapped around her forearm. She stopped and watched the "puzzle" demon cross her path she raised an eyebrow but continued on. Not noticing the demon in all black that sat on a tree watching her.  "If I get this done in the next 8 hours I get triple payout! YES!" she laughed as the castle in the distance loomed like and evil symbol.
     

    
</post>
<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						     Baka:  I think I'm going to rid myself of that whole "If wishes were fishes we'd all cast nets" thing.  I don't really like it.          Hey, I'm writing a new story that involves Baka's homies and a camera.  Let's just say it's going to be fun.    

						
</post>
<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Baka: I posed this question to myself just before I fell into a deep sleep and dreamed about giant spiders from space attacking Earth, how is Dais fifteen in the human world?      Well, first, I figured that maybe a demon year was shorter than a human year. That was immediately shunned due to the fact that I don't know how Yoshihiro Togashi thinks.      Then I figured that maybe she came into the human world just recently, but I didn't think that would leave much room for a plot.      Finally, I thought, "Hey, I don't need to change Dais! I can change her mother."      So, I decided that her mother had died centuries before Dais came to the human world and was reincarnated in the human world.      Then, it kind of takes on a Suichi Minamino story.      *winks*      Kurama: That's a creative way of fixing the problem.      Were you really dreaming of giant, space spiders?      Baka: Ha... *scratches back of head*   

						
</post>
<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Baka: Oh man, I have to take the curse words out of Dais Games. Mom is not on my good side right now.   

						
</post>
<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Baka: Oi! I'm so tired! I'm tired of trying to come up with ideas for my stories! I'm tired of it all!  Dais Games  is supposed to be easy for me to write, considering I have the personalities down to a fine art, but it's driving me insane.        I already know that there aren't many people reading it yet, and I should probably post it on another site as well to get it circulating a bit. I, however, don't think I can.        At first I just thought I was writing this for me, but now I feel obligated to write for others.        I don't like this pressure.        Kurama: You started it, why don't you finish?       Baka: Refer to the above.        Kurama: You're always complaining that you never finish what you started. Now is your chance.        Baka: I know, but I don't like all this pressure.        Kurama: 'Pressure turns coal into diamonds.' You can work past it.        Baka: Yeah, I guess you're right.     

						
</post>
<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Baka: Yo, I'm back dudes.        Kurama: What's with the introduction?        Baka: He's back too, dudes.        Anyway, these are just some ideas that I throw around in my head. Nothing in particular, some might make it and others won't. Although, I do think they'll all make it.        Kurama: You didn't answer my question.        Baka: Oh well.        ***    (date unknown)        Dais Games: Chapter (not determined)        (Spirit detectives and Dais somehow turn up in a pitch black cave, maybe teleported in, or some other-worldly apparition from Dais' past leads them there to uncover something; I'll work out the details later)(They know she is a fire adept)         Yusuke:  You know, it would be nice to have some light, like a torch? *turns to glare at the barely visible silhouette of Dais (Kurama has been using one of his plant concoctions to illuminate the cave)*         Kuwabara:  Yeah, that would be nice.         Dais:  *the general spiteful attitude it in place here* 'If wishes were fishes we'd all cast nets.'        Hiei: *sideways glance at the taller demon* Who the hell says that?        Dais: *very annoyed* The disembodied entities that people credit phrases to because they don't know or care who really said it. Why do you think I know?        *Hiei doesn't respond*        *Kuwabara stops for a second trying to make sense of Dais' statement*        Dais: It's not that difficult, dumb-ass.        ***    (date unknown)        Random Idea        I think I'm going to make Dais like Sohma Hatsuhara from Fruits Basket. I like the idea of her having two personalities, however, I'd prefer that she works progressively up to the darker side.        I was also thinking of putting in a scene like at the beginning of Saiyuki Volume 3 where an evil demon from Dais' past removes and obliterates her power limiter and she reverts to her ultimate demon form.        That evil demon could be named Yisou like that fellow who has it out for Hakkai at the end of Volume 3.        ***    (date unknown)        Dais Games: Chapter (not determined)        (The group is in the depths of the forest surrounded by shikigami of the evil demon, Yisou [why let a perfectly good yin-yang master go to waste])(Dais' glare is fixated on her ultimate enemy, unaware of what he is about to do)        Yisou: *eyes shining with insanely devious pleasure at his greatest scheme) You wandered right into my trap. How utterly stupid of you.        *Dais' narrows eyes*        *the other four glance at one another wondering about this mysterious demon*        *Yisou motions to one of the shikigami nearest to Dais*        *it grabs her arm and throws Dais before the demon's feet*        Kurama: *worried* Dais...        *she risesto her feet and meets Yisou's gaze*        Yisou: I suppose they don't know about your awful secret. Shame you can't be honest with them. All of you will learn the hard way.        *Dais, finally realizing the demon's plan, thrusts her claws at Yisou's chest*        *he grabs her wrist with bone crushing force*        *Dais gasps at the immense pain*        *Yisou smiles even more wickedly**he grabs the solid gold arm band above her elbow and squeezes it until it shatters*        Dais: No...        *for a second she looks as though she is about to faint**her eyes turn a blood red color and she sinks to the ground trembling in agony*        ***        Baka: That's all I really have for this particular entry.        Kurama: I can't wait for the ending.        Baka: Saying that just makes you sound like a perv, you know?        Kurama: Don't spoil it for everyone else.        Baka: You're starting to sound more and more like Sohma Shigure.        Kurama: Who's that?        Baka: You'd have to watch and read Fruits Basket.     

						
</post>
<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						     I saw "The Village" by M. Night Shyamalan.  OMG!  It was so awesome!          It also inspired me to do something different with Dai.          She's going to be completely blind, but she can see a color that represents Kurama.          Kinda like Ivy Walker and Joaquin Phoenix's character who's name escapes me as of yet.          I'm also thinking that she enters these woods that are full of demons.          I hope M. Night Shyamalan won't be upset that I'm kinda taking his idea.          If M. Night Shyamalan is reading this then I sincerely apologize and I think your name is really kick ass.          I'm just going to say it for kicks; M. Night Shyamalan.    

						
</post>
<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Yesterday I decided that I would stop writing on Dais Games. Wasn't my best work and wasn't going anywhere.      C'est la vie.   

						
</post>
<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       (Baka and Yusuke, deciding to do a little spy work, are watching Dais and Kurama on what was supposed to be a secret date)      (Dais and Kurama are sitting side by side in a booth)      Baka: I never thought I would live to see the day that Dais would wear a skirt. She looks pretty spiffy, but not as good as Kurama and that tux.      Yusuke: I think she should wear a skirt more often. She wouldn't be mistaken for a guy.      Baka: That's cold, dude.      Yusuke: It's true though.      Baka: Shhh... They're talking.      Dais: I'm never wearing a skirt again.      Kurama: I think you look nice, though.      Dais: You and about half the other guys on dates here. (Dais gestures in the general direction of someone behind her)      (Baka turns the camera to the guy)      (Noticing the angered look of his girlfriend he focuses on the girl's face and tries extremely hard to not stare at Dais)      Baka: That dudes busted.      Yusuke: Shoot, if Keiko found me starring at another girl she would knock me out.      Baka: Why am I the only one without a date?      Yusuke: Maybe you should start looking for other girls.      Baka: I'll kill you later.      Dais: We're being watched.      (Baka nearly drops camera)      Baka: Oh crap!      (Baka catches camera before it hits the floor)      Kurama: Just ignore them.      Dais: I plan to.      Kurama: Good.      (Kurama places his arm over Dais' shoulder and pulls her in close)      Kurama: Besides there is always that embarassing footage of Baka sleep-talking.      Baka: What's he talking about?      Yusuke: Uh... I...I don't know.      (Baka puts the camera on the ledge of the window facing her and Urameshi)      (She grabs Yusuke by the collar with both hands)      Baka:  Tell me!      Yusuke:  Ah!  Let me go!      Baka:  Tell me!      Some random person who walks out to smoke who is also off screen:  Hey!  What are you two kids doing out here!?      (Baka and Yusuke look surprised at the person)      (Baka snatches the camera and they both run off)      (Screen goes fuzzy)  
     
    
</post>
<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       (I apologize for the poor Spanish grammar here)      (Cinni put on a night vision attachment to the camera)      (Baka is sleeping)      (A door closes off screen)      Kurama:  Why are you filming Baka while she's asleep?      Cinni:  Well, about a year ago Baka invited Scrubby and me to a sleepover.  She made us watch a lot of scifi movies.  Finally we all got to sleep, only to be awakened by Baka shouting in a different language.      At first we thought she had been possessed by another demon, but as it turns out she was yelling in Spanish.      Kurama:  She does this every night?      Cinni:  Most.      (Yusuke enters)      Yusuke:  What's going on?      Kurama:  It seems Baka can speak Spanish in her sleep.      Baka:  Los monos atacan!      Kurama:  The monkeys are attacking!?      Yusuke:  Since when can you understand Spanish?      Kurama:  I took lessons.      Baka:  Mátelos!  Mátelos!      Kurama:  Kill them.  Kill them.      Baka:  Soy la morsa!      Kurama:  I am the walrus?      Yusuke:  I could'be sworn she was a fox.      Baka:  Témame!      Kurama:  Fear me.      Baka:  Molió el control a Mayor Tom.      Kurama:  Ground control to Major Tom?      Cinni;  Baka hates The Beatles, wonder why she's saying that.      Kurama:  I'm asking myself the same question.      Baka:  Los monos mascan en la pierna!      Kurama:  We're back to the monkeys.  She sais the monkeys are chewing on her leg.      Yusuke:  That's wierd.      Kurama:  I agree.      (Screen goes fuzzy)  
     
    
</post>
<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       (The camera is pointed at Baka's feet)      Baka:  Cin, bring the camera up.  It needs to be pointed at my face.      Cinni:  Why?  It's fine where it is.      Baka:  What have you been smoking?  It's pointed at my feet.      Cinni:  Those are some nice shoes, Baka.      Baka:  You're high on something, give the camera to Kurama.      Cinni:  No!      (Baka's feet walk toward the camera)      Baka:  Give it up!      Cinni:  Never!      (Camera is raised)      Baka:  No!  Cinni!      (Screen goes fuzzy)      ***      (Camera's on the tripod, by the way)      Baka:  So, you've picked up my cam...      (Tripod falls sideways)      Baka:  Not again.      (Screen goes fuzzy)      ***      (Kurama is holding the camera, he has to be sturdy)      Baka:  So, you've...      Is that thing on?      Yusuke:  Yes.      Baka:  I can't see the little red light.      Kurama:  It's on.      Baka:  Cut!      (Screen goes fuzzy again)      ***      (Baka and Kurama are standing in front of the camera drinking foamy cappuccinos)      Baka:  I'm telling you, Kurama, this could make it to America's Funniest Home Videos.      Kurama:  (Takes sip)  Perhaps you should consider sending this in when it's finished.      Yusuke:  Baka, we're rolling!      Baka:  Ah!  (Shoves Kurama out of the screen)  (Throws cappuccino to the side)      So, you've picked up my camera.      I hope you enjoy it.      Yusuke:  We got it.      Baka:  All right then.  Cut!  Print!  Moving on!      (Screen goes fuzzy)  
     
    
</post>
<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       (Hito has the camera turned on herself)      Hito: (whispering) I have stolen Baka's camera so I can confirm a suspision of Baka's Mafia ties.      (Turns camera so that it is pointed at Baka while she is on the phone)      Baka: (For some reason she is talking in an Italian-New York accent) Boss...Boss, please. I know I was supposed to hit this guy before today, but he's always surrounded by people who can kick my ass.      (Hito hooks up phone tap.)      Godfather: Baka, I have taken you under my wing. All I ask for is respect and understanding. If you can't give that to me, then I will have to disown you. If you know what I mean.      Baka: Godfather. I apologize, but I need more...      Hold on a second. Can you hear that tapping?    Godfather:  Yeah!    Baka:  Oh crap!  The feds!    (Baka slams the phone back on the hook)    (She runs to where Hito is hiding and finds the source of the tapping)    Baka:  Why you...!    (Screen goes fuzzy)  
     
    
</post>
<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
        Baka: Hello. This little section is just to acquaint people with Daisuko Tokenkura. (Who is, by the way, my cousin)          ***          Name:  Daisuko Tokenkura   OKA:  Dais or Dai (pronounced like dice or die)  Gender:  Female  Human Age:  15 years  Demon Age:  300+  Hair Color:  Brown with red bangs  Eye Color:  Brown  Weapons:  A modified staff, fire manipulation, a Smith  Wesson M10, and incantations  Normal Personality:  Frank, calm, logical, and rational ***    Baka: Hmmm... Dais is also going to be blind except for the fact that she can see a color that represents Kurama.          Kurama: She never told me what that color was. Baka, you're the author, why don't you tell me.          Baka: If she hasn't told you then she doesn't want you to know.          Kurama: But you created this whole scenario.          Baka: *eerie singsong voice* I'll never tell.          Kurama: Is it embarrasing or something?          Baka: Not gonna tell.   
     

    
</post>
<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
        Baka: Howdy sports fans! I have decided to write a brand new fiction.          Disclaimer: Eh hem.          Baka: Right... This is my not so good friend, Disclaimer. I'm supposed to tell you something, but because I live in my own world and stuff we had to invite that thing.          Disclaimer: Very funny, Baka.          *pulls out scroll* Baka has asked this to be unprofessional so she wrote this herself.          Baka: Blah blah, yadda yadda, can we just get on with this?          Disclaimer: Quote: I do not own Yu-Yu Hakusho, that honor belongs to Yoshihiro Togashi. The only character that is mine is Daisuko Tokenkura and her parents and her enemies. End quote.          Baka: Are you done?          Disclaimer: Yes.          Baka: Good! Now get the hell outta here! *kicks Disclaimer out of door*          Kurama: Was that really necessary?          Baka: You all know my faithful sidekick. One of the four Spirit Detectives and reformed demon thief, Kurama!          *Kurama raises eyebrow*          Baka: Anyway, this story is kinda romantic, and very kick-ass. You are going to like this.          ***   
     

    
</post>
<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Baka:  This is actually a prologue, but it's taken from the main story. I just thought it would be spiffy if I put it in the prologue.    Kinda like  The X-Wing Series.      ***    A  loud, raspy scream reached Sabina's ears. She continued to run, sensing the gaseous blackness that was nipping at her heels.  She ran into an empty room. There was no way to escape now.  Sabina turned and pressed her back against the wall as the shadow spread into the room. Through the vapor-like darkness, emerged a young man dressed in a black cloak and black suit.  A freezing feeling descended upon Sabina and her blood started running cold.  She sank to the floor.  By some ancient instinct, she reached up to her grandfather's coin hanging around her neck and clutched it tightly.  She closed her eyes against the figure. Her heart was now pounding in her ears.  Sabina was about to pass out.  All of the sudden what seemed like a miniature tornado blew into the small compact area.  It was quick to subside.  Out of shear curiosity, Sabina opened her eyes and was shocked by what she saw.  Someone else had appeared.  He was standing protectively in front of Sabina, a small dagger clutched in his hand.  "Stay away from her, " he commanded.  The other glared angrily at this new person and disappeared.  Sabina's rescuer turned and knelt down beside her.  He was very handsome.  He looked to be about her age except he had short white hair. His eyes were a stormy grayish-blue and shown with gentle worry.  "Are you alright?" he asked Sabina.  "Y...Yes," she stuttered, still in shock from the sudden appearance. "Um... Excuse me for asking, but who are you?"  He looked confused for a second. "You don't know who I am?"  "No," Sabina responded.  He reached out and touched the coin. "Yet you called me," he stated as if he was in a trance.  "What?"  Taking his hand from the necklace, he said, "I am Drake, a wind spirit."  He smiled at her and she felt safe. 
     
    
</post>
<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      SARAH:   You consider it dishonorable to attack enemies from the back, and yet you don't consider it dishonorable to manipulate someone else's mind? What kind of person are you? I suppose you already answered that.   Your hobbies include stealing and fighting? That's it? Don't you have anything better to do? Can't you browse the internet for something more... fulfilling... than that?
     
    
</post>
<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        USER PROFILE    Hello, I'm Kuronue.  A strange sadistic demon from Kurama's controversial past who is actually kind of gothic.  I have bat wings and wear mostly black clothes.  Like I said, I'm from Kurama's past.  In fact, I was his partner before I met a terrible fate while fleeing from the Castle of the Demon World.  My hobbies are stealing and fighting.  I use scythe and a pendant that I never cast away to manipulate my opponent's mind and make them believe whatever I wish them to believe.  Of course, I also just use the scythe.  And just to diminish any worries, I don't attack enemies from the rear.  It's very dishonorable.
     
    
</post>
<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        USER PROFILE    NAME: Sarah Anderson  I'm a twenty-five year old gal living in Colorado Springs. I have a black husky mix named Imperial Trainee Theodore Houndini Anderson. (He's as sweet a dog as anyone's ever had!)  Let's see... My job... I find people elligible to undergo a procedure to cure cancer and other terminal illnesses. It's really pretty exciting. I've actually had a couple people say no to it before. I don't really have many hobbies. I mostly just hang out around my house when I'm not working, play with Garshie, help my friend's son with his homework, etc. Sometimes I'll meet some friends at O'Malleys for lunch or dinner, but that's about it. 
     
    
</post>
<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Notice to all participants: You will now take on the role of one of your favorite characters, whether he or she be from some copyrighted media, your own, or any combination of the two. (Please stick to only one. Changing   occasionally   is not a bad thing.) These characters from now on will meet on IM, Blogger IM. Please begin your participation with a bio of some sort. For any sense of sanity, we're leaving out screennames on this; it'd get too confusing for anyone unfamiliar with the shows referenced, which include:    STARGATE: SG-1   (DISCLAIMER: "Stargate SG-1" and its characters are the property of MGM/UA, Double Secret Productions, Gekko Film Corp., Showtime/Viacom and USA Networks, Inc. This story is for entertainment purposes only and no money has exchanged hands. No copyright infringement is intended. The original characters, situations and story are the property of the author(s), and may not be republished or archived elsewhere without the author's permission.  YUYU HAKUSHO   Other than that, I have one thing to say:  Any use of copyrighted material is for the enjoyment of participants and readers only. We are getting paid only in our dreams, ie. not at all, not a penny, not a pfennig, not a pound, not one Euro. This is just fun. Any recognizable characters are the property of whoever holds the copyright or the author.  More will be added if more needs to be said.
     
    
</post>
<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      SARAH:  You kidding? We're gonna have a ton of people to calm you down, Mr. K.
     
    
</post>
<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Kuronue:  This should be interesting.  We should be getting a new member soon, just to give you a heads up.  I have no idea who they are.
     
    
</post>
<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      O'NEILL:  Go first with what? ...I shoot right handed, eat right handed, do most things right handed...
     
    
</post>
<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      SARAH:  Exactly. Did you hear that, Mr. K? A privelage! That means I have to like you enough to know that you're joking.   So. Let's all start off on the right foot, shall we? I don't know anyone here who's a lefty. ... Jack, how 'bout you go first?
     
    
</post>
<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      O'NEILL:  Baka?...oh, wait Danny says it means idiot.  And being able to call Reeses a snake-head and get away with it is a privelage, not a right, Bat-boy. Dead-Bat-Boy. Is it just me that finds that creepy?
     
    
</post>
<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      SARAH:  Excuse me, whoever you are, but I have a deep need to know why you feel the need to up and call me a snake head. I'll have you know that I'm NOT!  ... .... whatever you mean by "snake head" of course...
     
    
</post>
<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      KURONUE:  *glares evilly*
     
    
</post>
<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      SARAH:  Kuronue: Give me one reason not to; you just called me a snake head without any proof. Oh, right. Resurrection. Like I'll believe that! I repeat: What kind of person are you?  Nice save, Jack. It's so great to see that you're on! Could you lend me a hand here? He/she/it called me a snake head. You know exactly how much I appreciate that!
     
    
</post>
<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      KURONUE:  Don't call me a baka!  I don't need a sarcophagus!  And I could care less that you help people.  "I kill the spider to save the butterfly."
     
    
</post>
<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      SARAH:  "Snake head"? Excuse me, but I think I deserve a little more credit than that! You think I'm evil, do you?  How to live your afterlife? Yeah, right. It's called a sarcophagus, you baka!  Have you ever considered that I might be a caring person? Did I mention I help people find a cure for their cancer?
     
    
</post>
<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        USER PROFILE    Well, howdy, campers. I'm Colonel Jack O'Neill, but Reeses already knew that. My job involves lots of things that...well, I'd have to kill you if I told you about them, and I'm sure Batman wouldn't take that too well...  As for hobbies: fishing. When I'm not doing that, it's annoying Danny, pestering Carter, or teaching Teal'c the idiosyncracies of the American language. Wonder if snake baiting counts...eh, the  other  kind of snake; nothing personal, Reeses.
     
    
</post>
<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      KURONUE:  Give me a break, snake head.  Technically, I'm supposed to be dead; I don't need you telling me how to live my afterlife.  Anyway, why do you even care?
     
    
</post>
<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      SARAH:  I wouldn't be so certain, Captain Sparrow. I'm sure that, given the right circumstances, you could die just as many times as Jack. And as he and the rest of my friends from that... company... would tell you, it really doesn't matter in what manner you die as long as there's... a certain piece of technology... nearby.  Sorry, it's just seemed that way, what with the baka and rum and "snake head" discussions and all.  Yeah, I'll try to convince her of that! Wait, you're from, what, the 1800's? And you know about different kinds of peanut butter?  Ah, yes, dark chocolate. The best food-like substance in the world! Too bad it's so expensive. Now, I won't take you up on any offer of rum, but if you're going to be handing out some of that "fine Caribbean dark chocolate", I'll be more than happy to lighten your load of that!  Nah, I'd rather that they were fully conscious and understand exactly how we're gonna cure them. (Though I have to admit, drunk or not, it's hilarious to see their faces when we tell them!)
     
    
</post>
<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      CAPTAIN Jack Sparrow:  Well, unlike you, I can only live once and die once.  Im not afraid to die, love, but I would rather be killed doing something worth while than to be publicly exicuted.  Its to much publicity and i dont like crowds.  Plus if i have to hear my charges over and over again they could at least get my Rank right, savvy?  I have absolutely no negativity, and have not held a grudge since before i killed Barbossa, mate.    Peanut Butter is not even in the same catagory as Rum or Chocolate.  Peanut Butter is like eating sand, so corse and grainy unless you eat the crunchy kind.  Now, I have to say that sitting on the Pearl with a bottle of rum and some nice carribean chocolate is the best way to spend an afternoon at sea, savvy?  I prefer dark chocolate myself, it is a tad bitter, mate. I dont know... make them so drunk that they are oblivious to what they are going through?  Welcome Ava, at least someone around here thinks that Rum sounds good, in fact i shall go and endulge in some minor rum drinking, wouldnt want to be too drunk tommorrow Im sure.  Gooday, mates!    
     
    
</post>
<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      SARAH:  Welcome, Ava. If you haven't had time to get caught up, others here include Kuronue (some anime), Colonel Jack O'Neill (Stargate), Captain Jack(three extra characters here) Sparrow (POTC), and me, Sarah Anderson (Stargate fanficdom).  A noose? A noose?! Hah! You're afraid of dying once! When I go on "buisiness trips", I have to worry about dying several times, which the good colonel here can attest to.  Okay, thanks for that understanding, captain. I suppose we could get to a point without so much negativity between us.  Lemme point somethin' out, Cpt. Sparrow: I was interpreting someone else's message to Jack. And, by the way, she says peanut butter's better than rum, beer, or chocolate. ...Humph. Now, how could any alcoholic beverage   help   with "the whole cancer thing"?
     
    
</post>
<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      CAPTAIN Jack Sparrow:  ( Very calmly) I may not know what it is to be critised and judged because of my anatomy, love but try living your life in fear of a noose.  Nobody understands a pirates mind, most are not just mindless people who go stealing things and killing people.  Did You hear about when i sacked Nassasu Port without even firing a shot.  I did that to avoid casualties, mate.  Also, Im not like Barbossa, savvy.  He got what he want by killing.  Did you know that the cannons on my ship, when i was captain, were not used at all on ports but on the daily firieng against another pirate ship to see which where more powerful nines (usually wagered on a case of rum).  And, love, im sorry about the "baka" comment i realize it is that same as me saying "savvy".  (still calm but with a little more force) Never insult my rum, telling someone not to try rum is...is...blashphamy.  If CJ wants to try it, than he sure can, love.  Also, ever think that it could help with the whole cancer thing????
     
    
</post>
<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hello. i am one of your new members. my name is ava pierce and i am hawkeyes' younger sister (from the television show MASH). i am a "minny hawkeye", having the smae black hair (only longer) and blue eyes. and i am slightly short. i am a captain and a doctor in the korean war.  oh, and we have a still in our tent, so that rum is sounding kinda good...
     
    
</post>
<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      SARAH:  Just get over it, huh, Sparrow? How do I "just get over it"? I find it extremely insulting. I bet you don't even know what it's like to be criticized and judged just based on your anatomy,   sir.   I like "baka." Besides, Mr. K understands it better; it's his own language.  *Visions of drunk demons dancing in her head...*    Humans are indeed confusing, but I would like to point out that they're not impossible to live with.    Jack, you up for keeping to your beer and not touching rum? Miss V says that beer is bad enough (for you), but rum sounds to be even worse.
     
    
</post>
<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      CAPTAIN Jack Sparrow:  Kuronue, what kind of demon are you exactly? Also mate, exactly how much rum would you be needin.  The first  Sparrow Anger teatment  is to get the smell of rum so that you do not get sick.  I've had expiriance with Demons and rum before and, lets just say, it dosent sit well, savvy?  That Inuyasha couldnt stand the taste of it let alone the smell so "he settled for no less than total abstanence from the demon rum".  I say "demon rum" because of the effect it had on him.  If, demon-boy, you do not believe that i have met Inuyasha   you can go on Fanfiction.net and find the story called Pirates of the Carribean meets Inuyasha where  i am writing my adventures with this half-demon-dog-boy, savvy?  CJ, beer is  one  of the alcohalic agents in rum.  you also have the whiskey, burbon, and the vodca.  Your a military man no doubt, defenatly not a pirate because our rankings only go up to captain, but you should be able to handle some fine carribean rum.  And if you can't, mate, its pathetic, it truely is.     
     
    
</post>
<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      O'NEILL  So its more like Kuron-you-ay?  You don't know batman? What planet are you-never mind.  'Lo Captain Jack, I'm Colonel Jack...  I dunno about Rum, but i prefer Beer...a nice, cold beer sat my a lake with a fishing pole in my hand...
     
    
</post>
<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Kuronue:  No, it's not pronounced "Kuronay," it's pronounced "KuronUay."  You can't forget the "u" in there.  Who's this Batman, and what the heck is the Batmobile?    I'm keeping that rum in mind.  I think I'm going to need a lot of it.  *mumbles* Humans are so confusing.  This is why I never left Makai.
     
    
</post>
<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      CAPTAIN Jack Sparrow:            Ello, mates.  Its a strange thing this chat.  Sarah, love, if someone calls you snakehead, you should learn to get over it.  And why must you use the term Baka, idiot will suffice.  Also, demon boy - i would love to help you work out any anger issues you have.  Which, you must have because you got angry at someone typing your name wrong, savvy? Rum works wonders!!            Well for those of you who do not know me, I am The infamous Captain Jack Sparrow.  If you forget the CAPTAIN i might just send Elizabeth Swann after you and that IS something to be afraid of, mates.   adieu, avidosay, aloha, and all those other good-by things                                                           
     
    
</post>
<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      O'NEILL   What's wrong with Batman? He was cool...who doesn't want a Batmobile???  So its pronounced Kuronay???
     
    
</post>
<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      SARAH:  I have a bit of trouble spelling things I can't pronounce. I mean, I can try, but with the changes to this IM(ish) thing, "Kuronuay" is about the best I can do.   Call me "S" if you want to; I really don't care.
     
    
</post>
<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Kuronue:  Will you quit calling me that?!  It's Kuronue!
     
    
</post>
<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I'm sorry,  Captain , but that just seems like faulty reasoning to me. God knows what you're going to do, how you're going to go, what decisions you'll make, but that shouldn't give you an excuse for bad habits. Just because He knows what's going to happen doesn't mean that's the way he wants it to be, "savvy"? (Miss V wishes me to express her skepticism in my belief in a higher power. But that's the way she was brought up to think.)      Ah, yes, Anime. You know, I kinda quit paying attention to that when I found a ton of other things to think about. You know, well-being of my world, how my friends are doing (and what trouble they've gotten into lately), grades and school, etc. But, yes, I suppose I can figure what you're talking about. (Though I'm much more of a Star Wars person. Jar Jar and John Williams all the way!)      C. Sparrow, I think you need to give Mr. K a rather exact definition of the word "savvy". (Remember: proper capitilization can help to convey a clear and concise meaning!)   
     
    
</post>
<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Kuronue:  You know Inu-Yasha and Sesshomaru, I'm that kind of demon.  I agree with Sparrow.  Speaking of Sparrow, why do keep calling us all savvy?
     
    
</post>
<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      CAPTAIN Jack Sparrow:  But love, if God choses when i go then he also knows the exact way i will go.  So maybe God has planed for me to die of liver failure from drinking to much rum, savvy?  So technicly, dying because of rum is not dying prematurly at all.  Though i would prefer a natural cause than a noose.
     
    
</post>
<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      High accumulation of spirit energy, huh? Never heard of it. Hey, that reminds me of something Jonas told me. Did you know that if all the energy in a banana was released at once when you ate it, you'd explode with body parts flying up to a mile apart?  Okay, so you're not a "demon" demon. Got it. Dunno anyone who'd freely admit it to me. 'Course I try to stay away from people like that. They bug me.  You know what, Captain Jack? I'd rather not die prematurely at all! I'll leave this... dimension when the good Lord's good'n'ready for me to!
     
    
</post>
<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      CAPTAIN Jack Sparrow:  Rum has a different effect on me.  Im a pirate, it just is, savvy.  I would rather die of liver failure than from a noose, mate.
     
    
</post>
<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Kuronue:  As I have already pointed out, my eyes glow red, but I believe that is due to the fact that I have a high accumlination of spirit energy.  Also, I am a demon (not in the sense as you are reffering to).
     
    
</post>
<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Schizophrenia? Not really. I mean, in the sense that it's two personalities in one body, I suppose so, but it's not any kind of mental disorder. Much more rewarding than that, really.  Yes, just yellow. So? Eyes can glow another color?    That to which she is referring is neither schizophrenia nor multiple personalities disorder. To reinforce her idea on this, she even researched the two; you can be sure that her analysis is correct.  As for glowing eyes, I am aware of only one chemical which can cause this, and it has a tendancy to cause the eyes to flash in a yellow or golden light. I hold no expectation that there is no other chemical with such a property.  
     
    
</post>
<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Kuronue:  I seriously doubt that I'm a snake-head.  From what I understand from watching it, it seems that what you are speaking of is like schizophrenia.  Also, their eyes only appear to glow yellow.
     
    
</post>
<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Then maybeyou're a snake-head as well?      I'm thinking "run" is always a good option, though Miss V says that if you're really the aforementioned source of evil, by all means, "fight you guys" is the best option.      I can see the immense frustration. When my eyes glow, it's not usually in the dark, mostly because I like light. Halogen lamps are the best next to pure sunlight, though I'll settle for a set of incandescent bulbs. (I think; it's been a long time since eighth grade science!) Or the light provided by computer moniters. That's always good. Ah... the wonders of e-mail! Fanfiction! Star Wars fan sites! All wondrous things to be looking at late into the night! Of course, that's not usually when my eyes glow. In fact, I think my eyes glow the least then and--        I'm sorry. Sarah Anderson has become suddenly unavailable as a result of her unscreened babbling.   </post></Blog>