<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I witnessed two girls hit by a truck this afternoon. There is a park half a block down from my house. The red light had stopped me. My car humming, waiting for the green. I looked to my right and saw two girls, one around fifteen and the other eight. A gray book bag hung off the older girl’s shoulder. There was a light breeze, the world mute. I look away. A flash of red streaked past. I turn back. She looked like rag doll, a bump, under the tires. I thought it was a stunt. A joke. But she didn’t move, then the other girl appeared from the left. The truck stopped and reality crashed. Across the street a black truck stopped. A man rushed out. He ran to the older girl telling her not to move. An old man came out of the driver side of the red truck. The small girl cried, barely moving on the pavement. To ease the guilty he tried to get her to stand. Her little legs collapsing under the shock. The other man screamed at him, “Get away from her.” His cell phone on his ear, his hand trying to calm the older girl, now crying.   I stare at the two kids moaning on the floor. People honking. Traffic has been stilled and heaven forbid if the routine is interrupted. Three more cars stop in the middle of the road. They create a makeshift roadblock. I turn the corner, watching in the rear view mirror- fire truck lights. Order to the chaos. Cleaners of the mess, serving their purpose. Lives are split, molded, reformed into before and after, for everyone involved.    
    
</post>
<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Well Ladies and Gents…here I go. I have tried this once before. But much like an aged car on its last legs, I just sputtered and coughed. I never got anywhere. HELLO WORLD! Silence follows the announcement. Oh well, at least no one can say I wasn’t polite.     
    
</post>
<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Okay there should be a law which states fanfiction is illegal. I swear it is more addictive than sleeping pills, crack or lsd. I have just spent three hours on the computer submersed in the alternate muses of Harry Potter and Kenshin. There should be a cut off timer, a warning alarm, anything to help stop the madness. My head hurts. My right eye is threatening to pop out of my head. I feel nauseous, but the need is still there. Aching… Read me… it cries out Read me…like Alice and the rabbit  Damn!  The mouse clicks on other link…  So much for abstinence 
    
</post>
<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Arleen…how many years have I tried to run away from my name…from the sound of it.  Yet…I just as I sit here thinking about the name I want to stare back at me from the cover a book, I find myself staring…at Arleen not Amanda.  Amanda, as much as I would like it to be is simply a name to hide behind.  It is a name to say… See I am not a chubby Latin girl living in Miami.  See I am not ethnic.  I don’t speak Spanish I and don’t know what black beans and rice taste like.  I don’t want it because it is me…it is my voice and I am scared of it.  It makes it real, it makes it true and then I can’t hide behind it.  I can’t say, it is someone else…that is another’s words.  It would be easier, but then what would be the point.   If I can’t be proud, then why I am I trying.   I thought about using my maiden name, since this talent is mine and sprung from the well of my genes.  But as I thought about using it again, it didn’t feel right.  That girl-she has grown up, grown up and blossomed because of the man she married and the life she has experienced.  She has changed and so has her name.  When I first married I didn’t know if I wanted to change it.  Oh, my poor Loki…I even suggested he take my last name as his middle name.  He almost died.  Except he never told me I had to take his name. Never questioned why I hadn’t.  Never pressed.  It took me four years, but I did it.  I came home that day and showed him my new license.  He looked at me, with a thin film of tears in his lovely brown eyes and said, “Thank you.”  I am proud of my name.  Proud of what it represents.  The past of me mixed with the present. Because of his patience, his understanding-I have been able to move out of my cave into the light.   I think that is enough 
    
</post>
<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My friend Celie said those words not just five minutes ago.  Of everyone I know, she is the one who understands the pain and fear.  It is funny how we have remained friends despite our extremely different personalities.  It is the word that bind us.  It united us in high school, and ten years later continues to propel us.  We have often changed our roles- one the comforter, the other the fearful…one the author, the other the editor.  It is a fundamental part of our relationship; something that continues to nurture and strengthen it.   So I think the muses will be with me tonight.  Because Celie called to talk about a Dave Matthews’ concert, her battered back and in the end gave me a pinch of  kick-in-the-ass.    It is good to have friends.
    
</post>
<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        I find myself in a rut. Once again, the fires burn but I am not supplying the wood. I haven’t written in three days.  I tried to read Teresa Medeiros’ new book yesterday,   Yours Until Dawn  . I don’t know what it is about her that I just can’t get into. I mean the story was good and the dialog was passable, but 2/3 into it I stopped. It is a shame too, she has a following and her stories would normally captivate me. Oh well…  In an attempt to ease the need to absorb words, but too lazy to actually write them, I started to re-read Julia Quinn’s   Romancing Mr. Bridgerton  . Now this is a good book and it illustrates, at least for me, why I couldn’t get into Medeiros’ book. In Quinn’s story I could  see  it, while with Medeiros’ I was  reading  it.  I vastly prefer to see a book.      AWHWHWHWH! I am stressed. The project I have been working on for weeks is at the final stages. Good news…I don’t think so. My boss reviewed the dummy and came back with a “See Me”. I feel like I am in school again or my parents are about to reprimand me. I really shouldn’t, he is a wonderful boss. But I hate feeling I have disappointed him in some way.    
    
</post>
</Blog>