<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today I went on an LRT adventure and then I watched Shrek 2. OMG that movie is SO funny! haha its so great - Puss in Boots is the BEST!  Ha ha! Maybe I have an affinity for cats now I dunno but OMG Puss in Boots Rocks my Socks! They based his character on Zorro - man I love that cat!  Anyway from the beginning. I missed the bus at first today - whoops my bad. Oh well I think I also phoned Tom by accident. On my cell phone. Whoopsies. Yeh - I forgot to lock it. (i'm sorry!) anyway what was i talking about... Oh right my GRAND LRT ADVENTURE!   It started at the university - then it snaked across to the governement center (which is across the river) and then to other stations and it ended at Churchill station. whoo hoo! and it kinda ends there. But then it goes in rewind. because i took it back the the university after that day... and it was more eventfull because chris broke a bylaw... hahaha yeh - that was eventful  -till next time 
      
</post>
<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      For those of you who don't know Nick - this is Nick..And Me but yea that's Nick urlLink      urlLink        Hello - How is everyone? I put a picture up! Yah! This makes me happy... Although it is quite big. Anyway - since its Thursday and I'm incredibly bored im gonna go be not so bored. bye now! 
      
</post>
<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I think my English teacher is paranoid with other people doing other work in english class. - he kept walking around today looking for not worker people dudes. i though that was funny becuase he normally doesn't do that. hmmm... what else is funny. Oh i know what's funny. Mr "english teacher" stands behind our "asian group" because we talk and its great. hmm what else  Oh today is the nineteenth by the way i decided to like ...not write? i dunno i'm really tired right now and its late. I'm analyzing a poem and my silly goose... nevermind he came back... hehe he's so awesome! i love him! okay yeh i should go though.. bye!
      
</post>
<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      You know what? I got two phone calls today - from Sammy!  Sammy told me to call Andy: "Andy Pandy" - but I don't know why! haha yup! And oh and um... Midterms are scary  Oh um I know! I was just talking to nick ,and the words that I most often use are "good", "great" and "awesome!" because I am either good, great, or awesome! - if anyone has ever noticed..(although its hard not to notice.) hehe ohh and we told everyone about Nick and I going out. Chu took it rather well - haha a little over hyper but quite well! And then Willy was like "no surprise there." and then Kau was like...Well there's a lot to what Kau said. Here it is according to Nick --&gt; and if memory serves well:  Nick walked into his hallway and one of his friends is like "Hey Who's your new  girlfriend ?" and Nick figured that chu has been talking about it. And then Kau is like "you have a new girlfriend? Already?" and Nick's like "yea" and then Kau was like "do I know her?" and nick was like "yea it's Donna" and then kau is like - well lets just say I was worried of the awkwardness of it where two friends meet who meet two more friends and one of the original friends adds a friend and then the two friends that the two original friends have met pulls another guy into the loop. And then the other new guy and one of the original friends starts going out --&gt; although the outcome was awesome! hehe they have taken it quite well, quite well indeed! And its awesome because its almost like people expected it to happen, without us even realizing it.   Come to think of it, it's kind of scary - in a good way.
      
</post>
<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Evil. Well, I can't say that because math is okayish - I don't mind it, I just don't like it much. You know how many people have asked to see my "non existent" math portfolio? A lot and you know what? I don't have to do a math portfolio because I'm not in IB math - haha I've disappointed so many people with my not math IB-iness.  another thing. Math is hard to do without a graphing calculator. Mine broke... Twice. haha maybe I should stop abusing it. haha well the first one I didn't break - the second one I did break. But that's beside the point... I still need a graphing calculator to study for my midterm - unless I can do a whole bunch of math tonight and then graph stuff tomorrow afternoon (double math) and then hope I do well on the midterm... *ahem* 3/4 term test. haha you know what's funny?... Nothing that's what!  Oh yea I made a funny. Anyway I have to study for math. Bye bye! (where would I be without spell check?)
      
</post>
<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yea I should be doing homework..But I'm not...     PROCRASTINATION   
      
</post>
<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       TODAY  was more then I could eve thought just one night would be. Oh My it was so Great! Actually, no, it was more then great... It was the most amazing night I've had in a long time. Ha! It no wonder I love him so much. He makes me feel all great and special inside and I love that. He's so shy, but to me, he's everything in a word... Perfect.  Haha.. I guess I should tell you who I'm talking about - I'm talking about: Nick! My Silly Goose - Two birds of a feather. He and I had the most awesome time together, and I wish that time would just stop and we'd forever be there in the same moment. Wow, people think I may have fallen head over heels, but I truly think that Nick is my other puzzle piece.  Anyway - about my night. Well we met at four at the bridge in west ed, the one over by TNT in West Edmonton Mall Chinatown. Haha man was I nervous, haha oh well he was there and that was all that mattered. Well, we went to get bubble tea and He's such a gentleman. He paid for Everything today - Everything. He paid for Bubble tea, paid for supper, paid for the movie tickets - A gentleman. It was great, although I kept questioning if he was sure he got it all. -being Donna you know. Anyway, we walked around hand in hand and yea he was walking behind me and I was holding his hands - and us being both klutzes well... haha we were CAREFUL! We went "browsing" haha anyway we ummmmmmmmmmmm...... Right we walked through Galaxyland and stuff and yea ^__^  And then, and then, and then: we went for supper! Supper man Supper! haha we went to the old spaghetti factory. The old spaghetti factory was so awesome! Haha even though we didn't eat much - because we were slightly full - we had so much fun together. haha we talked and well I talked because he's so shy, but yea hehe we laughed so much. We also left a $3.00 tip - not the best but its not bad saying that its 10 percent of out meal.   and then we went to the movie. Oh my - Van Helsing was soooo awesome. haha scary but awesome. Haha I'm so glad he was with me. I was soo scared. I must have jumped like eight million times before the movie actually got going. haha I held on to his hands all movie long and everytime a scary part came up, I would bury my head into his jacket and squeeze his hands. Haha, He's got strong hands they are so great. Because I'd squeeze then and he'd just hold tighter - I felt so loved. haha and then yea it was so beautiful.(no we weren't snogging, I actually know what the movie is about) - but yea - No kiss if you are wondering though. haha so many opportunities for one too. ^__^ - oh well... Still I had a Wonderful time with him. *sigh* 
      
</post>
<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ha Ha its Saturday... I'm tired. Just though you wanted to know. </post></Blog>