<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      A strange day, spent sitting in a hospital ward watching my youngest daughter sleep.  Around 9am I got a call from my ex-husband to say that TD2 had been admitted to hospital at 3am with a suspected appendicitis.  Thankfully, it turned out to be swollen stomach glands and she was discharged early this evening.  It was a horrible sensation.  To know that my child was ill and I was not there.  To know that she had wanted me and I was not there to comfort her.  Apparently, her father refused to call me until either it was a reasonable time or he knew some thing for sure.  I understand, appreciate, his thinking. Yet still it hurt.  We did not talk much, my daughter and I.  I teased her a little, made her laugh and call me 'witch!'  She allowed me to cuddle her for a while, her head resting against my shoulder.  Mostly she slept. Mostly I watched.  The fingers of one hand were curled into a loose fist against the pillow. Blonde hair a Rapunzel tangle framing her face, slightly flushed with rose coloured sleep.  I felt a familiar contraction deep in my stomach.  The immortal, invisible umbilical cord that connects a mother to her child.  I miss her so much and the guilt of failure weighs me down like lead boots.  Even today we walked warily around each other.  Careful to avoid any words that might rekindle the war between us.  My little girl.  My last born.  The child I thought I knew so well who turned into a stranger as she turned into a teenager.  Last year she chose to live with her father.  I rarely see her. Even on Mothers Day she stayed away.  Last night, today, she needed me.   Nothing has changed.   Tonight, she is safe at home with her father and I have an ache deep in  the pit of my stomach.
     
    
</post>
<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My son is home from boarding school for half term. I miss him terribly when he is away even though the terms are short and the holidays long. Soon he will be home for good, preparing for the next stage of his life filled with A levels, college and new friends.  It was a difficult decision, to allow him to go away to school, especially given my background and my need to keep my children close. The opportunity arose, the chance to experience things that I could never provide. The fees paid, so the freedom to make the decision on its merits, not financial possibility.  Eighteen months ago he was failing in his state school. Flirting with the kind of trouble teenage boys so often find irresistible and talking of forgetting about education and getting a job. I encouraged him to take up the offer of a place at this new school but the choice had to be his. Especially as it meant going back a year and beginning GCSE's all over again.  I am so proud of him. That he thought it through carefully and against his own inclinations, took this unlooked for chance to start again. I am even more proud that despite home sickness, despite missing his friends, he has seized the opportunity and built success on what were the seeds of failure.  He has grown tall and self possessed. Confident of who he is and what he wants. He talks of university and his plans for the future. I wish, for his sake, that he was staying at the school to do his A levels. The school will miss him, he is a prefect and a popular boy with both his peers and those younger and older than himself. But it is his decision to make, not mine.   And I trust his judgment.  I see the person he has become and the man he will one day be...And I am proud. 
     
    
</post>
<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It had come at last. Suspended living, silent visits, ended with the click of the receiver.  The bitter taste of guilt filling my mouth with ashes of a funeral pyre not yet built.  Mourning long over, last words spoken and goodbyes said would now be resurrected.  Re-living that uncertain moment when vivid grey eyes had turned upwards with the  pleading helplessness of a child.  Confused. Frightened. She had stopped speaking one year? Two years ago? Day turned to week, to month, as did my visits.  The calmness was surprising.  Collecting belongings, turning the key in the lock, starting the engine. I would have expected more.  The nurse has a kindly voice and an anxious face. Discomfort showing like the hem of a petticoat peering from beneath her uniform.  There is no hope.  Death had been on hold for too many years in a cheerful lounge filled with waiting.  The television turned up loud to drown out so many lingering endings.  It would be a welcome caller, kinder than the sly thieves of her laughter, her wisdom, her sometimes spiteful tongue. Her dignity.  We had been strangers too long, she and I.  She lies there unknowing, uncaring.  The silence magnifies the forced cheerfulness of one-sided conversations whispered as if afraid to be overheard.  Words are toys scattered  to fill the minutes.  I gently brush a strand of limp hair from her now unfamiliar face, grown old and distant. My hand touches the hard-edged husk of her.  Too many hours in this night.  Minutes snatched to drink luke warm tea and eat biscuits.  A temporary escape. Afraid to be gone to long less the moment is missed,  the final betrayal.  But the sun comes up fighting fabric covered windows with sly fingers of light. Playing sulky shadow games.  Waiting continues.  Unable to outwit the crawling hours of exhaustion, fear recedes.  The nurse slips into the room unnoticed, observes each detail, each change in her patient,  finally announcing the arrival of death.  Too soon!  Too soon! Love erupts with childish rage! My arms cling, hold tight, refuse to let go!  A shrieking, sobbing stranger’s voice cries out  No! Come back! Who will love me if you leave?  The selfishness of grief forcing one more hesitating breath.  Let her go. Tears spill and splash, washing her face as once a woman's tears  had washed the feet of Christ.  The final reversal. Her words in my mouth.  Hush, go to sleep, Goodnight and God Bless, see you in the morning  with tea and biscuits.  Goodnight, I love you. 
     
    
</post>
<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hands fascinate me. From the tiny, grasping hands of a newborn child reaching out to discover the world, to the delicate fingers of a musician whose hands conjure magic and dreams.   I remember my brother David's hands. Large and strong, with nails bitten to the quick. Never still. Twirling a lock of hair between blunt, restless fingers or building model galleons with careful precision. Curled into a fist of frustration and violence. Gently, tenderly, cradling a child or an animal. The sensitive, loving man damned behind a macho mask escaping in the gestures of his hands.  I remember my grandmothers hands. As they were at the end of her life. The bones of her personality with the flesh removed. Tissue paper skin lying in folds of a lifetimes domesticity. Artistic hands that wanted to paint, to create but which grew old cooking, cleaning, caring for others.  One hand frozen into silence by a stroke, one by resignation.  Their silence evidence that she had withdrawn from life and now only waited for death to confirm her decision.   I watch my own hands. Flying across the computer keys. Resurrecting memories and pinning them to the screen. And suddenly I remember the man I loved. Feel the weight of his hand tangled in my hair, his palms holding my face.  And I miss them all. The hands that have shaped my life.      This is part of a chain of posts linked together by word association. The previous link in the chain was  urlLink here . If you want to write another link here's what to do: Find a word, phrase or theme from this post to inspire your own and go and write it. It's that simple. Try not to write something that's similar to this post. That way the subject of the posts along the chain will vary. E.g. if I write about going to the doctor's, then don't talk about the last time you were ill, instead describe how you used to play Doctors and Nurses with the girl next door. Get the idea? Your post can be in any style you want. Copy this paragraph and tack it onto the end of your post, updating the link to point here, then leave a comment here that points to your new post. 
     
    
</post>
<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I refuse to give up. There has to be a way to fight back, to finally take hold of life and shape it to my desires. For all these years I have been merely a shadow. Forcing myself into the shape of some blueprint, some me that I thought I should be. I dreamed of other things, dreamed of who I would be and what I would achieve, yet thought them only dreams I had no entitlement to.   A chameleon, defined by my surroundings, I have forgotten my own reality. Invisible. Each time I attempt to make a path of my own I fail. By my own doing. Fleeing back to the comfort of shadows with the sound of mockery and contempt ringing in my ears.   "Who do you think you are to be attempting this? Do you think you are special? Have talent? Abilities?'  Your dream is bigger than you are capable of being. Reaching for stars that are not yours to take. Vain, selfish, foolish woman. Go back!."  And with each failure the voice becomes louder and my retreat deeper into the darkness until I find myself alone. The world shrunk to these walls. Yet the dreams persist. Whispering in the silence, almost drowned.  Insistent in their demand for attention. Fulfilment.   Stinging my hands into hurried activity with pen, paint brush, needle or computer. Forcing their way through the smallest crack in the walls to touch the world outside.  
     
    
</post>
<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Nathalie Chica is a student from Los Angeles who, like me, has two blogs. The first is 'Cu urlLink p of Chica'  . A well laid out design and easy navigation makes this site a pleasure to browse. With well written comments on everything from music to gross tv ads, I enjoyed rumaging around and following the many links she provides in her posts.   But it is Nathalie's second blog ' urlLink Another ' that really caught my attention. To quote her own words...  "But, I don't want to lead poor depressive souls astray, so I feel obliged to say, I'm not yet sure my blog will be helpful. I want it to be, but my more immediate desire is this: to create a forum for critical thinking about mental health issues that doesn't require either an academic background or a passive acceptance of psychological tenets and practices. For some people, that kind of forum might feel unproductive or useless, either because it's an amateur effort or it encourages what seems like too much over-thinking. But, I do think my sideblog links to enough good sites that, at the very least, Another can act as a portal to more helpful information."   The range of links is excellent, pointing to many sites that I have not previously discovered for myself  ranging from general mental health resources to magazines, journals and recommended blogs. Nathalie's posts are well written and interesting. Her revues of articles concise and fair.    Another  is definately one for my blogroll.  
     
    
</post>
<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sleep has muffled the last few days into nothingness. An all pervading lassitude weighing down my eyelids. The only possibility to close them and drift off into a dreamless silence. Emerging only briefly, struggling for wakefulness like a drowning man coming up for air. To eat whatever comes to hand that does not need cooking. To feed the cats. To watch something on the television, soon forgotten.   A parcel sits on the table unopened. My eBay purchase, a personal CD player to take on holiday with me. There should be excitement, shouldn't there? Or at the least curiosity.   Unopened letters gather dust. Nothing important, not even a bill amongst the 'dear householder' and 'Prize Draw'. Maybe I should keep a waste paper basket by the door so that the postman could post his litter immediately to its final destination.  Email to answer. But nothing to say.  A web site to update. But no enthusiasm.  The hand of Morpheus rests on my shoulder once more and my eyes grow heavy.
     
    
</post>
<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have to say a great big thank you to support at  Blogger . I had a problem and they fixed it with a patience, courtesy, kindness and promptness that is unusual these days.  Thank you.
     
    
</post>
<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      On the day she turned 13, sweet baby daughter was sneakily exchanged by aliens for the teenager from hell. The last year has been, shall we say, challenging? Unwilling to accept the boundaries that I imposed, a constant state of what can only be described as warfare developed between us. Eventually she decided to live with her father instead of me.. His approach to parenting is more laid back than mine and involves constant compromise. Or in translation, more or less allowing her to do what ever she pleases. The Ex's justification was that my way did not work, his did. The evidence being that he rarely fell out with TD2. My counter claim that she and I could also get along fine if I left her to her own devices fell on deaf ears.  It has been a very painful time for me. This feeling that I had lost my child. The guilt of wondering if perhaps I had been wrong and should have done things differently. I love my children dearly. All three of them. Being their mother is the single most precious and important thing I have ever done. I can say in all honesty that every decision I have made in regard to them has been because I believed it was what was best for them. Watching them grow up, blossoming into unique individuals I could feel proud, that if I had done nothing else worthwhile in my life, I was a good mother, or at least a good enough mother.  Then the relationship between TD2 and I broke down, she moved out and I was devastated.  This morning, just as I was about to leave for my counseling session The Ex phoned. Would I please call our daughter because he was having problems with her. He could not deal with the particular situation as he was now at work and so was 'putting it on to' me, his words. As it happens the situation resolved itself without my intervention. The plain fact is that even if it had not, there was nothing I could do.   The Ex has consistently undermined my authority. With the situation as it is there are no sanctions I could use. I rarely even see our daughter.  I do not understand what he expected of me.  The call left me feeling upset, concerned about my child's behavior, helpless and guilty. The unspoken accusation was that I was refusing to help when in reality I could see no way in which I could.     
     
    
</post>
<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      That line from a song by REM sticks in my mind. I first heard it on a advert for something I think, maybe a trailer for a program's, I can't remember. It struck me as an apt metaphor for my life and has become one of my favorite songs. Thinking about it, it would make a better title for this journal. I feel a change coming on.  I have been awake since 5am, finally giving up on the idea that I might return to sleep an hour later. The cats were pleased to get breakfast so early and have returned to their respective favorite places to curl up and doze. Merlin, snuggled up to TD No1, Harry Potter on the second from the top stair and Pru purring loudly on my lap as I type.  Pru has been a Godsend in the weeks since she joined our family. Almost as demanding of attention as a small child, she prevents me from sliding into complete inaction. Her antics and chatter often bring a smile to my lips, no matter how down I feel.  I have a counseling appointment this morning. I don't want to go. Or rather the effort of getting ready, catching a bus, walking to the office, all seems too much. Never the less, I will do all of those things. If I don't, K will phone to find out why not and I will feel guilty for letting her down. I promised her that I would keep seeing her and I know that it will benefit me. 
     
    
</post>
<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have set up a second blog entitled  urlLink 'Diet Coke'  and already written a couple of entries. Those pages will be for the past and for writing about mental health issues. This one is for the present and the future.
     
    
</post>
<date>18,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The only thing I don't like about this blog (other than the fact that I'm not clever enough to skin it myself - design no problem - css etc is), is that there isn't a facility to put posts into catagories.  I want to write about the demons that fuel my depression and mental health issues, yet to have such entries interspersed with daily meanderings doesn't feel or look right. Besides, I would prefer to give people the choice not to read those posts if they don't want to. Not that anyone reads my blog anyway!  The only alternative I can come up with is to begin another blog to run along side this one. Not an ideal solution, but it will have to do for now.
     
    
</post>
<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday I was seen by a different doctor than usual. I was surprised not to be dismissed quickly with a prescription and a form for repeats. He asked me questions, wanted to know if I was self harming again and asked to see the cuts. No doctor has ever actually asked that before.   I got my prescription, but only for a weeks supply of antidepressants. He wants to see me again next Monday. He also told me to contact the mental health clinic where I am an out-patient and have my next appointment brought forward from August. I phoned them this morning and was told that they could not see me until the 8th of June at the earliest.   They do their best, it is not the fault of the doctors, physchiatrists, physchologists, nurses, etc., that the mental health service is under-resourced. The intentions are good. Information about care plans, crisis management, points of contact and so on is readily available, unfortunately, for the most part such things exist only on paper, in glossy leaflets on reception desks.   I have no care plan that I am aware of, when I once asked about it I was given a vague answer about not everyone having one. I have no contact with a community physchiatric nurse, because there are too few to go around, which means they are only allocated to the most needy.   As for crisis management... A few weeks after I came out of hospital I phoned the clinic one Friday, things were going badly and I did not know where to turn. I was put through to the clinic manager and after being asked a few questions, given a 15 minute appointment for the following Monday.   Which means that on days like yesterday, there is no where to turn.   I got through it and today is another day.  
     
    
</post>
<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I feel like a fraud in doctors waiting rooms surrounded by coughs and colds, small children with flushed faces and the elderly accompanied by carers with too loud, over cheerful voices. Today was more uncomfortable than usual. The receptionist searching for a record of the appointment I was so sure I had made. The one I should have kept at 9.10 last Friday.   Embarrassed, glancing at the paper on which I had carefully written down the day and the time, incorrectly, wanting only to leave and forget all about it.  A cancellation means that I will return this afternoon at 4.05 to see a different doctor. I don't want to go, yet know that I need to begin taking antidepressants again. I did not take my last prescription, the tablets are here somewhere but I cannot remember where I put them, or if I threw them out. So sure this time that I was well. Sure enough to tell my GP only two or three weeks ago that this time I could maintain the high.   Not even sure that the medication makes much difference, but not knowing what else to do I will be once again sitting there. Waiting. Patient.
     
    
</post>
<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Hiding urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      When I first came across  urlLink Andre Jordan's blogg , it was what he had written in his bio that caught my attention. His humorous description of what it is like to be depressed struck a chord with me, as did his determination to begin a 'beautiful revolution'.  It chimed neatly with my own intention to 'live life in reverse'.  So far I am not doing so well.  This morning I found Andre's entry for the  urlLink 6th of May 2004  and I have posted it in its entirety below.     Today, when my therapist asked me how I felt, I told her that I felt OK. The significance of what I had just said was not lost by either one of us.  A year ago I arrived at her door sad, depressed, suicidal, and tormented by my demons. At that very first meeting, my therapist asked me what I wanted, why I was there and what I hoped for. I told her that I just wanted to be OK, nothing special nothing amazing, just OK. Today, for the first time in my adult life, I feel OK. I am still paranoid, I am still shy, I am still irrational but my demons have gone. My therapist agrees and feels that her work is done. She tells me I have been a pleasure to meet and that I am 100% OK. Then I just cry, my relief is enormous, I am completely overwhelmed by the journey my mind has traveled.   A revolution can take on many forms but none are more beautiful, than a revolution of the mind.   That is my goal and there is the proof that it can be done.
     
    
</post>
<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    The view from my window urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Glancing at the clock a few minutes ago, I realised that yet another day had slipped from my grasp almost without notice. Can it really be almost 8.30 in the evening? It has been such a beautiful day, warm and sunny, even I could not fail to notice it, if only through the window. I should have been out there, enjoying the weather, but where could I have gone?  Walking up and down the high street lacks a certain appeal and as for my garden - there is no garden - only a bare yard. The extension on my little terrace house dividing me from the undertakers on one side and a low wall, separating my home from the empty one on the other. Perhaps if I added a small table to go with the chair and maybe a hanging basket or a tub, something with flowers and colours and life, that small space might appear more enticing.   I did walk up to the shop this morning. I needed milk for my coffee. In a moment of weakness I bought a large bar of  Galaxy  and ate that for my breakfast.   Then I allowed the day to fade into night while I sat at the computer. Designing the way I would like my blog to look and failing to understand how to edit the template. Wondering through the web, peeping into other people's lives, ignoring my own.
     
    
</post>
<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My ex-husband and I have lived apart for at least 4 years, so how come most days I get a phone call from one of my daughters saying "Mum? Where's Dad?"  Err hang on while I just consult my crystal ball...
     
    
</post>
<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink The Silver Ring Thing   is coming to the UK in the summer hoping to persuade British young people to sign a pledge of sexual abstinence before marriage. No doubt thousands of teenagers will part with ten pounds in exchange for a symbol that announces their virginity to the world, just as many have done in the States.   Personally, I have reservations about the project for several reasons. Not least of which is the claim by the BBC's   Breakfast   program's that 9 out of 10 scheme members eventually break their pledge and are less likely to take 'safe sex' precautions when they do so. Which is not surprising as peer pressure to become sexually active has been replaced by pressure to conform to a new group and that first experience is even more likely to be unplanned.   As a parent, I am well aware of the need to protect our children from growing up too soon, from unwanted pregnancy and from engaging in sexual activity before they are emotionally ready. I'm just not too sure about the 'all or nothing' approach of both organisations like  The Silver Ring Thing  and sex education in general.   I have tried to be open with my children, to promote an atmosphere in which it was easy to share both information and feelings. My goal was to help them to develop a sense of personal responsibility and enpowerment. The choice to abstain prior to marriage or not, the when and the where, the with whom, would be would be their own, informed decision.  Schools and the media do a good enough job in spreading what could be called the 'technical information' for little to be left for parents to supply. But there are gaps in the building of emotional frameworks. There is much talk about 'peer pressure' and yet little about the simple facts of their own instincts and desires.   I have one son and two daughters. Even in this 21st century there is still a sort of vague belief that it is boys who 'want sex' and pressurise girls into acquiescence, as if their own sexuality was non-existent. I suspect that many young people are caught out by the strength of their own desires partly because such things are rarely discussed.  Sexuality is a pleasurable part of our human nature. Sometimes it is a beautiful, precious part of the intimacy between two loving partners. Sometimes it is a physical response to a physical need. I have tried to teach my children that they will want to have sex, that is a natural appetite, and to be conscious at the same time that to desire does not necessarily mean to love. I have tried to teach them that to consider oneself old enough to engage in sex means accepting that you are also old enough and mature enough to accept the responsibilities that go with it.  Responsibility for the feelings of your sexual partner. Responsibility for your personal health. Responsibility for the potential consequences of creating another life.  I have shared my knowledge and my beliefs, but tried not to impose my opinions. They are individuals with a right to make their own decisions and their own mistakes. I only hope that I have given them enough tools to ensure that their choices are informed ones.
     
    
</post>
<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I wonder why I use a pseudonym when writing both my poetry and my blog? The more I think about it, the less I can come up with a valid reason. It can't be to protect my family. There is little chance of them coming across either site by accident and if they did, I have shown them most of the more 'sensitive' stuff anyway. The fact is, that friends and family would recognise me easily whatever name I use. It is hardly a secret that I suffer from a depressive illness, that I have a debilitating back problem and three cats named Merlin, Harry Potter and Pru! (Never mind the fact that my photograph is around here some where too. The children might be shocked to read some of my more erotic poetry, as TD No 1 recently said, 'Mother's don't have sex lives. The thought is disgusting!'  A comment that reminded me of a story my grandmother told me. Apparently, her mother came to visit one day and mentioned that she didn't think her husband was long for this world. Nan was somewhat surprised. As far as she knew her father was in good health considering his age. Both puzzled and curious she probed a little further only to be told 'He doesn't want sex anymore. Isn't natural and isn't like him.'  My poor grandmother didn't know whether to be embarrasses by this startling revelation or to laugh. Her parents, by the way, were both in their 90's! Although as the youngest of 16 children she conceded that her mother might have a point.  As a postscript to the story, my great grandfather died a few weeks after this conversation, proving, as his wife pointed out to her daughter, that she had been correct in her surmise.  
     
    
</post>
<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      There are some blogs that you return to again and again, not just to read the latest entry but to browse the archive of past musings. Over the months, I have spent hours immersed in the writing of Blackrat, 'The Accidental Journalist'. Always interesting, usually topical and with the kind of posts that have you reaching for the 'comment' button. The conversations between the author and his readers are often as compelling as the original article.  Blackrat introduces his blog with the following words,   I'm an ordinary bloke but feel as if I'm living the life of another. For the past five years, I've lived almost every dream I've ever had. Several careers and a lack of direction all came together when I was 30 and I found a previously untapped ability to use my experience and make things happen. It doesn't feel like work, I'd pay to do my job.  I am the accidental journalist and this is my story.   More of the story of how he came to find himself traveling the world, writing features and commentating on world events can be found in the section entitled   urlLink The Accidental Journalist .   For anyone interested in the Iraq war and current situation in Iraq -   urlLink The View From Inside  , is a must read. Blackrat spent a month in the war zone and wrote extensively on his experiences.  Polish off your opinions, make yourself a cup of coffee and take some time to enjoy someone else's life.
     
    
</post>
<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      just that, silence.  I have spent the evening reading blogs, on-line newspapers, news sites, what ever caught my eye. Anything to keep my mind occupied and stop myself from thinking too much. It works for a while, but there is a limit to how many hours even I can stare at a computer screen.   The house is so quiet, even with the television on. The cats are asleep and except for Pru, are not particularly good conversationalists even when awake. The last time I spoke to any one except TD NO1 was Wednesday when I got a phone call. The last time I saw or spoke to my daughter was the same day.   I am not the kind of person who needs to be constantly surrounded by other people. Quite the opposite. I like and need time on my own. Even so, lonliness is a smothering blanket tonight. I have an appointment with my doctor on Monday, my determination not to take any more antidepressants seems to be evaporating as the greyness gathers around me once more.  So tired, yet I do not want to go to bed. I cannot stand the thought of all that empty space and the darkness.   I really am turning into a mad old woman with a house full of cats.
     
    
</post>
<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink cede   A very funny post by Simon and like so much good humour based on how things really are.  Perhaps the government should scrap plans for a national identity card and simply make it compulsary for everyone to carry a utility bill?  Which leads me to another thought about the peculiarities of such things. If you have a reasonable income and pay your gas and electric bills on line, by Direct Debit etc., many companies will give you a small discount.  If, on the other hand, you pay as you use power through a card meter ( which inevitably means that like me, you are on a low and/or limited income), it costs more.   Now that makes perfect sense, doesn't it?
     
    
</post>
<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I would have a little more sympathy for the editor of  The Mirror  if he had apologised for the paper's error in judgment. I give him the benefit of the doubt that he did really and truly believe that the photographs were genuine, even though it is difficult to understand how and why he should have done so. That they were faked, seems to have been fairly obvious to every other experienced observer as well as many members of the public.  Mr Morgan's sacking was an inevitable development given the adamant stand that he took, although I do think that escorting him from the premises in the company of security guards was an overly dramatic gesture. Perhaps a normal action for dismissed executives, but an unnecessary gift for the headline writers never the less.  Despite all this,  The Mirror  has done a good job in preventing the UK from taking the moral high ground concerning the treatment of Iraqi prisoners. We have had to face the reality of war. There are no good guys.  
     
    
</post>
<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink WIL WHEATON dot NET    Coming across this blog site by accident (through a photograph of a cat at buznet), my thoughts returned to those I have lost because of cancer. Too many and I will not dwell on that now. I have written about them in my poetry web site (Scarlet Nails - I have added a link). One day there WILL be a cure for cancer and we will lose our fear of this thief of life.
     
    
</post>
<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    My eldest daughter and I urlLink      I am sure that there is a higher purporse for the existance of teenage daughters, if only to punish mothers for wrong doings in a previous life. I have two. Teenage daughters, that is, so I must have been very wicked...laughs.  That is the eldest, TD No. 1, in the photograph.  Beautiful, isn't she? Intelligent, loving, loyal, I love her dearly and am very proud to be her mother. Never the less she drives me crazy!   All mothers of daughters should be provided with a yale lock for their bedroom doors by the National health service. Toiletries should come in teenage tamper proof containers and kept in lockable bathroom cabinets. TD No.1 complains bitterly when her younger sister helps herself to her cosmetics or clothes, yet seems to think that my rants about her own, er, 'borrowing' habits are mearly signs of selfishness and bad temper on my part.   She has 'borrowed' cleansing wipes until the box is almost empty...again.  Deoderant is 'borrowed' on a regular basis.  She vehemently denies using my bubble bath (expensive and a rare luxury that I treated myself to at Christmas), yet the level in the bottle steadily declines.  This morning I discovered that my shampoo was almost all gone. A particularly strange disapearance as it is one especially formulated for fine hair and as you can see from the photograph, TD No.1 has the most beautiful, luxuriously thick hair.  Luckily, she can no longer fit her feet into my shoes, but my underwear, now that is another subject altogether.  The curious thing is, she left home last September. Curious because my bills have not decreased, nor the amount of housework to be done and I spend as much time with her as ever I did...  There is no point in asking her about the evaporating shampoo, she would only look surprised and ask why I always blame her.   My youngest daughter lives with her father, there is only TD No.1 and me in the house. Except for the cats.  I wonder...  Harry Potter's fur is looking particularly healthy at the moment.   
     
    
</post>
<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The sky is that particular shade of blue/grey that hints at rain before lunch-time. A dreary cast to the light makes it hard to believe that summer is close by. Like my cats, I am a warmth and sunlight person. Cold and rain send me running to curl up in some cozy spot, to sleep and dream of sparkling days.   I am stir crazy. Longing for the smell of salt on the wind and the sound of waves tickling the shore. I want to be cross at the importuning of seagulls and to pick sand out of curling ham sandwiches. I love the sea, it even makes bad weather bearable.  Soon. Soon. Only a matter of weeks and I will escape ordinairy life for two weeks. Excitement catches my throat and fear dances in my belly. It is many years since I have travelled abroad, years since I holidayed at all. And this time I will be alone.  Some days, I think I must be crazy, others I want to laugh out loud at the sheer adventure of it all. Choosing, booking, getting a passport, all exciting novelties for a middle-aged woman whose furthest excursion is usually to Tesco.  I love the sea, and the sun, and to explore new places. And this time there will be no one else to defer to. No children to entertain. No meals to cook or husband to make plans.   No seagulls.  And no ham sandwiches.   
     
    
</post>
<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Heck! I've managed to add both a counter and Buzznet! Amazing! Not only that they seem to be working ok, though rather lost down there at the very bottom of the scroll. There is a pic of me in my Buzznet album and profile, I'm sure that eventually I will manage to put one here too.
     
    
</post>
<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Diet Coke     My life is like a diet coke.  It looks like the real thing.  Smells like the real thing.  It is not until you taste it that the difference becomes clear. Artificial sweetness with an aftertaste of chemicals.   Citalopram is my additive.                                                                         (30mg daily)                                          It stops me from screaming.  Except I don't scream.                                                                                  Or cry.  I stripe my arms                             with frustration                                                      labelled                                                                   'superficial'.  The blade, brand new and shining, calls with a seductive voice                                                                     that I must ignore.                                                                     Today.  The hot weather traps me.  Sleeveless tops and short skirts make it impossible to hide from the prying eyes of children.  Too warm to cover up and still avoid their questions.                                                                               I do not scream                                                                                        Or cry.                                                                                         I wait.                                                                          For the weather to break.          Wounded    A need to justify, the pain inside with red stripes of flesh.  Words blunted like the blade tearing uselessly at the superficial.  Crying blood tears silently through white skin.       Temptation      The blades are out tonight. Siren sharp edges shuffle words between sense and no-sense.  A yes-sense place where the darkling parasite shifts and stirs. Some soundless, shouted thought  disturbed its sleep and now that mindless appetite devours light. Light or life?  What difference when coils choke and blind eyes see only blade shining red relief? So small and object of false promise.  Promise.  Promise-not-to balances promise-need-to. "Resistance is useless" "We have ways of making you talk!"  As corny as that and just as laughably true in this particular re-run of empty, pointless, battling.      
     
    
</post>
<date>13,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am not new to blogging. I have kept an on line journal else where for some time. Whether or not I shall continue to write in both is a question without an answer for now. I like the potential to use my own design ideas here at Blogger, though first I suspect I will have to improve my knowledge of html. There is no hurry, for the moment I am content to settle in and comfortable with using this site.   (Laughs! The spell checker wants to replace 'blogging' with 'flogging')
     
    
</post>
<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is it folks, for a couple of weeks, I am back very late on the 13th July, so expect a Francesca full of holiday stories to reappear very soon after that. In my bag there is a notebook to continue writing my story and a lovely brand new journal to record my adventures. No doubt I will bore you all to death by posting entries from it here!  Am I excited? I guess so. The trouble is that after the 'day from hell' yesterday I am in the kind of 'on edge' mood that makes me feel as though I might fly apart at any moment. My thumb is still extremely painful and did not make it any easier to sleep last night. I will have to find a doctor or a clinic to take the stitches out in 10 days time and of course any treatment required for what is considered 'a pre existing condition' will not be covered by my insurance. The annoying thing is that if I had  to cancel my holiday I would have been entitled to claim.   The injury will make some difference to my holiday. I can't get it wet, have to be careful of infection and will have to shower etc wearing a glove, which will be interesting, lol! Its also very difficult to use my left hand because of the pain, but hopefully it will ease over the next couple of days.  Yesterday is not a day I will care to remember. After leaving the house at 8am to take my ex to work I did not return or have an opportunity to eat until 5.30, except for half an hour when I took the chance to blog.    From A I took my son for his college interview (which went very well, btw), back home and then 30 minutes later out again to attend a meeting at TD2's school. The latter began well but ended badly. TD2 was there but her father was not, which as she lives with him made things difficult. I left feeling extremely worried about my daughter and feeling depressed. Not to mention the regulation guilt. It feels like a betrayal to be flying off on holiday when there are so many problems to deal with. On top of which I feel helpless, I don't know what I can do that would make any difference to the situation.  All that has to be some how put to the back of my mind for the next couple of weeks. In a few short hours I will be heading for the airport then off to Tunisia.   Wish me luck. 
     
    
</post>
<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just got back from the accident unit and am sporting a thumb about twice its normal size, stitches, steristrips and dressings. My ex loaned me the car this morning to help out and as I dropped him off at work he accidently shut the door (a sliding one) on my left thumb. Loads of icky blood, two open wounds, but I am very lucky not to have broken it or done any damage to the tendons.  Will write more later, but for now, it hurts damn it!!!
     
    
</post>
<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ever since I was a little child I have told myself stories. Some of my earliest memories (of which I have very few), are of day dreaming tales. When I first left home I had boxes and boxes of exercise books and paper filled with my scribbling. Very little, if anything, of it still exists. I have a habit of destroying both my writing and my art work during bouts of depression, even my journals went the same way. In recent years I have continued to write poetry but very little fiction. Some of that has survived thanks to the internet. The hard copies have often been torn to shreds, but if a poem made it to my web site it has usually remained.   Although it is many years since I had the urge to write them down, the habit of telling myself tales has continued. Then last week, out of the blue, the desire to give an idea a separate existence on paper reappeared. How long it will last I don't know. So far I have a collection of episodes and character sketches around the same idea but not yet linked together.   It is a strange feeling, writing fiction again. Like exercising a muscle that has atrophied from lack of use. The words are there but the synthesis that binds each part together is missing. Never the less, I am enjoying writing again...I think. 
     
    
</post>
<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My holiday looms ever closer, Wednesday will be my last blog for 2 weeks as I fly out that evening. There is still so much to be done that at this moment I cannot imagine being able to get everything ready in time. My mood has been very low for the past week despite the increase in medication and events seem to pile up one after another in an attempt to bury me under the weight of them. Taken separately each would be manageable but as it is I am acutely aware of my failures and feel as though I am merely waiting for the next.  Communications with my youngest daughter are much improved and I have hope that the rift between us is finally being mended. Yet I am consumed by a sense of helplessness. I have little or no authority over her, almost no involvement in her day to day life, yet it is me that takes her to the doctor each week, speaks to the teachers at her school and will be at the meeting with her head of year, school counselor, etc on Tuesday. Just me. Alone. There is nothing I would not do to help her, but she does not live with me nor wants to. I have responsibility without power and dread this coming meeting.  When the children were small I believed that I was a 'good enough' mother. Not perfect, but then who is? Never the less I trusted my instincts and we seemed to muddle along well enough. Now they are teenagers it is as if every decision I make is the wrong one. Every attempt I make to support and nurture ends in disaster. With TD1 and my son both at home I feel like something between a referee and a scapegoat. I am sick of being yelled at. Sick of feeling constantly in the wrong. Sick of doubting myself and wondering if their criticisms of me are right.  Sick of feeling guilty. Guilty that I feel resentment and anger.   In the scheme of things, the things that make me feel that way are so silly, petty even. Take today. I asked both of them if they would be home for dinner, suggested that it would be nice to all eat together for once. They agreed. I prepared a meal. TD1 was in bed and by the time she came down I had finished eating and her dinner was cold. The boy has only just arrived home with not even a phone call to explain that he had changed his mind.   I resent the piles of clothes and make up and hair products scattered over my bedroom floor that do not belong to me. That I need to buy more cleansing wipes before I go away even though it is not me that has used them, that my favourite eyeshadows, the ones I thought I had lost, turned up in TD1's handbag. I feel guilty that I resent my lack of privacy, the lack of having things that are 'mine', that I am made to feel guilty about going away without them.  Maybe this holiday will be good for me. A chance to get away from every thing and every one.  A chance to breath.  Something else to feel bad about. As one of my children said to me, I am a mother. If I had not wanted the responsibilities, the limitations of that role, I should not have chosen it.  
     
    
</post>
<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Just a short post, it's late and I am very tired. With no internet, in fact, no computer access at all since last Sunday, I have felt very isolated. Despite considering myself pretty well protected my computer managed to become infected with the Sasser virus. Very nasty indeed. It has taken my ex and his friend R until tonight to get rid of it and get me back on line. I've lost a lot of stuff, which is sad, managed to hang on to some, which is good and can finally get back to surfing and writing my blog.   But for now, if there is anyone out there...goodnight...~smile~
     
    
</post>
<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I rarely write about current affairs or political matters, not because I am not interested (the truth is quite the opposite), but rather because others do it much better than me. Sometimes, however, the issues are too important not to stand up and be counted.   Here in the west we take our freedoms fore granted. We go about our daily business safe in the knowledge that we live in democratic countries where our rights are safe guarded. We grumble and perhaps even demonstrate when governments intrude too far into our private lives and limit our choices in some way. Object loudly to 'the nanny state'. Here in the UK we endlessly debate the European Union and form political parties to protect our 'sovereignty'. 'We' do not want our freedom to act to be curtailed by 'foreigners'.  And while our attention is focused on the continent and the rights of government to intervene in the eating habits of its citizens, our fundamental freedoms are quietly eroded almost without comment.  The 'War on Terror' and the blood and guts war in Iraq are also big issues. Ones that most people have a strongly held opinion on. Many people write, speak, and comment on the injustices that have grown out of our fears.  Our attention firmly fixed on the safety of our soldiers, our cities, our citizens abroad; many of us have failed to notice the insidious tightening of a noose around our necks. The USA invents a new category of prisoners of war, 'unlawful combatants', removing the protection of international law in one move. The British government gains an exemption from human rights legislation in order to detain suspected terrorists indefinitely without trial. Joe public nods his head and says nothing. After all these people have given up their rights through their own inhumanity and besides, those of us with a clear conscience have nothing to fear.   Or do we?   urlLink Steve Kurtz , Assistant Professor of Art at the Carnegie Mellon University and a well respected artist in his own right is under investigation by the FBI. Last weeks several of his colleagues appeared before a Grand jury in Buffalo and further appearances are expected to follow next month. The story of how Professor Kurtz has found himself in this situation reads like something from 'The Twilight Zone'. On 11th May, Kurtz awoke to find that his wife of many years lay dead beside him. He dialled 911 and a bizarre series of events was set in motion:   'Paramedics, fire-fighters and police responded and found Hope Kurtz dead. Tests would show she suffered heart failure. Foul play was not suspected, and it would have been an open-and-shut matter but for one thing.  The emergency responders discovered a home laboratory containing bacteria samples, petri dishes and equipment to analyze DNA.  What authorities did next set the stage for an ongoing federal investigation with tentacles stretching to Carnegie Mellon University and the University of Pittsburgh.  Although Kurtz explained that the materials were for an upcoming art installation by his group, the cutting-edge Critical Art Ensemble, as well as research for a book, law enforcement was not taking the State University of New York professor at his word.  Suspicions aroused, Buffalo authorities contacted the local Joint Terrorism Task Force, eventually leading to a federal search warrant executed by agents in hazardous materials suits, some of them from the Pittsburgh FBI field office.  For 36 hours, they traipsed through Kurtz's house. They confiscated scientific apparatus, computers, research books whose subjects reportedly included bioterrorism and biowarfare, and correspondence.'   (Source  urlLink Pittsburgh Post Gazette )  Despite explanations that the materials found were for an upcoming art exhibition by critical Art Ensemble of which Professor Kurtz is a member with an international reputation, the investigation continues, although no one seems to know which laws he has apparently broken of what charges the FBI are considering.   The case has far reaching implications for both the artistic and scientific communities and is being closely monitored by both. It has sparked a global network of support for  urlLink Steve Kurtz  and fuelled the debate about the extension of government powers post September 11th.  It seems that governments have very long arms indeed and for those of you who believe, as I did, that they are entitled to voice their opinions freely in cyber space, I suggest that you think again. 'Someone' may be reading your blog and if they don't like your views...  Last month I reviewed  urlLink Someone Else's Life  as my contribution to the Aortal Open Portal Project. One of my long time favourite blogs, the author, Blackrat, writes with a sharp eyed humour and intelligence that often sparks long running debates in his comments. As a free lance journalist he spent some time in Iraq earlier this year and wrote some fascinating posts on the subject from a personal perspective.  A short while after his return home the blog fell silent. His many readers, including me, had become increasingly puzzled and concerned by his uncharacteristic silence. Then last Friday Blackrat posted for the first time since the 14th of May:   'Where have I been?   Nowhere unusual (although it hasn't been entirely dull either, although more of that later.) It appears that my coverage of a certain conflict and my reports from within did not meet with widespread approval and some, er, 'influential' people across the Pond discovered my blog and took issue with some of its content.   Governments may try, indeed, they may believe it desirous for them to keep a handle on what 'news' emanates from within a combat zone, but the internet and contemporary technology are proving more worthy adversaries in their attempts to do this than perhaps had been envisaged. Journalists and governments are always going to be diametrically opposed in these matters with incompatible objectives and compromise is a difficult thing to reach.  I haven't exactly been 'gagged' but...hey, go figure. You do the math.'   I had to read the entry several times before I could actually believe what I was reading. So much for the freedom of speech and freedom of expression. It seems that we are not only to be protected from terrorism but from artists and journalists too.   Doesn't that make you feel so much safer when you go to bed at night? 
     
    
</post>
<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I missed a day. For the first time in a long time I did not write an entry yesterday. Thursday was a weary day, the kind when words are both too much and not enough. That I had only had 3 hours sleep the night before did not help. I tried to catch up but although I rested, sleep alluded me.   There was no particular reason for feeling so down. Events had actually played out quite well. TD2 had come down from her bedroom and apologised for sending me away, then we had sat, cuddling and talking until 3.30 am. Making plans and searching for solutions for problems that only seem insurmountable when one is young and life is either wonderful or a disaster. I watched her sleeping and wondered what I could have done differently. Thinking how easy parenting is in hindsight.  I had to be up early on Thursday to take TD2 to her doctors appointment. These appointments have had an unexpected benefit, she and I get to spend a little time together. Things did get difficult, there was almost a quarrel, but the doctor was tactful and able to defuse the situation. Afterwards, rather than sending her straight back to school, we went to a cafe and spent a little time chatting.   I came home feeling hopeful that perhaps one day our relationship can be mended, yet at the same time wearied with guilt. Perhaps she will have to become a mother herself before she will understand how much I love her and that every thing I have done has been out of that love.  So today I return to my blog and find yet more signs of the kindness of unknown friends. Generous, unexpected words that brought a smile to my face and a warm feeling inside.  Thank you.
     
    
</post>
<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's 1.30 am and I guess I should be asleep. I'm tired (when am I not?)just don't want to be alone in the dark. So here I am listening to music on Launchcast radio and wondering what to do next.  TD1 just came home. Straight upstairs to her room after switching on every light in the house. Following her, I could hear her voice on the phone to a friend. She sounded tearful, it doesn't take a genius to know what the course is, or rather who. I wanted to hold her,let her know that I am here for her, but she sent me away. Friends are more comfort than mothers when you are 18. I understand. It still hurts though.  I downloaded the latest version of Yahoo Messenger this evening. It looks like fun, I like the new audibles and there are more emoticons too. It's also handy to be able to launch Launchcast radio from Messager. The most interesting feature is the invisible status. Rather than a blanket 'off line' status you can choose who to be visible to.   It's some time since I was on line so I suppose I should not feel so disappointed that there is no one I know around to chat with. Some company would have been good.  
     
    
</post>
<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      People are nice. Bloggers are extra special nice. As you can see from the addy on the right I have a brand, spanking new email address. A Gmail account of my very own thanks to  urlLink Morgan . Thank you, Morgan, ~smile~ this must be the first time I have ever been 'one of the first' rather than a minimum of 5 years behind every one else.  I can also add Belgium ( urlLink Zoe ), the Netherlands ( urlLink Anne )and Thailand ( urlLink Maisie ), to my list of visitors. Made all the more exciting because they were kind enough to leave comments so I have names and blogs to go with the countries. I also spotted a visitor from Singapore today.  I feel a child's excitement when first discovering a world outside of home.  Thank you, all of you. 
     
    
</post>
<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The most interesting thing about stats pages is not the number of hits received but the bit that tells you where people come from. I love looking at this list, it fascinates me. I am amazed that people from all around the world should drop into my weblog. As well as the UK and the USA I have had visitors from France, the Philippines, Canada, New Zealand, Australia, Romania, Singapore, Mexico and even Mauritius and I find that wonderful. All those places I have visited in my imagination, indirectly touching my life for a moment.   There is particular pleasure in finding that I have had a visitor from Mauritius. If there was any where in the world that I could visit, it would be there. My grandfather was born there, then sent 'home' at the age of seven for boarding school in the UK. I still remember the tales he told me, the way he loved his memories of what was the happiest part of his childhood. I wish he had lived longer to tell me more, or that I had been old enough not to forget so much.   ===========================  Please sponsor me! - Pledges so far: 15.00 GBP/27.12 USD  PROJECT BLOG - I will be blogging for charity on 24/7/04 - details  urlLink here 
     
    
</post>
<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      New post on  urlLink Diet Coke .
     
    
</post>
<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My Grandmother would have been very pleased with this particular Monday. Dry, warm and windy. A perfect 'drying' day. Mondays were, by tradition, the day the weeks laundry was done.   I remember as a small child, lying in bed, listening to her singing as she dragged the twin tub from its place at the side of the kitchen and plugged in what seemed to me, a confusing array of hoses. The tub filling, I would hear her footsteps on the stairs as she came to collect the dirty laundry and her voice calling to me that it was time to get up. By the time the water was heated and ready for its first load, I would be washed and dressed, breakfast eaten and ready to join in the fun.  If Nanny was in a good mood, she would put a bowl of water with a smattering of washing powder added onto a chair and I would have my own washday Monday for my dolls clothes. Out of the corner of my eye I would watch her as with large, competent hands, she sorted laundry, heaving a load into the tub. Reddened hands, with swollen knuckles, fingers that flattened out and showed traces of the cross shaped scars gained when she had trapped her hand in a mangle on some far distant Monday when she was young.   The best part was when each wash load was finished and it was time to put it into the spin dryer. Large wooden tongues were employed to drag the clothes from the scalding hot water and deposit them in the next door compartment. They had to be arranged carefully around the central spindle to balance the load, then a circular, open weave, rubber mat would be placed on top. Once the next load of washing had been added to the machine, the lids would be closed, and the fascinating process would begin all over again.  The machine juddered and shook violently sometimes inching across the kitchen floor. The noise made conversation impossible although I could tell by her face that Nan was still singing. I loved to watch the water spilling from the pipe in the spin dryer back into the main wash. Fast and furious, milky white and bubbling like the foam from a waterfall. Occasionally, the pipe would jump out and pour steaming, soapy water all over the floor, soaking our feet.  Next would come the ritual of 'pegging out'. Clean clothes flapping in the wind like a banner that stretched the length of the garden. For awhile I had my own line, stretched between the garden fence and a pipe in the corner of the kitchen wall. Once my own tiny laundry was dry and folded, I had discovered that I could sit balanced on my little washing line as though it were a swing. I remember swaying in the sunshine, happily day dreaming until the time I lost my balance and fell, cutting my head open badly. My washing line disappeared after that, never to be seen again. But a couple of weeks later a real swing appeared on the garden lawn.  Mondays stretched out busy and comforting in my childhood. Long after the laundry had been gathered in, Nan would be standing by the ironing board, still humming to herself, as the pile of neatly folded, fresh pressed clothes grew beside her.   And I would lie in my bed, surrounded by the moist, clean smell of laundry day, the faint sound of my grandmothers voice through the walls leading me gently into sleep.  ========================================== Please sponsor me! - Pledges so far: 15.00 GBP/27.12 USD  PROJECT BLOG - I will be blogging for charity on 24/7/04 - details  urlLink here   
     
    
</post>
<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sara began her current blog in June 2003 with the following words:   "I am a serious person, a nice person, even.  Each day I got to work and help people.  I do it with with care, and skill, and usually with success.  People are grateful for what I do for them, my colleagues appreciate my professionalism.  I suppose that this is all just as it should be.  And yet!  You see, I've learned to be a good person, but I'm not completely happy with my behavior.  There are times when I want to vent my feelings, be unreasonable, rant, rage, and generally behave badly.  I also want a space to be tentative, unsure, to rehearse arguments, change my mind, whatever.  Or to be trivial.  Or to be nonsensical.  Generally to mix up the serious and the silly, the sacred and the profane....."   If behaving badly means writing an intelligent, amusing, often acerbic weblog, then she has certainly achieved her aim. Observations of corporate life and  urlLink office politics , characters such as Indiscreet Pete, Kevin the Sociopath, his side kick John  and Barney the ineffectual boss,are interspersed with commentaries on news items or some small incident turned into the most wonderful and sometimes  urlLink touching , word pictures.  Sara's posts sometimes make me think, sometimes make me laugh, but it is the quality of her writing and her satirical wit that keep me coming back for more. Check out her entry for Wednesday 9th June  urlLink 'Just What the Doctor Ordered'  on recent comments made by the Health Secretary.  ============================================================  PROJECT BLOG - I will be blogging for charity on 24/7/04 - details  urlLink here   
     
    
</post>
<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Words fill my mind constantly. I revel in language, in the individual sound, shape, texture of a particular word. Sweet like honey words such as 'serendipity',damask',  'passion'. Sharp, shiney, metallic words like 'hot' or 'smack'. I love the way they build into stories, tales that waver then tumble into memories like a child's building blocks. Only to re-assemble into something new. An emotion, an observation sliding into thoughts.  It rarely stops, this internal dialogue. Fantasies created from facts, facts emerging from dreams. Words tumble out of me, overflowing the capacity of my mind and escaping into notebooks, journals, scraps of paper. Most are lost. Touched once then fading from my grasp. I bought a tiny dictation machine hoping I might capture the illusive.  Hoping to slow the dialogue by freeing it.   But speech has become unfamiliar. Uncomfortable from lack of use. Ironic for one always accused of talking too much. So I write, and type and close my eyes, drifting in words, sweet like honey.
     
    
</post>
<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Tigers Eye Pendant urlLink     PROJECT BLOG - CHARITY EVENT On the 24/7/04 bloggers around the world will blog every 30 minutes in aid of their particular charity. That is 48 posts that might be essay length, one liners, a photograph, artwork or maybe even a joke! The event begins on Saturday, 24th July at 8am EST, that is 1pm GMT for those of us in the UK.   To take part yourself or to sponsor me sign up at  urlLink Project Blog .  Potential sponsors can also contact me directly at francesca@beadmouse.com with 'charity' in the subject line.   WHY SPONSOR ME?  As those of you who read my blogs regularly know, I am a long term sufferer of depression. With that in mind, my chosen charity is the  urlLink Depression Alliance , a UK charity that funds research into depression, publicizes the condition and offers support to those it effects. The following is taken from their website:   "Depression affects 1 in 5 people in the UK at some point in their lives. Depression is the single most common reason for visits to the GP. More than 2,9 million people in the UK are diagnosed as having depression at any one time. Up to another 8.7 million cases are neither recognised nor treated. Depression Can be a killer - over 70% of recorded suicides are by people who have experienced some form of depression.  If it wasn't for Depression Alliance you probably wouldn't know any of the above. We need you to add your voice to ours until it's so loud that everyone knows the truth about depression. Then, together we can combat it."   To encourage you to visit my blog during Project Blog, I will be auctioning the tigers eye pendant (pic above),designed and hand crafted by me. Bids will be accepted by email or through my shoutbox during the 24 hours, with the current highest bid posted at the top of each hour. The winner will be announced at the end of Project Blog.  (Pledges/donations can be paid by credit/debit card or through paypal by clicking on the donate button in the sidebar. A copy of the receipt for the total paid to Depression Alliance will be displayed here after the Blog Project. If you prefer to send your donation direct to the charity, email me for details.)  Please support me and lets help to make this an event to remember.  Francesca 
     
    
</post>
<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I've had several questions asked about  urlLink Project Blog (blogging for charity), I am going to collect them all together and produce my own faq to supplement the one on the project site. So if anyone has more questions please feel free to email me.   I'm really excited about this. It makes me feel as though I have something to contribute.
     
    
</post>
<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday I blogged about the  urlLink Gmails for a good deed  project run by Jonas.  I said that I would like to do something for someone else but that I lack opportunity, but would keep a look out. Low and behold, this morning I received my copy of the newsletter from  urlLink The Blog Review  and low and behold the first thing that caught my eye was this:   Also up this year is the blogathon.  Unfortunately the fine folks over at blogathon.org are not hosting one this year.  Instead they are planning, coding and testing for a new and improved for 2005.  So now Wendy and I have decided we need to practice staying awake and raising money for charity and we created  urlLink Project Blog  (project-blog.org).  The event is just like the blogathon, 24 hours of straight blogging, so if you are interested, please visit www.project-blog.org and sign up.  Also, if you can, sponsor Wendy and Me.   There it was, something even I could do. Blog every 30 minutes on the 24th July for charity! I've signed up and my chosen charity is The  urlLink Depression Alliance   Now all I need are sponsers. If you feel that you could  urlLink sponser  either me or one of the other bloggers taking part, pop over to the Project Blog site and sign up. It would also be great if you could publicise the project in your own blogs.
     
    
</post>
<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wondering around from link to link, losing myself in cyber space, I came across this:   urlLink We've gots em, the shiny, the precious ("Do some good") | a preponderance of evidence   I am on the mailing list for info on Gmail myself although I can't quite see why it has become such a 'fad'.  Never the less I had to link to Jonas, I was so impressed with his idea, asking people to do a random act of kindness in return for a Gmail invitation. I have so little contact with people other than through the net that I can't think of anything I could do, other than add a little more publicity. But I shall look out for an opportunity, just because. 
     
    
</post>
<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Thank you once again to a  urlLink boing boing contributor for starting my day with a giggle.    urlLink Arcata Eye Newspaper : Arcata Police Log Index   Who can resist an entry title like  urlLink 'Lotion conscripted to evil purpose, ice cream cleared of wrongdoing'  and as for the local bongo problem, I always did have a fondness for lymerics.
     
    
</post>
<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Number 52 - Part 1  ------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------  He had been born in this house and his memories of those growing up years were still bright and clear. His eyes softened and his face took on the 'looking backwards' look of someone who sees what was rather than what is. I felt embarrassed by his gratitude. The stories he told were worth far more than the brief taking of my time and a cup of tea.  This had been his bedroom, that his mothers. Of course there had been no bathroom then. The cellar, now empty except for a few stored items, had been stocked with coal.   They too, had rented the house. During the day the owner, a dentist, worked in the front room, the back room a waiting area for his patients. The family lived upstairs or in the kitchen during those hours. His mother cleaned in exchange for the rent. She was also the local dressmaker, sewing simple dresses for local children and woman. That was how he first met his wife. A child with a new dress.  Next door had lived a large family. The old lady there now, the widow of this mans boyhood friend. Snippets of long ago gossip and childhood adventures kept me spellbound.   When he left, he shook my hand, thanked me again and wished that I would find the same happiness in this house as he had.  My home had been blessed.
     
    
</post>
<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It isn't really mine. I rent it from a private landlord. Above the door is a sign that says 'For Sale by Auction'.  It appeared there one day when I was out shopping, no warning, no explanation. Sometimes I worry about it. About what will happen if someone does actually buy the house. Mostly I forget about it. I have become accustomed to the sign as though it were a natural part of the house like the door and the windows.  This is the 5th house I have lived in since I became an adult and the only one that has ever felt like home. Part of a row of four terraced houses, number 52 is larger on the inside than one would guess from the outside. Like the Tardis in Doctor Who. It still has remnants of its Victorian past, the original coving in the back room (my lounge), and a wonderful sort of archway at the bottom of the stairs.   It has its peculiarities and inconveniences. The stairs are steep and the ceilings high. I need a tall step ladder to change a light bulb. The bathroom can only be reached through the smallest bedroom where TD2 sleeps when she is at home. And there is no toilet upstairs. The toilet is through the tiny square space between the lounge and the kitchen that houses the back door, through the kitchen, then on through a narrow corridor like room whose original purpose is something of a mystery. I keep my freezer and my fridge out there, trailing extension leads to the power points in the kitchen.   One day, soon after I moved in, there was a knock at the back door. I opened it to find a well dressed, slightly embarrassed elderly man standing there with his wife. He explained that he was visiting the area for the first time in many years and had not been able to resist visiting the house he grew up in.  I invited them in and made a pot of tea of course.  
     
    
</post>
<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What do you do when you find yourself wide awake at 5am?  Potter around the net of course!  and spend half an hour playing with  urlLink this . Thank you,  urlLink boingboing  for the link.   The results for my Amusing English place-names by post-code search is as follows:  Shavington Ho Butty Moss Dirty Gutter Bottom Flash Hole in the Wall Jughole wood Shatton Moor Nob End Menlove Gardens   Not one of which I have ever heard of before, despite living here most of my life and some of those places only being 10 miles away.
     
    
</post>
<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    When they were small urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      From out of no where came the memory of my youngest daughter when she was small. She was such a sweet child. Long blonde hair, big blue eyes, a sunny and loving disposition, she attracted people like moths to a flame.   I remember one particular occasion when we were visiting my grandmother in the nursing home. It was never an easy or pleasant way to spend a Sunday afternoon. We would sit, in plastic chairs, in a semi-circle around her in a busy lounge. Trying hard to make cheerful conversation that always sounded false. Some times Nan would complain bitterly that her granddaughter (me) never came to see her, had not visited for months. Other times she would recognise me and beg me to bring my father, her eldest son, with me the next time I came. I would promise, knowing that he would refuse and hoping that she would forget. Sometimes she addressed me as if I were my mother and my eldest daughter as though she were me. Most times she said nothing at all. Just smiled vaguely now and again.  My youngest daughter was the only one of us who never found these visits difficult. She remembered her great-grandmother in no other way than this and she had frequented old peoples homes and hospital wards literally since she was a few days old. She called all the residents 'Nan' or 'Grandad' and shamelessly solicited sweets and biscuits in return for a few minutes of her time and that radiant smile of hers.  On this particular occasion she was sitting quietly on the floor by my feet when suddenly, in a stage whisper, her voice filled with tenderness she said  "Oh look, Mummy!"  I followed her gaze and there, fast asleep in a chair was an old lady well into her eighties. She had whiskers on her chin, her false teeth had slipped and drool trailed from her open mouth.  "Look Mummy!" my little girl whispered, "Sleeping Beauty." 
     
    
</post>
<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My tickets have arrived! oh eck!
     
    
</post>
<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Eighteen days, that is all the time that stands between me and my first holiday in far to many years. On Wednesday 30th of June I will be heading off to Birmingham airport and then taking a flight to Tunisia. It still does not seem real. Clothes bought on eBay are folded neatly and waiting in my room for me to pack them. My first ever passport is safely tucked away. There is still so much to do, I have not ordered any travelers cheques or currency, little things, details.  I should be exited but instead I am frightened. I will never have been so far away from home. I do not speak French, the second language in Tunisia, I will be alone.   It is ridiculous, childish, to feel the way I do.   I do not know what to expect, at the airport, the hotel. Will I be brave enough, will it be safe enough, to explore the way I would like to? The hotel does not accept children so it will not be filled with families, but will I be one lone woman amongst couples? Will my tens unit cause problems at the airport?   Will I get lost?
     
    
</post>
<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It looks like it is going to be another beautiful day. The sun is already warm and determined. I slept with the curtains drawn back, not wanting to trap what little cool air there was from the open window. I listened to the traffic slow to an occasional passing car as the night grew old and then to the chirriping of birds as a new day took its place. My bed became a pool of dancing light as the sun began to fill the room. I felt as though I were bathing in sunbeams as it reached out to warm my skin. I smiled.  I love my bedroom, or rather my bed. The room itself still needs much to be done to make it the retreat I envisage. When I moved here, a year ago last May, I needed to buy a new bed. On an impulse, I made a bid on a second hand four poster on ebay. The fates must have been smiling on me that day, it did not reach its reserve and I was the highest bidder. My ex-husband's mouth squeezed into that disapproving line he does so well as he told me I was irresponsible and mad to make such a purchase.  Maybe he was right. Common sense had nothing to do with fulfilling a small dream held since childhood. My very own four poster bed. A modern reproduction that masquerades as brass it may be, but still it is beautiful. I clothed it with red and black satin. Piled cushions in red and gold by the pillows. Threw a heavy, black and gold, medieval design cover along its length. Rosebud, a doll once owned by my mother, holds court there during the daytime.   At night it is my haven. The place where I read and write and sketch. Gradually filling as the week goes on, with books and paper, pencils and pens. Until Pru complains that there is not enough space to stretch out and purr.   This morning I swam there in sunlight and day dreams and knew that sometimes 'sensible' is not the right choice.
     
    
</post>
<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am not going to turn my blog into a 'tribute' to MJ. There is no point.  There is nothing much to say. He left this morning with a smile, a kiss and 'I'll contact you before your holiday' and that was it. All day I waited for a call that never came. I don't know when I will see him again.   This is all I will ever have of him. A night, occasionally a few days. Phone calls. Why do I accept it?  I love him, yet is that reason enough to resign myself to being alone?  In his comment on my post  Swings and Roundabouts ,  urlLink Denny  said   ...It should always be a matter of the heart, but it helps if the mind and the heart are holding hands at the time...   Perhaps my heart and my mind are holding hands. Perhaps I am simply being realistic in my expectations. For the first time, I have someone who loves me. Cares about me. I don't have to pretend with MJ. There is no need for masks. Yet at the same time he describes me, sees me, in terms I don't recognise. I wish I was the woman he says I am, strong and talented. There is no evidence in my life experience that would suggest I could ever find such magic again. To love and be loved.   I could not find it when I was young so what chance now that I am middle-aged, with a history of mental health problems?  Perhaps this is all I was meant to have.
     
    
</post>
<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I had a clinic appointment today, I have posted about it on  urlLink Diet Coke .
     
    
</post>
<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Through a process of trial and error (many, many errors!), I have finally managed to remove the blogger comments from the template. It looks much tidier now, I think. I have also added HaloScan to  Diet Coke .
     
    
</post>
<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sometimes a disappointment is balanced by an unexpected pleasure, and so it was for me yesterday.  My Sunday lunch and 'girly' day did not materialise, which was no great surprise. TD1 had forgotten her promise and not contacted her friend to complete arrangements.  She says that it will happen, one Sunday, some time. It would have been nice, but still, I appreciate the thought.  Then yesterday MJ telephoned. He does so regularly. Although we are no longer together, he is still there for me. We talked for ages and gradually the idea grew in my mind that I was going to see him later that day. I felt the excitement grow as if someone were squeezing my heart and every thought that this was over vanished without even a seconds resistance.   I paid TD2 to help me with the housework and to go out that evening. She always does go out on a Monday but I know how short of money she is. It ended in an argument of course. She did not want to do chores, even for money and pointed out that in reality I was bribing her to make herself scarce so that I could spend time with MJ.  Amongst many things said and yelled was "MJ whistles and you come running!"  True.   How to explain to an 18 year old that hearts grow older but not necessarily wiser? That a woman can fall in love as deeply, as passionately, as foolishly, in her 40's as she can in her teens? That even after two years, something inside me leaps at the sound of his voice, just as it did in the beginning? That to wake in the night and see MJ sleeping next to me makes me feel safe and eases the loneliness I have lived with all my life in a way that no other man has ever done?  I know it is going no where. But, oh! The journey!  
     
    
</post>
<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I read with delight Denny's most recent entry,  urlLink Close Encounter with Screech Owls . Smiling at the tinge of envy I detected for a life where owls might watch you from trees in your own garden. The world of nature is in short supply in my home town without access to a car to escape the short distance into a more rural landscape.  Yet even here such magical moments can happen.  Until last year I lived on a housing estate on the edge of town. The gardens were unusualy large and backed onto a large strip of rough ground that divided the houses from near by factories. At the bottom of the garden next to mine was a tangle of bushes and a tree.   On this particular day, the children had left for school and I was folding laundry. Taking a pile of TD2's clothes to her room, I muttered to myself grumpily as I noticed that she had not made her bed or opened the curtains.  Drawing them back to let light into the room my attention was caught by movement in the garden next door. There, frolicking in the early morning sunlight, were two tiny fox cubs. In the shadows of the tree their mother lay relaxed, yet alert to any potential danger to her family. It was a beautiful sight, watching my silent neighbor's tumble and chase, unaware of their human observer. It was one of those perfect moments when only the 'now' exists.  Whether the vixen sensed my presence or perhaps it was simply time to move on, after a couple of minutes she moved closer to her cubs, looking around uneasily. A short, sharp bark of command and they were gone.  
     
    
</post>
<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My son returns to school today. A 4 hour drive then first night blues so hard on both of us. This time he carries the knowledge with him that within a few short weeks he will be home for good. A flurry of exams and leavers parties will mean the time goes quickly.  For months I have lived alone with my two eldest children only temporary visitors. Soon, they will both be permanant residents once more.   The wheel turns and we begin again.
     
    
</post>
<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      An act of remembrance. An act of gratitude. A reconciliation, between the past and the present.  May those who return find peace. May those who remained know that they are not forgotten. 
     
    
</post>
<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It seems to be a day for unofficial 'chainblogging'.  Other people's thoughts brushing against my own and opening memories, ideas, new paths for me to explore.   I enjoy reading  urlLink Ronni's  blog. She writes with such a calm, authoritative style. I admire her clarity of thought and 'togetherness'. She comes across as a woman who knows who she is and what she wants out of life.   Today she posted the second part of  urlLink 'A mother's final, best lesson ' (you can find the first part  urlLink here ).Beautifully written as always, evocative and touching, I could almost see Ronni's mother in my minds eye.   My mother also died of cancer. My memories similar and yet so very different. When she told me she was dying I poured my feelings onto paper. I never showed her what I had written. After her death I shared my words with my sister who asked me to read them at mum's funeral. One of the most difficult things I had ever done.   I have posted the piece on  urlLink Diet_Coke .    
     
    
</post>
<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My daughter and her friend sent me a text to say that they have planned a 'girlie' afternoon for the three of us on Sunday and that they will be cooking lunch, because I am 'ace'. Something for me to look forward, to although I admit to a certain trepidation at the thought of TD2 cooking. I am touched by their thought and appreciate the gesture enormously.   At the same time I have had to bite my tongue. I feel guilty at the ungrateful thoughts I am being careful to keep unspoken. Sunday will be nice, but it would be nice if TD2 washed up occasionally without an argument or even helped with the housework. The every day things that no one does unless I do them. I feel like a nag, going on about chores, the mountain of her belongings in the hall, the university application not filled in. So I try to say nothing. I am too tired to argue.
     
    
</post>
<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Dave's post was filled with his memories of school days and the way our lives link in to a larger history. My mind swims in the past searching for a foothold on the shores of the present. As I read his words an image came into focus.   I was almost eighteen. Our arms linked, I walked with my grandmother in the early evening towards the primary school I had once attended. It was polling day and the news had been filled for weeks with discussion of today's referendum. Would this be the year that the UK joined the European Union?  So many times Nan and I had taken this same route together, as the acrophobic woman who rarely left the house gritted her teeth and fulfilled her duty. To vote. She never missed. This time would be different, this time I had my own polling card and the right to voice my own opinion.  I felt such pride as I marked my decision. I felt part of a great solidarity of past souls who had fought so hard for my right to hold this small piece of paper in my name. When I look back, that day is my coming of age, much more so than any birthday.  Next week I will walk to the polling station with my daughter. I cannot help feeling a little sad that she does not feel the same sense of pride and responsibility as she votes for the first time, as I did, on that long ago evening.    This is part of a chain of posts linked together by word association. The previous link in the chain was here. If you want to write another link here's what to do: Find a word, phrase or theme from this post to inspire your own and go and write it. It's that simple. Try not to write something that's similar to this post. That way the subject of the posts along the chain will vary. E.g. if I write about going to the doctor's, then don't talk about the last time you were ill, instead describe how you used to play Doctors and Nurses with the girl next door. Get the idea? Your post can be in any style you want. Copy this paragraph and tack it onto the end of your post, updating the link to point here, then leave a comment here that points to your new post. 
     
    
</post>
<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have missed another doctor's appointment. Which means I have the embaressment of ringing the surgery, trying to explain to the receptionist and hoping I can get another appointment with the same doctor in a reasonable time frame. I have to do it because once again he only gave me 10 days supply of antidepressants.  Why on earth did I make an appointment for the same day, at the same time as my counseling session? Why didn't I realise before what I had done? and why oh why have I looked at the card several times and still thought it was for today?
     
    
</post>
<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have been roving the internet for the last hour. Catching up with favourite blogs and discovering new ones. It is always 'now' on line. When my day ends, someone elses begins. Each moment is filled with people somewhere writing something.I am not explaining myself very well. Vague thoughts and woolly thinking.   Some times I feel a though 'every one has gone to the moon' and left me behind. The internet is filled with people reaching out, our words brushing against each other like fingertips. The house may be silent and empty but through this window I glimpse other lives and I am comforted.    
     
    
</post>
<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have added haloscan comments, though whether I have done it properly is a moot point! Fingers crossed, folks.
     
    
</post>
<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm really sorry to all those who have been put off by the way 'comments' is set up. It's Blogger, not me. If anyone out there can tell me how to change it so that people can leave a message using their own email/url without having to have a Blogger account or be 'annonymous', I would be truly grateful.
     
    
</post>
<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I forgot to put the dustbin out last night. Which with both teenagers at home means no where to put the rubbish mountain until next week. I was awake early enough, and remembered early enough to have rushed out in my pj's and wheeled the thing down the alley way to the main road. I could not be bothered. Curled up in bed, the tens prickling pain into manageable proportions, Pru purring in my arms, I listened to the sound of the truck ambling down the road. The regular thud, the mechanics of emptying, percussion to Pru's song.  Bin-day. Wednesday. Counseling-day. Get up, get dressed and leave the house day. Talking day.  A so very difficult to do such simple things day.  
     
    
</post>
<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I got up at 5.30 am. A ridiculous time of the morning to be awake but the pain in my back was so severe I needed to use my tens machine, which of course was downstairs. I spent some time reading my favorite blogs as I waited for the pain to subside. A pleasant distraction as there was nothing else I could do. Walking, even standing was close to impossible.   I planned to tidy up. To go through the mail. To sort out my clothes ready for packing. Instead I slept for most of the day. Waking for short periods to blog or cuddle a passing cat. Such a waste of a day. Another day. I did not bother to dress, persuaded my son to go to the shops for me before he went out, struggled to stay awake for more than half an hour, sometimes even an hour.  This is not building a new life. This is slipping backwards. Failing yet again.
     
    
</post>
<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    'Hearth Cats' I like to think of them as the guardians of my home. My first 'Egyptian Mau's', far less mischivous than the real live version currently savaging a newspaper in the lounge. urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Against all odds urlLink     I have always envied those with 'green fingers'. My ex-husband had the knack of coaxing almost any plant away from the edge of extinction and back into optimistic growth. There again, living with me for almost twenty years he had lots of practice. Actually I was banned from going near anything that had roots and lived in a plant pot.   I like plants. I adore flowers, especially the scented kind. It is not my fault that rather than green my fingers appear to act as a kind of death ray. I can reduce the most healthy of house plants to a wilting, leafless stick in no time at all.  The 'money tree' in the photograph has lasted longer than most and I am rather fond of it. It stayed with me after the divorce and so far has managed to survive for several years. I use the word 'survive' deliberately as anything that suggested 'healthy' or 'rampant growth' would probably lead to prosecution under the trades discretion act. There have been anxious moments. Recently, most of its leaves fell off, but as you can see, there is still some nice, fresh, green ones struggling against the odds so there is hope.  Yesterday, it occurred to me that maybe the pot it lives in was a bit on the small side. The fact that it falls over so regularly was the give away. I'm not sure that being able to lift the whole thing out of its container, soil and all is a good sign either.  A quick trip to the shops to purchase a new pot, plant food and a worryingly large bag of indoor plant compost and I was ready to take emergency action. The new pot looked rather too large standing next to the old one. I'm rather hoping that is a good thing. I used up most of the compost, admittedly a good proportion of it ended up on the floor but there is still some left.  There is another survivor in the kitchen. I wonder how it would feel about moving 'house'?  
     
    
</post>
<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Two people agreed to allow me to ask them 5 questions, you can find the answers to those I asked Pogo  urlLink here  and Menina's answers  urlLink here .  The questions that  urlLink Black Ra t asked me and my  urlLink answers .  Any one else want to play?
     
    
</post>
<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
             When I checked the account this morning, I could hardly believe what I saw.    The total donated to date for the  urlLink Depression Alliance  is £85! What amazing and generous people you all are, I cannot say thank you enough times or show how deeply I appreciate your kindness.           </post></Blog>