<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The year is AD 21XX... The galaxy is at peace after centuries of fighting the Reploid Wars... The moon is the center of a swarm of orbiting space colonies. The largest, a massive colony named Eurasia, is undergoing extensive renovation to make it the most colossal and most advanced of all the orbiting outposts. When an unknown evil force occupies Eurasia, the peace collapses! Eurasia's artificial gravity device is wrecked. The colony spins out of orbit, and is now headed on a collision course towards Earth! The outpost will hit Earth in 24 hours. If they collide, Earth could be totally destroyed. It could even vanish! The only way to shield Earth is to deploy Enigma, an ancient particla cannon left over from the Reploid Wars. The future of the planet is entrusted to Mega Man X and Zero.   X rushes to the last coordinates where Zero was heard from, with Alia guiding him. When he enters an empty room, Zero teleports in with his Z-Buster damaged. Pretty soon, Sigma appears, but X easily defeats him. Meanwhile, the colony has been leaking out a virus. Sigma purposely lost as a diversion while the Maverick Virus spread throughout the Earth, and the colony plummeted towards it. The only way to stop it is to deply Enigma, an ancient particle beam. For it to work, Douglass requests that you find 4 parts to strengthen it; The Crystal Ball from Grizzly Slash, The Orifalcon from Squid Adler, the Laser Device from Izzy Glow, and Hydrogen from Duff Mcwhalen.   Getting the 4 parts wasn't enough to destroy the colony, and it crashed into Earth. Mankind barely survived the impact, and are living underground until the reploids finish renovating the Earth until it is fit for living. X rushes to go find Zero's escape pod, and when he reaches there he find a mysteriously powerful energy aura. The owner of that energy aura was Zero, who floated above X and challenged him to a fight. In order to save his friend, X a</post></Blog>