<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Chapter III: At last he noticed me  “Today is the 18th of July, Friday. Our P.E. day!! Oh God?! How can I make pa-cute if I’d be wearing a jogging pants and look all sweaty at an early hour?! Well… might as well just look funky today!” – ice  	It was like any other day for me. I was thinking of looking sporty so at least if my crush sees me, I’d still look noticeable right?! I know what you’re thinking… you thought that by now I should have forgotten about this so called soul mate of mine right? Well… for some reason I can’t. So as the saying goes, “if you cant beat them, join them!”. But I wouldn’t want to jump into conclusions and believe that he’s really my soul mate or anything so for now I’ll just think of him as my crush, to slower things a bit. You see, I’d believe that he’s my soul mate yet he doesn’t have any clue on who I am, that would just break my heart. It’s like this, he’s my soul mate but I’m not his soul mate. Get my point? Hell with that! I don’t even know his name!!! Stupid huh? 	Skipping forward, let’s talk about lil stuff that I did day. Well, you see, I’m in to witch craft. I like calling out names of Gods and Goddesses or sometimes just to look above the clouds and ask God for some answers. Well, I got an answer. 	Early that morning I had a dream. There I saw my crush and he introduced himself to me at the ladies comfort room in the 3rd floor. There he looked at me eye to eye and somehow I looked at him back. It’s such a big deal for me ‘cause I can’t look at people straight into the eyes, especially with boys. But at that moment… I felt comfortable… so then I woke up, I looked above me and asked God to give me signs. I was wishing that somehow He would show me or tell me that that 7th grader is the person who caused my long wait. I did not ask for specific signs, I just asked for something that would give me goosebumps when I see it. For short, when I see the sign, I would automatically know that that’s the sign from God that I want to see. 	Moving back to what happened that day, I came to school late. We were stuck in traffic and I got to school at exactly 8:00 a.m. well that seemed nothing, so I went to our first class at room 201. It was our P.E. subject. I couldn’t get near the door ‘cause apparently other high school students were waiting outside the room. I thought to myself: “they look a bit young, are they 7th graders?” well, my question has been answered! My crush was standing there and he was laughing with his friends. I felt really as in really really WEAK. Good thing my friend Frances opened the door and lured the 7th graders in. I was really shocked on what she did! My heart was beating so fast!!! Are we sharing rooms now?!  	“Ice! Ano ginagawa mo jan? tara! Pasok ka na. Wala si ma’am may 	performance kasi sila” said Frances.  	“bakit may mga grade 7 sa loob?!” I responded hesitantly.  	“may kukunin sila, mga libro. Room nila to eh! Tara na!” Frances answered.  	So that’s why they were standing there… so I got nothing else to do but to go in and stare at him! Hehehehehe… when I found my seat, I pointed my crush to my friends… all they said was…  	“Girl! Gwaping sha pero neng… sorry… di kayo talo!”  	Ouch! But didn’t affect me at all ‘cause it didn’t wake me back to reality. Then, at the black board there was this huge letter “M” over an infinity sign then a number 8 near it. I felt goosebumps crawling all over my body and I thought… “What kind of a sign is that?! Halurr?! Ano yun dava!”. Later on I saw a large graffiti. It spelled out as “MAF”…. MAF? Diba yung grade 9 yun? What does she have to do with it? But lil did I notice it was all in caps. So mainly those were just letters and not a word. My day ended and I kept seeing those letters over and over up until I realized what fate was trying to tell me. 	July 18, 2003 our lunchtime and we were asked to read a selection but I forgot to add that on my list, so, at lunchtime I was reading it. We met up with our barkada at our usual spot near the volleyball court. When we got there, some 7th graders were having their P.E. class. My other friends went to the canteen to eat while me, Malaysia and Sarah stayed at our spot. While I was reading my book Malaysia and Sar were eavesdropping to the 7th grader’s class then Sar interrupted me and surprisingly said:  	“Ice! Diba yun yung crush mo?!”  	She was right… It was him alright. I don’t know if he heard us cause he then stood up from where he was sitting and walked right passed us to reach to the trashcan. I didn’t know what to do so I played safe and kept reading. Then…  	“Hoy psssst! Bata! Oo ikaw! Ano pangalan mo?” – Malaysia asked him  after he realized that I was serious when I said I liked that guy so she thought she’d help me out.  “MARCUS….” He answered. He was smiling at us so I smiled back. With matching curtsy pa yun!  “Lapit ka nga dito!” said Malaysia “Friend ko nga pala si Ryzza but you can call her Ice. I’m Malaysia by the way. And that’s Sarah over there.” She then added.  Pointing at me, Sarah then teased and said: “Bata! Crush ka nito! Pinagpapantasyahan ka nyan eh! Kaya nga tinanong namin pangalan mo!”  I was speechless… All I said was “hi” =) after that I became hyper and danced my way to my friends and somehow, cause of my excitement, I asked my P.E. professor what he’s like in her class. According to her, he’s one intelligent kid but a very makulet one indeed. I told her that I have a crush on him. Guess what she said?  “What!!!! Anak! Seryoso ka? Adviser ako ng mga yan!! Anak ko na yan ngayon! Naging anak nadin kita noon alam mo naman kung gaano ko kayo pinprotektahan diba? Ice, bata pa yan. Wag mong sususlutin yan ha?! Pero nak, in fairness, gwapo sha!”  heheheheheeh… so much for scolding me… Haay… But I didn’t stop ther. I brought out my mobile phone and begged Sar to take a picture of him. And so she did!Ü Marcus was kind enough to pose for the camera. =) Incase you’re wondering, YES… I still have that picture in my phone. After that, my gay friend Darwin got mad at me for having a crush on Marcus. He was intimidated by him and for him; I was not what he had in mind to fall for someone who’s younger than I am. Shempre, ako nga yung maldita remember? For Darwin, Marcus is his competitor. You see, he wasn’t that popular when we were younger,,, har har har.. So, I got the picture, I know his name and finally he knows mine…Ü I can sleep peacefully na,,, yehey! =) at last! He noticed me…  	When I got home, all I did was to zoom in and zoom out his picture and I know this may sound weird, but I was talking to the picture and saying things like: “I think I’m inlove with you, will you love me too? Pede akin ka nalang?” Nyikes! Nababaliw na ata ako! Then I remembered the signs I got. I thanked God for it cause I can now say that I’m going on the right path. M stands for Marcus… but wait. What’s with the number “8” and what does “MAF” stands for?! 
     

    
</post>
<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Chapter II: Forgetting  “NOOOOO!!!! This is not possible!!! I shouldn’t believe in neither fate nor destiny?! I am not in love with that kid! He’s just like my lil brother, naaah! Wait.. Like my baby, my sweetie, my mahal…Ü damn! What the hell am I saying?! This is not right. I should just forget what I felt that day… yeah… right! I should forget him…” – Ice  	I am still in denial but somehow I can’t help but to wonder why I felt head over heels for him. Haay… anyways, nutrition month is near and we, the seniors, were assigned to cook a healthy yet affordable meal. As the president of the class, we have discussed ang argued on which meal we’ll serve. After the long debate was over, we finally came up with a conclusion. We’ve decided t sell “caldereta con teriyaki” with free juice for the low price of Php. 3o. Then came the awaited moment. It was the 1st week of July, and I have forgotten about this so-called soul mate of mine. Well, that’s what I thought… 	“o class! Sino mag te-table skirting? Kelangan natin yan to attract the  customers” – said prof. Manahan (our adviser)  “Ma’am si Ice po!! Hindi po kasi yan nagluto kaya dapt po sha yung mag  skirting!” – said Malaysia(my ever loving kabarkada”  Hmmm… I was cornered so I got no choice but to do my work! =( I sat on the floor and started to pin the cloth. God! That was really boring… oh well… might as well enjoy what I’m doing. I became very much focused on my work when all of a sudden a soft breeze seemed to pass my way. I can’t explain it but somehow I heard a voice whispering in my ear and telling me to look to my right. Nyikes!!! Creepy! But in case you’re wondering, wala sa lahi namin ang sira ulo! Oh my gosh!! I’m imagining things now… ano ba yan! Ganito ba talaga pag nag mamahal ka? Kelangan mong ma loka?! Going back to my story, when I heard the wind’s message, I was so obedient that even if I’m freaking out of what I’ve heard, I still managed to look to my right. Matapang na ko!Ü hehehehe… then my heart started beating really fast when I saw what or should I say whom I saw! It’s that 7th grader again!!! I stood up ‘cause some kids were blocking my view, but then, he disappeared. Multo ata to eh! So I walked and tried to search for him but I cant seem to find him. Damn… is this what you call fate?! Wait a minute… was he wearing a black fitted Capri pants?! Holy shit! Awww man! Sue fate!! They cant hook me up with that kid?! That’s merely impossible!! He might be fond of dancing ocho-ocho and spaghetti pababa!!! Whaaat!!!! Holy crap! I’m outta words! All I can say now are phrases which describes my feelings right now… haaay… when will I find my real soul mate… lagi nalang ba akong sawi?… After that, I’ve completely forgotten him… at least I thought I did. You see, when I saw him like that, for some reason I felt heartbroken… I felt deceived… disappointed… hurt. I thought to myself, “why am I letting my emotions get to me?!” there must be a good reason why I’m feeling all of these but right now, I should set it aside. Wow! Am a brave gal! Hehehehe… destiny was right on time! When I was feeling lost, something happened. My long wait to become a writer has finally arrived! A torchbearer organization put up a poster for application. Well, it’s not that easy to become a torchbearer. You see, when we got there, we wrote two entries. The elimination started at 5 p.m. and finished at 7 in the evening. I wasn’t feeling confident with my entries ‘cause I thought it was kinda lame and I know that I could’ve written a much better piece if we were given more time. That made me feel depressed and I thought to myself that I shouldn’t count on that anymore. The next day, I saw the list. I got in!Ü actually someone told me first. A friend of mine came up to me and said:  “Ice! Congratz! Ikaw yung may codename na HARSH diba?! Ikaw lang kasi  kilala ko sa listahan eh, luma na kasi codename mo! Hehehe… congratz ulit!”  I didn’t believe him at first, so I must see the list with my own eyes right? So I went to the corridor and looked for the poster. Wow… there it is… my codename. Right next to yum-yan. Malaysia got in too! And so did my other kabarkadas namely Freya and Jedz. Our first meeting…=) I’m a torchbearer staff now. The instructors told us that we are headed to a screening later on so they can pick the editors for the school paper. Whew! This is getting too tiring. We were asked to write anything so I made up stories about myself meeting my soul mate. Ü but when I was thinking of what I wanted my soul mate to be like… I ended up writing every little detail I can write about that kid who might be my destiny… damn… why cant I forget him?! 
     

    
</post>
<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Chapter I: my soul mate  “I met this guy 9 months ago. He’s cute, “makulet”, friendly, smart… for short, he’s plain perfect. But we all know that nobody’s perfect right? Everyone has flaws and for me, his is his being too young for me. Two years and something months younger than I am.” – Ice  	I am a grade 10 student of Philippine normal university. I’m just an ordinary girl, if you would ask. Friendly? Yes. But I can be quite the “malditang laitera” of the batch. My name is Ryzza but my friends often address me as “ICE”. Not because I’m coldhearted or anything, but because it fits my personality. I can be painful when you’re having a brain freeze or I can be harmful to your sensitive teeth. But I can be helpful at some times when you’re feeling a bit hot and in need of something cold to relax your whole body. You get my point right? Anyways, enough about me… this is where my life gets a little serious… the day I met my soul mate…Ü 	It was late June when classes start to begin. I wasn’t expecting anything new but I never thought that I could be wrong. Frankly, I don’t know anyone from grade 7-9 at least by names. By faces, I recognize then but I wasn’t that friendly enough to mingle with them, not because I’m not brave enough to speak to them but for the reason that I was rude enough to intentionally ignore them. I believe in karma that’s why I think; actually I know that I’m being punished for my rudeness to those who are younger than I am. Well so much for karma right?! 	A day came, which I thought was like any ordinary day, classes were suspended and we were dismissed early. Normally, my barkada and me would meet up at the multipurpose hall but for some reason, I was separated to them. I was called by my adviser at the faculty room then for about 15 minutes later; I went to the hall and looked for my friends. As I walked down the corridor, a bunch of 7th graders were hogging the way, so here comes the “maldita senior” to walk pass through their crowd, one eyebrow raised, slowly walking while looking at them and saying “ano ba yan! Harang ha!” yeah! Yeah! I know! How can I be more unfriendly?! I cant help it, sorry.. I’ve been like this since the day I was born! Blame my parents and not me. All the faculty members have known me as the “supladang anak ng may sinabi” and to add up to that, I’m already a senior… we rule now! So I’m more maldita than usual. back to what I was saying, I was walking down the corridor and pass the 7th graders then finally I’ve reached the hall. When I was about to step on the stairs someone bumped me and I thought to myself…:” aba! Leche tong batang to! Mangbabangga nalang, ako pa napili!” I wouldn’t just let that go right?! So I was taray enough to turn around and face that stupid kid who bumped me. I was so mad that I already made up sentences to shout to the kid and frighten her. Words like: “hoy bruha! Bulag  ka ba?! Ang laki ng daan diba!? Neng di mo kilala binangga mo! Dahil jan, asahan mong madaming babangga sayo. Trese kaming girlaloo lahat sing bruha ko kaya my advice to you is… takbo! Habang malayo pa ko sayo at baka kung ano pa magawa ko sayo…” o dava! Taray ng linya! But guess what? My plan backfired. I was surprised, the person who bumped me wasn’t a SHE but a HE! I was speechless but I thought to myself “what the hell?! Even if he’s a guy, I won’t let him to just leave me like that” so I walked closer to him but then I saw him smiling… not at me but he was laughing with a crowd of 9th graders. He was wearing a body bag and holding a magazine on his right hand. I noticed that he looks too young to be a 9th grader so I stared at him like I was a stalker. Afterwards he walked to a couple of 7th graders. Questions started to linger in my mind… was he a 9th grader or a 7th grader?! but I couldn’t have cared less… pakelam ko kung 1st year lang sha?! All I know is when I saw him smile, something hit me. I became speechless… I was forcing myself to just ignore him and leave… but I knew right then and there that that guy is the one whom I’m gonna love for the rest of my life… I’ve waited for so long for this to happen… atlast… I found my soulmate. 
     

    
</post>
</Blog>