<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      San Francisco, California, 2003  Melissa Williams made one last stop in front of the mirror before leaving for school. Being popular meant she had to look her best everyday of the week.  Only one more week ‘til summer vacation , she thought. The rest of the ‘in’ crowd were already gathered in the parking lot. Hannah Ackermann, a shy yet extremely cute blonde girl, her boyfriend; dark haired, dark eyed Danny Fernandez, quarterback of the school’s football team; red-headed Celine Baxter and her ever faithful boyfriend, Matt Jefferies; and her childhood best friend, Josh Thompson. Everyone had been expecting them to hook up for ages now. But they just didn’t feel that way towards each other. Melissa knew for a fact that Josh was hopelessly in love with someone else. Josh was the first one to spot her. “Hey!” “Hey. Where’s A.J.?” “Like that girl ever follows a strict timetable,” said Celine, tossing her hair over her shoulders. “I don’t know why we even bother with her.” Melissa never knew why, but Celine and A.J. never got along well. She admitted that Celine could be a real bitch at times and A.J.’s temper often made her unapproachable, but Celine often gave people a chance and A.J. had a kind of aura about her that attracted people.  Maybe it’s because A.J.’s new to our gang , thought Melissa. This wasn’t the first time the thought went through her mind.  A.J. had arrived at the beginning of the previous year. She fit in immediately. Everyone wanted to be near her, and everyone still did. Josh was the one who had brought her into their circles. He had been looking for a new bass player for his band,  Evocation . A.J. had a talent unmatched by anyone else. She was also totally indifferent about everything. Just then they heard the roar of a motorbike engine. A black 1999 Yamaha thunder cat thundered into the parking lot, ridden by a black clad figure, barely missing the gang who had to rush out of the way to avoid being run over. “Doesn’t that girl ever watch where she’s going?” fumed Celine.  Arianna Jacobs removed her helmet, revealing silken raven black hair cut just below her chin. Her flawless pale skin wasn’t even flushed from her ride. Her eyelids were darkened with kohl making her green eyes stand out. Melissa had to admit that A.J. never failed to look good even without trying. A.J.’s small stature often gave people the impression that she was someone who needed to be protected but Melissa knew better than to assume that. “Didn’t you see us, freak?” shrieked Celine.  “You got out of the way in time, didn’t you?” said Arianna shrugging her shoulders. “Why don’t you – “ The school bell drowned out whatever Celine was saying, avoiding the catfight between the two girls. Melissa didn’t think that A.J. would have cared, however. The girl was already heading into the school, leaving Celine fuming like she always did when they had a confrontation. It seemed like nothing fazed her. Melissa sighed.  Will those two ever get along , she wondered.  Arianna didn’t know why she bothered with these people. She got along well enough with a few of them, but that red-headed girl wasn’t worth her time.   There she is right now, complaining to that boyfriend of hers. Really, he behaves more like a faithful dog than a boyfriend.  For the billionth time, Arianna wondered why she was even trying to be normal, trying to be human. She just wasn’t; not anymore, and hadn’t been for a long time.   Arianna woke up to find herself enclosed in a tight, dark space. She felt weak – drained – and light-headed.  Where am I,  she wondered.   Her neck felt excruciatingly painful and she touched it gingerly, tracing the two tiny holes there. She blanched as she remembered what happened in the alley. She knew she should be dead yet it seemed the vampire had spared her.  Or maybe I’ve become like him,  she panicked. She placed a hand over her heart to be sure and felt reassured by her faint but steady heartbeat. Just then she heard a loud scrapping noise. A moment later, she was staring up at the pale face of her captor. “Good morning. Or should I say, good evening.” “Where am I?”  Arianna pushed herself upright, taking in her surroundings. She gasped as she realized that she was lying in a coffin. They were in, what seemed to be, a dank basement, the only lighting being wall-mounted torches. There were no windows that she could see. “How long have I been asleep?” “Two days. How are you feeling?” Arianna was surprised by the concern in the vampire’s voice. “Um…I’m fine. Why have you brought me here?” The vampire smiled. “How would you like to live forever? To never feel pain again? To have absolute power in your hands?” “What?” “I’m offering you immortality.” “Why?” His smile widened. “You anger is a great power you could tap into. What I’m offering you will help you do that. Think of what you could do with that kind of power. All you’ll be doing is trading this miserable life you’re living for a much better one.” Arianna fell silent as she contemplated what the vampire was offering. “You’ll be able to do whatever you want and no one’s ever going to be able to make you do what you don’t want to ever again. You’ll no longer be the victim, the world will be your toy, you’ll be in control…” The vampire paused before adding, “…and, if memory serves, there are a few people you’d like to exact revenge on, am I right?” It was Arianna’s turn to smile. She had made up her mind. She hardly felt the pain this time, giving herself over to the dark. She never even registered her slowing heartbeat. The next thing she knew, Arianna was looking up at a thin red line at the base of the vampire’s throat. “Drink, my love, drink…” Arianna latched onto his throat and did as he bid.  Kristopher…  As she drank, the vampire’s memories flowed freely into her…his transformation, his first kill… then something that surprised her – Kristopher had been stalking her for a while. This wasn’t some chance meeting. He had seen her climb out of the orphanage window and had followed her until she realized his presence. He had been prepared to present her with his proposal and had expected her to accept. Arianna wondered what this meant. Darkness sought to have her in its cold embrace again. The last thing Arianna heard was Kristopher whispering, “Welcome to my world, my Katriana…”    Katriana … Arianna hadn’t heard that name in a long time and had no desire to ever again. Katriana was part of her old life, one she had left behind long ago. As she entered the hallways of her high school, Arianna registered the strange murmurings of the crowd around her. “A.J.!” It was one of the hangers-on that constantly followed Arianna and the gang. The girl’s name escaped her at the moment. “Have you heard of the attacks?” “What attacks?” “You mean, you don’t know?” The girl was obviously ecstatic about being the one to break the news to a member of the ‘in’ crowd.  “I’ve been away all week-end. What’s going on?” “There were two attacks over the week-end. People are saying that an animal did it. It’s horrible.” “Cut the dramatics and give me the facts, Georgina.”  That’s right. The girl’s name’s Georgina Forbes . “Well, it’s not anyone from school. I can’t believe you haven’t heard. It’s been all over the news.” “There wasn’t any form of communication where I was. It was kinda like a back-to-nature thing. So, who were the victims? I assume it’s safe to use the past tense with them.” “Oh, perfectly safe. The coroners said they bled to death and there was no way that they would have survived anyway, considering the wounds they received. Horrible, really. At least, it wasn’t one of us, right?” Arianna suspected that Georgina’s ‘us’ wasn’t referring to the student body. “Were they from around here?” “Who?” “The victims of these attacks.” “Oh no, apparently they were bums. No need to worry.”  Yeah, no need to worry . Arianna had realized that people didn’t usually care what happened to the homeless. They were the most obvious choice when it came time to feed. Not that she would take another human life; not after the last time… She had been telling the truth about the whole back-to-nature thing. She had been out in the forest, quenching her ever growing appetite. Melissa had caught up with her by then – so had the rest of their little gang. Georgina immediately latched onto Josh trying to get his attention. Hannah seemed unnerved.   Then again , Arianna thought,  she always does . “So, Josh, have you heard the latest…” “It’s terrible,” said Melissa aside to Arianna. “You mean the attacks?” asked Arianna. “No, it’s the fact that no one seems to care about the victims. It’s like just because they’re homeless they have no right to anything. Not even a little respect. The entire school’s like gossiping about it.” Arianna smiled. Melissa could be said to be her closest friend in her new life.  This is why I like her , she thought. “Everyone’s saying some animal did it,” said Josh, having extricated himself from Georgina, who was looking rather forlorn. “You don’t sound like you agree,” Arianna commented. “You’re right, I don’t. If the attacks were near some woodlands or something, then maybe this theory about animal attacks is right. But they happened right in the city.” “So? Animals could wander into the city any time,” argued Celine. Matt nodded in agreement. “And the fact that their throats were practically ripped out supports the fact,” he added. Celine smiled approvingly. “As much as I hate to admit, I agree with Celine on this one,” said Danny. Hannah kept quiet. The late bell rung, cutting short any debate they were about to launch into. “We’d better get going. Don’t want to get detention during this last week,” said Danny, putting an arm around Hannah and guiding her to their first class. “Especially if you get stuck with Mr. Becker,” muttered Josh. Arianna and Melissa headed for their English class. Mrs. Peterson seemed to be in a holiday mood already and didn’t even seem to notice that half the class was late. She also hadn’t prepared a lesson. “We’ll just do a little role play, shall we?” There were a few groans from the class as everyone took out their copies of the Shakespearean play they had been studying, Romeo and Juliet.  “Why do teachers always pose things as questions?” whispered Melissa as she leaned over her bag to retrieve her book. “It’s not like we have a say in anything anyway.” “Who knows?” replied Arianna.  She was already feeling just as lazy as everyone else was. Fortunately, the role Mrs. Peterson assigned her wasn’t huge. Unfortunately, Mrs. Peterson was a perfectionist.  “No, no. Say that again, Arianna. And this time, say it with feeling!” Arianna sighed. She was just about to launch into another mind-numbingly boring monologue, when she was interrupted by the creak of the classroom door swinging open. There, framed by the doorway, was a boy with incredibly blue eyes and hair so blonde it seemed almost white.  Kristopher… It’s impossible , Arianna thought.  Be rationale. His hair and eyes are a different color. Yet…there’s no mistaking that smile or that face…No, it can’t be. Kristopher’s dead. I should know since I killed him…   “And who might you be?” enquired Mrs. Peterson. “Damion Grant,” replied the boy.  There, see, it isn’t Kristopher. The boy’s got a totally American accent and Kristopher’s too proud to disguise his descent . “Welcome,” said Mrs. Peterson with a flourish. Arianna sometimes wondered about the state of her mental health. Damion just looked amused.  Arianna couldn’t help but notice that no one was paying much attention to the role playing anymore. Not that anyone really was in the beginning. Everyone’s attention, including Mrs. Peterson’s, was fixed solely on the new boy. She couldn’t help but notice since it was normally she that was the center of everyone’s attention. By recess, word had gotten around about the new kid in school. Damion was all Celine could talk about. Arianna shook her head in disbelief at Matt, who was hanging on to Celine’s every word and didn’t even seem to mind that her attention was totally focused on another boy. Melissa caught her movement and gave a sympathizing smile. “He is like the hottest guy ever!” exclaimed Celine.  Georgina had returned with other hangers-on. All of them were nodding their agreement. “What do you think, Matt?” asked Arianna innocently. Melissa tried hard not to laugh. “What?” said Matt absent-mindedly. “Oh right…whatever Celine says…” Josh sighed. “Poor guy,” he said. Just then, Danny and Hannah walked up.  “Hey, guys,” greeted Danny. “Heard ‘bout the new kid?” “Yeah, that’s all we’ve been hearing,” replied Josh. “Celine won’t shut up!”  “Hey, A.J., lighten up. Besides, we already know that. It’s a well known fact.” “Hey!” protested Celine. “Can we talk about something else other than Damion?” pleaded Melissa. “Right…so…where are you guys going this summer?” asked Josh. No one had made any plans. “I’ve got an idea!” exclaimed Hannah. Heads swerved to face her, surprised that she was even contributing to their conversation. “My parents are like going to Tahiti this summer. The cottage in the mountains will be free. We could go there. Like just the gang. It’d be like one long party!” “Hmm,” said Danny, nuzzling her neck. “Just what are you planning, Hannah?” Hannah giggled and blushed. “Hmm,” said Celine. “Uh oh, what are you plotting, Celine?” demanded Melissa. “Oh nothing, just wondering if Damion would like to come along.” “I thought this was just the gang,” said Arianna. Celine glared at her. “It was just a thought. Oh! There he is right now!”  Everyone turned to where she was looking and true enough there was Damion Grant entering the school’s cafeteria. “I think I’ll go over and invite him.” And before anyone could protest, she had left her seat and was already half-way there. Josh gave an exaggerated moan when she intentionally tossed her hair over her shoulders and started simpering. Arianna and Melissa shared a smile. They watched on as Celine made her proposal and noted Damion’s look of surprise, as well as the smile he gave her. It wasn’t exactly the ecstatic smile that other boys gave Celine when they finally manage to get her attention. It was sort of embarrassed and it looked like he was desperately wishing that he was anywhere but there right then. He smiled again, but this time it was more apologetic than embarrassed, and made a hasty escape from the cafeteria. Melissa tried not to smile as Celine dejectedly made her way back. Arianna, however, had no qualms about smiling. Georgina and the other hangers-on were staring at Damion’s retreating back, their mouth’s gaping wide. Georgina turned to Celine. “I can’t believe he just blew you off!” “Shut up,” Celine muttered dangerously. Georgina must have noted the threatening tone in her voice for she did just as she was told. “So much for that idea,” said Arianna. “Shut up!” Melissa placed a hand on her friend’s shoulder before she could throw herself at Arianna. “A.J., lighten up.” Arianna gave her a look that Melissa couldn't quite interpret, shrugged and let the matter rest. Josh smiled at her, silently thanking her for preventing the imminent fight. Matt didn’t seem to know just quite what to do. Both Danny and Hannah tried to pretend they hadn’t witnessed anything. “So,” said Josh a little too cheerfully. “Are we still on for this summer getaway in the mountains?” “Definitely,” said Danny, casting an affectionate glance at Hannah. “Yup,” said Melissa. “Of course,” thundered Celine. “He doesn’t know what he’s missing…” They let her continue fuming and gave her space to calm down in her own time. “Whatever Celine wants,” said Matt. Arianna simply shrugged. “We’ll take that as a yes,” said Melissa. Arianna smiled. “Perfect!” exclaimed Josh. “This is gonna be so cool!” Melissa smiled at her friend’s enthusiasm and wondered exactly what had caused it. 
     
    
</post>
<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      here's the link to the fanfic i was telling you guys about... http://boards.harrypotter.warnerbros.com/web/messages.jsp?board=Book=44569884  it's under orli17 on the boards... enjoy!
     
    
</post>
<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      London, England 1919  Arianna hoisted herself out of the window, reaching in to pull out her bag before dropping to the ground. It was hardly a long fall and she made it without twisting her ankle or worst, breaking her neck. Taking one last look at what had been her prison for the last three years, Arianna made a rude gesture, felt the exhilaration of Mrs. Riley not being able to reprimand her, and turn her back on the orphanage forever. She wondered when they would notice her absence.  Probably when they wake us up for the early morning service , she thought. The services were another reason she detested the orphanage. Every morning, Mrs. Riley would wake the children up and they would gather in the common room. Then she would say a prayer for the lost souls and thank God for sparing their lives.  Thy will be done on earth as it is in heaven , Mrs. Riley would pray.  If God was all-powerful, why couldn’t He stop the damn war?  Arianna thought bitterly.  Why couldn’t he have saved Mama and Papa? But most of all, why couldn’t He save Robert?  Although Robert was five years her senior, she and her brother were always very close. It sometimes seemed that they could even read each others minds. But then the war started and Robert rushed to enlist in the army. Her parents were proud that their son would be defending good ol’England. To them, it was an honour to have a son fighting in the war. But less than a year later, Robert laid dead, a single bullet hole through his temple. From the minute she heard of her brother’s death, Arianna’s health deteriorated. She never was a healthy child to begin with. She was small for her age; her skin was sallow, her features pinched and her greasy dark hair just seemed to weigh her down. Now she began to lose weight until she resembled a walking skeleton. Then her parents were killed in an air raid. Her mother’s brother took her in for awhile, before her constant fits of coughing and doctor’s visits became too much of a burden. She was abandoned at the orphanage at the age of twelve. Mrs. Riley took an instant disliking to her. The feeling was mutual. Despite her ailing health, Mrs. Riley set her a number of tedious tasks; scrubbing the floors, doing the washing, white washing the privy. Arianna’s face twisted in an ugly scowl as she recalled her years of imprisonment.   “Put your back into it, girl! I’ll never for the life of me figure out why I ever took you in. I’ve just got a big heart. And look where that’s brought me!”   Arianna invited her to do something unnatural to herself. She didn’t say it out loud, of course, just thought it in her mind. Still Mrs. Riley frowned at her work.    “Look at this filth!”   Arianna bit her tongue to stop herself from pointing out that she was the one who was trailing filth behind her by failing to remove her boots when she returned from pottering out in the garden. She tried to block out Mrs. Riley’s voice by thinking of her life before imprisonment and proceeded to scrub the kitchen floor harder. Out of the corner of her eye, she saw Helen, another of the orphans, looking at her with pity.  How come I get stuck with scrubbing floors while everyone else does meager work,  thought Arianna.   She had protested about it before and Mrs. Riley had responded by telling her that such work would humble her haughty attitude and curb her anger.   Arianna readily admitted that she was a tempestuous child but felt that Mrs. Riley was really exaggerating by calling her haughty. She helped whenever she could and never thought ill of anyone until she came to the orphanage. Right then she was praying that some unfortunate accident might happen to Mrs. Riley.   “Hurry up, girl! Really you should stop being so lazy!” That did it.   “Why don’t you look at your own self before criticizing everyone else? What was it the Good Book said?  ‘Why, then, do you look at the speck in your brother’s eye, and pay no attention to the log in your own eye? How dare you say to your brother, “Please, let me take that speck out of your eye,” when you have a log in your own eye? First take the log out of your own eye, and then you will be able to see clearly to take the speck out of your brother’s eye.’”  Arianna watched with growing pleasure as the colour rose in Mrs. Riley’s face. She was a quick learner and previous lessons had taught her that, at least in Mrs. Riley’s eyes, Scripture from the Good Book should not pass her lips except in prayer. Any other occasion would be considered blasphemous. But she just couldn’t pass up the opportunity to show up Mrs. Riley.  Maybe she is right in thinking that I am haughty,  thought Arianna. However, she only considered this possibility for a moment before dismissing it.   Her sharp eyes were quick to pick up the warning signs. Mrs. Riley’s hands clenched into fists. Her eyes narrowed until they resembled slits. Instead of running away as she was always inclined to do, she braced herself for the beating to come. She knew that running away did not solve matter. It just made things worst. The first blow was sudden and it seemed that Mrs. Riley had poured all her energy into it. Arianna fell to the floor, completely unprepared for the next blow. Blow by blow fell on her. It was completely methodical. It wasn’t long before she lost consciousness.     Ironic , Arianna thought. She had always told herself that running away solved nothing. Yet she was doing it right now. As she walked through the streets of London, Arianna caught glimpses of urchins and rogues hiding in the shadows. The Ladies of the Night, however, where openly flaunting their wares on the streets. Arianna felt something else other than these common Londoners hiding in the shadow of night. A cold shiver ran down her back as she felt eyes on her. She quickened her pace, hoping to leave those hostile eyes behind her.  Funny , thought Arianna.  I can hear no following footsteps, yet I’m positive that someone is following me.  She cast a quick glance over her shoulder and saw nothing but shadows. Instead of reassuring her, however, the emptiness just frightened her more and she broke into a run. Even then she heard nothing. As she ran, her untidy mop of hair escaped the ribbon she had tied it in. A sudden sharp wind swept her hair across her face, slapping her cheeks painfully. Still she ran. Still she heard and saw nothing. All of a sudden, Arianna found herself face to face with a brick wall. She spun around and looked about her in search of a weapon she might use to defend herself. There was nothing lying on the ground she could use, but just as she gave up hope, her eyes light upon the boarded up windows of the two buildings forming the alley. Casting her bag aside, she reached up to the nearest window and attempted to pry loose a board. She was still hard at work when the figure appeared at the other end of the alley. It was wrapped in a voluminous coat, making it impossible to distinguish if it was a man or woman. Slowly, it made its way towards her. Arianna increased her efforts and at last one of the boards came loose. It was rotted through at one end, however, causing it to break away leaving a jagged edge.  All the better , thought Arianna.  At least now I have a potential weapon.  The figure laughed as she swung her ‘weapon’ in front of her. Arianna was rather taken aback. The stranger’s laugh wasn’t as harsh as she expected it to be. In fact, she found it sounded sweet and gentle. Yet she could sense the danger hidden behind that laugh. As the figure neared her, Arianna was able to distinguish its features. His skin was unnaturally pale, made even paler by his jet black hair, which was cut in the latest fashion. His dark eyes were cold and expressionless. “Why don’t you put that down before you hurt yourself?” His voice was heavily accented.  Definitely not English , thought Arianna. “Why don’t you back off and leave me alone?” retorted Arianna. “Why are you following me anyway?” The stranger’s lips curled in a feral-like smile. He simply said, “Your anger.” “What?” “You asked me why I was following you and I’m giving you my reason.” “You’re following me because I’m angry?” “Well, it’s not only that. It’s basically your hatred for everything that attracted me. It’s like a dark aura you’re emitting. It’s really irresistible to creatures of the dark like myself.” His answers intrigued her, yet she still held her ‘weapon’ in front of her, not loosening her grip for a second. “Creatures of the dark?” He smiled his feral-like smile again. He moved closer and as he did Arianna noticed his strange teeth. She gasped. The canines were at least an inch longer than any normal human’s. “No,” she breathed. She held onto a thin shred of hope, however. The ‘weapon’ she wielded was of wood and from what little she knew of vampires, wood could kill them. All she had to do was stake his heart. “Take one more step and I’ll take the liberty of introducing you to the sharp end of this stake here,” threatened Arianna sounding a lot braver than she felt. The vampire laughed again. “Now, really, do you think you can hurt me with that?” “I mean to kill you not hurt you.” The vampire looked amused. He stepped closer and Arianna swung out wildly at him. However, all the running and her efforts in obtaining her ‘weapon’ had weakened her considerably. He easily side-stepped her swing, but Arianna was determined not to be defeated so easily. Halfway through the swing, she changed directions, swinging her ‘weapon’ towards the vampire. He was taken aback, and was barely able to get out of the way this time. Arianna heard his shout of rage as her ‘weapon’ hit him. It hadn’t done much damage, however, and the amount of strength she had put in the swing threw her off balance. She fell and, before she could stop him, the vampire had kicked her ‘weapon’ out of reach. Pulling her up roughly by her hair, he hissed, “That was a really dumb thing to do. I should kill you for even trying that.” “Go ahead then,” Arianna challenged. The vampire’s angry expression changed to one of puzzlement and amusement. “Are you not afraid of dying?” “No, I’d welcome death. Go ahead, kill me.” He smiled that feral-like grin that Arianna hated, and that made her skin crawl, revealing his pointed teeth. “With pleasure.” Arianna felt his teeth pierce through her skin and felt the pain that accompanied it. He drank deeply. She felt her heartbeat weakening. Slower…slower…Before he had finished, Arianna was enveloped by darkness and felt nothing. 
     
    
</post>
<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      the reason for the creation of this blog is...well...i dunno really...but i've decided 'hey what better way to share my creative talents(?) with the world?' i've written a book...well in the process of writing it anyway...it's entitled 'Shadow Child' and is about a vampire and her struggle with herself...while at the same time she has to keep her identity a secret as there has been a series of killing in the city she's been living in which bear similarities to vampire attacks...i apologise before-hand to those who find fault with my work...i'm not entirely sure about what's real and what's not in the whole vampiric realm and all that...all the facts in the book i got from other books*sorry* hope you enjoy it^^ btw...i've also co-written a harry potter fanfic with a friend of mine. i'll try to find the link(you'd probably be wondering why i don't know it myself...it's because she's been posting all the work because technically i'm not suppose to be writing or even reading anything dealing with magic/vamps/demons/and so forth) you can check that out and i'd really like your honest opinion about my work. thanx.
     
    
</post>
<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       “Really, Katriana. I never figured you for a coward.” “I am not a coward! I just don’t feel right about this.” Kristopher shook his head and smiled that feral-like smile she had come to love. He wrapped a cold arm around her waist, drawing her close. She giggled like a school girl. “Come on, love. Can’t you smell him? All that blood flowing through his throbbing veins? It’s driving me wild!” Katriana didn’t giggle this time. She peered out of the dark alley and into the almost deserted street. It was one hour before dawn and she and Kristopher were out hunting. The boy was still there. She frowned. “Why are you hesitating, love? It isn’t like you. Normally you’re the first one to spot our dinner.” “Can’t you feel it?” “Feel what?” “The…wrongness.” “Wrongness?” Kristopher laughed. “My Dear, I can’t sense anything. Unless, of course, your psychic senses have suddenly far exceeded mine.” “Don’t laugh, luv.” Then. “You really don’t sense anything?” “No.” Katriana eyed the boy. Even from this distance, her sharpened senses could hear his heart beating and smell the sweet, sweet blood flowing through his veins.  Well, a girl’s gotta eat.  “Right, then. Let’s go.” Kristopher rubbed his hands together eagerly. Katriana smiled. His excitement was infectious. They stuck to the shadows and made their way towards the boy. He didn’t sense their presence until it was too late. Kristopher blocked all means of escape. Katriana approached the boy from behind.  “What the – “ Before he could turn around, Katriana had pulled his head to the side exposing his neck. She was surprised that he barely struggled as she sank her teeth into him…   Arianna woke up with a start, gasping, the bed sheets thrown off her bed and sweat covering her body. Melissa was in the only other bed in the room, sound asleep. She swung her legs off the bed and made her way to the bathroom that separated their room from Celine’s and Hannah’s. Splashing cold water onto her face to fully wake her up, she peered into the mirror; a pale, drawn face peered back. Her dreams had been haunting her for some time now. Memories of times she would much rather forget. Returning to her room, she pulled a dressing robe around the tank top and shorts that passed for her pajamas and noticed that it was just before dawn.  Just like in my dream , she thought.  Maybe I should go hunting before everyone wakes up .  She checked to make sure that Melissa was still asleep. Then reached out with what little psychic energy she had to check if everyone else was asleep as well. Not surprisingly, she couldn’t sense Damion.  Whatever. I’m hungry. I’ll just make sure I hunt far away enough from here so no one gets any nasty surprises . Silently, she opened the sliding doors in the bedroom that led out onto a balcony that connected almost all the upstairs rooms. Silently, sliding the door shut again, she breathed in the night air, not that she really needed it, and smiled a satisfied smile. She fingered the thin silver ring on the third finger of her left hand. It had a tiny blue stone set in the middle and on the inside, closest to her skin, were engraved the Latin words that formed the spell that activated the stone which prevented her from bursting into flames at the touch of sunlight. It brought back memories, some pleasurable, some she wanted to suppress.  Turning to face the horizon, she screwed up her face.  I’d better leave now before the sun rises . Taking another deep breath, she cleared her mind and concentrated on her sharpened senses. Picking up the scent of the other seven teens in the house she tried ignoring them in search for prey that she could actually feed off. It wasn’t long before she picked up the scent of a large buck, no more than three miles north-east of her. Its scent was driving her wild. She felt her canines enlarging; her tongue darted out to moisten her lips.  “Bloody ‘ell”, she muttered, reverting to her gutter English. “You’d reckon Aah haven’t eaten for ages”. Then back to the accent she had cultivated over the years since she moved to America. “So not good. I just fed this afternoon. Oh man, if it goes on like this, I might not be able to stop myself from feeding off my friends.” “God,” she moaned. “So not good.”  Melissa was startled awake by the fluttering of wings. Rolling over in bed, her body protesting her exhaustion, she tried to focus her eyes out of the window. She was surprised to see a colony of tiny bats, no larger than sparrows, flying past.  Weird , she thought before drifting off to sleep again. When she woke up five hours later, she had already forgotten about the bats. Arianna was already up. She and Josh were ransacking the kitchen, putting together breakfast for everyone else. “How’s pancakes sound?” hollered Josh so that everyone could hear him. From all over the house the others called back their satisfaction at his choice for breakfast. “Sounds great,” she said. Arianna smiled. “Hey, sleepy head.” “Hey, A.J. How long have you been up?” “Ages. You want anything with your pancakes?” “Honey, if you can find any.” “No probs. Coffee’d do you?” “Sure.” Everyone was drawn to the kitchen by the delicious aromas it emitted. Together, Josh and Arianna had already made three stacks of pancakes, more than enough to feed all of them. They had also laid the table, setting out pots of honey, bottles of maple syrup, jars of blueberry jam and steaming pots of coffee. “Yum,” said Hannah. “This looks delicious.” “I totally second that,” said Danny. It didn’t take them long to completely demolish the meal set out for them. Melissa noticed that Arianna wasn't eating much. She was half-heartedly pushing her pancake around her plate. But she was downing several cups of coffee. Melissa decided that it was best not to confront Arianna about it. After all, there could be a simple explanation for her behaviour. She could just not be hungry. “So, what are we doing today?” asked Josh, eager to start enjoying himself, even though he still had a sinking feeling that maybe being isolated up in the mountains wasn’t such a good idea after all. “There’s a waterfall somewhere nearby,” said Hannah. “Really secluded. And romantic.” “I’m beginning to really like this vacation,” murmured Danny, cuddling up to his girlfriend. Celine cast a sly glance towards Damion who seemed to not see it. Arianna made an exaggerated motion of rolling her eyes.  “Whatever, you guys,” she said. Then added, as she got up, “Who’s gonna help me do the dishes?” The kitchen emptied amazingly fast. Arianna wasn’t surprised. She was surprised that Josh had opted to stay behind though.  “I’ll give you a hand.” Arianna smiled. “Thanks.”  They chilled out for an hour before their little excursion to the waterfall. Melissa finally persuaded Arianna to come along with them, with a little help from Josh. “Come on, A.J., if you don’t come, we’ll have to suffer Celine flirting with Damion the entire time.” “And how does my accompanying you make it any better, Josh.” “Well, for one thing, you’d make witnessing the event less painful,” he said with a smile. Arianna wore her bikini under a tank top and board shorts but she doubted that she would actually be doing any swimming. She had also brought along her sketch book. Hannah was right. The waterfall really was secluded – the perfect romantic hide-away. She and Danny immediately shed their clothes and headed for the water. They had somehow gotten behind the waterfall and could be clearly seen necking each other. Celine abandoned her clothes as well, revealing a  very  revealing bikini, if it could even be called that. Matt’s jaw dropped, and it pretty much stayed that way for the next couple of hours. It didn’t seem to have any effect on its intended victim though. Damion made his way to a peaceful spot under a tree and sat watching everyone. Melissa and Josh cast each other a look, before tearing off like maniacs towards the falls. They cannon-balled in together and came up sputtering and laughing. Arianna had found herself a nice, quiet spot up in a tree and was observing everyone from there. Every now and then, her gaze would stray towards Damion, her mind still shooting questions about him.  He practically reeks of danger. Can’t anyone else sense that?  She spaced out for a while and therefore was shocked to find him meeting her gaze. She turned away quickly, but not before she saw him smiling.  It wasn’t long before Josh got bored with cannon balls and started looking around for Arianna. “Come on down from that tree. It’s a lot more fun in the water.” “I’ll just take your word for it.” “Come on, A.J.,” joined in Melissa. “You’ve gotta loosen up every now and then.” Arianna smiled, then flipped open her sketch book, ignoring them. “This just won’t do,” muttered Josh. He shot Damion a conspiratorial look then waded closer to where he was sitting. “Wanna give me a hand?” Damion followed Josh’s glance to Arianna. He smiled. “Sure.” Arianna heard someone calling her name. Standing just below her was Josh. “Sure you don’t wanna join us?” “Sure I’m sure.” “Even if I get down on my knees and start begging?” Arianna laughed. “Even as amusing as that would be, I’m still not coming down, Josh.” It was then that her senses started warning bells ringing in her head. She turned around. Damion had somehow climbed the tree without her knowing and was now standing right behind her. He grinned.  “Wha-?” Before she could stop him, Damion gave her a hard push that sent her falling off the tree and into the pool below. She surfaced sputtering and letting loose a string of curses that would have impressed any soldier. Josh was standing by the edge of the water, laughing his head off. Damion was still up in the tree, laughing as well. Then it clicked. They had been working together. While Josh distracted her, Damion came up from behind. “Ha ha, very funny guys,” she muttered. “Hey, Arianna! You look just like a drowned rat!” said Damion before bursting into laughter once more. “Yeah, no thanks to you!” She waded over to where Josh was and extended an arm. “Help me up, will you?” Josh wiped away a tear, bent double with laughter. Once he had regained his breath he said, “Yeah, sure thing, A.J.” But as soon as he had his hand in hers, he found himself off his feet and falling into the pool. He surfaced beside Arianna who was now laughing. So was Melissa. Damion was still up in the tree, but not for long. He soon lost his balance and came plummeting into the water as well. He came up gasping with a look of surprise on his face. This sent them into another fit of laughter. Danny and Hannah didn’t notice them, still lost in their paradise behind the falls. Matt was ogling at Celine – again – and Celine was positively glowering. She swam towards Damion and, linking her arm in his, pulled him away from Arianna and the others, and into deeper water. “What’s her problem?” muttered Josh. “Leave her alone,” said Melissa, defending her friend. “Yeah,” agreed Arianna and when they gave her puzzled looks, she added with a smile, “This is going to be interesting.” Josh shared her smile. Melissa rolled her eyes. “You two really need to grow up, you know?” “Yeah,” sighed Arianna, still smiling, “I know.”  “So how’re you enjoying this vacation so far?” simpered Celine. “Um…yeah, it’s great. Thanks for inviting me.” “You know…if you ever want some privacy…Hannah’s almost never around…I basically have the bedroom all to myself.” Celine was batting her eyes flirtatiously. It still didn’t seem to have much effect on Damion. “Hmm? Oh…um…thanks,” said Damion rather absent-mindedly. Celine fumed. It wasn’t usually she that had to work to get a guy’s attention. They were normally falling over themselves to try to impress her. She turned to look in the direction he was looking. She was furious to see that Arianna was who he was looking at. Arianna felt several pairs of eyes on her. She turned to see both Damion and Celine looking her way.   Weird , she thought.  Well, I guess this means Celine hasn’t been having much luck . She smirked.  “I wonder when those two last came up for air,” mused Josh. Arianna shot him a puzzled look until she realized that he was talking about the couple behind the waterfall, still necking each other like there was no tomorrow. “Do you think they’d notice if we left?” asked Melissa, though the question was posed more like a rhetorical one than an actual question. “I seriously doubt it,” said Arianna answering the question anyway. “I’m getting out.” Josh placed a hand on her arm to stop her. His face immediately dawned on a worried look. “God, you’re freezing cold!” Arianna smiled. “I don’t feel that cold. Maybe it’s just the water. Anyway, I’m going back to my nice little spot up in the tree.” “You sure you’re all right?” Josh still had that worried look in his face. Arianna knew what he was thinking; that maybe it was his fault for convincing Damion to push her off that tree, that if he didn’t she wouldn’t be so cold, and desperately hoping that she wouldn’t get sick.  If only you knew , thought Arianna.  For some weird reason, I’m really contemplating telling you the truth. But what if I did? Would you still view me in the same light, or run away screaming bloody murder?  “I’m fine. But thanks for being so concerned. That’s so sweet.” Then Arianna did what she had never thought she would do again. She kissed Josh tenderly on the lips. Josh was completely shocked by this. But before he had time to pull himself together and react to her kiss, she had already pulled away. Arianna registered his look of surprise mixed with ecstasy and smiled.  That was nice. I don’t even remember when I last kissed a living, breathing human. It’s so different from Kristopher’s cold, harsh kisses. Hmm…I could get used to this . She got out of the water and climbed up her tree again. Her sketch book was right where she had left it. Pulling out the pencil she had slipped into the ring binding, she proceeded to sketch what had been on her mind since she first saw Damion. Arianna got so engrossed with her work that she didn’t hear Josh when he called to her. “Arianna!” It took him a couple of tries, but after calling out the fifth time, he finally got her attention. “What?” “We’re heading back for lunch. You coming?” “In a minute. You guys head back without me. I’ll catch up.” Josh nodded. Arianna looked around for Melissa and found her at the edge of the waterfall, trying to get Danny and Hannah’s attention. She finally gave up. Arianna smiled. She got back to her sketch as everyone, with the exception of the necking duo, headed back. It was while she was flipping through her sketch book, searching for a reference sketch that she wanted, that she noticed that something was wrong. Someone had been into her sketch book recently. The charcoal sketch of the young girl that Mr. Tarantino had wanted to showcase was gone. 
     
    
</post>
<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I dedicated the next chapter of 'Shadow Child' to Wonderer (um...i'm not sure about your name...but I think it's David...sorry if I got it wrong), for thinking that my story's great. Thank you!
     
    
</post>
<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      glad u liked wat i wrote...yeah i'll send u a copy of it when i've finished...i've even planned a sequel 4 this 1...probably gonna make it in2 1 of those three part type of things...but not d annoyinly frustratin type where u hav 2 read all 3 books 2 get d story...i'm gonna make it so tht ne1 can just pick it up n get d story even if they've never read d otha 1s...*sigh* tht's my dream 4 d moment... btw...who r u? r u d same wonderer fr xanga?
     
    
</post>
<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The last few days passed in a blur, and three more bodies were found, and before anyone knew, it was the last day of school before summer vacation. All of them were finding it increasingly hard to concentrate on anything. Hannah had already made all the arrangements and it was decided that they would take Josh’s van there. Well, most of them anyway. Arianna had been determined to ride her bike there. “Three more hours and we’ll be outta here,” said Josh. “I don’t think I can wait that long. I just wanna get away from here. The further we are, the less the chance that we’re the next ones to get mauled.” Melissa smiled. “Yeah, but then it’d be a couple more hours on the road, and I’m not sure I can last that long in the back of your van, Josh.” Josh’s van was his pride and joy. Officially it belonged to  Evocation , but none of the band members had any use for it except to transport their gear to each gig. Josh unofficially claimed it as his own. “The only problem with this vacation,” said Josh, “is that we’d be stuck with both Celine and A.J.” “At least A.J.’s taking her own ride. We won’t have to put up with the two of them squabbling all the way there.” The remaining three hours seemed to drag on forever, but finally the bell rang. School was out for the summer. They met up in the parking lot and Danny took a head count. “Hey, where’s A.J. and Celine?”  “Celine told me she’d be here. Do you think something’s happened to her?” This was from Matt who was looking worried and anxious. Josh rolled his eyes. “Puh-lease, Matt. Just because they’re late doesn’t mean it’s the end of the world. Grow up! Anyway, it’s not like Celine’s gonna pay much attention to you even when she does finally arrive.” Melissa glared at her childhood best friend and tried not to let the pity she felt for Matt show on her face.  Where are they?   Arianna followed Celine out of the Art Department. Arianna had an urgent last minute meeting with one of the faculty members concerning the possibility of one of her sketches being displayed in the Art Festival the next semester. Arianna was against it, but Mr. Tarantino, head of the Art Department, had been adamant about having her work on display. She had run into Celine, who was just emerging from the dark room. As soon as they had seen each other, Celine immediately launched into another argument which Arianna, try as she might, eventually got drawn into. They were still in a heated argument as they turned the corner, Arianna silently contemplating sinking her teeth into Celine’s exposed neck, and did not see him. “I’m so sorry,” he said. The sketch pad Arianna had been carrying fell out of her hands, and her sketches were strewn all over the floor.  “Why don’t you watch where you’re going, freak?” This was from Celine, who wasn’t lifting a finger to help Arianna retrieve her sketches. If looks could kill, Celine would have been dead. “Are you all right, Damion?” “Yeah, I’m so sorry Arianna. Have I got back all your sketches?” Damion had scrambled to help Arianna retrieve her fallen artwork despite her protests.  “Yeah, it’s all here. Thanks.” “Here’s another. Wow! Did you do this?” Damion was holding the piece that Arianna had just argued over with Mr. Tarantino. It was a charcoal sketch of a young naked girl, with bat wings sprouting from her shoulders, curled in a fetal position and covered in blood that poured from the slashes across her neck and down her arms. Arianna looked from the sketch to Damion.  He sees something. But what?  “Yeah, I drew it. Can I have it back now?” She held out her hand to take back her sketch but Damion was too engrossed with it, either ignoring or not even registering her outstretched hand.  There’s something about him. What does he see? Why is he so affected by it?  Arianna thought she saw a hint of emotion in his eyes but when she looked again it was gone.  Celine had been standing nearby the entire time. By now she was tired of Damion paying so much attention to Arianna. She snatched the sketch out of his hands and pressed it into Arianna’s.  “Here, take your stupid drawing back.” She turned her attention back to Damion who had just seemed to realize that he no longer held the sketch in his hands. “So, Damion, do you have anything planned for the summer?” “Hmm…um…no, not really.” “Oh…’cause, you know, I was just wondering, that is if you’re not doing anything, like me and my friends are going up to the mountains. A girlfriend has a cottage up there. Do you wanna come?” “Didn’t you already ask him, Celine?” said Arianna innocently. Celine glared at her. “Let’s not waste anymore of his time. Besides, the others would be waiting for us.” She placed her loose sketches between the pages of her sketch pad and stuffed it into her bag. As she started to walk away, Damion said, “Sure, I’d love to come. That is, if it’s all right with Arianna and the rest of your friends.” Arianna whirled around and narrowed her eyes. Something about Damion Grant sent alarm bells ringing in her head, but she couldn’t quite place it. All she knew was that having Damion tag along would not be a good idea. But Celine was already assuring him that he was welcome to join them. Arianna kept her mouth shut, despite the burning urge to snap at Celine, or at least permanently silence her. “Whatever,” she muttered.  This is not good.   “Look, here they come,” said Hannah. “About time,” grumbled Danny. “Who’s that with them?” asked Matt. “Oh no,” groaned Josh. “She must have convinced super-hunk to come after all.” Arianna shrugged the duffel bag she had collected from her locker off her shoulders. She tossed it to Josh. “Is this all you’re bringing?” he asked, with a raised eyebrow. “Hey, I’m not Celine,” was all she said. Celine scowled. “Hi, I’m Damion Grant.” He held out his hand for each of them to shake. “Yeah, we know,” said Melissa as she shook his hand. “You’ve become like an instant celebrity here. So, did Celine finally convince you to come or something.” “Something like that.” “We’ve gotta stop by Damion’s place so he can get his stuff,” said Celine, latching herself onto Damion. Melissa sneaked a glance at Matt to see how he would react. Not surprisingly, he didn’t seem to be too bothered. He was just ogling at Celine.  “You guys don’t mind, do you?”  He seems to be really sincere about making sure he’s got our approval , thought Melissa.  He must feel really awkward. Really, it’s just like Celine to pull something like this . “Of course not,” assured Melissa. “We don’t mind, do we?” She had targeted this question mostly towards Josh who she knew had taken an instant disliking to Damion. Everyone gave their assent. “We better get going then,” said Arianna, who had already gotten onto her bike and was pulling on her helmet. “Sure you know how to get there?” asked Josh. She nodded before revving up her engine and thundering out of the parking lot. “Right,” said Danny. “We might as well get going. Where do you live, Damion?”   This just does not feel right . Arianna thought that she should have felt exhilarated as the wind whipped across her face, but was troubled by thoughts of Damion.  There’s something about him. But what? Why can’t I sense anything? Maybe I’m running low on psychic juice. Nah…that’s not it. Still, something’s definitely not right…  She noticed a turning off the road that lead to a nearby woodland.  Hmm…time for a little snack…   The ‘cottage’ turned out to be a two storey hide-away with all the modern facilities. There was even a heated pool out back. “Wow!” exclaimed Melissa. “There’re four rooms; two upstairs and two down here,” said Hannah. “Right, so the girls will have the rooms upstairs and you guys bunk down here,” said Melissa. “Now hold on a mo,” protested Danny. “No, Melissa’s right,” agreed Celine. “Hannah and I’ll bunk together.” Melissa shot Celine a funny look. She had expected her to be on Danny’s side. Danny looked around for support. Josh agreed with Melissa, he knew better than to disagree, and Matt was putty in Celine’s hands, he agreed with her decision to bunk with Hannah. Danny turned to Damion. “Come on, man. Surely you don’t agree with this?” “I’d rather not get involved,” said Damion. “Whatever,” Danny muttered. Just then, the familiar Yamaha thundered up next to Josh’s van. “Hey, A.J.,” greeted Josh. “Hey, yourself. What’s everyone standing out around here for?” “We were just assigning rooms,” said Melissa. “You’re bunking with me.” Arianna shrugged.  “The guys can figure out their sleeping arrangements themselves,” said Celine. “Come on, Hannah.” Hannah followed her inside. Danny and Matt followed them, carrying the girl’s bags. “You know what,” said Josh to no one in particular.  Arianna turned to face him. “What?” “Somehow, this whole set up reminds me of a horror movie. You know? Like a group of teens up alone in the mountains and then they get killed off one by one.” “Really, Josh, do you have to be that morbid,” said Melissa. “Enjoy this vacation, ‘k? Or at least let everyone else enjoy it.” Josh smiled and gave Melissa a mock salute. “Yes, Ma’am.” “Come on, A.J.” Arianna followed Melissa inside. Damion turned to Josh. “Looks like we’ll be bunking together. You don’t mind, do you?” “Not at all. Come on, let’s go inside.” 
     
    
</post>
<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      anyone know a quick and easy way to make some money? i'm desperate here...k maybe not that desperate but i've gotta find me a job...think of sending my story to a publisist or something...maybe i'll make some cash that way...by the way april...my name's matilda...but my close friends all call me tilz...question: are you fighting against the elementalists? just wanna know...
     
    
</post>
<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Arianna stared at her sketch book in disbelief.     Who in the world would steal my sketches? It’s not like they are valuable or anything. Unless…  Arianna fumed.    How dare he? This is invasion of privacy it is. When I get back, I’m gonna give him a piece of my mind at the very least.  She slammed shut her sketch book and scrambled down the tree. Danny and Hannah had just seemed to realize that everyone else was gone. They spotted Arianna and called out to her. “Hey, A.J.! Where’s everybody?” “They went back for lunch. I’m heading back now. See you two love birds later.” Arianna found Damion on the balcony. She avoided the kitchen as she knew that either Melissa or Josh would insist she ate something and she really didn’t have the time, or the patience, to deal with them now. “Where is it?” she demanded. “Where’s what?” replied Damion, his voice a lazy drawl. “My sketch, that’s what. I know you have it.” “Look, I have no idea what you’re talking about. You probably misplaced it or something.” Arianna ran a hand through her hair and slowly counted to ten, trying her best to curb her anger. “Look, Damion. You can keep the sketch, ‘k? All I want to know is why you took it. And don’t try denying it ‘cause I know you did.” Damion shrugged. “It’s a cool pic.” “So, do you always just take what you want?” “Yeah.” Arianna lashed out at him, or rather the reclining chair he was sitting on. She kicked it so hard that Damion was practically thrown off it. “What the hell was that for?” Arianna left Damion indignantly brushing himself off and stomped up to her room. Melissa, Celine and Josh came out to see what the commotion was all about. Celine let out a little gasp and rushed to Damion’s side. “That girl seriously needs some anger management sessions,” said Damion, this time letting Celine mother over him. Celine nodded her agreement and strangely enough, this brought to Melissa’s mind the idea of roles being changed. Celine’s behaviour reminded her so much of Matt’s behaviour when he was around Celine.  So, the tables have been turned , thought Melissa.  Poor Celine.  The look on Josh’s face, though, told her that her best friend was immensely enjoying this scenario. She punched him on the shoulder and frowned at him when he gave her a questioning glance. All right, he mouthed. Melissa rolled her eyes. She doubted that Josh would be able to act the grown-up for more than ten minutes. But her mind soon turned to more worrying matters.    What’s wrong with Arianna?  Damion was still complaining about Arianna and Celine was still sympathizing with him (“I always knew that she wasn’t all there, you know what I mean?”) when a piercing scream brought them all to attention.  Arianna stood in the shower, fully clothed, letting the icy cold water cascade down her lifeless body. Resting her head on the cold tiles that lined the shower, she let her mind assess the situation.    Okay, things are just getting weird. I’d have given Damion the sketch if he’d just ask. I wonder why he wants it anyway. Surely he doesn’t know what I had meant to represent with that picture. After all, no one’s figured it out yet. They just think it’s another teenage angst thing. And then there’s that annoying fact that I can’t sense a thing about him. That’s driving me crazy!  Arianna screamed in frustration, not caring what the others might think about that. Barely a minute later, Josh burst through the door. “Arianna! Are you all right?” She looked up at him, her soaking hair plastering itself onto her face, and smiled. Josh was taken aback, and worried. In that smile he had seen more than he wanted to see; pain, grief, misery, anger, longing and turmoil. She smiled again. “I’m fine. Really,” she added when she saw the look on his face. Behind him she saw Melissa, Matt, Damion and Celine, the first three looking at her with similar expressions to the one that Josh was wearing just a moment ago. Celine just looked pissed. She smiled again. “Oh, stop being such a drama queen, Jacobs!” hissed Celine. “No, I’ll just leave that position for you to fill, Baxter,” said Arianna. Before Celine could come up with a bitter retort, the air was pierced by another blood curdling scream. “Not again,” moaned Celine as everyone pushed pass her to get outside. Arianna was the first to arrive on the scene, still soaking wet and leaving behind her a trail that the others could easily follow, if they didn’t mind making their way through a thicket. “What the hell is going on?” asked Damion appearing behind Arianna, but stopped short at the sight that greeted them. A dead buck lay before them, its throat ripped open. Danny and Hannah stood on the other side of the carcass, Hannah sobbing into Danny’s shoulder while the look on his face clearly told them that he was trying hard not to be sick. The others had caught up with them. On seeing the carcass, which had already begun reeking, Matt headed off deeper into the thicket where he was clearly heard throwing up. Melissa went to check if he was all right. Celine cowered against Damion. Josh just stared disbelievingly at the dead buck. “It’s probably just wolves or some other wild animal,” he finally said. “No, it’s not,” whimpered Celine. “Don’t you think that if it were wolves they would have eaten the buck as well, not just killed it? There isn’t a mark on it other than at its throat.” Matt reappeared then, only to be sick again. Arianna cautiously walked over to Danny and Hannah, taking care not to touch the carcass. Placing a reassuring arm around the both of them, she led them to the others. Melissa smiled. It wasn’t often that she saw her friend showing any sign of affection or of caring. “Ugh!” moaned Matt bringing his hand up to his mouth. “I think I’m gonna be sick, again.” Celine rolled her eyes. Josh glared at her. “I’ll bring him back, along with these two. Come on, Danny, Hannah.” While Josh led the three away, Damion extricated himself from Celine’s grip and slowly approached the carcass. “Damion!” exclaimed Celine. He ignored her. “We should bury the body or something,” said Melissa, speaking for the first time since they found the carcass. “I don’t like the idea of something killing so near the house. And we don’t want the body to attract more wild animals.” “Melissa’s right,” said Arianna. “Why don’t you take Celine back? Damion and I can handle this.” “Hey! Wait a minute! I’m not leaving him here alone with her!” protested Celine. “If you’re going to stay, you’ll have to give us a hand with disposing this carcass,” said Arianna. Celine blanched. “Whatever. Just don’t you dare make a move on my man.” Arianna rolled her eyes. “Wouldn’t dream of it.”  Man! She’s fallen hard. What about Matt, you two-faced bitch? You’re acting like Damion’s already proposed or something . “You can go back with the girls, you know,” said Damion after the Melissa and Celine had left. “I can handle this myself.” “Stop patronizing me. I’m not one of those girls who faint every time they break a nail. I can handle this.” Damion shrugged. “Whatever.” “Yeah, whatever.” “Um…you don’t happen to have a spade or a shovel with you, do you?” “You know what, Grant? Why don’t you stop being such an ass and do something useful? Like getting those shovels and stop asking stupid questions.” “Hey, lay off, Jacobs. Why is it that every time I do or say something, you bite my head off?” “’Cause you’re just asking for it, that’s why.” Arianna glared at him. Damion glared back. Just then Melissa appeared, bearing two shovels in her arms. She looked from one of them to the other. “Um…hope I’m not interrupting anything. Just thought you guys might find it easier to get rid of that thing if you had some shovels. Right, I think I’ll be going now.” She propped the shovels up against a tree and left as quickly as possible. Arianna’s eyes flickered from Damion to the shovels then back to Damion again. “What are you standing around for? Pass me a shovel and let’s get this over with,” growled Damion. Arianna tossed him a shovel, still not taking her eyes off him or turning her back on him. “You know what,” said Damion as they set to digging the hole to bury the carcass in, “you’ve got some serious trust issues. You haven’t taken your eyes off me or turned your back on me the entire time we’ve been here.” Damion smirked. “Or that could just be because you find me so damn attractive.” “In your dreams, Grant,” growled Arianna. “Keep digging or I’ll smash the back of your skull in with this shovel.” “Ok, ok, sheesh! You really need to lighten up, Jacobs.” “Keep digging, Grant. I want this hole to be at least six feet deep.” They spent the next hour in silence, concentrating on completing the task they had set themselves. Finally, Arianna was satisfied with the depth of the hole. “Let’s get this over with.” Dragging themselves out of the hole, they approached the carcass, which had begun to attract a few crows. Damion shooed them away, muttering curses under his breath. As they lifted the reeking body, its head flopped off, landing at their feet and splattering them with blood. Damion grimaced. Arianna shot him a withering look, as if daring him to bail on her. Still keeping a hold on the carcass, Arianna kicked the head into the hole. “Hey, have some respect for the dead,” protested Damion. “Don’t worry I have a lot of respect for the dead. But that head was kinda in our way. If I didn’t move it, you would have probably tripped and fallen head-first into that grave. I don’t want to have to tend to your broken neck in addition to having to bury this myself.” “Gee, I didn’t know you cared.” “Whatever.” Between the two of them, they made quick work of burying the carcass. Fifteen minutes later, leaning against his shovel, Damion wiped his sweaty forehead with his sleeve. “You know, I thought that it would have taken longer to get this job done. That went a lot faster than I thought it would’ve.” “Let’s just get back. I need a bath.” “Yeah, ditto. I’ve got to get this blood off me before I do a Matt imitation.” “Hey, it’s not the guy’s fault if he can’t hold his lunch down at the sight of a dead body. Leave him alone.” Damion smiled. “I knew it! You’re not an uptight bitch after all, Arianna. You do have a soft side!” Arianna rolled her eyes, but couldn’t help smiling at what he said. “Whatever.”   There’s something here. Only I can’t tell what. I can sense it yet at the same time…not. That buck had too much blood in it to be the one I killed this morning. Plus I know I hunted a lot further away from here. Something’s here. Something’s hunting. And I doubt it’s going to stop at just big game. We’re next .  When they got back to the house, they found Josh armed with a hunting rifle. Matt held a shotgun in his unsteady hands. “Um, how ‘bout I take that, huh?” asked Damion with a worried look on his face. Matt handed over his weapon without a word. “Where’d you find these?” asked Arianna. “Hannah’s folks have a gun safe in the basement,” replied Josh. “While you were gone, we decided that it would be best if we had some sort of protection against whatever’s out there. Even if it’s just a bunch of wild animals.” “Better safe than sorry,” said Danny with a protective hold around Hannah. “They’ve got a point,” admitted Melissa. “I for one want some type of protection against whatever’s out there.” “So much for this vacation,” mumbled Josh as he loaded his rifle. “How ‘bout we just pack up and leave?” suggested Arianna. “No! We shouldn’t let something as trivial as this ruin our summer,” protested Danny. “Oh! This is trivial?” retorted Arianna. “Tell me, Fernandez, when will it become serious? When one of us dies?” “Chill, A.J.,” said Matt. “Besides, it might just have been wild animals. You’re talking as if it were some psycho killer or something.” “Yeah, freak,” said Celine, slowly advancing towards Arianna. “What do you know ‘bout this?” She turned to face everyone else. “You know what I think?” “Ugh, we’re gonna be here for ages,” moaned Josh. Celine ignored him. “I think that the freak did it.” She raised her hands to silence the protest that followed her statement. “It would be just like her to do something like that. Besides, I don’t see her denying it.” “Well, she’s not admitting it either,” challenged Danny. “Yeah, I don’t think A.J.’d do something like that,” said Hannah. “Oh, what do you know, Ackermann?” sneered Celine. “If I were you, and thank God I’m not, after an accusation like that, I wouldn’t turn my back on me,” said Arianna. Celine quickly spun around to face her. Arianna laughed. “See? She’s a lunatic! We’d all be better off if she were dead!” “Now who’s the one obsessed with killing?” said Arianna, her voice totally calm. Josh laughed. “She’s got you there, Celine. You’re accusing her, but how do we know that you’re not the actual killer? Who knows, you might have convinced us to murder A.J. then killed us all in our sleep!” Matt gave a nervous chuckle. “Of course she’s not a psychotic killer,” he said. Then as an after thought, “Are you?” “Don’t be stupid, Matt! Of course I’m not!” “Quit it! All of you!” commanded Damion. “Hey! Stop ordering us around!” growled Melissa. “Yeah, who died and made you king?” hissed Celine. Everyone fell silent. Celine’s facial expression morphed into one of complete horror as she realized what she said. “Gawd!” Damion finally said. “I think we all just better stick around here for the time being,” said Josh. “And no one leaves the house unaccompanied.” “Or armed,” added Arianna. “We should have like someone to stand guard at night or something,” said Melissa. “We’ll do that in shifts,” said Josh. “Each shift will have two people. There’s safety in numbers.” “Right,” agreed Arianna. “Damion and I’ll – “ “Wait a minute! I don’t think anyone’s safe with you,” said Celine. “If Damion’s gonna be paired up with someone, it’s gonna be me.” “Ladies! There’s plenty of me to go around.” “Ugh! You’re welcome to him, Celine.” “Aw, A.J., that hurt.” “Whatever, Damion.” “Quit it, you two,” ordered Josh. “’K here’s how it’s gonna be. Celine, you’re with Damion. Danny…Hannah. Arianna…Matt. And I’ll pair up with Melissa. That arrangement okay with all of you?” Everyone more or less nodded their agreement. “And that’ll be order in which we take our shifts. I think two hours each shift’s enough, don’t you think?” Everyone nodded again. As they dispersed, Melissa stayed behind to talk to Josh. “That was smart, pairing the weak with the strong,” she observed. Josh began protesting. “That’s not true…it’s not you’re weak…I just…” Melissa laughed. “It’s okay, Josh. I’m not offended or anything. Besides, I know I’m not exactly like Arianna or anything. She can take care of herself. Good job pairing her with Matt, by the way. She’ll be able to handle him. I just wanted to ask if you could show me how to use that thing,” said Melissa, pointing to the rifle he had laid across his lap. “Sure. Maybe we should make sure every one of us knows how to fire a gun.” “That’s a great idea. We won’t want Matt accidentally killing himself or something.” They smiled. “Come on. Let’s get the others together and have a shooting practice or something. Maybe it’ll scare whatever’s out there away.”  “Ouch! You step on my foot one more time, Matt, and I swear I’ll kill you myself,” hissed Arianna. “Sorry. I can’t see anything in this dark.” It was three am in the morning and they had been on guard duty for an hour already. Being on duty with Matt was as bad as Arianna had thought it’d be. For the first thirty minutes. He wasn’t as much a coward as she had originally thought him to be. For one thing, she had expected him to be whimpering the entire time, or complaining about something stupid, like the dark. Instead, he was putting on a brave front, though she could smell his fear. It disgusted her, yet at the same time she respected him for trying to overcome his fear. Plus he had amazingly sharp hearing. Though the only drawback of that was that every time he heard a twig snap, he’d move a step closer to Arianna, most of the time ending up stepping on her foot. “So,” said Matt after a long uncomfortable silence. “Why’re you always acting the tough kid? I know you aren’t all that bad really.” “Who says I ain’t?” Matt kept silent. Arianna sighed. “It’s not an act. I have to be tough, stand up for myself. ‘Cause no one’s gonna do that for me. Okay? You should do the same. Stop letting everyone push you around.” “I do not!” This time the silence came from Arianna. “It’s just…” “Never mind, Matt. I know you’ll do something about it sooner or later. I just hope it’s sooner.” Even in the dark, Arianna’s sharp eyes saw his smile. She smiled back, although she knew he would probably not be able to see a thing in the damned, impenetrable darkness of the night. “Um…A.J.?” “Yeah?” “Is that what I think it is?” he asked, his voice quivering. Arianna looked to what he was pointing at. Not more than a few paces away was a tree, one side of its thick trunk splattered with blood. She was surprised that he had even spotted that. “It’s blood isn’t it?” Arianna nodded gravely, her hunger aroused just by the sight of it. She bit down hard on her bottom lip instead, sucking on the bloody mess, hoping that she’d be able to curb her hunger. “’K, I think I see a blood trail. We should follow it.” Matt took a step back, this time not bothering to mask the fear on his face. “Come on, Matt. I need your help, okay?” Finally he nodded slowly. Arianna felt sicker and sicker with each step. The trail was leading to the back of the house. Matt realized this too. This time he began whimpering but she didn’t hold it against him. If she wasn’t what she was, and hadn’t seen some of the things she’d seen, she’d be just as frightened. There, lying by the side of the pool, was a body. Human.  
     
    
</post>
<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      *sniff sniff* m i losin readers or sth? 1st micah goes away then david (or r u still here but just as a silent reader?) i dun know if emiko's been here yet...has my writin suddenly gone down d tubes or sth? d rents rn't happy bout me postin my writin here(then again, when were they eva happy bout wat i do?) i havn't told them wat i'm writin bout yet(they're not so hot on vampyrs,witches, daemons, necromancers n all tht kinda stuff) i wonder wat they'd do if they found out? newaz...should i continue postin this? ne1? helloooooo...
     
    
</post>
</Blog>