<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well today was a rugby practice - good an plenty! Semi Finals tomorrow:D   GO VIKES!
    
</post>
<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Quote of the Day   " it's like kryslte's dog; sometimes cute, but just cut it off!!!"  holy crap too hilarious... and appropriate... :p       today i realized that i go for the boys who i need to find a heart in 
    
</post>
<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         sooo! friday was WAY cool! lol... i woke up an went for a lil' run... came home, had a shower, and ate some lunch. Emma said she might drop by but i sorta forgot and failed to mention this to my mom so i was heading to the washroom and i saw her through the window and said EMMA! cuz she was right there! so thennn we hung out, played a game of pool, i think we both won once by default? or no! we played one game and i lost by default!? damn! and i was doing so well... *shakes head* haha so thenn we were gonna watch a movie er something but we didn't really.. and i ate a snack of m's and almonds! it was good! umm i guessss i don't really have to write down every single thing i did but OH well. soo then we made plans for me to come to stratford and we went to the teashop on the sorta way there!!! and i had a strawberry-peach freezie drink and emma had a choc. mint thingy drink and they were both very good! and no i didn't like yours better:P we rented video games and i suck! lol... well not really but oh well, all o'th boys in stratford are gay....so that's a shame! i went home on saturday and we rented mystic river..it was pretty good. Cassandra came over on sunday...cuz she got back !! yay... we played a couple games of pool and went for a swim and it was fun...we played prez and war  and i do not like waR! lol welll it's minday and i'm just chillin' at my house... i have a soccer game later ;););) i think im gonna go watch a movie ...       *slats of the sky outside bright clouds through the charcoal sky inky leaves flutter impatience* 
    
</post>
<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          me Look out for the       m   HOLE      Username:     From  urlLink Go-Quiz.com  
    
</post>
<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         ugh i'm so fricken meh!!  i did , oh, nothing today! vacuumed, talked to emm on the phone and watched the soccer game...it was a good 'un! *sigh* i think i'll go for a run tomorrow. or something. *needs to get out of house* maybe i'll go... feed.. the ducks. ^o).... i miss rugby! Iarrra! I'm only going to be home for ... about 5 more weeks before i go away for a month and i've seen nearly none of my friends for the past 2 weeks. And it's gay. And i wanna go for a swim. Or maybe get invited somewhere. And perhaps not have to invite myself someplace. Yeah. That'd be cool. Ah well.  later peoples, i'll stop complaining maybe.   *am i in europe yet?*  (8) i laugh the hardest, who'd've known?!*
    
</post>
<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today i went with my mum and Tanya to get baby shower gifts!! it was pretty fun... mum got me a skirt for the trip and me and Tanya had a frappucino...mmmmmmm... We were on our way home when we suddenly felt a jolt, swerved out of control and stopped in the middle of the road. Can you just imagine the rim of our front wheel spinning by itself down the road. My goodness. Freaking scary. At first glance it just looked like the rim had fell off, but we knew by the fact that the car wouldn't drive, and that crazy bump action that that wasn't the only problem. The ball joint broke, and the wheel was ... well, not attached to the car any longer. We called my dad and CAA and they towed it a half hour later. A lot of people are nice. At least 10 asked if we needeed any help, a few were rude though, shaking their heads as if we just decided that would be a cozy place to have a picnic. Losers! So i got home at...oh quarter to 6, the time i was supposed to be at Katie's to meet for DODGEBALL! I got to her place at ... 6:05. The car shananigans didn't take too long i guess.... and my dad drove off in our van. By the time we got in Katie's van to leave, my dad was back asking, "oh, you didn't want me to drive you tot he movi...okay just making sure....*mutter* aww i love him so much it was awesome! ... heehee... soooo the movie was pretty hilarious, i'd recommend it ;);) ... if you like retarded-funny-laugh-ass-off kinda funny... and/or Ben Stiller.  soooooo how did that dance turn out Kris...? didja go? Tomorrow i get to vacuum! wooh, wooh! *go, GO, GO!!!*... haha... bit of a private joke there... ^o).... aaanyway, gonna go watch the end of the re-run game... byeeeE          </post></Blog>