<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      went to the gym yesterday im goin to start going evry week with jodie. it aint really fun but u feel really good afterwards and im so proud cos I DIDNT HURT IN THE MORNING!! how gud! half term last week tnk good skools drivin me mad!!!!! hope its warm so i can go to the beach. i got chosen for drama in our yr 10 options so im dead proud, they're were only 20 places they must lov me. as usual im bored cos i only eva write in this crappy blog when im bored. oh well nt much happened at skool today, i had queche for lunch . wow
     
    
</post>
<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      its monday :( another skool week how borin, but coronation streets on a bit so that'l cheer me up! lol im feelin all lonesome n bored! y am i always bored? WATS WRONG WITH ME????? happy happy smile ishie thats it. :D ok bye then :D still smilin :D
     
    
</post>
<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I don’t know dude… I think everyone’s all jealous and shit cus like I have an inflatable bone dude… And I think everyone’s got a fuckin problem with me dude… And they need to take it up with me after I feed my toad… Because…   These guys don’t even know the name of my toad, But they’re all on me like they wanna link toes, Cus once I go they know that I’ll be their hoe, All because I have an inflatable bone.   So I get out from school right, my shirt’s all tight, Walk up to these fit guys and I’m all like, Sup’ dishy, my name’s Bombishi, I have a bone and my real name’s Ishie. They’re all like, “Oh my god, who are you?” “Dunno who the fuck you are but you stink of poo,” “But never mind that, you’re still pretty fit, Please Ishie, please can I suck ya tits?” And by now, the rest of my bitches are jealous, I can’t think of any fuckin’ thing that rhymes with jealous, All my mates start yelling’, they think they’re hot babes, But they haven’t got a bone so they just don’t compare, So like if from time to time they pick a fight a with me, Then my imaginary toad will always fight for me, But then they’re back at school the next day with me, Dude you know that you just can’t compete with me, Yesterday some bitch tried to pull a knife on me, Cus no bitch can stand just to let me be, This schoolgirl shit, it’s the life for me, And all the other girls just despise me because…   These guys don’t even know the name of my toad, But they’re all on me like they wanna link toes, Cus once I go they know that I’ll be their hoe, All because I have an inflatable bone, My bone, My bone, My bone, My bone, My bone, My bone, My bone, My bone, My boooone!!!   You just wanna see my bone inflated, don’t you? Then you blow it up, don’t expect me to, I’ll shake my bootie and do a performance, Dancing wit my bone I bet I look real gorgeous, If you say you hate my bone then you’re a liar, When you look at me, do you get a boney desire?  What the hell is wrong is wrong with my mushroom? … Mushroom? See I know I know how to rap, though I’m pretty crap, All I did was change the words to a D12 rap, So I’m all … fuck fuck can’t rhyme can’t rhyme, Why does this happen to me all the time?! Look at you little punk ass thinkin’ you’re the shit, How many times do I have to tell ya? I’M FUCKIN IT! Hey I heard you want my bone wit ya little crew,  If you touch my bone, I hit you with my shoe, If you touch my shoe, I hit with my bag, Touch my bag; you’ll soon regret that ya hag! But oh well - back on the subject, You got a big bone? Didn’t think so, What, don’t ya like my bone, what’s up? If you got sumthin’ to say then… shut up! But the bone don’t even matter at the end of the day, But still, Mr. Boney is here to stay!   These guys don’t even know the name of my toad, But they’re all on me like they wanna link toes, Cus once I go they know that I’ll be their hoe, All because I have an inflatable bone.   Well I really know I rock, but some hoes to not, But I wont name names cus then we’ll fall out… no! I’m wanna let you know that I am hot, Damn I had a rhyme but then I forgot! I’m ready to pounce on a hot-ass bloke, When the say (hey babe I love your bone) Yeah I love my bone bitch and its mine, But I’ll let you touch it if you’re pretty fine, You probably hate me well I don’t care, (I hate you) yeah well I don’t care! My toad’s called Timmy so now you know, But will you remember!? Fuck it hell no! Goddamit this song is so long, I want to stop but it keeps going on! I’m still marvellous even though I can’t rap, And if I had the chance I’d be willing to take crack, Family photographs; I was in the back, Friend group photographs; I was in the back! Fuck my school, they really stupid, Rubbed a teachers leg, and got fuckin’ excluded!?! Their so much shit I don’t know where to start, They put me in a form with a bunch of retards! Anyway, I’m the bestest girl in the group, I’m different yeah, very nicely put, I don’t do sit-ups so I stay buff, I prefer yoga that’s more my stuff, I work in a shitty assed little hotel,  Crap job, good pay, so – oh well.   (singing) Boy why can’t you see you’re the only one for me? But it just tears my ass apart whenever you fuck me anally!  These guys don’t even know the name of my toad, But they’re all on me like they wanna link toes, Cus once I go they know that I’ll be their hoe, All because I have an inflatable bone, My bone, My bone, My bone, My bone, My bone, My bone, My bone, My bone, My boooone!!!   I am the owner of the bone and I make all the sexy boys take off their underpants, I am the owner of the bone my ketchup makes all da sexy boys go to France, my ketchup!  Where did my bone go?                              
     
    
</post>
<date>21,May,2004</date>
<post>

     
      hi i dont know wot this is, i thought it was a website but im writin a letter :S dodgy im guessin this'l cum up on my website so hellooow my name is ishie n im 14 n live in england, cant say where or ill get stalked!!! like my friend jodie hu's bein stalked by a freaky little yr 8 kid, and shes havin to hide in the changing rooms!! bless her! well no1 will actualy probly go on my website, unless they happen to search ishie or itsasnake. o if u dnt get the itsasnake thing go on www.badgerbadgerbadger.com it hilarious!!! thats all! bye xxxxxxxxxxxxxxxxx 
     
    
</post>
<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      wow this is such a great day, ive just got paid a weeks wages (48 quid for 6 mornings 8-10) the sun is shining ive got all day free, and best of all, ive finally got my letter back from MODELS 1!!!!! they spotted me at pop beach last month i thnk, n sed "ishie u r gorgoues" and they called my dad and sed "ishie is gorgous" and then then send me a letter saying "ishie u r gorgoues"!!! im too short for em tho but ill b havin a meetin next year to see if ive grown and if they still want me. course they want me, im   irresistable  !!!!!!!!!!!!! 
     
    
</post>
</Blog>