<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>29,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      *yawn* so tired..... feet hurt.... gah!!!! fun time tonight. booty smakin' fun! literally.  me and lennon had another holding session. i really like him. and no all you suspensful people, no kiss yet.  lol i just wrote him an email explaining some junk about that.  the shirt didnt work!!! the almighty pirate god has failed me... *tear* BUT! the god of sugar consumption did not! yay! *dances* hmm... sugary lip gloss didnt work either. DANG YOU BECKY! lol. speaking of Danging people.  tierah was a no show today.  i kinda wanna beat her in the side of the head with one of my skates! poor josh seemed very disappointed. a few minutes my donkey... i think im going to go to bed, toodles!
     

    
</post>
<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Only 20 hours and 20 minutes until we go skating! yay!!!! Me and Lennon were discussing how to pass the time until then.  we decided to watch the dark crystal together over the phone. after about 5 minutes of pausing and fast forwarding we finally got them on nearly the exact same part. coolness.  too man good laughs today man.  Lol lennon will need cole during the T-era. inside jokes are fun. check out these masks that rei rei made: http://www.geocities.com/veliusandlarazell/masks.html awesome huh?i enjoy the music thoroughly as well.  dang big words... haha!!!! havent talked to josh all day. he probably has someone over or something. everyone is so anxious to see my hair! its awesome! im just like nuh uh uh gotta wait till we go skating ha ha ha ha ha! Methinks I'm gonna wear my kiss me I'm a pirate shirt.   maybe a certain soem one will take that as a hint? *coughlennoncough* I am a pirate you know... i'm not crazy i tell ya! im not! really! dont you believe me?
     

    
</post>
<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      lol thats would be a good song title. ha! me and josh are still talking and he has updated his blog. lol i just had this massive rant about good charlotte because he typed in some lyrics and i thought it was good charlotte but it really truned out to be sum 41 which i also dont like. but i went on and on and on about stabbing benji and joel and threatening stuff i would do if he even mentioned anything reklating to good charlotte around me ever again. then i realized it wasnt them. i am making fun of myself! *fetal position* i am so vulnerable... *tear* lol. see this is me at... wait... its 12:27... wtf? i think my clock is backwards. gah! stupid inventors! josh i think is trying to make his posts longer than mine, but i have three posts for 1 night already! Muwhahahahahaha!!!!!!! Hee hee. hearing all this stuff about lennon (not "the story") makes me smile a bunch. ha ha ha ! *yawn* well good bye from the world of typos!
     

    
</post>
<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Nikki couldn't believe this was happening. This was the moment she waited for since she met him. Not just to have sex, but to be with him and love him. Lennon was moving at a moderately quick pace now, in a smooth motion, and Nicole's moans increased in volume as she panted harder and quicker. They were both sweating profusely, all over their bodies. Lennon was now moving very rapidly, almost slamming into her, and thier moans made a powerful music together that echoed throughout the room.
     

    
</post>
<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      omfg i think im about to die! check out what josh wrote just now!"Nicole closed and locked the door, then wrapped her arms around his neck and they began to wildly and passionately kiss, their toungues playing against one another. Lennon felt what little grip he had on reality slipping away and wrapped his arms around her waist then began to move quickly toward her bed. Nicole kept up with him, rapidly moving her feet backwards, then stumbling on her back onto the bed. Lennon fell over her, laying on top, neither one thinking too rationally. " not too bad but no josh no... GAH!!! lol bad thoughts bad thoughts! OUT DEMONS OUT! dang you josh! im not gonna be able to sleep now! oh man... thats great. see how wonderful he is. can make anything up just to get a kick outta your reaction... butt wipe. lol j/k josh is awesome... i just really hope he doenst write a sex story for me and lennon... oh goddess help the boy. *crawls away to rock in a corner in fetal position from all the disturbing thoughts*
     

    
</post>
<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Hee hee!!! I dyed my hair auburn yesterday! I have black tips as well, YAY!!! I got my ears peirced again too. Coolness.  I told Lennon he wouldnt recognize me this weekend when we all go skating.  Josh needs to get his butt online so that I can tell him about it! Grr... Anywhit. I borrowed a bunch of cds from becky and bill last night.  Lol! I also scavenged art work from the art room that was gonna be trashed. They are awesome paintings... i'm in love with them... lol.  Monday in science we did an "expirement" about bears.  I got to be the mama bear and carry around two stuffed animals. Lol i named them Josh and Lennon then Dylan asked who the father was so Lennon became Lennon Jr. lol. This school year is over. I'm happy, but not.  There's alot of things I'm gonna miss.  It went by way too fast.  Very disappointing.  I'm gonna miss:  Mrs. Ashby and all of her jokes against eric that i help egg on in english class.  Eric and Ben ~ love to pirates! Gary~ who am I gonna laugh about Mongolia with? Joe~ well... i may not MISS him but i will surely REMEMBER him... dang irish jokes! Rob~lol... big in the pants... lol Patti~ im just gonna miss everything about her Lunch time with Alicia, Anna, Jairus, And Britney~ too many inside jokes made, so many forgotten, and oh my the fights, the fights...lol Mr. Nuss~ for poppin at the pep rally! Anime Club~ all the times i screamed at people in there Medieval Battle Association (MBA)~ best anger management class EVER! Mr. Jolley~ whos not gonna miss him. Grendel's Arm~ LOL Stephanie~ dang girl... stage kisses... AND LAST BUT NOT LEAST Lennon~ for the 'anger' he had towards josh at mba the day we started going out AND ABOVE ALL Josh~ the piggy back ride... lol, plus being a good friend! Well thats pretty much all I'm gonna miss from Science Hill, eh oh well.  Im gonna go. toodles! 
     

    
</post>
<date>24,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Today was National Love Josh and Lennon Day. I follow this holiday everyday, lol.  Tomorrow is Josh's b-day, also when "the pact"(a pact they made that they would both be kissed by the end of josh's b-day) ends.  No kiss with Lennon yet.  I want to, its just that I get nervous and abandon the whole idea.  Very VERY frustrating.  Today in anime was great.  I played Soul CalaberII (spelling please josh?) and super smash bros. melee.  Lost both times, but hey its all good.  I cheered for Lennon and Josh on the side lol. *sigh* it was the very last day for anime... I will miss them all, except Kevin... nah he's pretty cool.  Josh says that when I want to do something with Lennon, I should go for it because they are equally the amount of hopeless romantics.  WTF is a hopeless romantic? Anyone? Never mind, thanks again Josh!Looks like they are both losing on the pact...poor guys.  Josh makes very interesting videos lol. Today in shop I was complimented on my "indian." Gym... well watched Rob stare at my boobs and hid behind Michael.  Math.. nothing special. Social Studies... continued to be interested in  First Knight  which is a pretty cool movie. Science... I got to be the mama bear in this expiriment, my cubs were josh and Lennon Jr. lol.  English... the usual goof off with ben and eric lol. very entertaining people.  Encore... studied my elvish.  after that i watched pirates of the carribean in Mrs. Ashby's classroom. CLeaned out my locker at the end of the day.  Then went to anime and you heard about that already.we sat around outside till my dad came, josh was 'spying' on me and lennon, again attempting to make us kiss.  its quite entertaining when he does this. Oh yeah, before i forget, some one burnt up the recycle bins on the 8-9 campus, there was paper and ash EVERYWHERE! Very amusing. well gonna go. toodles.
     

    
</post>
<date>23,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      *yawn* Yay! Finally figured out how to start a blog thanks to Josh! Love you 4everz! Much happiness today! Everyone seems to be feeling great and all, everyone is happy. Oh yessuh! Last night me, Lennon, Josh, Don, Cassidy, and Dylan went to the mall.  I think Josh and Dylan felt left out considering they were the only single people there :*( Josh is a great guy, hes the one who acctually hooked me and Lennon up, and if it wasn't for him, we (as in me and Lennon) would probably not exist.  We had a great time yesterday I think.  The end was especially nice for me. Lol.  Me and Lennon all kinda cuddly and junk.  I almost fell asleep from so much comfort. Evil pyro people who like to cause death to things kept being rude and mean... grr! Dylan threw pennies at people as usual... particularly me and Lennon and Josh.  He says he "seriously was trying to hit the wall and not us." Yeeeeeah, suuuuure. Anywhit, tomarry is the last day for Anime Club *tear*.  But hey, I get to see Lennon and Josh again! YAY! Thinking 'bout wearing a skirt... hmmm... eh well since my comp sucks (!!!) I guess I should go ahead and post this before it locks up on me like it frequently likes to do! Much love!  ~Nicole/Nikki/whatevertheheckyouwannacallme~ 
     

    
</post>
<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      okay i went to the blue plum festival yesterday to hang out with lennon, and we walked around for a while then sat down and started counting stars and all that stuff, then we held each other for a really long time just talking about things that mean nothing to anyone and i fell asleep on him for about 15 minutes.... we just sat there looking at the stars and holding each other and listening to rather good music....it was so sweet! We were sitting on the bench for 2 hours when the music acctually stopped and we had to go.  He and his mom and his little brother (they were walking ahead of us a little bit) walked me to my car, so lennon gained another ounce of respect from my day (YAY). and get this.  DAD OFFERED HIM A RIDE HOME!!!!!! it was awesome. i came home and considered getting online, but decided not to (sorry josh) and went to bed, only to lay there and watch tv from 12am-1am, watching old reruns of courage the cowardly dog. before mine and lennons star counting, we walked around with Don and Nick for a while and watched don drink the cheap $2.46 a bottle Boones Farm Mountain Berry Wine. Lol. he tried to get lennon to take a drink of it (it was in an ibc root beer bottle, not the original) and good for him he didnt, then i grabbed the bottle and sniffed it and immediately recognized the scent (lol what does that tell you about me?).  then later don asked me if i had ever heard of smirnoff or knew what it was and i was juts like "no don, im just a dumb ass."  then we were following don and nick and they started going to where i wasnt supposed to be so me and lennon turned back and they just kept walking on and on and on. im not sure if they even realized we were gone... very very very entertaining night.  i was so happy at the end of it all though!!! hee hee *dances* i wanted to kiss lennon so0o0o0o0o0o0o0o0o0o0o0o bad last night, and had the perfect oppurtunity to do so too, but naturally, i chickened out and didnt.  his lips were right there! and so were mine! dang it! why do us humans have to get so nervous at times? well im gonna quit writing now. see ya!
     

    
</post>
<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      *yawn* man... i am so tired... and all i did was lay around the house and then went grocery shopping with dad for 4 hours. I talked to lennon a bit today, around noon or so. he was helping with the yard sale or something and i was cleaning off the porch, so there wasnt much conversation, but there were some good jokes, which i cant remember worth a poop.  Tomorrow we will all go and see shrek!! YAY! another oppurtunity (spell check anyone?) for josh and tierah to hang out! yay! he FINALLY called her today and talked to her.  i was so proud... my little babies are growin up! *tear* the movies will be yet another </post></Blog>