<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>28,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Many years ago in what now feels like a former life, I met J.W. He was attractive, charming and talented. He bought me flowers, took me out to dinner and wrote songs for me. My deflated ego lapped it up. I thought I fell in love with him, and I used that to justify staying with him through nearly three years of emotional, physical and sexual abuse. One day I finally found the will to push him out of my life. And somehow I found the resolve to withstand the torments that followed. The promises, the pleading, the threats. He was an alcoholic and a psychopath (by the DSM IV criteria), and I could finally see him for what he was. A few months later, as the haze began to lift, I fell in love with the most wonderful man I’ve ever met. I had known him for years, and had a crush on him from the time I met him. But graduation and job prospects had lured him away for several years. Now he was back. One day, in an uncharacteristic move of courage, I told J.C. that I had feelings for him. His response was little more than “Oh.” I was crushed, and worse of all, we worked together. So I had to see him every day. Our friendship continued to grow, and I remained optimistic. However as time stretched on I decided that he truly had little to no interest in being anything other than my friend. Then one day he started talking about something our boss had said about us…long story short we kissed. Thus began our relationship. Things were tough from the get go. He was the first person I had dated since my ordeal with J.W. Not only did I have those issues to deal with he was also my first boyfriend after having my daughter. I also worked 20 hours a week and went to college full-time. It’s hard for me to put into words exactly what my mental state was at the time. I was terrified of J.W. I truly believed that he would show up at my door one day and try to kill me and J.C. and take my daughter (also J.W.s daughter). I was afraid of being home alone. I was scared of the dark. The smallest unexplained noise would leave me crying or locking myself in the bathroom. I felt like a horrible mother. I felt guilty about the type of man my daughter’s father was. I felt guilty about sending my daughter to daycare all day while I went off to work and school. Our time in the evenings was also divided between dinner, housework, homework, my boyfriend, and the ever-elusive time alone. Bedtime was a fight almost every evening. For all that I know she loved him, I felt that she resented my boyfriend. That made me feel even more guilty. I felt like a horrible student. My school work was done in the evenings after I put my daughter to bed when I had the energy not to pass out (the deep state of depression I was in had left me with hardly any will to live let alone energy to stay up late and study). Oftentimes, “studying” was reduced to reading the chapter(s) the night before the test. I felt like a charlatan. When I got As I felt like I didn’t deserve them. When I got Bs I chastised myself for not working harder. But most of all I felt like a horrible girlfriend. I was damaged and in search of security and stability. But I had absolutely nothing left to give in return. I knew that life had not been easy for J.C. and I wanted to provide him with the love, security and stability I so desperately wanted for myself. I truly believed (and still do, for whatever it’s worth) that he was the most amazing man in the world. He is intelligent, compassionate, talented, sensual, generous, sensitive, and kind. Unfortunately, I was not all of those things in return. I was wounded and angry over everything that had happened with J.W., and I was determined to never let the things that had happened in my last relationship ever happen to me again. At the onset, J.W. seemed like a wonderful man, but as time went on I realized the demon I was involved with. With J.C. anything out of line with my initial perception sent up red flags. During our courtship, J.C. spent excessive amounts of time with me, didn’t eat meat, and didn’t smoke. As these all began to change, I reacted as though Dr. Jekyll was morphing right before my eyes—and I would be damned if Mr. Hyde was going to appear. I played upon his fear of me not staying with him if he failed to live up to my expectations (staying within the Dr. Jekyll persona). It was a stupid gamble and an out-and-out bluff. But he bought it. God, if only I could quit loving him over a steak! Despite his best efforts to adapt to me and my daughter, I complained about J.C. not “doing his fair share.” He would drive her around at night to try and get her to fall asleep so I could do my schoolwork, and I would complain that he didn’t cook enough or clean enough. Despite almost all of my furniture coming from someone who didn’t want it anymore (several items literally rescued from another’s trash), I refused to let him put posters on the wall (for fear that it would make the place look “dumpy.” Isn’t it ironic? After many lectures from my father regarding the inability of the male half of the species to properly use a toilet, I insisted that J.C. sit down while peeing. (My dad actually does—and this is his own desire not that of my mother.) Partially because of my fear of being home alone at night but mostly because of my frustration and anger over my lack of time for my own social life, I tried to make J.C. feel guilty about hanging out with his friends. Anytime he tried to do something that didn’t involve me I would play “poor-little-me” and make him miserable. He had wanted to change careers, and I encouraged him to do so. After Sept. 11, J.C. lost this new job. This only further worsened our relationship. I felt incredibly guilty for encouraging him to pursue the job in the first place. I tried with everything I had to make it easier on him. I knew that he felt like a failure, and I didn’t want to make it any worse. But nothing I did seemed to help. Sometimes when someone needs help or advice or even just an encouraging word I can say the most eloquent and thoughtful things. Unfortunately, this was not one of those times. I truly didn’t know how to act or what to say. A couple of months later when he got another job things yet again got worse. The job was doing what he had done before the career move—only with worse hours and a huge commute. Instead of being supportive and understanding (as this was incredibly hard on him) I was upset that we would now spend even less time together (he now worked Saturdays and got home an hour before I went to bed). I also made cruel jokes. In my mind, most of them were good-natured and intended to pick on him for caring about (what I considered) stupid things. J.C. has issues with just about everything from his weight to his graying hair. He’s absolutely beautiful and has a few grey hairs. (I still think he’s crazy.) I would pick on him in hopes that he would see how ridiculous he was being. In my ignorance and outright stupidity, I failed to see that I was indeed not helping. And worse, I was only deepening the wounds. This is not to say that everything was bad all of the time. We had the most amazing physical relationship the world has ever seen.  We have shared secrets and shared our crosses more times than I can remember. I know things about J.C.s life that literally make me cry. I’m sure he can say the same. There were many times—as there still are—where he was the only person who could comfort me because he knows things about my life that no one else knows. I know how desperately he wants to be loved and accepted for who he is. When I was not being sucked into the black hole of my own affairs, I think I did a good job of making him feel that way. But my “tragic flaw” was my inability when things were rough in my life to get outside of my own problems and see how I was treating and meeting the needs of those I love. I’m sure this has not been exhaustive, but I believe it was sufficient. I am a fiercely private person by nature, so admitting personal problems, flaws, shortcomings, and outright failures is not easy. But here you have it. I have laid out my sins for any interested party to see. I am deeply sorry for all of this. There is not a single day that passes when I am not consumed by the guilt and humiliation I feel for all of this. But I decided that it was time to stop hiding what I did. I have been in two relationships since J.C. and both have been emotionally intense yet free from the head games and abuse that the proceeding two relationships had been plagued with.  I’m going to share a quote from my quote jar. This is from Maya Angelou’s inaugural poem for President Clinton “On The Pulse of Morning.” “History, despite its wrenching pain, cannot be unlived, but if faced with courage, need not be lived again.”  Truer words were, perhaps, never spoken.  Until next time.  
     

    
</post>
<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      “Is “love” as we know it an exercise in futility? In all likelihood, I’d say yes. Love is an isolated event that you can feel for a moment or several moments until ultimately that feeling either fades away or one or both of you get hurt and the bitterness ensues.”  How horrible. Number two on the list of people I love (second only to my daughter) recently expressed this sediment, and I feel I must retort. First, love is not futile. Unfortunately, love is also not blind. It is often harsh and unkind. But it is what animates us—as individuals and as a species. The ability to love someone or something beyond oneself is what makes us more than dirt-babies (if I may borrow “dirt-babies” from Dr. Dillon). Without love in my life I would have no drive, no ambition, no passion, no desire. Everything would seem pointless and futile without love. Try for one moment to imagine the world without love. I don’t mean in the “CareBear Movie” sense (where everyone is in a zombie-like trance and being mean to one another). Without love the music, art, and literature of the world would all be reduced to homogenized pop-culture crap. For it is only through great love—and the suffering it causes—that one is inspired to create great works. Second, love does not last for “a moment or several moments” unless you are speaking in the universal “our-lives-are-nothing-more-than-the-blink-of-an-eye” sense. Anything that lasts for “a moment or several moments” is not truly love. Love is not fleeting. Love becomes written in the very fiber of ones existence. At the risk of sounding cheesy, I dare say it is stamped eternally on the heart and mind. Lastly, (having already established that it does not “fade away”) “one or both of you get hurt and the bitterness ensues.” All I can say is that you will never have a relationship with anyone that you truly care about without hurting that person and/or being hurt yourself. Any relationship that does not involve pain does not involve love. It is simply the nature of our species, and perhaps any other species capable of love, that we cause each other pain. Sometimes it is intentional, and sometimes it is not. But when you love someone you hand that person a tremendous amount of influence over your happiness (whether you want to or not and whether that person wants it or not). Much like the stock market, love has its ups and downs, its good days and its bad days (and rarely its Black Fridays). But if you ride it out, you see that, more often than not, the return is far greater in the end than the initial investment. This is not to say that love is easy and all one need do is “ride it out.” Love is work and love is sacrifice. People change—sometimes for the better, sometimes for the worse. And sometimes they stagnate. Life is hard. It takes its toll on everyone. And sometimes we take it out on those we love. But when you love someone you help that person shoulder his/her cross, and you both make it through life’s trials together. Hard pressed to think of a happily married couple? I know of at least one. And I’m the product of it. I can attest to the difficulty of my parents’ lives. But I know that if they had it all to do again, they would—without hesitation. 
     

    
</post>
<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Dear Blog,   Do you think it’s true that there’s just one person out there—a soul mate, so to speak (or type)—for each of us? In some ways, it’s a nice thought. Comforting, I suppose, to imagine that there is someone out there who compliments me completely. But in reality there are over 6 billion people in the world. The chances of just one being perfect for me are slim. But for argument’s sake let’s assume there is only one. What are the odds on me meeting this one-in-six-billion-perfect-person. And even worse: What if I meet him and screw it up? What if I’m not ready (for all that I might want to be)? Do you get a second chance? Or are you doomed to forever regret letting The One slip away? Well, Blog, as you may or may not have figured out by now, that’s precisely what happened. And here I sit typing this and playing a game of FreeCell—half-determined to let the fate of my next relationship be determined by whether or not I win this hand.  I guess that’s the way I often prefer to handle things—letting them fall to chance or “fate.” If someone or something else makes the decision, it’s not really my fault if it gets screwed up. Right? That’s the track this train of though follows, anyway. I guess part of it is me not really trusting myself to make the right decision. I’ve made a few really bad ones in the past (which will probably be the topic of later blogs). And just perhaps the combined forces of my unconscious and some computerized card game are better at making my life decisions. After all, they have yet to steer me wrong. And, at the very least, it’s often an effective tool in unearthing my most deeply guarded and truest feelings. On that note, I’m going to bed. Thanks for listening. Good night, Blog.   
     

    
</post>
<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I am a recovering security junkie. I’m practical to a fault. My parents have always flitted through life scraping by without ever laying roots. My sister is stubbornly following their example. I, on the other hand, have a career, a child and a house—all before age 25. I like to feel like I have a fortress—even if it’s only made of papier-mache. I try to blame motherhood for forcing the necessity of practicality upon me. But the truth is I’ve always had to have a plan. Whether or not I fulfill the plan, I like to feel that I’m headed in a distinct direction toward a determined goal. The goal is not a fixed ideal. It’s more of an evolving concept. As I change, as life demands, as needs and desires warp and mold it, the goal is altered—sometimes even abandoned. I used to seek security in others. Sad, stereotypical and embarrassing as it is, I went out on at least two dates with one particular individual because I knew that he was ready, willing and able to take care of me and my daughter. However, I, fortunately, came to my senses and realized that my soul was too high a price for anything that could be offered in return. As much as I hate to admit it, I do believe that assessing ones mate or potential mate is a fact of life. One must determine whether any potential life partner will be a liability or an asset. But, truth be known, even the best actuary is simply making a stab in the dark. I can latch on to people I think will make my life more fulfilling, satisfying, enjoyable or easy. And I can avoid those who I think will only cause grief, unhappiness and anger. But, like so many other things in life, the truth is somewhere in the middle. Everyone has strengths and faults. Anyone who plays a significant role in my life will expose plenty of both. But I digress, back to security. My last two boyfriends were like the Ying and Yang of security. The first was very independent and free-spirited. All told, I’m proud of myself for giving him a chance. He reminded me too much of my father. And he is about as easy to figure out as a Burroughs novel. I was never sure exactly how he felt or what he wanted (until he broke up with me because he was falling in love with me and it scared him—brilliant). But he was definitely a gamble. The second was very smothering and an open book. He owns his home—in a very good school district, no less. He would passionately and frequently profess his love. He wasted no time moving clothing and other miscellaneous things into my house. He is the type who would have also wasted no time making an “honest” woman out of me. In large part, that’s why I broke up with him. He would have been a great husband/father. And he will someday for someone else. But it almost felt like I was being smothered in all the security—or at least trapped in it. I think part of my fear is the knowledge that I am reaching the “marring” age. There’s this looming fear that my next relationship might be my last. So the security I once so desperately sought now seems like more of a yoke tethering me to a life I stopped planning several years ago. 
     

    
</post>
<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I must give “props” to my friends. The last two weeks I’ve been hanging out with a lot of people I haven’t seen in a while. Some it’s only been a few months. Others, it’s been a few years. But there’s one thing that struck me about everyone—the seamless transition from our friendship of “then” to our friendship of “now.” We’d spend ten minutes or an hour catching up on what has been going on in our lives then hang out just like old times. It’s almost as if the last seven years were merely a night’s sleep. And we’re seventeen again and best friends. And despite everything that’s happened—good or bad—in our lives, it hasn’t made the slightest dent in our friendship. If anything, it’s stronger. I’m truly blessed to have such amazing friends. Hella love for you all. 
     

    
</post>
<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I have, perhaps entirely too often, entertained the notion of inventing rituals or holidays because I feel a cultural void in my life. As an American, and more specifically as a white American, I feel a certain lacking of culturally significant rituals. Those few holidays we do honor were adopted so desperately and recklessly that, on the whole, the history, purpose and meaning were lost. I’ve felt this way for years, but it’s been in the forefront of my thoughts lately as the anniversary of my birth approaches. Then two days ago my old boss (now partially retired) while visiting my office spontaneously asked me, “So, when are you getting married?” Unable to control my laughter I asked, “To whom?” I was engaged a couple of years ago, but he knows that is long over. I’d been dating someone else fairly recently, but that relationship only lasted a few months (and even if it was still on-going I would have only been dating him for 7 months—not quite an appropriate courtship if marriage is to be considered). In any event, it got me wondering: What is the big deal with marriage? My old boss was, actually, the third person in as many weeks (all of them friends or colleagues) who had inquired about my marital status. As my birthday has not yet arrived, I’m still only 24 years old. It’s not freakish or unthinkable that I could make it this far without taking at least one stroll down the aisle. Isn’t it? So I’ve been pondering marriage—especially those who marry young—the last couple of days. And I’ve come to a conclusion. I can joke that—much like parenthood—marriage is a cruel cult that people get suckered into and then try to recruit other members to join (to feel less foolish and more normal). I can wax philosophical about cultural needs and societal building blocks, the “collective unconscious” or hormonal urges. But I think that the plain, simple truth is that we are in a cultural vacuum. And we latch on to things that promise community and tradition (no matter how many anarchy tattoos we have). Weddings are one of the few lifetime events that will bring together far-flung family and friends (like the alliteration?) for a celebration of life and family. Our worlds involve so many boxes. We live in them, drive in them, stare mindlessly for hours at them (both computers and TVs qualify). Weddings offer small respites when the lids are yanked off all the boxes. And we cry. And we laugh. And we love. And we dance with reckless abandon. And for one fleeting day we are human again.  
     

    
</post>
</Blog>