<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      看著窗外 雨下的好大 發呆發呆 直發呆  幻想 彷彿就可以感受到老公撫摸我的臉 我的頭 我的髮 幻想 真是個奇妙的東西啊
     
    
</post>
<date>30,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      you know the feeling when you're busy doing something...........but in the back of your mind   there is something for you to look forward to there is something you know will come soon someone's voice you anticipate to hear  yes you never ask me to wait for your call  yet I am more than happy to wait for your call   I don't do it because you asked me to, I don't do it cuz I want you to appreciate what I would do for you. I just do it cuz I look forward to hearing your voice. And I know the time of the day when I can hear your voice is coming soon.   Don't ask me not to wait, cuz I don't need you to tell me that.    But.....I am a Grammar God!!! ahahahaaa..........which is why I don't think the person who wrote up the quiz is a grammar god him/herself......cuz many mistakes, many mistakes.    You are a  GRAMMAR GOD !   If your mission in life is not already to preserve the English tongue, it should be. Congratulations and thank you!    urlLink   How grammatically sound are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    
     
    
</post>
<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    The little woman and the big man....no matter what still so in love urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      他們說男人不可以寵壞 不可以太聽你男人的話 要不然他會得寸進尺 是真的耶 風真的被我訓練成大男人 還是我被他縱壞成小女人   真的很莫名其妙 我刺青問你准許 你聽到原因說好  可是其實一點都不感興趣 也不認同 可是其實是我的決定耶 我問你是因為我尊重你 我愛你 可是到頭來你又怪我弄得太大 太明顯  誰叫你不聽我形容! 誰叫你不多問! 我以為就全程由我決定 你不干涉 照我喜歡 你如果要管細節 那你一開始就應該多問清楚啊!  更何況 對 是為了紀念我媽  所以我並不覺得我需要躲躲藏藏的 好像很見不得人一樣 我不會刻意隱藏他 也不會刻意秀他 別人看到就看到 沒看到我也不會叫他來看  我真的不開心  我不應該是你肚子裡的蛔蟲 我怎麼知道多大對你是太大 多小是太小 你對女友要求太多了啦   我真的覺得跟你在一起 我一定要聽你的話 做錯的話 我就是個非常不盡責 讓你非常失望的女友  真的是這樣嗎? 我不覺得耶 是我想太多嗎 我覺得你都沒有認真的去了解我的想法 而我卻為了不想再吵下去 就跟你撒嬌道歉 因為我也不會過於堅持什麼啦 而你是不是因為這樣而take me for granted?   I know this is not as big of a deal as I am making it sound,  and it really doesn't bother or hurt me as much as it seems....... but I know I would have to let you know, or else things will only get worse in the future........but you have told me before I don't need to talk about everything......  It is 12:23 now. you still haven't calle me yet.  I was pissed and decided not to call you if you don't call me..... but I am so weak. I really want to call you now.  I miss you and I love you. You know that right? 
     
    
</post>
<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I don't know if it's quite a good idea to be so in love with someone that you lost all your ambition.........hohoho......everyday I just fantasize what it would be like to be his wife, to live with him forever.........to be loved by him forever........  We've been together one year and one month and 11 days......他還是一樣把我捧在手心裡呵護疼愛   包容卻不會縱容 疼愛卻不會溺愛 管我卻不會限制 在乎卻不會猜疑 保護我卻教我獨立堅強 體貼、體諒  天啊 你說他是不是完美的! 我完美的白馬王子 even after a year he is still my Prince Charming  maybe my fairy tale might come true after all..............
     
    
</post>
<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      出外是貴婦 在內是主婦 在床是蕩婦 is that every man's definition of the perfect woman? 
     
    
</post>
<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Keung ahh says: babieee....I am going to lay on my bed ahh...dont' want to sit in front of the computer...so tire!! I call you tmr when wake up...love you so much my candy bar... Keung ahh says: love love love you ..I miss you ...miss you ....
     
    
</post>
<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      被溫柔體貼的老公捧在手心的我 被寵愛 被疼愛 但卻不會被溺愛 我好幸福喔 我好開心  昨天失眠睡不好 從一點到早上五點一直處在睡睡醒醒的狀態  根本不知道為什麼  最後受不了 起身打電話給老公 他還以為我玩到五點才回家或是超早起床 結果我很可憐的跟他說我睡不著  他馬上很心疼的說 我可憐的小寶貝 老公抱抱親親你睡覺 乖 老公從後面抱抱摸摸你 很快就睡著了   嘻嘻 我心裡就一直想像躺在他懷理入睡的感覺 好幸福 好幸福   而且還是他figure out most likely it's cuz my teeth hurt cuz even though it's not an obvious pain, but 隱隱約約就是有個東西在痛 在不舒服 想想 真的對耶 my teeth were throbbing and hurt so bad.........  he always puts my life into perspective  he always makes so much sense  ahhaaaa i worship him like the gods.........he is my idol, my prince charming,  MY EVERYTHING  he puts a smile on my face he fills my heart with love he completes me    
     
    
</post>
<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The past week  Something unexplainable This feeling in my chest Smothering Suffocating  Dragging me down, down, down           into the depths of the valley   the valley of uncertainty hopelessness despair  I want to fling my arms and call for help  But I am weak from crying But I am tired from wandering But I am bursting with loneliness  Drained free of happiness Drained free of energy I lay myself down to sleep  Hoping to never wake up
     
    
</post>
<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Lou gong always says,  as long as I am loyal to him, anything else are all minor.  I think maybe it has something to do with all the girls he's been with, had a bf at the time, at least in the beginning. After being the 第三者 so many times, he knows how easy and susceptible girls are to be unfaithful. Just as much as men.    I know of course, he has his own insecurities. And that is why this is such a test, such a big show of faith in us. Cuz right now both of us are in different continents of the world, with our doors wide open, and neither of us would ever want to fly away.    Because in this cage of love that we trap ourselves in willingly, is the best place to be. It's such a safe cozy harbor, a shelter we can retreat to when we are tired of roaming in this cruel cruel world.   It's so soothing just to hear his voice. Especially his voice when he just wakes up in the morning. And the first thing he does, even before he opens his eyes stuck together eye shit, is pick up the phone and call me.   He doesn't need to say it outloud, but I know he imagines me sleeping next to him when he does that. Lying softly in his arms, snuggling to that delicious resting place in the crook of his neck. Hear his heartbeat, wrap my arms tightly around his thin body.   And then i start jumping on him to wake him up! Rip the covers off him, and cackle at his comical shriek as he swiftly moves into the fetal position to protect his.......to the place that he knows I will attack next. Hahahahaa But that just leaves his butt out in the open for me to poke and pinch........I know I am weird.......that is how I show the man I love how much I love him.   I know he'd much prefer me to be girly and guai guai rest next to him. But I also know he finds my wild playfulness cute, for a while. ahahahaaaa I can play whatever role you want me to play, baby, and you will love me in every way.   I so much look forward to the day we will meet again. And know this time, we don't have to seperate again. I wonder when that day will be. 永遠的第一天.  When I see your brothers with their wives, that they've been together so many years and still so sweet. I know I will be that happy with you too. And I really look forward to it. I really look forward to be the happiest girl in the world.   I love you so much lou gong. And you love me so much too.    
     
    
</post>
<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Wish I can wake up with lou gong next to me again...... urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I am so not kidding. I would do anything, anything, to fly to SF right this moment and never come back. If it was the only way to save our relationship. It is so ridiculous, the reasons why I can't do that. Cuz of my braces. Cuz of his job situation. Cuz of...... of what? What is holding me back? The issue now is not that I love Taiwan or I don't wanna live in the US anymore, right now, I'm just lost.   前所未有的徬徨 通常吵完架的電話一定是甜蜜的結束 我原諒你 你原諒我  結果今天竟然只是一個接一個的爭吵 吵到他睡著  睡前他一直說 我要睡覺 我要睡覺 就連我問他 愛不愛我 他也只說 我要睡覺  我那時心理的 驚恐 無法形容  他是不是不愛我? 是不是不要我? 我是不是親手毀了自己的幸福?  是的 我們的溝通出現問題  是的 我們的個性似乎不合 該怎麼辦呢 我就是愛你 我離不開你 我不能沒有你了啊 而你呢 你也是嗎   我好害怕 我腦中竟然出現了  你的生活 有我沒我其實是沒差 的想法  是我從初戀以來沒出現過的想法 是最痛苦 最難敖 最令人害怕的想法   我好矛盾 我卡在一個 討厭你大男人 討厭你像老師教小孩般的口氣 討厭你在這段感情中佔優勢強勢 但卻不可否認的認同你解說的大道理 懷疑自己的幼稚 責怪自己改不了 痛恨自己不會有條有理的理論  我好懷念以前的我們喔 我突然想不起被你捧在手心的感覺耶 雖然那也不過是不久以前的事 可是我的 insecurity, immaturity, spoiled nature is wearing your patience down.   Down down down......................................  Please don't give up on us, please don't give up on me.  Please............let us work things out together.   Love can overcome anything right?  right? 
     
    
</post>
<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      人間的真愛是很難得的。在人的一生中，很難找到一個你真正愛、真正可以跟他過一輩子的人。所以一旦有可能是這個人，千萬不要放棄機會，縱然失敗，你也沒有損失，因為本來你就一無所有；可是如果成功了，那可能就是一輩子難得的幸福。我們常說『願天下有情人終成眷屬』，有情人倒不一定非成眷屬不可，但希望天下的眷屬都是有情人。  有很多人即使結了婚，過了一輩子，生了一堆孩子，但在他心中，對方可能還不是他的真愛。若是不信，可以問你媽：『媽！爸是不是你最愛的人？』你媽可能會不說話，跑到廚房洗碗，而且還會把碗打破。因為人間的真愛是如此難得，所以千萬不要輕易錯過。  另外，感情的真諦在於無求。愛一個人並不是要從對方身上得到什麼利益，你愛一個人，願意對他好，因為你覺得很快樂這就是為什麼現實是個無情的時代，因為每個人在付出感情的同時，就像在做生意一樣。我們去愛一個人時，喜歡先去確定他是不是愛我，若他不愛我，我就不要愛他；但是對方也會有如此想法，因此兩人只好空等著美好的日子平白溜過。  感情是一種付出，而不是一種得到，也不應計較對方能給你多少，因為你本來就一無所有。你也可以為愛情犧牲，但這犧牲一定要是自己心甘情願，而不是委屈、很勉強、然後要求對方來報答你。有人說：『偉大的愛情應該禁得起考驗』，可是感情既然這麼可貴，就應該小心翼翼的呵護才對，而不是有事沒事拿來考驗一下。就像一顆雞蛋拿在手裡，應該小心呵護，而不是將它丟到地上，才訝異它怎會破掉！不要去考驗愛情，但也不要害怕考驗，更無須害怕考驗會失敗。  我們當然都希望愛情能談的平凡順利，一輩子都沒有任何問題。但若愛情必須受到一些波折、一些打擊、一些傷害的時候，我們也能挺身去接受。假使我們真的失去了它，那只是表面或形式上失去它，在生命裡卻能永遠擁有它。（在一次愛的過程中，不容否定的，它讓我們學到了許多東西，不管愛的結果是合是分）在這時代，一方面我們不要高估愛情，因為愛情不能讓我們克服一切、得到一切、也不全然是美好；另一方面，也別輕忽愛情，因為『愛』是每人都有的天賦，千萬不要捨不得付出。  當你遇到某個適合你、又與你相愛的人時，就『選你所愛，愛你所選』吧！努力的把你的感情維護好。但要如何衡量愛情是否可以持續下去呢？也許有個標準：你在愛情中樂大於苦，它使你上進的力量大於墮落的力量，它使你得到的滿足大過你想要的。  人生如果沒有了名利、富貴、權勢，仍可能幸福。假使人生沒有了愛情，幸福的機會就微乎其微了。勇敢的迎接自己所得的愛情，盡力去享受愛情的美好，避免它會帶給我們的痛苦、傷害才好。 
     
    
</post>
<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I lost faith in us.  I doubt our future.  I want to give up. I feel tired.   FOR THE FIRST TIME I don't want to be the one to give in.   It's ridiculous, the stuff we fight about. It's ridiculous, the comments he makes about me. Does he think his words have no effect on me? Does he think I don't take his words seriously? The trouble is, I take them all way too serious. They are all like daggers in my heart. Stabbing me. Reminding me that I am nothing like the type he likes. Reminding me that I am not good enough in every way. Reminding me that, like before, I don't deserve to be loved by the one that I love so deeply.    I don't know what to say. I don't know what to do. 
     
    
</post>
<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      是我口才不好 是我不會表達我最想表達的重點 因為我不想需要自己說出來 this is what I want to hear you say because if you didn't think of saying it, then you don't mean it But I  know  that you think it, just that maybe you didn't think of saying it outloud, cuz you didn't know that that was my point, that was what I was upset about.  我會再拿這個話題跟你說 因為我想讓你知道 我準備好了 隨時你想要我回你身邊 我就過去 因為你以前說過 隨時我想回去 你會張開雙手歡迎 哈哈 很好笑吧 我們兩個一直把責任推到對方身上 其實是因為自己不敢當那個開口當真的人 因為真的不知道 這個改變 到底會演變成如何 結局是好是壞 誰知道  I'm not trying to force you to move anywhere, I'm not trying to say you are 不關心我 cuz you won't move here to be with me. I'm just saying I'm willing to be the one to do it, but don't 否定我的犧牲，don't say that my situation is less important than yours, don't take it for granted, it's not 理所當然. It is different, cuz I don't live with my dad, but it's not less important cuz my friends and sisters have a different level of meaning to me. When I tell you how i feel, it upsets me when you just 很固執說你的看法 可是一點都不試著認同我的point of view, that is why i get mad, that is why i keep talking...........I just want to hear you say " If I could, I would do anything so we can be together. I would be willing to try and live somewhere else that best suits us both.  But i feel obligated to take care of my parents, etc." That's all I need to hear. I won't feel like you're giving up on us, I won't feel like you're not willing to make any effort to make us work.  相愛容易相處難 我們會相愛、相惜是順其自然的結果 可是感情可是要靠用心經營的 不是順其自然就夠的 要如何相處下去才是難的部分  你不是罪人 你沒做錯 我也沒錯 可是我們可不可以互相配合 there are no such thing as a perfect lover, perfect relationship, everything requires communication and compromise............... 可能你覺得很累 我無法完全的聽你的話 可是你也知道 如果我100%聽你的話 我就不是我自己啦 我知道我個性比較急，沒耐性，沒辦法跟你一樣一切順其自然。我會覺得真的想要的東西必須要爭取來 不是說要強求 而是總得試試看 至少有付出努力 其實 我對我們兩個有信心  所以不管我們兩個到底是在哪裡 我覺得我們只要在一起 就可以成功 所以你不用擔心我到美國會don't work out, and then I leave I know what you mean, it will hurt more to 曾經擁有我過再失去 我無法100%保證就算我去美國一定會成功 但我可以保證 只要在我的能力範圍內 我一定會盡我全力去愛你 讓我們這個童話故事有 happily ever after ending 讓我們成功 I promise :D   我好怕好怕你會討厭我 不要我 不理我 Life without you will be a life not worth living.  I love you.    I know how much you love me. Yet, i really have no idea why.....why do you love me so?  Anyways, no matter what, I'm so honored to be loved by you. And only you.      
     
    
</post>
<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink      This is the kinda girl lou gong loves......   he would love me to look like this everyday.........    Sweet and girly.....which I am......just not everyday~~   Eat your heart out 林心如!! My lou gong loves meeeeeeeeeeeee      
     
    
</post>
<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink      Every night I go to bed, and know that his head is lying on the same pillowcase    I wish I could rest my head on that same pillow case too.....I wish I could wrap my legs around him, rest my head on his shoulder I wish I could feel his hand wrapped around my head        I feel so naive to love him so much. And to want to give everything up for him.....    I hope our feelings would never disappear, granted they will change and evolve over time, but I would be devastated if our souls were not connected in the same direction anymore, if our hearts were not intertwined with each others.....and never to let go.        I am so so so so lucky to have found this kind of love in my life. I will cherish and treasure my pure good luck to be able to experience the kind of love I've always dreamed of. I used to imagine, when I was with my first bf, what my dream  Prince Charming  would say to me, he would tell me how much he loves me, he would tell me he can't live without me. But no man ever said that to me. Until now. Fung said exactly every phrase I secretly wished to hear. He knew what to say, and he said it genuinely. I didn't have to push for anything, I didn't have to hint for anything. He said it straight from his heart. Cuz he felt the same way about me.    
     
    
</post>
<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      我的心靈很老 真的老  可是在老公的心裡 我是個小女孩  他說他是逐漸慢慢的發現   其實 我當然不只有小女孩的一面 我也有成熟 的一面 固執 悲觀 堅強 主觀  也有cynical mature independent strong 的一面  你會把你的每一面在另一半面前表露無遺嗎 還是你面對者某些人的時候會表現出不一樣的一面呢 
     
    
</post>
<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      是我 嘻嘻  他跟benson在一起 我一直吵著不掛電話 他就把電話交給benson to reassure that it's only the two of them and no girls.  Benson said, 他只愛你一個 ok?? 雖然他有說我很煩 可是感覺的出來 他沒有特別介意 雖然不可以常這樣 可是我好開心 他不會隱藏他對我的感覺   他週末去clubbing......everytime he goes home late after partying, i think that's when he misses me the most. I can feel it from his voice......... 他難得跟我撒嬌 說  老公好可憐 老公回到家 沒有老婆可以抱抱  我要老婆在我懷裡 回來房間好空 好空虛的感覺  說的我心好疼啊 我好想可以在家等他回來迎接他 讓他可以鑽進被子裡 雙手環繞著我 擁我在懷裡 說他想我 愛我 需要我 因為我也一樣的愛他想他需要他  Keep it simple.  I like it this way.   Just I love you, you love me.  沒有誰愛誰多 誰對誰錯 就是直覺 我愛你 你愛我  愛 真的可以很簡單 
     
    
</post>
<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      After my 2 hour long chat with Juu, sometimes I wonder what is the definition of the perfect man.  If only fung is a combination of himself and Hei's career ambition.......then he would be the perfect man.......but since he is not, is he worth my time and love?  For me right now, definitely yes.  I would walk anywhere, go through any obstacles with him......he is worth it to me. 
     
    
</post>
<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      想想想想 七夕情人節 我想跟你一起過  因為西洋情人節被我搞砸了 其實你也沒準備什麼啊！ 哼  老公 最近看到好多失敗、不開心的情侶、夫妻 我好擔心  雖然因為看到你哥哥 而放心一點 因為你跟他們相同性格 可是 以我的個性 我怕你會受不了我 你的耐心已經被我磨的快見骨了  嘻嘻 可是通常吵完 你都一樣的愛我 不知道你心裡想的是不是不一樣呢 拜託不要 沒有你 我會。。。。。。。。死   
     
    
</post>
<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I got issues. I want to marry my lou gong so bad! I want to start a new life with him.....in America.    I don't mind if it's in America..........but somehow, i don't want to be in SF...........I want to start anew......like NY or Miami (that's why I secretly hope he will get transered there by Customs) then I will go with him 二話不說      He says being at Melanie's wedding, 參加別人的婚禮，令他也想結婚   我聽到真的是歡喜若狂 哈哈哈 終於聽到他說出口了！！ 雖然他都常說 希望有一天我可以正式的當馬太太 可是他從沒如此認真說 他想結婚 老公 我也想 我超想 跟你結婚   他還一直說他們婚禮哪些地方不夠好，如果是他的wedding 他會如何做 哈哈 聽的我好開心啊！！！   我就說 我不在乎婚禮 小小就好 他說他也是 可是他媽不同意 他媽說一生一次一定要風光 哈哈哈    我就問他 那我會跟誰結婚呢 他說 你說什麼 你只有一個the one and only    Dino Ma   DIno Ma   Dino Ma   DIno Ma   Dino Ma   Dino Ma       I tried loving you less...........but I cannot..........so now I just embrace it~~hahahaa i love you       他說如果 i got a gunshot like heidi, he would be crying, so worried for me..............I know he would. I know he would.  
     
    
</post>
</Blog>