<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      FROM APRIL 24, 2003:   So last night was nothing exciting, just some regulars-- who were not enlightening. We have a new waitress and Imani's her name. I asked if she was like Iman, of model fame. She threw back her hair and haughtily said, "Are you comparing me to her?  I'd rather be dead!" So she is a model too, and super thin, It's really ridiculous because she eats nothin' We have a chocolate garnish that we use for a drink an entire piece (1 ounce!) would not pass the brink of her lips.  Well, in fact, she refuses to eat carbs, dairy, and primarily meats. When she ordered dinner at the end of the shift, the kitchen almost killed her with all her bullsh#t. She wanted vegetables steamed, which we don't really do, But the kitchen appeased her when she became unglued. As for me, I laughed and ate, my chicken ceasar with great appetate.  There were no gypsies, I'm happy to say. But there were 'tutes galore working the business way.  Overall my anger was most directed, at two business women who had neglected to develop any social skills. If this was the 50s, I would say they were pills. One, in particular, had such a big head She owned a limo-- that's enough said. Then these two ladies went onto get bombed even though I short-poured them all night long. Without doubt, the best part of the night, was when they bonded with the hookers-- they had no insight. Then they laid on the tables and danced in the lounge, and bothered my customers with cigarettes they scrounged. One of them had the gall to say, That I was no fun.  Can you believe it- ey? I just smiled at their silly jest, andcharged them again.  A bartender knows best. But the worst part:  that with a corporate card 10% they left me-- those annoying ba#tards!  But I had the last laugh when it came to the end, one left her palm pilot on the bar by her friend. As soon as they left, I took it from the seat, and put it in the trash-- my revenge complete.  So if there is one thing to be gleaned from this night, it's be nice to your bartender.  She has unknown might.
     
    
</post>
<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      FROM AUGUST 18, 2003  Hi Ladies-   I am not having a good morning.  I just lost the e-mail that I was writing to you, and it was almost finished.  That e-mail started with cheerful banter, but now I am going to cut right to the chase.  I hate fu^k#ng Wednesdays.   WHAT I HAVE LEARNED ABOUT GUYS WHILE TENDING BAR   1.  Beware of men who go to bars by themselves on a regular basis.  Most of the guys I name in my e-mails fall into this category.  I know that I sometimes say that so-and-so is not a bad guy.  By this, I mean that he is not psychotic and listening to him ramble doesn't make me want to jab a beer bottle into my eye.  But under no circumstances would I hang out with him outside of the bar.   2.  If a guy is mildly obnoxious when he is hitting on you-- watch out.  That was him trying to make a good impression.   3.  Things that sketch me out in male customers: shirts that are half-way unbuttoned, muscle shirts, removing wedding rings, and buying a girl a shot when she can barely stand.   4.  If your boyfriend goes to a bar, you have two choices, go with him or stay home.  If you decide to stay home, do NOT repeatedly call him and ask him exactly what he is doing.   5.  Guys who pull out chairs for ladies or stand when they leave the table are smooth or super-smooth.   6.  If a guy is hitting on you and offers to buy you a drink, this can mean one of two things.  a)  He is a decent guy and this is what decent guys do.  b)  He wants to get you drunk and take advantage of you.  Assume B.   7.  If a guy is hitting on you and doesn't offer to buy you a drink, this can mean only one thing, -- he is a cheap ba$tard.   8.  If a guy is on a date and asks how much all of the drinks are before ordering them, he is an idiot.  He is not stupid because he is worried about the money, but, rather, because he wasn't smart enough to ask for a drink menu so that he doesn't look like a cheap ba$tard.   9.  Guys who treat women well also tip well.  There are no exceptions to this rule.   10.  Fact:  I have never seen a man under 35 go home with a 'tute.   11.  If a guy is out all night at a bar and doesn't come home, he probably cheated on you.   12.  I often see pretty girls get picked up by unattractive guys.  I rarely see unattractive women go home with hot men.  Question:  Are beer goggles more of a female phenomena?   13.   If a man tells you how much money he makes in the first ten minutes of conversation, run away from him as fast as you can.   14.  Guys who use cheesy pick-up lines seriously or hit on the bartender are often the most confident men in the room, even if that confidence is often misplaced.   15.  What a guy's drink says about him:  --Beer:  He is a man's man, and he is easy to please.  There is also the possibility that he is stupid or unsophisticated.  -- Aged Scotch:  He is wealthy and pretentious or dreams of being so. --  Martini:  He likes to drink almost as much as he likes telling people what to do.  (I'll have that chilled with grey goose, up, with three olives.)  -- Any liquor + diet coke: He is fat.  -- Vodka + red bull:  He thinks that he is having sex later.  -- Hypnotic, red wine with ice, or a white wine spritzer:  He has no taste  --Shots:  He is in a hurry   16.  Fact:  The bachelorette parties that I have witnessed have been wilder than the bachelor parties that I have seen.   17.  When women get up and start the dance party, it is cute.  When men do it, it is sort of pathetic.   18.  Beware of the guy who has a $3,000 suit and really screwed up teeth (This applies to many of the customers at my bar.)  He obviously has weird priorities.   19.  A man is much less likely to return a drink  to a bartender than a woman is.   20.  Men are better tippers.  It's sad, but true.   21.  Men who are doing "business" while sitting at a bar are employed in a shady industry.   22.  When a man wants to start a tab but can't provide a credit card it probably means that he doesn't have a valid credit card.   23.  When men are at a work function, they are much less likely than women to make idiots of themselves in front of their co-workers.   24.  Forms of polite interaction between men and women that still should occur in bars,  --  letting the girl order first.  --  letting the girl get the first glass of wine  --  helping the girl if she is choking (Last night, I had to run out from behind the bar and pat a girl on the back because she was choking and her bf wasn't doing anything)   25.  Fact:  I have never had a guy admit to me that his girlfriend broke up with him.  He has always claimed that it was mutual or that he did the breaking up.   26.  If a guy is at a bar watching a sporting event, he doesn't want to talk to you.  He really wants to watch the sporting event.  The only exception to this would be if you looked like Molly Simms or Heidi Klum (sp?).   27.  All good looking, full-time male bartenders are players and can't be trusted.   28.  The most bad a#s drink that a guy can order is a vodka on the rocks with no fruit or a gin martini.   29.  Do not be impressed if a bartender knows the guy that you are on the date with.  He probably spends too much time in that bar.  See reason #1.   30.  I hate to say it, but men are much better bar customers than women.   That's about it, ladies.  I do have one important announcement to make.   THIS SUNDAY, AUGUST 16TH, IS THE ULTIMATE BAR TRIVIA SHOW DOWN.  WE WILL BEGIN OUR MARCH TO VICTORY AT AT 8:00.  GO A-TEAM!  
     
    
</post>
<date>25,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      FROM 7/23/03   Good Morning Ladies:  How are you on this miserable rainy morning?  I am getting a late start on  this e-mail because when I came to work this morning the "s" and "w" keys  were stuck on my computer.  Rather than wait until the techie people came in  so that they could fix it, I decided to try to respond to a bunch of e-mails  without using those letters.  Am I crazy??  My name begins with a capital  S for goodness sakes.  Luckily, when I began to pound on the keys in  frustration, they became unstuck.  So having overcome technology's attempt to thwart me, I'll move onto the  recap.  I think that the main reason that I write these recaps is because I  can't believe the things that I am witnessing.  In other words, I sometimes  have to take a step back and say to myself, "Yes, me, a  naive Catholic girl from Pennsylvania, is hearing a h*oker joke  with a customer about the blo#w jo$ she just gave him in the bathroom."  I  find that I must tell these random events to others because I don't want to  be the only one whose morals have been corrupted.  When I see the event that  I just described above, my most common reaction now is, "Well, at least the  'tute will have a lot of cash.  She'll probably tip me well."  But last night, even I was a little bit shocked or grossed out by the events  that transpired at TheBar.  It all started when Jack came into work and  asked me if I liked pork.  Not suspecting anything, I went on about my deep  regard for bacon.  He told me that this was very good because he was armed  with bags of food that he had cooked for select members of the staff.  He  cornered me and told me in no uncertain terms that I shouldn't order dinner  from the kitchen later that night because he would give me some of his food.    Now, I tried to back out of this as gracefully as I could, mostly because  my stomach never responds well to untried foods.  However, Jack was adamant,  and I didn't want to hurt his feelings.  I agreed to try his food, but I  silently planned to throw out most of it.  Around midnight, I told Jack that I wanted to eat, and I thought that he was  going to take me to the kitchen.  Unfortunately, Jack told me that I  couldn't eat there as I usually did because he didn't make enough for the  kitchen staff.  So he took me to the little room where we keep our stereo,  gave me a plate full of food, and shut the door.  Now, there is no other  exit to this room, and Jack was standing outside by the trash can.  I knew  that I was going to have to make a go of it, and eat some of the concoction  before me.  The rice wasn't bad, but the pork was horrendous.  After holding  my nose and shoveling down about five pieces of it, I remembered something  else that Jack had said earlier in the night; he couldn't afford to get a  hair cut.  It suddenly occurred to me in that if Jack couldn't afford to get  a five dollar hair cut, he probably couldn't afford to buy high quality  pork.  I abruptly stopped eating, went outside, and I told Jack that I was full and  he should wrap the rest up.  Unfortunately, he actually did wrap it up for  me, and, after closing, he chased me down in my cab to give it back to me  after I had "left" it behind.  It's really amazing how the smell of  Bengledeshian pork can ruin a perfectly good cab ride.  The customers last night were an absolute joke. The longer I bartend, the  more bitter I become that I have to listen to these drunks whine on and on  about their problems. (Yes, I do realize the irony that I am whining here.  But you are voluntarily reading!)  What I really don't understand is that the people who  complain about their problems to me are not the ones who should be  complaining.  For example, I have never heard a 'tute complain about her lot  in life, but I can't tell you how many businessmen whine to me about the  market.  For one night, I would like to tell the whiners the answers to, or  what I really think of, their problems.  I'll use one of my least favorite  customers, Matthew, as an example.  I am using him because a lot of you met  him last week.  He was the random guy sitting in the corner on Tuesday.  I  guess he felt shy in the ladies' presence, because he kept his big mouth  shut that day.  Last night, I was not so lucky.  First he began by telling me how badly his  business has been doing and how he is losing money.  My solution to  this problem: Stop spending $100+ at Merchant's five nights a week.  I  refuse to feel sorry for someone who b+tches to me when we are out of Grey  Goose so he can't pay $11 for a martini.  Another big complaint of Matthew's is women.  He complains that he doesn't  understand them.  However, this is also the man who told me that he takes  women out on 15 minute dates.  If he doesn't like something in the first 15  minutes, he abruptly ends it.  Ahhh... if only I had that power of  discretion over my customers, he wouldn't have made it through the door.  But my absolute least favorite thing about Matthew is the way that he  comments on my life.  He always makes inferences to the fact that, though I  am much "better educated" (his words) than him, he is making a lot more  money than me.  What forty-something year old man rubs it in a  twenty-something girl's face about how much money he makes?  Last night, I  mentioned that I was thinking of applying to law school.  (Note* this was  extremely stupid on my part.  Normally, I never tell hated customers  anything about my life.)  He asked me why I didn't just want to" get married  and raise a family, like most girls."  I told him that I was suprised I  hadn't snatched someone like him up yet.  I don't think that he got the  irony.  But the absolute highlight of the night is was what I will henceforth call  my page 6 moment.  Two 'tutes came into the bar around 2:00.  Fee and H:   You may remember the one as the friend of the crazy 'tute from Saturday.   Anyway, I will just put it out there that I am not mistaken about what these  ladies did for a living.  They were sitting at a bar when this random guy  sat down next to them.  He immediately pi#sed me off because he sat down,  lit up a cigar, and orderd a glass of water.  Come one, taking up my bar  stool, polluting the air with cigar smoke, and not tipping me breaks all  proper customer credos.  Anyway, he told me that he comes there a lot, but I  was tuning him out.  He then began to talk to the 'tutes.  He asked them  outright if they were working, and they said, "Yes."  They asked if he was  interested, but he said no because he was a STATE ASSEMBLYMAN.  However, I  think this pillar of the community changed his mind later in the evening.   He eventually  started to drink, and he offered to buy them shots, but they  declined.  Then, he demanded that he they tell him a dirty joke, and they  said that they could "show" him one outside.  Shortly thereafter, they all  left the bar.  I'll leave you to draw your own conclusions.  Anyway ladies, that's all the news here.  I hope that you are all well, and  I'll talk to you soon-
     
    
</post>
<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      FROM 9/10/03   Hi Everyone-   Have you all noticed what time I am composing this recap?  It's almost ten in the morning, and I just got in.  Because my boss is quite possibly the greatest woman in the world, she agreed that I can come in at 10 on Wednesday mornings.  (Insert wild, enthusiastic applause here). After getting four hours of sleep, I feel like I could run ten miles, or, at the very least, stare at this computer for eight hours without nodding off.   FIrst of all, I would like to give a big thank you shout-out to Kellyfor coming by the bar last night.  It was great to see you.  I couldn't tell you this while you were there, but you were very close to making a love connection.  Do you remember that group of guys at the bar?  They aren't hard to remember because they were my only other customers at that time.  Anyway, the youngest one, i.e. the one in his early forties, thought you were quite the little studette.  He seemed pissed when Tom came, but, don't worry, I assured him that he was not your boyfriend.  I am hoping that I can arrange for  a way for the two of you to meet.  He is full of great lines like asking me, "So... are you into girls?" and, to his friend, "I'm telling you, your daughter's friends are hot."  Don't worry, Kelly.  I promise to pursue this promising catch for you.  This sort of thing is all part of the bar's motto.  My bar:  Bringing people together for the better, but usually for the worse.   I do have to update you all on a bit of bar gossip.  We have a new customer that has been 86ed/banned fromt he bar- Mart.  Now, I know that most of you have met Mart.  FF:  He is the guy that bet you a grand that you couldn't drink a martini an hour for the rest of the night.  Everyone else:  Do you remember when you came in with Little H?  He was the guy that was sitting in the corner.  Apparently, on Monday night, Mart used his charm and boyish good looks... or money to convince one of our lovely female patrons to give him a bl#w jo in the back room.  Klassy!  Apparently, both Jack and Bergen walked in on him, and now he is banned.  The only saving grace to this story is that he didn't come in last night so I didn't have to break the news to him!   Do you remember the guy that I threw out three times in one night and then he hid in the men's room?  Well, my bar is apparently his new favorite hang out.  He was there again last night.  Both Bergen and I don't like him.  He got drunk and kept accusing us of talking about him... which was essentially true.  Some woman came in to see him for a little bit.  The best part of my night was when she stood up, yelled at him, and then stormed out of the bar.  Take that, Captain Urinal.   Other than that, I don't have too much to report.  Have a great day, and I'll probably see a lot of you tomorrow-   
     
    
</post>
<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      FROM 9/3/03:  Hi Ladies--   How are you doing?  Just think:  Only two more days until the week-end.  For those of you that don't know, that title refers to Jack and his response every time you ask him how he is doing.   So... last night was quite an excellent night by the bar's standards.  The first good thing that happened last night was that Penny continued to train with  me.  It's always pleasant to have some company behind the bar, and she is still doing an excellent job.   The night go to a rip-roaring good start when the new, female manager Ollyman (pronounced something like OL- LEE - MON) asked MY permission to leave before close.  I was basically like, "Sure, that would be fine with me."  Is she crazy?  Half of the time, a manager just leaves me there without a  goodbye or his card to void things.   Then, two other bartenders came in to booze for a bit.  Ollyman joined them and before I knew it, the three of them were bombed.  There was one customer there that I didn't like (for those of you that really follow these, he was the guy that I threw out three times and then he hid in the men's bathroom), and one of the bartenders, Jan, began to berate him.  He told Bergen that his glass was dirty, and Jan yelled across the bar, "You're lucky that we don't spit in it."  Yowsers!   Other than that, I just had a lot of quality customers.  A group from a local bar left me a ton of money, and so did this random guy with a 'tute.  Actually, the latter was a pretty funny scene.  The couple consisted of a late-twenty-year-old 'tute and a mid-fifty-year-old married man.  Well, he had a ring anyway.  At one point in the evening, he turned to his companion and said, "I am going to ask you three questions, How old do you think I am?  How old do you think I feel at heart, and how old do you think I will seem later tonight?"  I guess that lady was going to be earning her dough that evening.   That's about all that's new.  Barring unforseen circumstances, penny and I should be closing upstairs on Saturday.  Feel free to stop by.   PT:  Did I miss anything?   
     
    
</post>
<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      FROM 9/3/03:  Hi Ladies--   How are you doing?  Just think:  Only two more days until the week-end.  For those of you that don't know, that title refers to Jack and his response every time you ask him how he is doing.   So... last night was quite an excellent night by the bar's standards.  The first good thing that happened last night was that Penny continued to train with  me.  It's always pleasant to have some company behind the bar, and she is still doing an excellent job.   The night go to a rip-roaring good start when the new, female manager Ollyman (pronounced something like OL- LEE - MON) asked MY permission to leave before close.  I was basically like, "Sure, that would be fine with me."  Is she crazy?  Half of the time, a manager just leaves me there without a  goodbye or his card to void things.   Then, two other bartenders came in to booze for a bit.  Ollyman joined them and before I knew it, the three of them were bombed.  There was one customer there that I didn't like (for those of you that really follow these, he was the guy that I threw out three times and then he hid in the men's bathroom), and one of the bartenders, Jan, began to berate him.  He told Bergen that his glass was dirty, and Jan yelled across the bar, "You're lucky that we don't spit in it."  Yowsers!   Other than that, I just had a lot of quality customers.  A group from a local bar left me a ton of money, and so did this random guy with a 'tute.  Actually, the latter was a pretty funny scene.  The couple consisted of a late-twenty-year-old 'tute and a mid-fifty-year-old married man.  Well, he had a ring anyway.  At one point in the evening, he turned to his companion and said, "I am going to ask you three questions, How old do you think I am?  How old do you think I feel at heart, and how old do you think I will seem later tonight?"  I guess that lady was going to be earning her dough that evening.   That's about all that's new.  Barring unforseen circumstances, penny and I should be closing upstairs on Saturday.  Feel free to stop by.   PT:  Did I miss anything?   
     
    
</post>
<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      FROM 8/27/03:   Hi Everybody-   Another Wednesday, another recap.  How is everyone doing today?   First things first:  I don't know if all of you know this, but Penny is training with me behind the bar.  That's right; I am imparting all of my worldly, bartending wisdom to another in hopes that she can join me in my seedy part-time job and contribute to these e-mails.  For her first time, Penny was absolutely amazing.  How are you feeling today?   Thanks also to KC and JF for stopping by last night.  It was great to see you.   In terms of random bar events, nothing too bizarre went on last evening.  My favorite part of the night was when this random woman came in at 3:25, and she wanted a drink.  Then, she began to try to tell me some sort of story that  involved her cell mate, her birthday, and robbery.  Hmmm...   However, Penny was also witness to some of the regular events that make the bar the ghetto place that it is.  After 2:30 Bergen takes over the music which means that she plays one or two songs repeatedly.   Last night, her favorite was Rod Stewart's BROKEN ARROW.  I swear to God, that Bergen, Penny, random drunk men at the bar, and I were singing our hearts out to this Stewart classic.   Second favorite comment by Jack:  Upon meeting JF, he burst into some song that had her name in it.  Ahh... Jack.  You're so romantic.   Favorite Jack comment:  A weird, dirty guy in a tight tank top kissed him.  He came over to the bar and told us that he didn't like that.  Jack then proceeded to say, "I maybe poor, but I am clean.  I take two showers a day."  Ahh... Jack.  You're so romantic.  Bergen told this manager from another bar that I am the best bartender that she knows (blatant lie).  Then, she told them that I can pour four bottles at once (another lie).  That last one didn't work out too well though because they then asked to see me do this.  So, I had to go back behind the bar, and give it a shot.  I actually was able to do it, but I don't think that I looked too confident in my attempt.  The whole bar cheered when I didnt' break anything.    So that's the news.  I hope that everything is going well with all of you, and I'll talk to you later.  
     
    
</post>
<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      FROM 8/20/03:  How are you this morning?  I hope that you are all well.  It's Wednesday morning-- We're halfway there.   Last night was an average night at the bar.   The highlight of the night was having Bergen back.  She has been on vacation for the past two weeks in Spain.  She came back to the bar in all of her glory, and even managed to get me a present.  She bought me a black shawl.  Very nice.   The most memorable thing about work last evening was the gross behavior of the women at the bar.  Sometimes, it really boggles the mind.  I'll break it down.  First, a couple comes in.   The man is named Jimmy and he is a trader in his 50s.  The woman is named Wanda, and she is in her 30s.  As far as I can tell, her occupation may involve using men for their money, but more on that later.  Anyway, they sat in the corner and consumed a LARGE amount of alcohol.  I think that she had five martinis.  After two hours, they were all over each other at the bar.  Fine.  That's no problem.  Then, Wanda goes to use the rest room, and Jimmy uses that opportunity to tell me all about his life.  He's been married.  He has three kids.  He travels all the time, yada, yada, yada.  Then, he throws out  the fact that stuff like this with younger women never lasts.  Uh... okay.  Thanks for sharing with me, Jimmy.  I had to shush him so Wanda wouldn't hear what he was talking about.   Eventually, the two of them leave, and I breathe a sigh of relief.  After about two to three hours, Wanda comes back.  Jimmy is gone, and she is dragging one of her girlfriends around with her.  She's still plastered, and she orders drinks for herself and her friend.  Then, she begins to talk to the only guys at the bar.  The first man that she corners is a man I mentally refer to as old, scary wine guy.  That's probably because he is old, scary, and he drinks one glass of wine and leaves.  Before I know it, he is feeling her up at the bar.  Wonderful.  There's nothing like a little soft porn to spice up your night.  Eventually, he tells her that he has to go, and she gives him her number.   Now, Wanda is left with only one feasible male option-  Hugo.  Before I know it, Hugo is throwing me $50 and telling me to save his beer and not to cash him out.  The two of them head out the door holding hands.  Hugo returns alone around 3:00.  He doesn't comment on what happens and only says that, "People can be disgusting."  I cannot even imagine what transpired to make Hugo say something like that.   Another woman who makes me ashamed of my gender is named Shanshee (sp?).  I have seen her in ther bar a few times before with one of the old owners, Artie.  She is about 22, and Artie is in his late 40s.  I always thought that they were a couple, but I think that I may have been wrong.  Apparently, Shanshee is engaged to a different 45 year-old man.  Hmmm... She told me that she was going to her fiancee's daughter's wedding in a couple of weeks, and his daughter is a week younger than her.  She kept asking me what she should wear.  At one point, I realized that I was counseling her not to go with her original suggestion of wearing red.  Then, I realized that I was wasting my breath even talking to her, and just agreed that she should wear her short red dress, and that it was okay even though the bridemaids were wearing red too.  I hope that the daughter chews her up and spits her out.  Did I mention that Shanshee tipped me  $1?   The final disgrace to womanhood was the crazy, middle-aged smoker woman.  Literally, this woman was a chimney.  She had to finish a pack in the two hours that she was there.  She came in with two men that worked with her.  Here were some of her best comments of the night:   Crazy lady to co-workers:  You guys are just too young for me.  Sorry.  I can't do it.   Crazy lady to American co-worker:  Feel these babies.  They still stay up on their own.   Crazy lady to foreign co-worker: You're not circumcised??  I am never going down there.  Foreign co-worker:  What are you talking about?  It is beautiful.   Crazy Lady: I'm sorry, but there's nothing worse in life than a small pen#s.  Foreign co-worker: No, it's okay, if he knows how to use it.  Crazy Lady:  Honey, that's just a lie.  But let's ask everyone else at the bar what they think.   Crazy Lady to me when I asked if I could have my pen back:  Are you calling me a pen thief?!?   To top it all off, the woman left her cell at the bar.  Someone called it, so I picked it up.  It was the crazy lady's daughter, and she kept asking me where her mother was.  I felt like saying, "Well, I don't know, but don't worry:  One of the guys she is with is uncircumcised."   That''s the news, and I'm Outta Here
     
    
</post>
<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      FROM 6/25/03:   Let me give you a hypothetical situation.  Would you ever go  into a bar, when they are closing, demand a drink, and then tell the  bartender that you were willing to "sign a napkin," because you are the  owner's friend, and the owner wouldn't expect real payment?  Well, this is  what happened last night around four.  Not only was my bank counted out, but  it was already separated into neatly-labeled envelopes and ready to be  dropped.  Kit, a guy who I have seen in the bar once or twice, honestly  thought that I was going to give him another drink, not make him pay, and  then hang around and shoot the sh#t with him until he finished.   And this wasn't a single, timid request he made.  He tried to convince me to  do this for about ten minutes.  Of course these had to be the ten precious  minutes from 3:50 until 4:00... ten minutes I could have been asleep.  I  tried to tell him very politely that my bar was closed.  But he said that  the upstairs bartender had sent him down to my bar (mental note:  never  speak to the upstairs bartender, again!).  My fatigue at the end of the  night is so great that I am completely unintimidated by a customer's size.   By the end of the conversation I was shouting at this very large man that I  had been up for 20 hours, and I absolutely would not  give him a cocktail.  He had to settle for writing an angry letter to our  owner... ON A BEVERAGE NAPKIN.  I know that I always take letters written on  table linens very seriously.  Crackhead...  The highlight of my night had to do with Jack.  I believe that I have  mentioned how much Jack loves my roommate.  Well, my friends, that is no more.  Jack  told me that he has "fired" her, and that I am the new love of his life.    Now I don't know exactly what this will entail, but, so far, I have gotten  an extra large carton of Pringles from the deli across the street.  Honestly, at  three a.m., there is nothing more romantic.  I usually use these recaps to make fun of my customers, but I have been  known to do many stupid things myself.  Last night, when shaking two tequila  shots to chill them, I realized that I didn't have the shaker together  properly, and tequila flew all over my shirt and into my eye.  Now, a smooth  bartender would have pretended that nothing had happened.  I chose to yell  at the top of my lungs, "I'm blind.  I'm blind."  Tom Cruise from Cocktail,  I am not.  I would like to give a big shout-out (Come one, when was the last  time you heard the word shout-out in a sentence?) to my roommate for coming in  last night.  She made the trek to the den of sin around 11 with Seth.  Way  to go!  I guess the most picturesque moment of the evening occurred around 3.   Bergen and I were playing her R. Kelly CD for the fifth time.  And if it  was the 5th time for the CD, it was the 20th time for the song, "Ignition."   I looked up at my bar, and I saw that everyone was dancing in harmony.   There were two, white powerful lawyers busting a move in their Ron  Howard-like way.  There was Heavy (thus named for his heavy metal band in Japan), and his Asian friends sort of bobbing their  friends.  There were African American bartenders from down the street dressed in  their super-fly style and busting a move.   I guess I only have one thing to  say-- My bar:  bringing the world of drunks together.  Have a nice day.  I know that during lunch today, I plan to go to  the bank and make a withdrawl.  I am hoping that if I tell them that I know  that bank president and sign a few beverage napkins for them, and, of  course, bring the letter from Kit,  I should be in the clear.
     
    
</post>
<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      FROM JUNE 18,2003:     Hi Ladies--  Happy freaking rainy Wednesday!  How is this for a buzz kill for you?  I  barely make it out of bed as it is on Wednesdays.  I think God maybe asking  a little bit too much when she expects me to come to my office on 3 hours sleep in  the rain in LATE JUNE.  But enough about me and my anger at mr. nature, it's time for the wednesday  morning recap.  last night was pretty excellent overall.  since i have  recently added a lot of people to this e-mail, i thought that, rather than  give you a summary of last night, i would give you the cast of the  bar's characters.  JACK:  this bus boy/barback/everything-you-need guy is  the most important part of the bar's staff.  he is a tiny, begladeshian (sp?)  man who works at the bar SEVEN days a week.  i believe he told me that his  last day off was over six months ago!  he takes most of the money that he  makes here and mails it to his wife and child in bengladesh.  on a side  note, jack mailed one picture home to his wife of his "friends" at  the bar.  this picture was of just the two of us.  so to a small town in  bengladesh, i am the representative of jack's gang.  ha!  but before you begin to think of jack as a noble character, as i once did, i  have to tell you that jack is obsessed with finding a girlfriend.  he is  often upset if the bar is slow because he knows the truth of the old  adage, "no money, no honey."  hilariously (in my opinion anyway), the  objects of his desires has become my roommate.  her beauty  transfixed jack at the bar one night, and he has been smitten with her ever  since.  a night doesn't go by when jack doesn't ask me if my "friend will  come in?"  i have tried to let jack down easy by telling him that she has a  boyfriend. this is honest-to-god, exactly what he said, "i know i  don't have a good job.  i know i don't have a big palace, but you... you  tell your friend i have a big heart."  there's my girl for you- breaking the  hearts of short busboys left and right.  BERGEN SHOW:  how's that for a stage name?  bergen is a struggling actress  who works three nights a week at the bar.  i think it is safe to say that  the two of us are the bar's worst employees.   bergen forgets drink orders, forgets to pick up drinks, and spills stuff.  but the beauty of bergen is that she still makes great tips.  she has been  doing this for years and is able to make the customers feel great, even when  they have been waiting for a drink for a half hour.  this is also impressive  because she is also incredibly lazy.  during the  course of our working relationship, i have seen customers massage bergen's  feet.  i have seen her fall asleep in the bathroom, in the kitchen, and on a  chair.  last night, she fell asleep in front of the fireplace.  and let's talk about bergen and men.  i am not really sure what her "deal"  is, but i have seen her leave the bar with some very questionable people.    besides the motorcycle rider last week, there was the gypsy, the drug  dealer (he told me that he couldn't tell me what he did, but he was forced  to move around a lot), the pothead, and the little person.  okay... i was kidding  about the little person, but that's only because I haven't seen one come into the bar on a Tuesday yet.  i don't know if  she goes to another bar with these characters or takes them home, but she  somehow manages to hone in on the sketchiest men in the place, and that's an  impressive feat by my bar's standards.  THE BAND:  aka my nemeses. a jazz band plays downstairs every night,  and the players change on a daily basis.  for the most part, all of the  players are really nice guys, but they all have one fatal flaw.  they need  to learn that THE BAR IS NOT MADISON SQUARE GARDEN.  there is a time for  a ten  minute, pound-your-heart-out drum solo, but that time is never on  Tuesday nights when i am working.  Some of the regulars...  HUGO:  this crazy guy is a waiter at some random restaurant downtown.   his favorite pastimes include drinking over 15 beers at one sitting, and  then hitting on any and every female at the bar.  i think his beer courage  masks a deeper insecurity.  would you believe this forty-year-old man once  asked me if i thought he was cute?  due to his propensity to tip well, i  assured him that he most definitely was.  DOCTOR SEAN:  he is one of the owners friends and comes to the bar to get  rip-roaring drunk at least two nights a week.  watching him doesn't instill  much faith in the medical profession.  would you believe he is a surgeon?  'TUTES:  i won't narrow it down to one lady of the night (though if i did,  it would definitely be the one that wears a blond wig that makes her look  like julia roberts in the beginning of pretty woman) because there are too  many to be named.  i think that because the bar is open so late every night, it  has become a  lot of tutes' "if-all-else-fails" destination.  i don't mind because they are very good tippers.  my favorite times  with them are when they pick up a guy who, i am almost sure, has no idea  that he is talking to a 'tute.  now depending on how nice the guy is, i  decide whether or not to give him a heads-up.  now how many of my customers  do i think are nice?  right.  most of them are in for a big surprise later  on.  I could go on, but i really do have to get back to work.  i hope you ladies  are having great days.
     
    
</post>
<date>04,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      FROM 6/11/03:  Hi Ladies--   How are all of you?  H:  I threw you on my Wednesday morning recap e-mails.  Last night was actually pretty great by the bar's standards.  Let me break it down for you with the best of the best.  BEST CELEBRITY SIGHTING:  Derek Jeter.  He was upstairs drinking lychteenis (vodka martinis with lychee nuts) with some other people who may or may not have been Yankees.  F:  I know you are going to disagree, but he is very, very handsome.  BEST COMMENT FROM JACK, MY BUS BOY:  "YOU CANNOT LIGHT THINGS ON FIRE.  YOU CANNOT LIGHT THINGS ON FIRE."  This was said to crazy customers who were lighting up beverage napkins.    BEST MOMENT WITH BERGEN, MY COCKTAIL WAITRESS:  "My ride is here."  I look up to see Bergen being escorted out by a man wearing a black, leather jumpsuit complete with a motorcycle helmet.  Think Mr. T meets Knight Rider.  Wait a minute... Didn't I just serve that guy five rounds?  "Uh... Bergen," I said in a hesitant voice, "I think that guy maybe a little drunk."  Bergen told me "not to worry because" she "only lives around the corner."  Sure, Brooklyn is just around the corner from the upper-east side when one is riding on the back of a motorcycle.  BEST CUSTOMER:  Definitely a bartender from Gustavino's.  He was very handsome, albeit a little bit shorter than me.  He is a struggling actor who went to Yale and was telling me all about his ba#tard of a girlfriend.  I think that I convinced him to break up with her.  F:  He would be PERFECT for you.  I tried to mention your name a few times, but he told me that he is taking a "break" from women.  BEST PRESENT FROM A CUSTOMER:  A dozen roses.  I don't know.  Some guy just gave them to me.   BEST COMMENT FROM CUSTOMER:    Skinny guy from the Bronx:  I just wanna buy one round."   Fat guy from the Brox:  What's the matter with you?  Your money is no good here.  If you try to buy one round, I'm gonna beat your head in.  Then, we can't be friends no more.  Skinny:  Come on, this is gonna look bad in front of the girls.   Fat guy (smacking skinny guy upside the head):  What did I tell you? You're dating my little sister.  Now sit back down before I have to hit you again.  BEST OUTFIT WORN BY A HOOKER:  White leather mini-skirt.  White halter.  Short red wig.  Her name was Darla.   BEST HIT-ON-THE-BARTENDER LINE:   I was standing on a bar stool, wearing a black sweat suit and sneakers, with my hair in a pony tail, polishing bottles.    Random, fat guy at bar:  You know, you're turning me on when you do that.   ME: I'm turning you on.  I'm wearing a sweat suit and I've been up for 18 hours.  I think you have some problems.   That's the news-  
     
    
</post>
<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      FROM 7/30/03:   Hi Ladies-  How are you this morning?  Last night was actually pretty stellar... by the bar's standards. It looks like things could finally be picking up  there.  A WOMAN SCORNED:  Do you remember my page-six moment of last week when I  told you about the assemblyman who went home with two 'tutes?  This was  especially galling to me because the guy was a jerk and didn't tip well.   Anyway, I had a group of people, who obviously worked together, sittting at  my bar for a couple of hours.   When I finally got around to asking them  what they did, they told me that they worked on different political  campaigns.   As soon as I heard that, I knew that God was giving me my own  personal lightening bolt to seek revenge.  So, I quickly described  what the assemblyman looked like to the bar customers.  I remembered what he  looked like pretty well (smarmy!), and I also knew that he was a native, Spanish-speaker  and his district was in Harlem.  They immediately knew who I was talking  about.  I can't remember the full name, but it was Alan something-or-other.   I quickly told them that Alan had left with not one, but TWO 'tutes last  week.  The guy said that Alam sort of described the situation to him, but he  had explained that he didn't know that the ladies he walked out with were  'tutes.  I told him that he was obviously lying because as soon as he walked  into the bar he asked if they were working.  I also explained how he asked  the 'tutes and I for dirty jokes (I declined to comment), and then went  outside with them so that they could "show" him their joke.  If all goes as  planned, Alan will be the talk of gossip tomorrow.  Now, picture me  cackling evily here.  HOTTIES:  Would you believe that not one, but TWO, hot guys came into  the bar last night??  That's breaking the bar's record by a whopping  two!  Of course they were bartenders (please refer to previous e-mail, "What  I have Learned While Bartending" to know why they are off-limits).  However,  I have to say that it is much more pleasant  to close when I get to stare at  them.  Hopefully, they will come back, be wowed by my beauty and humor, and  give up their player-like bartending ways... but I am not holding my breath.  WHY BERGEN IS MY HERO:  That girl is really the best cocktail waitress that  has ever lived.  Here's why:  She can insult the customers to their faces  and they still like her.  She tipped me out $150 last night.  She supplies  me with Swedish Fish and Red Bull throughout the night.  She gets more men  than anyone I know.  (One night, FOUR guys that she was dating came into see  her!)  Did I mention that she tips me out super-well?  JF:  Thanks for stopping by last  night.  Who was your friend?  END OF THE NIGHT:  Throughout the night, we all make runs to the deli across  the street to buy gum, Swedish Fish, Tylenol, and other necessities.  Now,  Rock never gets anything from the store except for mangos.  At the end of  the night, he was walking me to a cab as usual.  When I looked over at him,  I noticed that he had put two mangos under his shirt and was pretending that  they were breasts. I have to say that I never thought I would be riding off  into the sunrise with a large-breasted Bengladeshian man, but it is really  not as bad as it sounds.  THE END!!!  Happy Upcoming Birthdays to Heather and Kelly!!  Come into the bar, and  I'll buy you a drink.
     
    
</post>
<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      FROM: 7/16/03  Hi Everyone-   Sorry.  There's not much to say today.  I worked for ten hours last night,  and made an all-time low of $87.  I would like to thank my friends for  coming in because I would have made about $47 without their support.  But  since it really isn't Wednesday unless I tell you something about my  previous evening, this is what I did.   1.  I watched Jack peel a Mango so that the skin stayed in one long strip.   I thought it was cool so I bought him another one so that he could do it  again.   2.  Bergen, the cocktail waitress, and I played the alphabet game for two solid hours.  Here was the stumper:  an author whose name begins with X.   3.  Bergen and I decided that there must be a way for us to pick up some  extra money that doesn't involve working at the bar.  In our  sleep-deprived delusion, we decided one option that is too often ignored in  the United States is pickpocketing.  Come on, how many pickpockets do you  hear about in the newspaper?  We could go to Europe, corral a gang, and come  back to NYC to make our millions.   4.  I tried to mentally picture an outfit that I would wear the next day to  work so that I wouldn't arrive with my usual, Wednesday morning,  "I-could-possibly-be-homeless" air.  It didn't work.  Today, I am sporting  blue linen pants, a red shell that I managed to spill cream cheese on, and  pink flip flops.   5. I unwillingly listened to the jazz band and their "musical stylings."   That is what they called their music when they gave their "shout-out" to the  crowd.   So that's it.  I'm sorry that I can't be more entertaining, but I need to  have some customers or to start lying to do that.   Never was a story of more woe  Than that of this bartender with no money... yo.    
     
    
</post>
<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      FROM JULY 2, 2003:   Hi Ladies--   Another Wednesday, another recap.  Things were pretty uneventful last night,  so I have compiled a little list that some of the things I have discovered  during my years behind the bar.   1.  If you are drunk and you absolutely have to kiss someone, stay away from  guys with ponytails.  A man with a ponytail is just one trim away from  having a mullet and should be treated accordingly.   2.  You can only hit on a bartender if he is ugly.  If he is hot, avoid him.   3.  Never ask for a "light" or "weak" drink.  That means that I will put no  alcohol in your cocktail, but i will still charge you for it.   4.  One out of fifty guys who will hit on you behind the bar will be good  looking.  However, if you do miraculously find the one in fifty, he still  won't call.  That's probably because he's a male bartender.  See reason #2.   5.  Never ask a bartender to "suggest" a beverage for you.  This means that  I will make you a brightly colored drink that is simple for me to make and  expensive for you to drink.   6.  Never order a drink if you can't pronounce it.  I once spent ten minutes  with a customer swearing up and down that we didn't have CO-VO-SEER.   (Courvoisier)   7.  If you order a bottle of wine and smell the cork you are undoubtedly an  a#shole.   8.  Public displays of affection are cute if you are 20 and under.  They can  become a little graphic and disturbing in your 20s.  By mid-30s, you are  looking desparate.  By 40, you need to get a room because you are scaring  the 20-somethings in the bar with what they could have to look forward to.   9.  Drinks that signal the guy ordering it is a loser:  a cosmo (especially  if it is on the rocks), any shot that has a name like surfers on acid,  schnapps, any drink mixed with diet coke, or any form of gin and juice.   10.  What a girl's choice in drink says about her.   Apple martini:  She has no originality.  Beer:  She's easy to please, but probably not the best tipper  Scotch on the rocks:  She's my hero.  A Martini that requires two adjectives or more to order (i.e extra dry, with  olives and a twist):  She's high maintenance.  Shots:  It's her birthday.  She's looking to hook-up or, most probably,  both.   11.  When you are trying on your outfit at home, and you notice that a  certain pose makes your breasts or a#s hang out, get ready for the other bar  patrons to see your breasts or a#s later that night.   12.  If you want to get up and dance when no one else is dancing be sure  that you have been complimented on your dancing skills by five to ten SOBER  people throughout your life.   13.  If you leave a big tip, do not stick around until you are sure that the  bartender has noticed.  The coolest move is to leave without expecting a  compliment.  You will be remembered anyway.   14.  If you drink Guiness from a can or bottle, you are an idiot.   15.  Outdrinking a guy you are on a date with never goes well.   16.  When people meet at a bar and are romantically inclined, eight out of  ten times the girl is better looking than the guy.   17.  Week-end drinkers are amateurs.  The hard-cores come out on Sundays,  Mondays, and Tuesdays.   18.  Guys CANNOT be cool if they don't tip well.  If they are ungenerous  with their bartender, they will be ungenerous in other... uh... more intimate areas.   19.  If a bartender remembers your name, it signals one of two things:  a)   you're hot or b) you tip well.   20.  Never wear a short skirt while tending bar.   21.  If you cut your hand while working behind the bar, the best way to stop  it from bleeding is to use Crazy Glue.   22.  Signs that a customer is a potential jerk:  returning a drink,  commenting on the tanons in a wine that came from a bottle that has  been open for a week, explaining how he makes his drinks at home, ordering a  drink for his date without consulting her, or telling you that the owner's  is his friend.   23.  Any of the above can be cancelled out with a big tip.   24.  Signs that a customer is potentially cool:  asking the bartender about  her day, putting the drinks on a card but tipping in cash, or buying a drink  for a man or woman he just met.   25.  Most common way for people to try to pick each other up:  jump into a  conversation that the other is having with me or with another patron.   26.  Never order martinis in a dive bar.   27.  If a bartender doesn't charge you for a coke or a sprite, she thinks  that you are reasonably cool.   28.  There is no excuse for tipping less than 20% on a corporate card.   29.  When you are tasting a wine, you are merely checking to see if the wine  has gone bad/turned to vinegar.  This custom is not about you trying to  return it because you meant to order merlot not cabernet.   30.  The hardest working people in restaurants and bars are the dishwashers  and the barbacks.   31.  Guys that order light beer are either trying not to get too drunk or  are calorie conscious.   32.  Best pick-up line ever used on me while I was tending bar:  "Honey,  heaven must be missing an angel because you are right here in front of me."   Not kidding...   33.  Heavier girls usually tip better than skinnier girls.   34.  Men usually tip better than women.   35.  Sitting at a bar and not ordering anything to drink on a busy night is  not acceptable.  Standing behind the bar and not drinking is fine.   36.  If you are ever cut off by a bartender, settle your tab and leave  immediately.  That sort of thing is never negotiable.   37.  Commenting positively on a customer's appearance can increase your  chances of getting a bigger tip.   38.  The people that tip the best work in the restaurant industry.   39.  Never complain to the waitstaff about things that they obviously have  no control over.  Some of these topics include:  the temperature in the bar,  the type of liquor the bar has, or the time last call is given.   40.  If you have ever been thrown out of a bar, don't go back there.   41.  I know of five different ways to make sex on the beach, so don't  complain if the drink comes out in a color different from the one you  usually receive.   42.  If a guy orders a Long Island Ice Tea, he is in a hurry to get drunk,   43.  'Tutes tip better than pimps.   44.  If you are in a lounge and it has sofas, never take off your shoes and  recline on the furniture.   45.  Never ask for more than two changes to be made to a food or drink  order.   46.  People from Europe, unless they have permanently moved to the States,  rarely tip more than 10%.   47.  Try not to comment on how high a tab is, no matter how suprised you  maybe.   48.  Most romantic thing I have ever seen in a bar:  A guy (who was a good  singer) seranading his girlfriend with U2's "Sweetest Thing."  Their eye  color was even correct.   49.  Always tip your barbacks and the other restaurant employees out  extrememly well.  If you don't, how can you rightfully expect your customers  to do #50?   50.  TIP WELL.   If I don't talk to all of you,have a happy fourth! 
     
    
</post>
</Blog>