<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I biked to my library today and on the way passed my mom who then decided to tell me she had just picked up my book. Well, at least I can still go to the bank, I thought. It was about then that I realized that I had left my money, a home. Great day so far.so. got woken up early, (12;50pm), couldn't pick up my book, bikes a piece of shi*, got cramps going on, and I forgot my money. The good news is that I now only have $8 dollars on my card and I found a giant cat fish in a stream near the library good for a Monday though way, yester-night at the very stroke of midnight, my radio turned itself on! I was highly surprised as I was reading. I also felt a warmth in my chest. Two minutes later, my folder fell! I think it was mainly me, but I think my old friend, The Presence, came back these "dreams" happened when I was half awake me explain... At the end of December last, as I was waking up around midnight (I have really odd sleeping habits).. In my dream------.					I was sleeping  on a mat that had four chairs surrounding it. I was at a sleepover and my friends were sleeping on the chairs. I dozed of then re-awoke in the corner of the room( which was very large and had nothing in it) and it was my be. There was something over me and it was naked to my eye(invisible).It was very malevolent and I could feel it as an aura. I was under the blanket and my head was to the side. IT began to blow/whisper in my ear. I tried to cover it with the edge of my pillow but couldn't. I tried screaming and thrashing but I had no control over anything. I then got control of my arms and tried to hit it but there was nothing there to hit! I being myself was never afraid of it but I hate being controlled finally left and I awoke. my second dream goes like this-----					 I was in my room sitting on my mattress talking to Aaron on my new phone when I felt it enter nearly rushed in and I felt it coming and knew what IT was. I was going to tell Aaron about it when it got control over my voice. I struggling fiercely for a few seconds when it left my room. I was wondering why it had left me without doing anything to me when it rushed at me again. It did this process 3 times I awoke and got angry with it then marveled at how it was doing this and for what purpose. the third one occurred as such on Monday, January 5 or 12------ I was in my bed in the same position as in the waking world, body straight and fingers clenched. Suddenly, the PRESENCE was at my side. Not malevolent in any way,but there. I tried to talk but again, I couldn't. IT began laughing and then IT spoke! IT's word went something like this "You don't have..." and the rest was lost as I awoke.  	those are my PRESENCE 'dreams'. I know that they aren't just dreams but something of a another sort. I have nothing to influence them in any way. No movies, conversations, pictures, nothing. It might just be a poltergeist *tucking* me out from my slumber. Whatever IT is, its as if its testing me... kinda. In the first, it enchants me by whispering in my ear. Then it tests me of my strength, then it even talks to but of what I hope to learn. Then it checks upon me periodically. What does this mean? Why me?Oh well, why try...? 

						
</post>
<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   hey people. this  is my blog of dreams. sortra like an online dream journal where people can post comments. i'll be titling all the posts by when i had them. so yeah... welcome to my world 

						
</post>
<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hehehehehehehehhe! liz, be;ach, aaron, erica and me went to see harry potter 3 at the willow creek theatre. IT  was a great movie. though when i looked over at aaron who was sitting next to beach, they, aaron and beach, here sucking eachothers fingers.... eeewwwww. i kept poking beach in the ribs and he bit me a few times but i only bit him twice onnthe arm really, really, hard. it swelled up after that, his arm. i warned him not to mess with me... so we left and i went to ridgdale mall for awhile and read chobits. its cool and i love the outfits chi gets to wair. i went into hot topic and saw so many cool things, it was cool.
    
</post>
<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i went over to my aunts house to use her internet and instead watched 'eurotrip'. it was funny, AND pornish!, but i wouldnt watchg it again. eeeeeewwwwwwwwww.... naked, RUNNING men. the pope p[art was funny too, but not the men....eeeeeeeeeewwwwwwwwwwwwww.i just made a blog to put my dreams in, not just my odd ones, which there all pretty odd, but the ones i can remember too. there was a sweet car inthe front of the house but it just left....^~^china! so much to do, so little time. im leaving now.
    
</post>
<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ggggggggaaaaaaaaaaaaahhhhhhh!@ i just learned that eathen leaves tuesday! i should throw a perty then for monday, a birthday party! yesterday i had to get up at 7 am- i was so irked at my mother  cause we didnt have to leave till 7;20! i lost 15 minutes of sleep. we had to pick up charlie then go to the optomotrists.  even though we were late, we still had time to get icky mc donalds. when we got there, 3 old people came and went before us. agan, i ws irked. they shot air in my eye! the rest of the day was absolute crap!. o well.i went to liz's birthday party today and it was fun. she has a pool (hence birthday pool-party) and nobody went in for a long time. liz, neda, aaron, erica, jesse, halley, alez, max, micheal, sara, me, other friend,sam and other people(most likely) came. there was a turtle in the pool and it would fallow some people around...like halley.she was on a thing and tried to move the turtle away and she lifted her leg up and it ended up between her legs. it scared the shi* out of her!it was fun and i think liz had a good time too which is good. i didnt know aaron had a celebrated birthday party... this coming from the girl who talks to him every day. at the end of the party i ended up forgiving aaron, i just cant stay mad at him. damn!neopets is still down. i think i might be a weather witch person thingie..../ i can kinda control the rain. whenever im starting to get annoyed or depressed- the sky gets all cloudy then eventually if im angry, itl rain harder with every pissed thought. when i was at my aunts being held back by the rin, i was talking to my cousions about being stuck there by it rainging hard and it began to rain harder for about 5 secionds. i said it again, and again it rains harder. cool! 
    
</post>
<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i found my notebook during my last class at skool! im so happy! heres the peom/song that i wrote in civics. i love this song.... The Key theres a key in my head to a door i need to open. Finding th door with the key is leading me farther away from my dreams.  the path i've taken has lead me from the way with contradictions to my dreams  theres so many doors here, i can't find the one. I feel the waves, washing,  washng me away.  the things I'm finding i never knew i had. i know now that i've learned. i've locked away ....so many things. mistakes are made, and so i learn.   the key i've found  has unlocked so many doors. the waves i know, the friends i've made. so many things rushing a head.  through thick and thin ive learned to cope. death will come and ill tag  along. this is what the door has opened.  this is what the Key has done.    thets it. i love it so much. (just to tell you it is capywrited and if you use it, you have to notify me!) i went to the dentist this morning and we talked about toads. my dentist(she lives near me) told me that she has toads in her backyard and she wont mow her lawn while they're in front of the mower. DARN!!!! hehehe... bloody taod... hehehe.ha! i'm going to concordia now for TWO WEEKS instead of ONE!!!!!!!!
    
</post>
<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I biked to my library today and on the way passed my mom who then decided to tell me she had just picked up my book. Well, at least I can still go to the bank, I thought. It was about then that I realized that I had left my money, a home. Great day so far.so. got woken up early, (12;50pm), couldn't pick up my book, bikes a piece of shi*, got cramps going on, and I forgot my money. The good news is that I now only have $8 dollars on my card and I found a giant cat fish in a stream near the library good for a Monday though way, yester-night at the very stroke of midnight, my radio turned itself on! I was highly surprised as I was reading. I also felt a warmth in my chest. Two minutes later, my folder fell! I think it was mainly me, but I think my old friend, The Presence, came back these "dreams" happened when I was half awake me explain... At the end of December last, as I was waking up around midnight (I have really odd sleeping habits).. In my dream------. I was sleeping on a mat that had four chairs surrounding it. I was at a sleepover and my friends were sleeping on the chairs. I dozed of then re-awoke in the corner of the room( which was very large and had nothing in it) and it was my be. There was something over me and it was naked to my eye(invisible).It was very malevolent and I could feel it as an aura. I was under the blanket and my head was to the side. IT began to blow/whisper in my ear. I tried to cover it with the edge of my pillow but couldn't. I tried screaming and thrashing but I had no control over anything. I then got control of my arms and tried to hit it but there was nothing there to hit! I being myself was never afraid of it but I hate being controlled finally left and I awoke. my second dream goes like this----- I was in my room sitting on my mattress talking to Aaron on my new phone when I felt it enter nearly rushed in and I felt it coming and knew what IT was. I was going to tell Aaron about it when it got control over my voice. I struggling fiercely for a few seconds when it left my room. I was wondering why it had left me without doing anything to me when it rushed at me again. It did this process 3 times I awoke and got angry with it then marveled at how it was doing this and for what purpose. the third one occurred as such on Monday, January 5 or 12------ I was in my bed in the same position as in the waking world, body straight and fingers clenched. Suddenly, the PRESENCE was at my side. Not malevolent in any way,but there. I tried to talk but again, I couldn't. IT began laughing and then IT spoke! IT's word went something like this "You don't have..." and the rest was lost as I awoke.  those are my PRESENCE 'dreams'. I know that they aren't just dreams but something of a another sort. I have nothing to influence them in any way. No movies, conversations, pictures, nothing. It might just be a poltergeist *tucking* me out from my slumber. Whatever IT is, its as if its testing me... kinda. In the first, it enchants me by whispering in my ear. Then it tests me of my strength, then it even talks to but of what I hope to learn. Then it checks upon me periodically. What does this mean? Why me?Oh well, why try...?  
    
</post>
<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      meh... nobody loves me, or thinks of me as a good friend... when i got back from my aunts house and was puttimg together the gazebo(yes im still working on it)i was talking to my mom and she said i didnt love her. then when i came inside and she was dooing laundry, she asked me if $20 was a good allowance for a week. YESYESYESYES!!!! of course it is but then i remembered our little money crisis, aparently we didnt have enough cash in her savings account and our hopkins house was sold for less then our new one, and mom wanted to pay in cash... were a bit chort on money... Is she trying to buy thisLOVE she speaks of from me? if its that, then what      the       fuck! she also said that Bill was going to move out(again, he already has had an appartment for about the past 8 months, but doesnt live there because apparentl;y(again) somebody wants to kill him.so he thinks its safe endangering his mother and cuddley baby sister!), that were going to rent it out. there goes my second bedroom....yeah.. elliot found two mice in the shed today after the gasoline canister got knocked over. he then tried to kill them. there was a hole in the floor that they went through so he took the gas canister and POURED and sloshed it over the hole!this coming from a christian AND an 17 year old boy with his mother right outside the doors! he then blocked of the ground route to get out, and i took a really pointy, sharp, sgardening tool and jabbed it countinously into the hole. but whenever i pulled it out, there wasnt any blood...0_o
    
</post>
<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      uh,.... beach?.... sorry about pulling thAT  dominatrix trick on you during the chat...
    
</post>
<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      meh. today is the second day whithout food completely. havent eaten any thing since ....wed. im not hungry anymore. i found out that i really just ate out  of habit and i already knew this, but I my self dont really need to eat as much food as anybody else. i'm livin' of the fat'a my fat. kinda humourous. im still drinking stuff. ive been gardening for about 3 hours now. so bored... meh. had a waked up dream last night that ill post later on my dream blog.  meh
    
</post>
<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      nuthihng exiting rtoday. went to hot topic and bought a book thingie there. the book, SQUEE!, is really funny and has alot of comics in it and happy noodle boy and its hilarious. i went to my uncles hous and played cards with my cousin for a while. everybody was drinking beer... theyve never really done that. it was mainly adults but there were some children and they were swearing sometimes too. bought some 'sex' bracelets at a cad place buit i dont know which colormeans which. i bought green, black, and blue or ...purple. yeah.be free little poptart!i wanted to write something but i cant remember anymore. ive also been writing on my walls and tearing of the wallpaper at night. i didnt go to sleep till probably 3am last night but im not really tired now.
    
</post>
<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i found an actual CHUCKIE DOLL(AFTER BRIDE WHERE HES ALL SEWN uP) It was really cool and i would of bought it if it hadnt of been in the sex area and if i werent with my mom, and without any money on me... it was at spencer gifts. it was cool and came with a replica of the knife in 'bride'. but it was plastic, the little peice of crap.im gonna read squee again... 
    
</post>
<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Fight Club!    urlLink   What movie Do you Belong in?(many different outcomes!)     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   heeheee. my inner child is 16! 
    
</post>
<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Mors    urlLink   ?? Which Of The Greek Gods Are You ??     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   i dont think this one is really accurate to ME in particular. ithink this one is,   Nemesis    urlLink   ?? Which Of The Greek Gods Are You ??     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla   yep. thats definately me. 
    
</post>
<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      meh, i cleaned my room today. changed everything around and now my monm just got back and will probanly be pissed with me. i also got grounded from the tv and no allowance. yep, i was right, she got pissed. my room looks cool now. i found a lot of crap in there and i suppose i can clean off the blue prints that i drew on my wall. i might be going towashinton with my grandfolks adnd my moom. coooooooooool! ive never been there. but still, nobody loves me.....`_` meh. i now have 26 sex braclets. blue, green and black. i also might be going to cali9fornia soon too. yeah! i actually gett to go somewhere for the summer holidays.ive been eating for about a full day now(yesterday). let me see... i ate; about 12 peices of sliced thinnly ham, i nasty jello snack thing, 5 peices of graham crackers with peanut butter on them, 2 halfs of a grilled chees sandwich, frenchfries, 3 smoothies, i container of pringles(the whole container), and....two mini cans of pop, 1 bottle of BIC black cherry, i bottle of water, i  KFC biscuit, and other stuff i cant remember. i ate this the whole day throughout sunday.ive also been watering my new plants and i finished the GAZEBO finnally!why does nobody comment? i feel so lonely here....i worked at my aunts house with Elliot and Whitney, chopping up their tree for wood. also found out that they decapitated a baby squrel accidentaly. there was blood stains on the wood. hahaha.then i went on the internet for about 3 hours. i need to earn more neopoints so i can get the final peice of the spooky treasure map.also need to call up friends to return there stuff. note to self: maria-tape annalie- pc game jazmin- cd has everybody thats going to mori no ike with erica left yet? if not, when are they going?got a cool new desktop thing for my computer.
    
</post>
<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      heh. cool! i was just looking through my japanese learning things for the computer and i found a translation thingie. it can translate any english word into japanese and find its kanji too. i havent found ' pimp' yet, but i have found other words like... other stuff. its cool. this is the only exiting thing that ive found today other then about...6 new cool dvds. 5 are monty python ones ('holy grail', 2 'life of the pythons', 2 'moty python live') and the other one is hotaru no haka (grave of the fireflies). i was surprised though to find out that miyazaki's name wasnt on that.other then this,all ive done today is bike to the library for a book. i was so surprised and felt like a main, favorite charicter had just died when i read that Armound killed himself over a littloe thing like the actuall Veronica's Veil. that sucks. i also picked up Di Gi Charat. its interesting so far, but not really. i still havent given people their stuf back, and i so want to. so bored....
    
</post>
<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      well, im less pissed now then this morning. i went and saw 'around the world in 80 days'. it was good. i liked the evil chinese warlord ladies finger attachments. they were cool. then i got pissed off at the MC again because she took way too long  with her friend and so i left the store. at slumberland i found a bunkbed thats bottom was a futon. only $349.99. we'd have to buy the mattress thiing to it seperatley but im ok wit that. didnt get to remake my quilt though. i found a pretty, petite, black cat in the forest behind my grandpas house. i fallowed it into the forest and continually treid to coax it out but it kept going deeper in. i was waring my cat ears and i think it was confused. that and i kept meow-ing back at it convincinly. hhhh,mmmmmm, is she a cat or a human? i think she (the cat)(yes, it was obviously a she) was being called by something and kept going deeper in. i faintly heard something too  but im not sure what.
    
</post>
<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i hate being an insomniac. also dont like the show on comedy central. i also currently dislike the MC( Mad Cow(mother)) right now because she woke me up and tried to give me this crap of a drink to help swally down my pills and i nearly choked on them as i hacked them back up and was aghast at what shed done. i had told her that that stuff was crap a bout a week ago. i told her ALL flavors of that were crap too. but noooooo! she just had to make me nearly throw up! gah! then she tells me to get ready for a dentists appointment. really tired of her doing this to me. the stuck a needle in my mouth for about 30 seconds, ignoring my gurgles of pain as i could feel it touch the roots of MY TEETH! i still cant feel my nose!i hate them all! they also gave me a head set to listen to where it only had the tv newsstation, an oldies station, a classical crap station, and a crappy oldies rock station. god , this should of been a monday! on a ;ighter not, i saw a guy without legs. yep. a real highlight of my day. we have 96 dvds, not including any tv series, which would make the #.....37+96=133 dvds together.then we have over 160 vhs's.wow... yeah.im ganna go on neopets now.
    
</post>
<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      alex, thanks for reading this, your probably the only one that does without me forcing them to.yeah! i only need 39 more Monty Python episodes then i'll have them all! only about alot left to go for the sailor moon series though. im missing the last whole seoson(the one with pegasus)and the one with alen and ann(the doom tree thing). i'm helping Cassie plan her birthday party too. i want to go buy that cool red and black skirt and shirt set at hot topic. it was really cool. it was in the eden prairie site and the shirt was all laced up the front. the skirt was black with a triangular slit in the front with red underneath. it was cool! tell me, if youve done everything you've ever wanted to do, and you want to expirience death, why shouldnt you kill yourself? this is a serious question. and yes, im still on about it. what could you tell your friend to stop them?dont worry, im not gonna do it and dont you dare spread it around!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!
    
</post>
<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      never wake me up early in the morning (about9 o'clock or so)! the only words you'll get out of me will be "i'm not going" and"get out!". then i'll just go back to sleep. that is till this morning when my mother told me my brother GOT SHOT! yeah, he got shot! it was shrapnel- ish as far as i know....he got hit in the arm and something to do with his hip. i know its bad of me to say this, but he didn't get hurt enough to be sent home only enough to stay in a hospitl for a few days.&gt;</post></Blog>