<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>09,May,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I’m going to try and actually update this journal as often as possible and not make them really short, dumb entries.   Yeah, so anyway this weekend wasn’t too shabby. Last night I went to go see Almost Fandango and a few other bands. West Gate was playing too. West Gate is my sister’s boyfriend’s band. Anthony is the drummer. Anyway, West Gate kicked ass. Almost Fandango… they’re talented and all but I think people make too big of a deal out of them. They’re good, don’t get me wrong, they’re not that big of a deal. Not to me anyway. I went with Ryanne, Amy, Zoe, and Danielle. Hector was there too. Great. Yeah, that was sarcasm. Anyway, that was the first show (not just local) that I’ve been to that I was scared to go into the pit. It was... scary. Man… I wish I could dance like Dusty and those other guys. They were skanking the whole night. They were awesome. Anyway, Ryanne met this guy named David at the show. He seems cool. At like the end of the show they were like holding hands and cuddling and shit. I was like… “wow, I wish I had that kind of luck with guys…” haha. I thought Patti (my sister) would come but she didn’t.   I have  no  idea why, but Patti has been a  bitch  lately. She’s so snappy about EVERYTHING. Like, I’ll ask her a simple question and she’ll start bitching at me over nothing. My dad and I were talking about how whenever she’s arguing with someone, she always has the impression that she’s right. She always thinks that her opinion is the right one. I dunno, Patti’s cool to hang out with but she needs to chill out. I don’t know. I kinda feel bad for Anthony ‘cause he loves her  sooo  much but she’s so strung out and so bitchy all the time. I don’t know how he handles it. Poor guy… Anywho!   I helped my mom deliver flowers today for Mother’s Day. My Gramma has worked at Mercer’s Florist since… before I was born. And my sister works there too, and my mom and I help out sometimes so it’s sort of a family thing I guess. Tonight I went to Kasey Blowe’s party. It was pretty cool, a lot of people were there. I went with Beth. I mostly just hung out with Keith, Caroline and Matt, and Beth. Oh, and Alex. Haha. It was cool… tired me out though.   But… on Monday my friend Shaun asked me out. He’s such a sweet guy and he’s so nice… but I feel horrible because I said yes. I shouldn’t feel bad. =\ I feel bad because I said yes when I didn’t really have those types of feelings for him. And this guy I talk to on Yahoo (he lives in Canada, yay! Haha) said that the longer I string him along, the more it will hurt him. He said he likes me a lot, but I just… I dunno. He’s my buddy so it doesn’t really even feel like we go out. God, this sucks… I dunno what I’m gonna do. I know that I’m going to break up with him, but I really don’t want to hurt him. Damn… Well, I’m exhausted and I’ve had a long day, so I’m gonna go to bed. Or try to. I guess I’ll just lay in bed and think… at least it’s comfortable there. Night, guys.   Love,   Cassie 
     

    
</post>
</Blog>