<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      basically nth much to write...tis noon went for facial wif my mum! 1st time lehz...erm, the feeling quite shiOK! tada~! =D the "mei rong si"(facialist? dunno la) say i a lot of "black heads" muz take care...hmmm sad~ haha! den xiu my mei mao(trim eye brow) already no hair liao den still pluck! haha...quite pain but hehex~! tml sch starts meeting my frenz at 1120am at NP...my rM is still in a mess! alamak lazy to pack but haf to so tt i'll haf a tidy for poly! nehz dunno wat to write liao bye! =D
     
    
</post>
<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hmm, ytd which is sat i went harbour front centre for shopping wif seow. bought an adidas bball shorts which is worth buying den after tt went for bball gathering at joan's mansion...having finished my dinner(buffet gl ordered) i did a mischievous act--&gt;puShed ann into the poOL! wahahax...but i did not haf a gd ending too...3 ppl came after me! i hugged the pole but to no avail...sze hui, papa n ann tickle me, got me off the pole n there i go into the pOOL! =X soOn we got every1 into the pool hehex! we played games in e pool n horz the siao cha bo(yuna) n cynthia always win! know y? cos yuna too gd at fighting! lolx...there's sauna in the toliet! so shiok...we left the place at 10+ den went newton circles to eat den went home! oh ya muz mention tt xy n mogu ps me! sa si ni men ar! lolx! as for today, went queensway in e noon wif seow again(she tOO oNs blehz =P) hEy mAn queensway sports products r not cheap in fact even more expensive! harbour front offers better price man! ended up nv buy anything den went home...oh yea b4 going home went kfc to have shrooms meal *yummy* tinking of it makes me hungry! den now home writing blog...sch starting next weEk, man tt's fast...me mum's fren juz brought 2 bags to fruits to my hse..omg a lot lot lot of ANTS! *ee yer* dunNO hOw m i goIng to geT riD of it(ants) *alamak*! kk i shall stop here...
     
    
</post>
<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ngee ann poly BA(business accountancy) orientation so so sucky! man damn bored lorx...i m so dumb to go for it! it lasted frm 23th-25thjune...waste of my time! aRGH! 1st day go there do nth...2nd day played games n the games all i played b4! wah sianx maN! 3rd day which is today juz went there to watch concert...omg...so so damn bloody hell boring! hmmm, my class ppl all nv go for the orientation only 5 pathetic ppl...no shuai ge also...my class gals all quite girly. jia lat not my type lehz...haix...sch starts next week so so fast...iyA tt's abt it...
     
    
</post>
<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hMm, 3 days nv write tis bloggy. i shall start fr 18th e fri...went sentosa to haf fun n of cos to tanned! not enough tanned cos went too late but lucky nv get sun burn my frenx all chao ta..*phew* iYo i getting lazier n lazier to write blog liao...=P den after sentosa went juan's hse to stay overnight. e fEeliNg i gEt frm hEr rM hOrz majiAm likE hotEl! lolx...we watch "kill bill" in e middle of e night, wah SEh so So dAmn violEnt but i luv it! so so nicE! cAnt wait for "kill bill 2" to launch! also watched an fighting show but forget it's title. it's an korean show? hMm, den sLp till morning 10+am den rot at her hse haf duck rice as lunch den went home at 2+pm get change den went out in e evening go hougang watch bball match...(obviously next day liao, 19th!) after e match, went to haf chicken chop as dinner den went home...we board 53 alighted at serangoon MRT station den we realised LAST TRAIN GONE! oh maN...dEn any how boarded 153 to toa payoh...so sway 1150pm only, 157 no more! sHIt mAn got stranded in toa payoh till 2am...(we=me, HL, marina) all taxi pass us will look at us lehx! all my fans! haha...cAlled up qilin to come n fetch us(lucky gt saviour) den went coffee shop sit sit listen watching zeng ye n weiliang lame...reach home ard 5am...den slp! haha...as 4 today...surf net, at night make pizza n fish n chip myself as dinner so delicious *yummy* den online till next morning...tt's abt it man! liFe's so lONely wHO undErstAnds mE?! lOoKIng 4 soME1 tt cAn shAre sorrOws n jOys wiF me...i nEed a reAl clOSe fREn maN! buT sEeMs impoSsibLe to fINd forGet iT! Oh mUZ bE haPPy everyday! blah blah blah la la...lolx! *crAzy* i shall stop here...=P
     
    
</post>
<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hMmm, injuRed my knEe ytd during the match wif kai xuan but thanxfully juz minor injury. got a swollen right knee back home! haha...my bBall sux mAn cant help it! *sad* slack whole day at home today den went out to take back my bike n chat...nth much la...sch gonna reopen soon a bit lost ya know...half year nv touch books n study! hOpe tO haf a greAt scH life in NP! =P
     
    
</post>
<date>14,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      yOx...feeLing mucH betTEr todAy than ytd! wAh still cant breathe properly...duNno it's bcos of ytd ppl bang me too hard on my stomach or wat...i did a lot of miss pass ytd n i really sux as a controller! still dunno y coach put me as controller -_-'" let's tok abt something happy...hmm, last friday went JE library. wOOhx i lUv iT maN esp. the "vErgIngteeNs"(tink i spell wronging) section! grEAt atmospHere n muSic in tHEre! goTTa pub fEeling! lolx! i shall visit it agAin luV iT! =P wE r oUt of the milo cUp bEttEr i fEel...;) goIng out to plAy bBall later...i shall stop here...=P
     
    
</post>
<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      aRgh F*** oFF! gOt foUl out at tHe startinG of 2nd quatEr...hEll shiTty aSs! tt's way tOO fAst...i m too toopit cAn't help it! fOUl thEm fOR wAT! idIOt mE! no moOD anyMore bYE...
     
    
</post>
<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      noRmAlly i wAkes uP at 1130am (considered early lEhz...HL mIlk hORz wAkes up aT 3+ or 4pm! tt xy alSo!) cos they slp at 4+ 5am in the morning! toDAy i woke up at 945am n my piano lesson is at 945am! wahaha...cAnt heLp it toO tired lahx! =P luCky my chEr nv scold me! XD hmmm...played haydn's sonata in C major...so so nice...n of cos my exam pieces hAydn's finale sonata in D major n scarlatti(tink i spelled wrongly! =P) duNno wAt song...haha! dEn bought chicken rice again as lunch for sis n me...oN my wAy hOme pass by tHe park agAin n almOSt gOt kiLled by an idiot crOW fLying towArds mE, scAre me tO deAtH! -_-'" sOme dAy i drEAm tO kiLL aLL crOws! i sAw 2 pairs of butterflies...1 pair yeLlow n whIte in colour, tHE other dArk brOwn(pretty n ugly...=X) so luvInG! i goNNa gO bbdc lAter to aSk fOr baSic theoRy exAm...=D hEex tt's abt it! byE! =P
     
    
</post>
<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      heEx..today's my mum's bday! how m i going to celebrate? hMmm...may b trEat hEr go mAkan! Hur hur~ 360degree change in mOOd--&gt;frm siAnx to hAppY! ya kNOw y? wahaha..cos juz nOW on mY wAy hOMe, i pass by the parK n at the same time eating my french fries(dinner) i saw a dog ShittING! dEn it's owner placing newapaper on the grass patch...the sHIT gOEs rOund n rOUnd dEn pOo oUT! goSh~ neArly pukEd aLL my friEs ouT! lolx..i had bbq chicken rice as my dinner n i was almost half dead during training no mood...gOt oUr jErsEys toDAy...hEex...didnt gO fOr the spORts cAmp n mY fRenz sAy it's pretTy fuN...now a Bit regRet...N ya kNow Y i m dOWn juz now! Hmmm...coS tis n tt lahx! NOw i kNow e trUth hAte U! yA nOt gONna disRupt mY lIFe! wAHaHA...i gOnNa stAy hAppy evErydAY! hyMpH! ooPs...soME hoW goNe a lil mAd =P bYe...
     
    
</post>
<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      wAke uP at 1125am in the morning feeling distorted for no reason...lolx! feel like slping again but not so pig...eat bee hoon again! den play piano, change bed sheet den online writing tis bloggy cos no one to chat wif...xiang dao later got training muz travel so far i sian half~ but no choice muz jia you! =D i gotta get my shooting back...100% shooter *day dreaming* i look out of my window...so sunNY n as i type there's a excruciating pain on my left hand...feng si? i old liao cant help it...lolx~! my hse a lot of "kaka"! buitahan~ cos the balcony all flowers--&gt;the creation of my muM! lolx! k stop here bYE!
     
    
</post>
<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      arGh sIAnx~! rOT thE whOle daY todAy...lIe on My BEd sLp n sLp...turniNg zombIe soOn! sIAnx=down=no mood! suddEnly feeliNg sad...bOO! =P i ask andrew a very toopit quest tis afternoon "y humans r created wif emotions?" he replied "if not we r no diff. from robots!" yeA...vEry tRue but soMEtiMEs i fEel tt i rAthEr noT hAf emotIonS!  
    
</post>
<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Now i get it...it's so siMple..."su-gU" me! cAnt hElp it i came fRm cAve...cAVegal u knOW! haha..other words "shuA gU"! =P hmmM, 1st time writing...where n how shall i start? the time now is 2.46pm! *full of craps* today's weather is way too gd...making me feeling languish~ rAiNing all the wAy so cOOliNg! bUt nOt gd coS maKIng me lAZy! er...contradicting myself?! lolx! oH i kNOW! firStly, muz intro myself 1st ritex? HMmm..i stands 161cm...arGh a shoRty...bOO! a skInny pOle wiF weIghT 44kg. iF evEr thEre's toRnaDo in SG...i shAll b thE 1sT fEw tO b bLOwn awaY! haha! i lOoK noRmal juz a nORmaL gAl wiF 2 eyes, a nose, a mouth, a pair of ears, hair, hands, legs, fingers, toes...-_-'" sorri entertaining myself! haha! arGh...stomach ache tInk nEeds tO go lOo...iYA...latEr lAhx too laZy to WalK! sEe i toLd u bAd wEathER! haha! oOPs got carried away bY crAps...hMmm, liFe's greAt fEr me. i hAf gOt a bIg bRo n lil sIs n oF cOs deAreSt mUm n dAD wHO supPorTs mE in eVerYtHing i dO...=D i M goIng NP tIS 28th june..hOpe tO meEt lotSa gREat pPl thErE n oF coS to exPAnd my cirCle Of frEnz! XD i M in BS(business studies). pPl sAy BS wEll-knOwn fOR mEi NU(chio bUs) buT i CMI(cannot make it) cos i goTta bAby facE...;) i ate a packet of bee hooN juZ now...tt's my breAkfAst n luncH! haha...Hmmm, eough of crAps...continue next time...bUaix~!
     
    
</post>
<date>09,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      how to use it? so blur!~ -_-'"
     
    
</post>
<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Haven been writing since last sunday! hmm, i shall start on last mon. MON--&gt; i went for time trial for NP track. Did a 2.49min for my 800m gosh way way away my target. hoping to do a 2.40min instead. i guess i nv pace myself properly. if i carry on in tis timing 800m medal can forget it...Did a try out for long jump too...hehex so fun! mr lim wanna train me up for long jump! yuppie... TUES--&gt; went for bball training but in the end nv train cos no court wth nvm...i m still in dilema now i dunno which to choose bball or track hope ms chua let me off for IVP track season den i dun need to tink so much! WED--&gt; did a time trial for 400m...still alrite did a 66s tinktt's my PB...den do some workouts for long jump..alamak..i dunno how to lift my my C.G...haix i will jia you! den my thigh still pain for like almost 2 weeks already? strange still can run but if after sprint the pain will increase. hope it doesn't go any worse...den today hehex pon CIP n OCOM lectures! lazy n sianx dun feel like going...reach home very early so happy! nan de(rarely) u know...everyday like reach home at 930pm...iyo...tiring! den i slp the whole afternoon now online...hehex! tt's all...=D     
     
    
</post>
<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      dunno wat title to gif. hmm, i say i wanna study but till now nv! no discipline...say wanna revise my work nv again. stuck in the net...surfing net n chatting. oh gosh i cannot carry on like tis! bad bad bad very bad~ argh...i m aching all over now...blehx =P i better go n study n stop using net! hehex..buaix 
     
    
</post>
<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        tell u a secret! i still dunno how to use tis bloggy lorx...all i know is juz to publish! see so plain, no pics no songs...can't help it i am com idiot! =P  duNno y i m so tired today! i slept all the way in mark zee's lecture! zZz...my inspiration is back...before my inspiration ceases i muz stop it from ceasing(crap) lolx...wAh lao eh...bball n track as cca so tiring lor...ivp coming den bball still cannot stop. i wonder at the end which will i choose to stay...hMm...stats n econs is getting more diff...and horx when ever i reach home and wanna settle down to do hw...i realise i will fall asleep...deep shit man cant carry on tis way! if not i jia lat...i wanna slp now very very tired nitex sweetest dreams...-_-zZz    
     
    
</post>
<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       hehex i m in sch now having CIP lesson...yucks i dislike tis tcher! so naggy like ah ma...i dun feel like going training later so tired! &gt;_</post></Blog>