<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>31,mayo,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      越貼近社會，越發覺得，整個生活逐漸是陷落於某種模式在循環著。 以不同的時間單位切割法，呈現的人生，味道亦有所不同﹔一生彷彿如同股市走勢圖，選擇那死達克式、盜窮式、恆生，還是抬骨式？  從專注於1min、1hr...間發生的瑣事中，暫時脫離，挑遠點再反觀，原來抬骨式高頻率的震盪波動，也可像那死達克式的平穩持續上揚。
     

    
</post>
<date>31,mayo,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink 2TOKYO2 東京設計版圖 
     

    
</post>
<date>31,mayo,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       2004.5.6 - 2004.8.1於北美館展出，分五個階段探討義大利設計文化的蛻變與演進，並以編年方式選自1945~2000年期間的一百件展品，從戰後重建時期到晚近的「追憶與未來再認識」物品，不但兼具源流和現況，且脈絡清晰呈現義大利的設計風貌。這些隸屬於 urlLink 米蘭三年中心 之重要藏品，涵蓋義大利著名設計家各時期的代表性作品，如：卡斯提庸尼( urlLink A. Castiglioni )、門蒂尼( urlLink A.Mendini )、佩薛(G. Pesce)、龐迪( urlLink G.Ponti ) 、羅西(A.Rossi)、索札斯(E. Sottsass)、札努索( urlLink M.Zanuso )等，展品類別包括：打字機、摩托車、電視機、家具、燈飾、器皿以及日常生活用品。本展具有藝術與文化啟示的價值，同時也希冀提供國內文化創意與藝術設計的深層思考。   &gt;&gt;&gt; 6/6  14:30從義大利的設計發展看臺灣的設計趨勢」  &gt;&gt;&gt;鄭源錦（台灣設計創新管理學會理事長） →設計師賦予每件作品的造形、功能、材質及審美價值，這些具有個性與表情姿態的作品豈只是“物品”， 猶如義大利的雕塑與建築一般，讓我們感受到美好生活中的精緻與優雅。它們不僅是近代設計史的重要的器物和符號，更是結合創意理念與科技，投射夢想和現實需求的精湛寫照。傳統典雅及現代化需求，即手工藝與工業化風格之間，多樣豐富，同時反映生活時尚風華，這些都是義大利戰後最具代表性的經典作品。 義大利設計可讓我們以較寬廣的視野來瞭解義大利的全貌，搜羅及介紹許多企業的整體成果，而非強調個人表現。這些依年代排列的作品分成五大部份，並與義大利當代歷史中的重大階段相呼應：其中包括戰後與重建、經濟繁榮、社會動盪不安的年代；消費者瘋狂的年代；最後一個則是上個世紀的末十年，那個汲汲尋求新認同的年代。這麼做是為了要讓大眾明瞭設計的角色和演變，就算是和義大利歷史與文化相距遙遠的台灣觀眾亦然。  &gt;&gt;&gt; 6/19 14:30「義大利設計展」作品賞析  &gt;&gt;&gt;胡寶林（中原大學室內設計系主任） →這些展品來自米蘭三年中心(Triennale di Milano) ，該中心建立於1933年，是義大利以及國際設計界最重要的展演場所之一，尤其關注現代建築設計與工業文化進展的趨勢論壇，該中心策劃探討的課題包括：建築、設計、藝術、家具、時尚、工業產品、都市計劃生態、以及跨領域學門等。     
     

    
</post>
<date>31,mayo,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Dali urlLink   
     

    
</post>
<date>31,mayo,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Dali's wife urlLink     貼張我迷戀→達利﹔達利迷戀→他老婆 測試看看
     

    
</post>
<date>01,junio,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      性別不一定，年齡不一定，不過通常適用於超過14歲之人。 中澤滄人程度不一但全部統稱，可能特徵如下： 經常翻閱COOL雜誌，BANG雜誌，以及壹週刊。 喜愛追隨雜誌的腳步穿衣服，沒有了雜誌就沒了準則。 極度需要團體認同感，一個人便失去了生存目標。 喜愛網路遊戲，聽SHE，HIP-HOP或是砰砰台式電子樂。 認為頭文字D裡出現的畫面和理論是真實可行的。 在網路上玩交友遊戲並各組小團體以此為生活重心。 MSN上面有一長串名字，自己都搞不清楚那些人是誰。 喜愛聽MP3勝於聽CD。 會用注音文字打字，並擅用各種表情符號表達情緒。 朋友非常多，走三步得停兩步打招呼，揮手像是總統一樣頻繁，卻在裡面找不到一個真正了解自己的人。   →疏離的社會關係，渴望被認同，又希望是獨特的個體。 　衝突拉扯的結果產生的是一群，始終未脫離社會化循軌的自我意識。 
     

    
</post>
<date>01,junio,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      人應在正視人生的殘酷和血腥的前提下，投入現世生活， 每個人都要在充滿苦難的抗爭中，完成自己獨特的一生。  世界是荒謬的，人必須忍耐一切， 以至於對一切荒謬形成習慣的態度，人的存在才能達到自由。   →接受人生本是苦痛多於快樂的事實，盡情享受一切，不要有所遺憾 
     

    
</post>
<date>01,junio,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      美國史坦福大學醫學研究所Phillip Marter先生，半年前在網路討論群組發表了一篇文字，引起了許多網友的共鳴，紛紛張貼轉載，歷久不衰，特別介紹給讀者。 如果我們把全球人口壓縮成只有100人的部落，而且維持人類的各種比率，那麼我們會得到：  1.57個亞洲人、21個歐洲人、14個美洲人、8個非洲人 2. 52個男人、48個女人 3. 30個白種人、70個非白種人 4. 30個基督徒、70個非基督徒 5. 89個異性戀者、11個同性戀者 6. 6個人將擁有全部財富的59%，而且這6個人全部來自美國 7. 80個人的居家生活不甚理想 8. 70個文盲 9. 50個人營養不良 10. 1個人即將死亡、1個人即將生產 11. 1個人 (Yes, only ONE!) 擁有大專學歷 12. 1個人擁有電腦  當我們從這樣壓縮的角度來看這個世界時，我們會更清楚這個世界需要更多的接納、諒解、和教育還有一些值得我們深思的： 如果您今天早上醒來時還算健康，恭喜您，因為有一百萬人將活不過一星期。如果您不曾經歷戰爭的危險、被監禁的寂寞、被凌虐的痛苦、或是飢寒交迫，恭喜您，您比5億人還好命。如果您可以參加宗教活動而不必擔心被騷擾、逮捕、凌虐、或死亡，恭喜您，您比30億人還自由。如果您的冰箱裡有食物、有衣服穿、還有地方住，恭喜您，您比全世界75%的人還富有。如果您在銀行有存款、錢包裡有鈔票、還有一些零錢，恭喜您，您是全世界前8%的有錢人。 如果您的雙親都還健在而且沒有離婚，您算是幸運兒。您可以讀這篇文章，那是雙重幸運：有人想到您這個朋友，而且有20億人根本不識字。  工作，可以不必要汲汲營營；盡情跳舞，引喉高歌，管別人怎麼想；讓自己活在人間天堂  
     

    
</post>
<date>01,junio,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink archINFORM  → International Architecture Database   urlLink tribu-design  → Decorative Arts  Design of 20th century  urlLink  Yamagima  　→ 日本家飾網
     

    
</post>
<date>01,junio,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink     Marco Zanuso→ 'Ariante' Fan urlLink    (1916-2001) was one of a group of Italian designers from Milan shaping the international idea of "good design" in the postwar years. Trained in architecture at the Milan Polytechnic, he opened his own design office in 1945. From the beginning of his career, at Domus where he served as the editor from 1947-49 and at Casabella where he was editor from 1952-56, he helped to establish the theories and ideals of the energetic modern design movement. As a professor of architecture, design and town planning at the Polytechnic from the late 1940s until the 1980s, and as one of the founding members of the ADI in the1950s, he also had a distinct influence over the next design generation coming out of Italy.  The major pieces of his career run a broad spectrum from early experiments in bent metal to luxurious, plush furniture to sleek industrial designs in plastic. The underlying motif throughout each phase of his work is that he was pioneering the use and market accessibility of every different material he worked with. Some of his first work to be shown at all, and certainly to be shown outside of Italy, was at the Low-Cost Furniture competition sponsored by the MoMA in 1948. His design featured a metal frame chair that used a breakthrough method to join the fabric seat to the frame. In 1948 Pirelli opened a new division, Arflex, to design seating with foam rubber upholstery. They commissioned Zanuso to produce their first models. His "Antropus" chair came out in 1949, followed by the "Lady" chair, which won first prize at the 1951 Milan Triennial. Zanuso lauded the new material, "One could revolutionize not only the system of upholstery but also the structural manufacturing and formal potential...our prototypes acquired visually exciting and new contours...with industrial standards that were previously unimaginable."   In 1957 he partnered with German designer Richard Sapper. One of their first projects was a small, stackable child's chair (1961) in non-reinforced plastic. This piece was light, functional and playful, manufactured in several bright colors and it was among the furniture designs responsible for convincing people that plastic was a viable and appropriate material for the modern home. Zanuso and Sapper were hired in 1959 as consultants to Brionvega, an Italian company trying to produce stylish electronics that would, at least outwardly, best those being made in Japan and Germany. They designed a series of radios and televisions that became enduring icons of an aesthetic known as "techno-functionalism." Their rounded, compact and portable "Doney 14" (1962) was the first completely transistor television. Working with the language of sculptural minimalism they designed the successful folding "Grillo" telephone for Siemens (1966). This was one of the first phones to put the dial and the earpiece on the same unit.   In a 1972 they designed a series of dwellings for the "New Domestic Landscape" show at the MoMA. Each stacking unit, like ultramodern teepees, unfolded to a living area complete with all the facilities and many of the accessories of a small apartment. Zanuso wrote that they were, "designed for all situations that require immediately available, easily transportable living quarters." As with the rest of their work, the hallmarks of these designs were elegance and imagination.   　¡相關網站!   urlLink Lezionidi design   urlLink Design Addict   urlLink completelymodern   urlLink R   urlLink è 
     

    
</post>
</Blog>