<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Wo...this is my first online diary?! So perhaps i might wanna give it a name so it sounds more...sweet...this is my teddy bear's name too!  Dear Brownie,           Hmm...went to watch The Day After Tomorrow with mummy,wow it was WONDERFUL! It can be counted as one of the best movies i ever watched.The effects are certainly better than what i was anticipating!Hehe...long time never went to take a break le...went to Orchard Road Shaw House ...the night view is certainly pleasant and sort of romantic yar.Now then i know the journey is not that long! So perhaps mummy shall take me to Orchard Road occasionally? Then with my friends we go Shopping too!          Then just came back from Science Centre from the LORD OF THE RINGS EXHIBITION,it was marvellous too.Wow,these few days are sure  MOVIE days.The exhibition showed the unique clothes and the weapons as seen in the movie,although i don't really like the movie,i still give thumbs up because i also learned some effects of how they do the movie!Today was a fruitful and learning day!         Yeah...just now went to play soccer with my siter,it was tiring!Cux that idiot sis kept on scaring me with the dog and seems that the cat and the dog became so good friends and trying to make me jump at my own shadow!HAHA..lalala...well that's all Brownie! :D
       
    
    
</post>
<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yea...the day before tomorrow is...?TODAY! Just got back from Holland Village...yeeps...Bought badminton rackets...long time neva play badminton le...Osh...the shopkeeper of the sports shop was terrible sia..How i hope i could give her a tight slap just now,So RuDE! She was asking in a rash manner ,"are u going to buy them?" Siao la i dont want to buy then i take for wat. Haiz..No COmmon sense sia even if i dont want to buy,so what ...Haiz this kind of people better snap out of my sight.!  WEll...hope hx will change her mind...Join Karate or takewondo or judo or ...with me le...cux it's beta to learn somthing in the green age now rite.So as long we keep a healthy mind n body n academic results are fine,that's all ...  Toro is in SIngapore? yex...going to sign contract with singapore ? 0_0 issit the first time an overseas idol like him doing that? Hehehe...  Yea! FInally found the library book that i renewed...i was thinking that i must pay for lost report..luckily i found it today when my sis asked for posters! HooraY...can save $20 over dollars...with that i can print alot of neoprints with my friends lehx...then somemore i need to buy shopping socks,blah blah...$20 means much to me...cux no money le....keke  Erm,later going to play badminton with my ah jie le...hehe...i think i grew fatter le ! HUH HOW ?DIE? OH MY GODNESS! I can't control my food...or is that my pants shrunk? not pants...should be beach shorts rite?...........Sobssss  Ok brownie...Bye Bye...i gotta leave this bloggie! :D
       
    
    
</post>
<date>10,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yoz...now i am planning for tomorrow ...cux i dont know wat to do tomorrow ...go to the sch lib and meet up with they all?The thought of this makes me sad...they seem to be drifting away further and further away from me...yes...it's happening...cause we have different interests-as in different point of view of society...they want guys-meet guys,fun during class,and i don;t know how to describe. WS had been my best friend she was a wonderful gal,she has what it takes to be a very good friend.The type i had been searching but yet other took her away.Not to be too blunt,it's that i was the one who had not been matching with her? I'm not that sure.I still have my other friends right? Do i have to be like that? No...i'm still satisfied.It's alright with me...Look on the bright side of life...  It's just that i have one shopping campanion less.Still,it made a great difference,a shopping campanion like her ...as i am a great shopper...always looking for excitement must go out one...my other friends always have no time for me to shop with...they are sort of 'workaholics' or they are spending their time on Idol dramas. haiz.not that i am backstabbing them but it's just that i have to go out alone...thinking of getting a boyfriend?...will there be a day that comes...hope so...but i shall have to love myself alot first...yea~wateva then  My passion is music rite? yea...now trying to figure out 'piano'...anyhow play one la~ still can play bits here and there :P ...woo....  Argh...pimple poke out again! SObS! y everytime like that one...i wanna grow taller! hmm...maybe by this year grow till 163?...or at least 160 cm pls god...lala...  Ewww...a mole on the eye meaning attractive? hehe...i have that...but am i attractive? Not so ?...agrees...  Your Life You never live your life in the way others want you to. You are an independent individual who loves challenges and excitement. You are ready to face with the result of your decision. You are usually the one your friends count on. Your Love Because you love excitements, you occasionally get involved in forbidden love affairs. You may fall in love with a married person and no one can stop you from making progress. You are very charming, although you might not realize it.  hoo...think all these really somewhat reveals the true self of me...haha...quite true though..i think    luv brownie bear bear :P
       
    
    
</post>
<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      LiFe is like a breeze? Though things doesn't always go about like how i want it to be i am still struggling for happiness...  Yesh?.....yesteday went back from camp,ya 2days 1 night camp.NO big deal...small fry? haha.~ Yet i slept like a thousand year old log...slept from 5pm to the next day's 12pm...haha   The camp was...quite okay though hard music for 2 days...i am struggling for breath! My trumpet...we are getting ready for outdoor performance-my first outdoor performance.hmm...hope i won't get kicked out of the performance last minute cux of my poor skills...need to buck up le... haha..kk.............................. 
       
    
    
</post>
<date>05,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      A Reccount of today ...i stayed at home after band all day listening and singing to music...hehe  music-Shine,Rock Bang,F.I.R,Ocean o de yang,Daniel zhang feng qi,Huang Yi Da,Hins Zhang Jing Xuan,Fan Fan. tata~  yu jian ni zi hou ai shan ni ran hou heng tou ni yuan lai ai shi yong bu wan de lu xing -yi da   天地一秒 演唱：Shine   这一场雨下得好美丽 把世界和我们暂隔离  我靠近把你看仔细 那么贪心 你浏海上还沾着雨滴  晶莹剔透仿佛有香气 你看着伞外的雨 那么专心   * 这一秒的天地 我想无限延续 好象能 完全拥有你  这画面的记忆 美得无懈可击 深深的留在我心底  这一秒的天地 我想无限延续 才迟疑的不敢打扰你  (一秒比一秒爱你 一秒比一秒爱你 一秒比一秒疯狂的喜欢你)  强忍着 拥抱你 的冲激 *   忽然我开始有点担心 害怕这场雨终究会停  我只能放你回去 那纷乱世界里 怕吵闹的选举扰乱你  怕积水的路面弄脏你 怕风会吹干浏海 芬芳雨滴   Repeat * x 2   这一场雨下得好美丽 把世界和我们暂隔离  我靠近把你看仔细   我们是... 演唱：Shine   我失眠 有你来泡面我失恋 有你来开解  没有钱 我们就跑到天桥做表演  一起看 老师的嘴脸一起为 世界而争辩  要Ｋ书 我们到半夜还在速食店   * 有时候 想快点毕业有时候 怕一切改变  赶在你面前 把梦想说一遍   # 我们是Superstar 有你做我的COVER  我不怕生活找我麻烦我们是Superstar  就当我们躺在老树下(就当我们弹着不结他)  谈未来计划我们是Superstar 有你我觉得伟大  我不怕人家当我傻瓜 我们是Superstar 就算我想退下  总有你拉我一把   我很想 唱自己的歌我也想 拍自己的戏  全宿舍 只有你了解 我口中狂言  一起猜 明天的考卷一起聊 不管到几点  是兄弟 作战就并肩 同病就相连   Repeat * #   心情好 就冲到阳明山看城市在脚下  看未来 天大地大 梦想更大  我们是Superstar 有你做我的COVER  我不怕生活找我麻烦 我们是Superstar  就当我们躺在老树下 谈未来计划  我们是Superstar 有你我觉得伟大  我不怕人家当我傻瓜 我们是Superstar 相信我吧   Repeat   从校园走到天下 我们是Superstar   -shine (LOVE IT)thumbs Up* :D  wo xiang ni de kuai le shi yin wei wo zhe shi yi zhong jiao ao de mei li zhi yao ni dui wo za za yan wo jiu wei xiao -Rock Bang  Lydia~mei li de yan kuang... ta zhou le ni ke yi ba meng liu xia zhong you ge de fang deng dai ai feng xiang~ -F.I.R  si miao -lyrics too complicated :P -Daniel Zhang Feng Qi  Leng feng shoo shoo shoo song zhou wo de ai~ shao le wo de shou bi dang zheng tou ni xi bu xi guan ni de wang yuan jing wang bu dao wo gu dang de bei ban qiu -Ocean odeyang  静静地陪你走了好远好远 连眼睛红了都没有发现 听着你说你现在的改变 看着我依然最爱你的笑脸 这条旧路依然没有改变 以往的每次路过都是晴天 想起我们有过的从前 泪水就一点一点开始蔓延 我转过我的脸 不让你看见 深藏的暗涌已经越来越明显 过完了今天 就不要再见面 我害怕每天醒来想你好几遍 我吻过你的脸 你双手曾在我的双肩 感觉有那么甜我那么依恋 每当我闭上眼 我总是可以看见 失信的诺言全部都会实现 我吻过你的脸 你已经不在我的身边 虽然你不在我的身边 我还是祝福你过得好一点 断开的感情线 我不要做断点 只想在睡前再听见你的 蜜语甜言 -Hins Zhang jing xuan  1.i'm thinking of you wo you ni zheng hao   ni neng rang fan nao bian de miao xiao   wo yu jian yi ge jiu dong wo de ren  wo hui ti xing zi ji ba zhe fen ai shou hao 2.jiu qu de meng xiang jue due hui dao da`lalala 3.xiang dao da ming tian xian zhai jiu yao qi chen  ni neng rang wo kan jian wei lai de lu cheng -Fan Fan  
       
    
    
</post>
<date>01,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Dear dear brownie                  today nothing...? Went to jurong east to walk about in the Cd Shop and splurged money to buy Fan Fan's latest cd...now no money ...how am i going to survive? So also no money to eat lunch so just bought a 70 cents bread...Maybe i should save more cux now i spent more money nowadays on shopping.                  okay...then went bm library orhz...as jurong's is opening only in 5th june...borrowed one chinese book on youth hehe...it talks about the life of a youth-romance,ignorance,etc...then went to band. Just another blowing day,preparation for Macritchie Performance,haiz 2 seniors never come.When J come,X neva come and vice versa~.Y was sick!Again?~take care...nowadays many ppl sick ...perhaps of weather?n that reminds me of The day after tomorrow! i wanna watch it again n again! Maybe i buy the VCD? i Saw the Book in Kinokuniya! still,the movie is better than book right...hehe never mind...                  Yea`reached home at 5 pm...tired...listening to FanFan's Cd...Superb...it's full of heart-felt songs. Full of emotions,other cds only talk about Romance but this talks most of happiness in life like angel and dream ...Zhui Chu De Mong Xiang! And i like singers who compose songs themselves...rather than like some "ppl" only depend on looks n sing horribly yet proud? Lolx...i wanna be a wonderful musician! Can i? i wait... i shall compose n pen my own lyrics yea...~                       I really can't express very well how much i luv music,why?i Dunno...Perhaps perhaps perhaps...Maybe because some songs are ways of communicating and heart-felt themes...Describes my feelings and mood and life...Though,it's some sort of weird? not weird i should say...it's because i seems to like music my friends don't...they like Jolin,Jay..lalala...haha ....and i dun really...it's okay la.                 Hmm...kinda hot now...drink water? Yea i should cux jus now drank lots of soft drink must use pure water to replace...later got diabetes?   kekeke...lolx!                  Tomorrow i stay at home and slack...yea cux these few days quite busy orhz then no time to rest...today i met the neighbour's friend again...we dunno each other..he's bout my age? not sure or perhaps younger than me...but he always has the weird sight when seeing me come out of lift n that's where i always see him...opps..?No nothing...prefer guys taller than me hehe lala! Ok ok...continue to pursue my dream! :D                 *gave brownie a kiss on the nose*                      
       
    
    
</post>
<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It's been days i neva logged in...Hmm saturday's SYF was not bad lar...though quite boring n was slapping flies all over. Nearly SLeEp sia~wat kind of festival lar?? YOuth Festival?? LIke OLD festival BahZ.  TomorroW aint i going play BIlliarD?POOl? yesh.....Can't make up my mind...That Idiot SM going ar...SHe's SOmtimes FIne sometimES jus CAn't BE botheRed to CarE her FUckING attituDE~ Well waTeva not my prob......Just Ignore!  WEll.....Just nOW went TO chinATOWn yoz....Did somE shopping...Arh hmm. BEta Stop HERe,NOthing TO expRess TOnite? Cux     no feelINgs LE i becomE a DeVIl! 
       
    
    
</post>
</Blog>