<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>31,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Wheeee, I'm just using this to comment in Trey's blog. Don't expect any posts. Go to my LJ if you want that.   urlLink  
      
</post>
<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      My lips are all bruised...       I didn't know lips could bruise. -_-'
      
</post>
<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So. Expect this to be a very long and crazy entry, people. It's the 4 in the morning and I'm totally on a sugar high, yo. :D  Soooo, today...well, actually, yesterday, I went over to Trey's. Again. ^_^ That seems to be all I've been doing lately. Hm. OHHHH WELL. I like hanging out with him. :D So, anyway, I went over there at around 11:15 and woke him up. He didn't look too happy about it. o_0 Sorry, Trey. &gt;_  We ended up hanging out in his room and watching TV and stuff until about 4 (among other things ;D) After he did some merit badge stuff we got ready to go to Hamilton Pool. WHEEEEEEE. Fun stuff. :D We stayed there for about two hours, most of that time consisting of us dunking eachother under the water. XD   After leaving around 6 Trey's mom decided to stop at McDonald's for food. I wasn't going to get anything, but Trey kinda forced me to because he thinks I never eat. O_O I do, just not until about 2 in the morning when I've realized I haven't eaten anything at all that day. XD So, yeah...Trey now thinks I'm an alien who only eats about once a month. Great. -_-'  We went back to his house to eat our food. But Nolan's friend who was over, took my food thinking it was his. Little fucker XD. So I ended up eating Trey's sandwich and Trey ended up eating Nolan's friend's nuggets...o_0 I told Trey he should eat his own burger, but he didn't want to. =/ Blahhhh.  I left his house at around 8 and got back home around 8:30. Since, you know, I live in fucking Texass now apparently. bvuieabivgubiergb. Blaahhh.  I got onto the computer immediately, since it's what my life revloves around pretty much. I started talking to Bruce, and somehow the topic of marriage came up and we ended up planning our two weddings for the next hour and a half. w00t, go losers! *waves flag*   Now, just because I feeeeel like it, I'm going to give you a basic outline of what I'd like my wedding to be like. ^_^  - Very classic/traditional. Though, I was wondering....what do atheists do for weddings? I mean...they mostly revolve around religion. Likeomgwtf. - Outdoors. Much prettier. ^_^ - Both my husband and I write our own vows.  - The floral stuff will consist of roses. Only roses. Red/white ones. XD - I want a long dress...but I don't want it to be too prissy, covered up, etc. I think I'd really like a strapless one with an uber long train and a really simple, but pretty veil. Like, a classic themed dress...but modern at the same time....that didn't make sense...*sigh* - Red Bride's Maid dresses - My dad better be there to give me away, or else I'm going to really depressed. =( I love my Dad too much, he better show up O_O - When we're walking out of the church, the people are throwing RICE, not blowing bubbles. Bubbles are lame. -_-' - We drive away in a horse drawn buggy ^_~  And then, of course, there's the RECEPTION! Party, baby. ^_~  - On a seaside pavillion (stole this from Bruce XD) - Lots of lights,  flowers , fountains, etc. Oh, and a lot of candles too. :P - As everyone's walking in, I'd like there to be like a chamber music group playing something like ball music. But, after they play a few pieces, we could play songs from our childhood, like..."It's Getting Hot In Here" or "Get Low" XDXDXD - We're gonna have a slide show, yo. Like filled with pictures of me and whoever my husband will be and us with our friends and when we were little and such. (also stolen from Bruce XD) - Top-notch food, only the best - A bar of course. What's a reception without crazy, drunk family making fools of themselves?! - HUGE cake. That way, after we cut it, it won't matter how much of it I stick in my husband's face XD - A professional photographer, of course - And then, after the guests are free to do what they want, we'll have a FIREWORKS SHOW! (ALSO stolen from Bruce XD)   Yup, that's my wedding in a nutshell. Not that any of you care or anything O_O. And of course, this is inferring that I actually find someone who would want to marry me. &gt;_  Anyway, after me and Bruce finished planning our entire future(XD), Trey called and I talked to him for a few hours. ^_^ That's always enjoyable. =P  And now...I'm sitting here...writing this...singing. O_O   I'm really glad none of you can hear me right now. I'm a horrible singer. &gt;_  -Alysia  P.S. Trey and I have been together for 3 months, today. :D  I love you, Trey. </post></Blog>