<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It’s like only once a week I write here…so many things can just happen…*phew*…so I think I should start. Till now, God never really revealed Himself to me but I learned something else. It should be in the later part of this blog. This morning, I woke up and I actually dreaded to go to school although I wasn’t sleepy and I was kinda awake but in any ways, I still go to school. I was kinda worried in school coz something is going to get wrong somehow…on Wednesday night, I told “her” that I want to talk to her and we set appointment. Then I started to dream that very night I asked her. I dreamt that we were enemies and we didn’t talk to each other at all. We hated each other a lot. And when I awoke, I was like I hope that won’t happen or not I’m going to be dead. Then, today I went and talk to her lar.at fist I dunno where she disappear. She’s just no where. Not sure. The after that I felt so thirsty and thought that I should go get water and then I band into Grace and she say Serena wants to see me. So went and find for Serena forgetting bout my hungry stomach and my thirsty mouth. And then when I met her she was like: are you free now? And I said I don’t think so. She was like: Oh then never mind. Just want to ask whether you want to do the newsletter. You want?....okay…at that moment ar…I also dunno what to say coz I really want to do but I scared I can’t handle so many things. But ended up I say okaylar coz I don’t think it will be hard lar…some how I will find the time wan. Oh yar…then in the morning right, Su Yi told me I’m in the worship team. At that moment I was like wanna scream already…I was really happy and excited lar…I was really desperate lar…it’s three years already I applied to be a vocalist…so I was overjoyed lar. Okay. I think I should continue. So I finish talking to Serena and then “she” appeared. I was like…there you are. I walked her to block G to put her bag first. But on the way, she asked me what I wanted to tell her. I told her that she’s know later. Then she start guessing lar and then she say ‘is it about me?’…then I was like ‘erm…something like that lar’…I think that’s what I say…it’s somewhere there lar. and then she so suddenly say ‘then I don’t want to talk about it’. I was so so hurt at that moment. I didn’t know what to do. I just got kinda stunt at that moment but I’m still walking and talking lar…I was kinda disappointed coz I put aside all my cowardliness and took up all my guts to talk to her. I have a problem in talking to people face to face especially when it’s some kind of problem. I was very disappointed and I didn’t know what to do. I tried to make as if nothing is wrong and it’s okay…I went up the stairs towards the canteen lar. When I was about to go up the stairs, “she” called me lar but I turn behind and she didn’t look as if she just called me. But then she so suddenly she appear next to me lar. And then she ate her fries while talking to me lar. we went into one of the classes in block E…and we started talking. It wasn’t what I expected lar…I couldn’t really talk to her. My heart was beating so fast…and one scary thing…she say ‘look at me!’…I was like…arrrrrr….she look so scary. Very scary indeed. Staring at someone is not nice. Then we started the conversation. I have to keep quiet for like a few minutes coz my heart feels like coming out and I feel like leaving the place. While talking to her, it seems like I dunno what to say. My words are all gone. My heart wasn’t there. It pumped out of me already. It’s so hard for me to get all the words out. Then I told her bout everything…not exactly everything coz I totally forget what I want to tell her and what I want to ask her. Just staring at her makes me want to run away already. And then after that she asked me a few things…actually a lot of things….and she told me a lot of things also. ‘I realized that I’m not the first one you have this problem with. And I don’t think I’m wrong and there’s nothing wrong with me. I treat everyone the same. You just have to know. You should sit down and ask yourself what you want and how you really feel. You know, I don’t feel hurt or angry. But I feel sad for you.’ I was kinda quiet. Thinking about what she was saying. And I told her that I know it’s because of me but then I really can’t understand myself and I dunno how to look within myself. I really don’t know and I think that’s why I can’t really get along with people. And she actually went through a lot. She went through all this before. And then I start to try to change topic. I don’t want to continue like that coz we kept quiet for some time. I was thinking a lot and she just stare at me. So I told her about everything in my heart. My family, my friends and my walk with God and most of the things I am going through, she went through before. She told me a lot of things which really encourages me. And God really spoke through her to me. Faith is not feeling or something you can see but something you believe although you can’t see or feel it. And I should be very grateful coz I’ve known God at this age. I thought of everything she said. No family is perfect. Everything we’re gong through helps to build up my faith. I don’t know how’s it going to help me yet but I’ll wait and see.  And today, manda came for CF. I miss her a lot…she seems taller I think. And then the speaker, pastor melcam…I think…can’t remember his name and dunno how to spell. Anyways, he really spoke to me especially near the end…keeping the fire burning and how to get caught in the fire. And that I should stand firm, do my quiet time and trust in Him. Maybe slowly I’ll see the difference. Everyone is experiencing different things and yarlor.  In any ways, I’m seriously very happy now coz I can sing….heehe…and I got a chance to serve God…I got to do the newsletter...i’m actually very desperate although I might have to make my whole schedule even more pack…but I really want to serve God…He’s so big and even as I face a giant I’ll still look at the giant like it’s so small coz I have an even BIGGER GOD!!!! AMEN!…ohyar…I hope I will remember to bring an empty cd for Serena on Monday. Have to get rid of the forgetful me. okaylar…I think this should be all for now…hope to blog again soon…my exams are so near already. I’ve like exactly 100 more days to study only. Hopefully by God’s grace, I can get really results. My parents are kinda pressuring me now. Okaylar…got to go…bye!! Love, Jovy. 
       
    
    
</post>
<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      dear diary, you know what….there’s still no changes and I’m getting even further and further already. and just now, I told God that if today tze yuen would call me, it means that He will do something…and all I need to do is wait…but it will be in this 8 days time lar…and if tze yuen didn’t call me, it means that nothing will happen and I will just backslide lar. and so, now I also dunno what to do….if tze yuen never call me today, should I still continue to wait till the time comes…I really don’t know…and now, I’m really not sure with everything….i remember something I once read in my devotionals…it said that God can do much greater things than you can ever imagine…then how come He can’t just do this small thing for me…okay…I shall not continue blabbering….bored already. haisheh…I wonder…I wonder…dunnolar…we’ll see…I thought of talking to stef about how I felt bout her but I don’t know how…and I want to do it by this week coz I scared that if after this week, then maybe I will not even be a Christian anymore then how…I don’t know…there’s so many things I want ot ask her and there’s so many things a want to tell her…but when I look at her, it seems like there’s nothing for me to say…my words just go missing…and I think I find her kinda scary…though friendly lar…I hope tze yuen remembers the appointment we will be having tomorrow morning before school. I’ll see whether I should do it this Friday or not…or not then see lar…have to see she’s free or not also…okaylar…gtg...bye.love, Jovy. 
       
    
    
</post>
<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Dear diary, I don’t know what to do now…my leg so pain and I had to limp…anyways…that’s not the reason I blog here…there’s like 6 more days…last Saturday…I was suppose to go for prayer in church but I couldn’t go so I pray at home lar…and during prayer, there are so many things I didn’t expect alr…it’s been some time since I really spend time with God telling Him everything and how I feel and things like that lar…and when I spoke to Him…the starting was like normal lar…all the prayer items and things like that…and then only I start really talking to Him…I was under my blanket…hot in there…and through the prayer…I was really tired and I was really lost…I didn’t know where was God anymore…I don’t know whether is He still real to me…I even doubt a lot…whether is there really a God out there…I didn’t know…and I really seek Him and I really prayed really hard…I want Him to be real to me…I’ve gone through most of the time this year without Him….even though I’ve been encouraging people to hold on to Him but I don’t know about myself…I cried and cried…I plead to Him…I really want to know the answers…all the questions which stayed unanswered…I really don’t know…and that very moment, I challenge God…and I think it’s not a very good challenge lar…I was like: God, if you still love me, if you still want me, if you’re still there for me, please...please God let me see…let me know…and let me feel You again…and God, You see me through…and You know me best…God, if you are the true God…the Almighty God…if You are real…open my eyes…and my hearts…let me feel Your touch and Your love again…I know that this might not be the right time yet…but there’s 8 days…by Sunday, I hope there would be a difference…and I really hope that you heard my prayers…Lord, pick me up again. That was part of my prayer to God…I really don’t know but it was exactly how I felt at that moment…last year, something like that happen also and I really had a hard time through it…I had a few people help me up and I found my way again. But this year, I really don’t want to disturb anyone…and if God really is real, He will bring me home. That’s all I know. this year, I’m having PMR and many are having SPM…I really don’t want to disturb any of them…I know that somehow…somehow…everything would be fine…I hope…I’ve been really worried…I really don’t know…and I dunno what to do now…just sit down and wait…I’ve seek for Him for 15 years already…and I really have no strength anymore…coz I know that no matter how I seek for Him but if He doesn’t draw me back…there’s no use and I’m starting to give up…I dunno…I really don’t know…Love, Dunno… 
       
    
    
</post>
<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      heyo!!! wow….yeh yeh!!....today CF is awesome…I think this is the first time I actually am going to CF feeling very relieved and not so much worries and thoughts…this is the first time I actually go to CF in peace…like I say, I never ask my mum lar…and through the whole morning…school lar…I’ve been thinking a lot…and I really can sense that something is not right….and that something is going to go wrong somehow…I felt so confused and worried…I felt so scared of what’s going to happen and will I be a ble to go for CF…will my mum just pop up in CF and say I’ve to go home…I really don’t know…I was very scared….and ended up…when school ended…I went to the toilet and then I went to put my bag and then went straight to call my mum…while I was waiting in the line, I was like thinking and guessing a lot…if my mum say I have to go home then how…and if she scold me how…but in the other hand…if she say okay then at least I think I won’t feel so bad kua…I really didn’t know…I was very scared…my heart was beating so fast…and when I dialed the number, she picked up the phone and I told her that I’m going CF and that Melissa is fetching me home…actually I wrote it on the white board in my kitchen already wan but jus tin case she don’t allow lar…and guess what she say….she say okay…I was like ‘okaylar…bye!!’…I was so happy lar…coz I got to stay for CF and I really feel a lot better….i felt no worries…there’s such great joy and peace in my heart…and also today….i never really talk much to the form 5s coz I dunno why…seems to slowly drift away already lar…I can’t really talk to them anymore…not much already…I don’t really know why lar but yarlor…I was with Joyce and Evelyn…and we talk a lot…yarlor…for a change lor…mix with others more…Melissa ushering mar and Tze Yuen she go toilet…and never return…so yarlor….at least I enjoy talking to Joyce and Evelyn…it’s nice chatting with them…at least it doesn’t remind me of any problems lar….today I’m kinda weird also lar…when I meet Joyce and Evelyn in the canteen, I saw Stefenie and Pei Wern and a lot more people lar…but I never say hi to them as if I never see them….but I never really look at them anyway…just make as if yarlor…but today was a kinda perfect Friday… in school today ar….let’s see…bm…class teacher plan the school carnival thing and we’re doing haunted house…and I’m the flier-girl…with Suk Teng and Pei Jie…but then I can be the ghost also if I want lar…but I have to see coz I scared I can’t make it for that day…got church lar….and James is suppose to give me the article…so see first lar…maybe I can ask my sis to help me get from him and yarlar…since the ghost thing…we started talking bout ghost a lot…eheh…and we were wondering if a small kid would go in and then got shock by the ghost and started crying…then how ar…the ghost comfort the kid…wow…ghost can comfort kids…that’s cool….how nice…friendly ghost…dunnolar…we’ll seeeeee….and then during moral…Cik Magdalene is our teacher lar and she ask us to go into groups and act out a drama using any of the nilai morals…and my group ‘kasih sayang’…and we came out with a story where a we get back results and then one of us did really badly…and couldn’t accept the fact lar…and wanted to die…jump down the building but then the other tow and the teacher stopped her…and so on lar…but hten ended up we didn’t do the dramam coz not enough time…wait lar…next lesson… and this Sunday….teach small kids…scary…hopefully they will listen somehow…and hopefully I don’t lost my temper…I won’t lar…I think….heheh…not so fast wan…but then the materials all also I haven’t get yet…I have to get it later…I just remember…dielor…so many things…nevermindlar…I’ll make it wan…besides that…I can’t really remember what already…ohyar…today during science in science lab, I and Melissa played a game call ‘look and don’t laugh’…through the whole game, so many interruptions…and we started so many times until the last time where we just stare and stare lar…neither one of us laugh and just stare and stare…but for me, I just stare lar and I was thinking of a lot of things…whenever I just stare at something too long already, I’ll start to think a lot…and that’s what happen lar…I just think lar…and the first thing I thought of is the time when my great grandmother pass away…when I was standard 5….although I wasn’t close to her and I only see her like less then 10 times a year…but she’s very nice…when she passed away, I was really sad and I cried…she wasn’t a Christian…and I was very disappointed…I just cried through…and as I stare at Melissa, my mind is drifting towards that very moment and Melissa changed into my great grandmother…and then after that, my mind flash to another scene…and Melissa turn into Stefenie now…and the sleepover night start to come back again…the time when Stefenie was just staring at us…and I didn’t dare to talk…I was just looking at her…my heart was beating so fast…I was about to cry and then I told her that I was the one who secret-mailed her and she said she knows and she’s proud of me…for telling her lar…and she gave me a hug…a big hug….but in my heart…I really don’t know…there are so many things…I felt so scared…I feel I’m lost…and I feel really bad…there are a lot of things in my heart that I never told her…and I dunno how to tell her…I didn’t dare to…all I did was smile and pretend like nothing…I was worried lar…and at that very moment Melissa look at me lar…the whole scene just pop off…and Melissa ask me whether am I okay or not…and I was kinda blur lar but I say I was okay and one thing is that…she say I was crying…I didn’t realize lar…but dunnolar…scary lar…just pausing for a moment can make me think so much…and in between all those thoughts there is also another thing lar…then after that, I just start thinking of why I’m still thinking of that lar…my great grandmother is not a Christian and that moment had really make me want to save each and everyone of my close ones…so many people is dieing and I really want lives to be saved…I don’t want to see people die some more…I’m scared…I dunno…that incident of my great grandmother’s death had motivate me to bring people to Christ…and I’m still kidna working on that lar…and bout Stefenie, I think it’s coz not everything is solve yet and nothing is done yet…and I’m worried lar…so yarlor…for now, I just don’t want to think of it…headache only…okay…today CF was soooooo SUPERB!!! they have testimonials and I just found out that Keshia only came to know God when she was form 1 and accepted Christ verbally when she was in form 2…that’s a surprise. and becoming a committee for camp is really tough…wow…I wonder man…and I bought camp t-shirt…it’s so nice…I got the camp book too…I love it so much…I think I will hug it to sleep tonight…today ended up really fun and it started really fun too…but then in the morning I got tummy ache lar…ate something wrong kua…but it went off after a while and came back again and I don’t care already…hehehe….okaylar…that’s all for now…bye!!! Love, Jovy. 
       
    
    
</post>
<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      dear diary, there's so many things i want to say but i dunno where to begin...there's so many things happen lately...friends got problem and i've been thinking very far and very much...and now, i don't even know whether my mum allow me to go CF or not and now is already friday...haiyo...okay...yesterday, i was doing stef's auto book...until 11 i think... i never really expect ot take soooo long and i actually took up 10 pages....heheeh...dunnolar...i think it's just me...like to write a lot...leave as much memory as possible...if can lar...i wish she got a bigger book. then i can write more. okay...while i'm doing stef's book, i called Tze Yuen and we chit chat lar and then i told her what happen lar: i have a friend...A...and another friend...B...they both actually very close wan but today just right after recess i dunno how but they so suddenly stop being friends and then when i see them...they were saperated...can't even sit next to each other...stand next to each other...talk to each other...look at each other...and me as the middle person is memang force to stand in between them...don't want to look at each other mar...haiyo....i ask them what happen and A say 'dunno, ask her lar...'...i adk B she say 'ask her lar'...and now, i dunno who to ask and then i say 'how to ask wor...ask both ar...ish'...i shall continue later...got to go school now....
       
    
    
</post>
<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      dear diary, i'm not very sure how i feel now...i'm so confused...there's this girl i know and she was once my role model...but now she's not lar...after i get to know her more...she's a pastor's daughter and i really thought she would be a really good example to me till i meet the real her and her surroundings...and i don't know why i just start to dislike her character...not her but ehr character...she's a very nice girl and very friendly when her friends are not around...and true that she can get along with people easily if she wants but she stays in her group most of the time...and now, i'm not sure why i feel like so but then i think she don't really like me...i think she's trying to avoid me...i secret mail her before lar and i relaly hope it's not becoz of that lar...really hope it's not becoz of that...please tell me it's not becoz of that...i will really really regret...now my heart also cannot go in peace...it's like gong round and round my head...she can be kinda bad you know...who knows right??? okay....i'm not suppose to dislike anyone...ish...have to think of what to do and ask God to help me up again...help me to love and love and love...okaylar...  let's see...today cfers came back from camp....wow!!!...how i miss them so much...they sound soooo tired and dead...stef didn't sleep at all for the whole 3 nights...and she ran sooo much...keshia mummy...i call her at 8 and her dad she she sleep already...wow...she must be really really really really tired...poor girl...all the campers must be having their nice sweet time sleeping now...how sweet...hopefully they will wake up tomorrow...awake...hehe...and may God strengthen them...anyways...gtg now...bye...
       
    
    
</post>
<date>08,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Yoyoyo!!!!!! Today is CF camp....so fast....i’m wondering what are they doing now....i really wish i could be there...*sadz*....anyways, i’ve rested for the past whole week and this week i’ve to start doing homework and finish up all my projects...*sigh*...at lest there’s not much homework...*phew*....yesterday, i rewrite my ‘new year’s resolution’...in a nicer and harden piece of paper and i spent 2 hours doing it...haha...and i realize also that i’ve not really done much especially the studying part....and also the part about knowing God more...and i’m really working on getting closer to my parents...since my dad’s birthday on the 5th, i’ve been trying to be the good girl and respect him a lot…try not to hate him and try to understand lar….and so far, it’s kinda okay…it’s not that difficult and I like it this way coz at least I feel that I belong to the family and I don’t feel left out alr…I’m trying my best to no make him angry for the rest of this year…I know deep down in my heart there’s still love towards my dad no matter how bad or harsh he’d been to me…God id seriously working lor…I’ve been praying bout it…for my family, for my friends… I’m still wondering how to learn more bout God…I want to go Salvations but my mum don’t think she’ll allow…haiya…how to search through internet…I’ll go check out…anyways…this should be all for now…byes…God Bless!! Love, Jovy. 
       
    
    
</post>
<date>06,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      heyo!! it's been a very tiring day...the whole day out...went to church and then go shopping then go to my uncle's house. let's start with church...today in church, we talk about love and seriously i'm still thinking of something...dunnolar...then during second session, we had committee meeting...it was kinda fun but the president(James) and Teck Meng never come...so sorta quiet and they will miss a lot fo things...besides that, we did feedback on the 'Lost and Found' night...there are a lot of changes we had to make and for me, i think i have to be more aware and build my communication skills...and also do my very very very best to put God first in everything i do, say and think...i want to make a difference in my youth and i want to see the fire burning brightly in everyone's life...this year, i really really want to make a difference in my home, school and youth...i've been kinda praying bout it...and God is seriously working...He's been opening doors for me but sometimes i dunno how to use the doors...i enter half way and then i dunno where to turn...and i think i'm really starting to learn as i meet more nad more people...God is seriously teaching and guiding me through...i've really want to make a difference in my home...my family...not just my small family but my big big family tree...my cousins...today, i visited my uncle. i never really talk to my uncle coz they speak chinese...i went and talk to my cousins...who are bout 26 and 27 i think...somewhere there...i was chit chatting when all of a sudden they started talking bout Christianity and religions...they ask a lot of questions...there are even questions i dunno how to answer....kinda tuff...proofs that i don't really know much yet and i need to move on...but after talking to them, i'm not sure whether i planted a seed or watered a seed....i'm not sure but i really can't do much...sometimes, i think they know more than i do although they are not Christians...in the car, i thought of it for a very long time...how should i answer the questions...if next time i face this kind of questions again, how should i reply...i really dn't know and i really want to know...i wish i can have a bible class where i can just go to when i really need answers...i know i don't know a lot still but i dunno how to know more. i don't know how...i need help and that one is really really need help...God is seriously helping me and answering my prayers...but i'm not ready and i didn't know...i kept on asking God to open doors for me but i'm not ready...not that i'm too young...just that i haven't get ready the answers...i haven't know bout my own belief deeply yet...and for now,i guess i should stay put to studying bout the Bible and and bout Christianity...i really got to know more...a lot more... i also got stuck with one song...not exactly a song but it's a game lar...it goes like...Malaysia sofamiredola lai ya lai ya tat tat tat...laiya laiya tat tat tat...1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10...hehe...young kids play but i like it too...just learnt it...today's worship was good also although there wasn't drum...kinda quiet lar...without drum...not enough noise from the drums...but it was good...we can worship God even if there isn't music coz music is not all that matters...Jesus Rox!! Amen!! love, Jovy.
       
    
    
</post>
<date>02,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      hey people!!! my birthday just pass and i'm trying to get a new blog....i just can't do it...confusing....
       
    
    
</post>
<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      You know what…I haven’t tell serena that I don’t want to do the newsletter already…I dunno how to tell her…I finish doing the one she gave me already but I haven’t tell her that I can’t help her to do the newsletter everytime already…I don’t dare to tell her…later she gets really disappointed…how….arrrr….i really don’t know…how….what should I do next…haih...okaylar…I got to go already…it’s 86 days to pmr…bye…love, Jovy…
       
    
    
</post>
</Blog>