<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      SKOOL REOPENS TOMORROW AND I STILL HAVENT LOOK AT MY HW...LET ALONE DONE IT.THIS SUX...CAUGHT UNPREPARED AGAIN.JUZ CANT WAIT FOR DAT KWOK TO SCOLD ME AGAIN AND STARTS ACCUSING ME OF DAYDREAMING IN CLASS.CRAP...I JUZ WOKE UP FROM A NAP.MUAHAHHAZ...THIS IS COOL.LIFE IS TOO IMPORTANT TO BE TAKEN SERIOUSLY...  ANYWAES,HAVE BAND DAILY.5 AND 1/2 DAY MORE TO COMP.NEARLY BROKE MY THUMB FROM TWIRLING WATEVER DAT NEEDS TO BE TWIRLED.IT WAS FUN...SAD... FUN CUZ I'M DOING WAT I ENJOYED.FUN CUZ I GET TO BE WITH MY FRENZ AND CAN FORGET ABOUT LIFE FOR A MOMENT.BAND IS GREAT.  SAD CUZ I FEEL LIKE A HYPOCRITE.I FIND IT DIFFICULT TO HATE AND LOVE...BUT EASY TO LIKE AND DISLIKE.I CANT BRING MYSELF TO HATE DAT SUMONE BUT I WONT FORCE MYSELF TO HATE DAT SUMONE JUZ COZ MOST OF DE P'PLE HATE DAT SUMONE EITHER.I'VE TOLD THEM DAT I JUZ DISLIKED DAT SUMONE BUT I'M NEVER ON DE VERGE OF HATING DAT SUMONE.CAN I MAKE IT ANY CLEARER?WHEN I TALK TO DAT SUMONE,THEY THOUGHT I LIKE DAT SUMONE BUT I JUZ TALK TO DAT SUMONE CUZ DAT SUMONE IS MY FREN...EVEN IF I LIKE OR DISLIKE DAT SUMONE,HE OR SHE IS STILL MY FREN.BUT SUMTIMES,I TALK ABOUT HIM OR HER BEHING HIM OR HER BACK AND I FEEL LIKE A HYPOCRITE.BUT AT DAT POINT WHEN I WAS TALKING ABOUT DAT SUMONE...I REALLY MEAN WAT I SAID BUT AFTERWARDS...I FEEL LIKE A WORTHLESS,NONSENSICAL BITCH WHU IS A HYPOCRITE NOT FIT TO DESERVE ANY FRENZ.MAYBE IT IS TRUE... NVM IF U DONT UNDERSTAND THIS POST.TREAT IT JUZ AS A PLAIN PIECE OF CRAP.BUT IF U UNDERSTAND WHU I WAS REFERRING TO DAT SUMONE,JUZ FORGET WAT THIS IS AND TREAT IT AS A PIECE OF SHIT...THX...                          ~NEARLY 5 MORE DAYS TO COMP~
    
</post>
<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      woohoo!!finally!!i got my new ez-link..phew...a relief from de misery of purchasing standard tickets everyday and digging into my wallet for coins to board de bus...so happy sia!!  tomorrow,there'll be band prac.woohoo!!yippee!!happy happy happy...yeah ok..lame..  yesterdae,band prac...almost everyone cried.the alumni and bandmasters were angry at us.then,de mojors give a 'talk'.touching sia...then,weiqi fainted.it was scary...watching her fall to de ground while i was sitting there and watching.hope she'll get well soon..then,de 'drummers' were supposed to fall in.leon didnt cuz he dont need to push de drum.so,i asked de person next to me if he need to fall in and he say yeah.so,i ask him how to tell him to fall in and he say juz shout.me...being totally clueless....shouted'LEON!!....PLS FALL IN!!' i tot he didnt hear so i was about to shout louder but he came...then,shortly after i shouted...sum p'ple laugh.anywayz,then this one gurl in de flaggies got a position in main block and i was supposed to take her place.vanessa is de one whu told me about it first but tot she jking so,i juz laf lor.then,it was later confirmed by sumone.but i dunno...i'm quite happy being in drummers...but watever...still got 19 more hours to decide.wat for rush things? then,fall in in de hall.we are allowed to do de same gimmicks as de main block for dat time.quite hilarious...then,leon dont noe where to stand and there was one empty space in front of me and he want to exchange place.so,i tell him cannot and juz get on with life cuz i develop a slight soarthroat after shouting at him and his reply was funny...he said he tot it was an alumni whu tell him to fall in...muahahahhahz.  then,got home earlier.at 5:45 pm instead of 6:30 pm...i took de long route to de busstop as usual after band prac.de route which cuts through gmps.i like to walk there.no one was there...then it was deserted..so peaceful..calm my mind after a long day.yeah okay..it is getting a bit too sentimental..  then,arrived at de busstop...nearly missed de bus 135 cuz i was too busy reading a poster about an outdated competition.then,had to run a few meters away from de busstop...nice...got home at 8 pm sharp...ate dinner,shower,then switch on de comp. @@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@@ today...juz got home from my aunt's house.nothing much...get my new ez-link...bought sum new hairclips...basically...nuthing much. #-#-#-#-#-#-#-#-#-#-#-#-#-#-#-#-#-#-#-#-#-#-#-#-#-#-#-#-#-#-#-#-#- 
    
</post>
<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      watever happens...all i want is dat wat my sis say this morning will not cum true...  TK standard is dropping and this year,bowen is better..hahhaz...i cant wait for de downfall of tk...  dat is wat she said.sumthing like dat.i'm not prepared to lose.but neither did i believe dat we can win...  today,there's band prac.  watever it is...i'm praying dat TK BAND will win.  juz hope for a miracle.  juz work hard to achieve the standard...  practice and give all i've got...  watever it is...i'm trying to avoid talking about 3rd of july for de time being...    
    
</post>
<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I LAUGH DE WHOLE DAY LONG BUT FEEL EMPTY.FEEL LIKE A HYPOCRITE... ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ HMM...NUTHING TO TALK ABOUT.FOLLOW ME BRO GO FOR A HAIRCUT.IT WAS SO DAMN SHORT HE LOOKED WEIRD.HAIZ...READ THIS BACKWORDS IN ORDER TO UNDERSTAND IT.  ...SSENIPPAH HCUM TON SI EREHT...DEIRROW...WORROS...YTPME...DAS...DESSERTS...DETARTSURF M'I    GOODBYE...MAY THE TK BAND FLAME BURN FOREVER. EUPHONIUM ROX!! TK BAND ALL THE WAY!! 
    
</post>
<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      MUAHAHHAZ!!TODAE IS FRIDAE...OKAY,GUESS YOU ALL FIGURE DAT OUT OREADI.YESTERDAE HAD BAND.GREAT DAE.JUZ LAUGH A LOT.DISMISSED AT AROUND 1 PM.GOT HOME...THEN,SUDDENLY GOT TIRED.BY THEN,IT WAS OREADI 3.SO,DECIDED TO TAKE A NAP.HAD A WEIRD WEIRD DREAM.  I WAS AT THIS ONE RAILWAY STATION.THERE WERE LOADS OF P'PLE THERE FROM ALL COUNTRIES AND GENERATIONS.THEN,SUDDENLY,I SAW THIS GUY AND I CALLED OUT TO HIM CUZ HE LOOKED SO DAMN FAMILIAR.WHILE I WAS CHASING HIM,SUDDENLY I FIND MY SELF AT MY SCHOOL HALL AND DE BAND WAS PRACTISING THERE.WEIRD THING IS DAT ON DE STAGE,INSTEAD OF DE TK BANDMASTERS,THERE WERE ALSO OTHER P'PLE...AND GUESS WAT?..DE OTHER P'PLE WAS BOWEN BANDMASTERS STANDING NEAR DE TK BANDMASTERS.THEN,I FALL IN.ALL OF A SUDDEN,AN ARGUMENT BROKE OUT.I CAT REMEMBER ABOUT WAT BUT IT HAS SUMTHING TO DO WITH SUMONE AND ME.I WAS WATCHING AND WAS FASCINATED BY DE SCENARIO WHEN SUDDENLY THE GUY IN FRONT OF ME HIT ME WITH HIS TUBA.THEN,HE LOSE HIS BALANCE AND HE FELL.  OK...IT IS A CRAZY DREAM.GUESS WRIE MORE LATER.  
    
</post>
<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      BAND CAMP IS  COOL   ON DE FIRST NITE,THERE'S DE TREASURE HUNT.MY GROUP HAS ONLY 7 P'PLE IN IT,BRIAN,JUN YING, JUN HUI,MING BEI,SYARIFAH,ME AND DE OTHER ONE I FORGOT WHO...SO,THERE WAS NOT MUCH SCREAMING.WALK AROUND DE SKOOL,TRYING TO FIND DE NEXT CLUE.DUNNO WHY BUT I FREAKED OUT AFTER DE TREASURE HUNT.DIDNT WENT FOR SUPPER.WENT TO DORM INSTEAD.DAT IS WHEN I TOTALLY FREAKED OUT.STARTED TO THINK DAT THERE IS SUMONE AT DE DOOR STARING AT ME STANDING NEAR DE TREE DAT IS IN FRONT OF DE DOOR[DUNNO WAT TREE]...THEN...STARTED TO FEEL AS THOUGH THERE IS SUMTHING BESIDE ME.THEN,STARTED PANICKING.BUT SOMEHOW,CALMED DOWN AFTER A FEW MINUTES.  ON DE SECOND NITE,THERE'S A TELEMATCH.COOL.HAD A GREAT TIME.DE SHOWER ROOM WAS FULL SO,DECIDED TO DO SOME HW INSTEAD OF STANDING LIKE A ZOMBIE INSIDE A CROWDED SHOWER ROOM.SO,DO MY HW NEAR DE BASKETBALL COURT.SUCH A NICE,COOL STARRY NIGHT.AFTER AN HOUR OF MISERY,I FINALLY WENT TO DE SHOWER ROOM AGAIN.WOOHOO!!IT WAS NOT CROWDED.SO,I SHOWERED PEACEFULLY WITHOUT P'PLE BANGING ON DE DOOR.  ON DE THIRD AND FINAL NITE,WATCHED VIDEOS FROM '91 TO '02.NO COMMENTS.  ON DE FOURTH AND FINAL DAY, HAD DRILLS SESSION.WAS SURPRISED DAT I WAS IN DE HALL FACING DE SEC 4'S.TOT I WAS STILL AT DE BACK OF DE HALL.OK..I ADMIT DAT I SHOULD BE ALERT,AND NOT PAYING A VISIT TO MY DREAMLAND.THEN,WENT TO ITE MAC.LEON WAS DE 'DRUM MAJOR'.IT WAS QUITE HILARIOUS AT FIRST BUT AFTER A FEW ROUNDS OF RUNNING,STARTED TO GET ANNOYED.BUT TOO EXHAUSTED,GASPING FOR BREATH,SO, DONT REALLY CARE ABOUT IT.I NEED DE EXERCISE ANYWAY.  THEN,WENT HOME...AND TO MY CHOCOLATES.NICE...
    
</post>
<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      cant sleep and this morning has to wake up at 5 to prepare for skool.feel uneasy..restless..he still havent checked his mailbox.this guy ah.i think if angry, dont give a damn about de world one.wonder when he will cool down.yeah okay..i admit dat i'm in de wrong...i'm de one to blame but cant we juz call it a truce? wah liew eh...now have gastric...hate it when i feel guilty...i will sure eat a lot one..then still got gastric...  hmm...*thinking*...maybe i will apologize again later.no point sending him another postcard by mail.how to say??  me :erm...i wanna sorry.  him :(will drone on and on about my mistakes...)  me :yeah ok..i noe it is my falt and no one is to be blamed except for me.(then held out my hand)truce?  haiz..no point..bb  
    
</post>
<date>11,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      dat is wat i need now.yesterdae was de suckiest day ever.first half of band(b4 lunch),was ok...till after lunch.hope he has cool down.sent him a ecard as an apology but i doubt he will open it till after camp.he looked so angry sia...watever it is...i hoped he opened it today.then..Imma suggested apologizing to him tomolo.i am going to but i dunnoe...depends on his mood lor.if he is still angry...then i'll juz say two words-i'm sorry-and go off....if he looks normal or looks like anything except angry..then maybe i will elaborate my apology... ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ i want my bro here with me...at least i can joke with him...y muz he go for camp???tomolo he came back...tomolo i go camp...maybe see him on tuesday nite.sobsob...miss him lor...de person not so much but i miss his jokes and stuff... i'm going crazy....i miss my mum...i miss my bro...i miss my cousin...but i dont miss him..&gt;.</post></Blog>