<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      okay so while Myers is at home pimpin it up on three hott cleveland guys..im sittin here debating whether or not I want to call Heath or not. He didnt come see me. He chose not to..but said he couldnt when I KNOW he could have. Oh well. That makes things easier I guess?  Ben..promised to come see me..and didnt. Therefore..im depressed. Oh well.  I almost cant wait to get out of here and just forget about everything for a week..and put my focus on God and helping other people out. Plus..I know Im gunna have fun while Im at it..even if I do have to wear a one piece bathing suit to the beach. The only thing im afraid of..is them seperating us..boys from girls..on the bus..or during other things. I reallllly hope they dont. Dang Homie..that would be bad.   I went out for my bday dinner with my fam tonight after I took my bag to church. We went to Ming..it was good. Mom said she got me a digital camera..my own..for my bday..but shes taking it back to get a better one or something. Doesnt matter..i wouldnt have been able to take it to Mexico anyways.   Today is my cuzin Katies bday..so Happy Birthday babe...and Sunday is my other cuzin Billys..so Happy Birthday to you too..and then Monday..is mine..so happy birthday to me..whoop whoop!  Welp...I guesss im gone...Wont be on this thing for 8 days..Holler at the cell while Im gone..write me emails..send me text messages..whatever u can think of..PLEASE! HOLLLLLAAA Fiddy
      
</post>
<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So..I leave in 14 hours for Mexico.  I havent seen Heath or Ben. The Ben part makes me extremely sad since last year around this exact time..we were spending every waking moment with each other. But oh well.  Heath..well..hes another story. I dont even know what to say about him..so Im not gunna say anything. Lets just wait til I get home?  So..last night at my bday thing..we had talked about going to see a movie tonight. Well according to Davids little MSN name..only him Trevor and Justin are invited..which makes no sense for two reasons. 1..WE are the ones who planned it last night and 2..trevor told me earlier..and these being his exact words.."im going to the movies tonight with my best girl friend, *something about justin..i forget*,my best friend alison..and my bitch david"...so yeah david..sounds like we werent invited.. Forget you.  Anyways..now that im done bitching about everything under the sun. Im gunna go finish packing. Ill probably write one more time before i leave... holler
      
</post>
<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I cant bring myself to actually write this..or at least I havent been able to until now.   I dont feel like talking about whats happened in the past few days since the last time i blogged so Im not going to. I had fun tonight. I celebrated my birthday with 9 of my friends at Applebees and it was fun.   I dont think I want to be with anybody in a relationship. Im confused. Im happy when Im with my friends. I like having fun like I did tonight. The "relationship" im in right now isnt that much fun. so...Im waiting until I get back from Mexico to decide if I really want this or not.   Im done with this. Goodnight.
      
</post>
<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      okay..so today I wake up around 11:15. I dont do crap until around 3 when i figure i better clean the basement like mom said before she gets home. Well when she gets home...she brings 5 11 year olds with her. So..I decided it would be best if i left for the night.I get in the shower due to the fact that i hadnt taken one in 3 days..gross. Myers me Em and Gled all go to Applebees at 7:30.I picked Emilee up and when I get there..Coby decides to walk to the door with emilee..as if hes her dad..waving her off to go to her first day of kindergarden. So after Dad is weirded out..we leave. WE get to Applebees and we start to eat. In the middle of it..this black guy thats sitting behind us at the bar gets a call on his cellular phone...decides he doesnt get service where hes sittin or something..so he has to get up and stand about 2 feet from our table. Well..when hes done with his phone convo I decide Im annoyed and need to make a smart comment about what he did. Apparently it was loud enough to where he could hear me. So..he gets another phone call and decides to stand 1 foot from our table instead of 2. So..I stare him down..and it was FUNNY..so. He shakes his head at me. He gets another phone call and stands up again. I think it was one of his hoes because he was gettin smart..he like started yelling..'WHAT COMES AFTER THREE..WHAT COMES AFTER THREE' so Myers turns around and yells "FOUR". hahaha. we died laughing. The guy starts talking about Myers to his hoe. "see the girl in the blue shirt right here even knows". it was good. So then I decide Im gunna take a pic of him with my phone to put on my display pic. Well..he starts saying.."dont take pictures of me up in here". So im like..."IM NOT". He doesnt say anything but gets off the phone and comes to our table and starts telling me that he wasnt talkin to me..it was someone else. So im like..sure nigger..go sit down? So then Myers tries to tell me I need to take fifty cents over to where hes sitting and smack it down and go "Wad Up Fidy" but I decline the invitation because Im not that brave...but it was Hilarious...but I think its one of those things where u gotta be there.Well finally we leave after we decide that hes probably famous and thats why he doesnt want ppl takin pics? I duno. So me gled and myers come back to myers house and ping pong it for a while. I beat Myers twice thanks. After that Glad decides she wants to hit the ball in the fan so that was fun. She left and Me and Myers played some more. I end up peeing on myself because shes crackin me up. Then..Heath calls and well..we arent on the best terms right now. Apparently he doesnt like talking to me when im with my friends..yet hes always with his and I dont have a prob with it..but whatever. So..now Im sittin here..Myers is talking to Aaron B on the phone. Jeremy Jon and Wade called her tonight and wanted us to come to Gee Creek with them but we decided to wait til tomorrow. Gee Creek is also known as "G Spot" now..hahaha thanks to Myers. So yeah..now Im bored. I gotta be home at 1:30 tomorrow to babysit Coach Earls' kids so thats fun. I love them actually..thanks. I duno if Im goin to the river tomorrow or if Im goin to "G Spot"...I guess ill find out later but im gone for now..Hollllla Fiddy
      
</post>
<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      yo yo yo. Okay so last night I actually ended up doing something. Me Heath Emilee and Braden all went to Myers house. We sat around there for a while and just hung out. Braden killed Heath with the ball in the eye. Lets just say,Heath wasnt too fond of Braden after that,but thats okay.So then we watch Jeepers Creepers and Braden wont shut up.Poor guy..gotta love him*muah to b*fetz! Anyways, Me Em and Heath leave and take Emilee home. On the way, I put in some Kenny Chesney and totally screwed up the words but hey, it happens. Hahahaha! *Oh WE SANG BOBBY MCGEE ON THE...*oops. hahahaha I wuv u emiwee! anyways..get home and Marni FINALLY calls me! We talk for like an hour then me and DJ get into this big religious talk. I love that kid. Then..I go to bed after talking to my cuzin about how better im becoming*mu hahaha*! Wake up at 8:35..call Amanda..she doesnt pick up..call back at 9..still no answer..so I head to church on my own which was okay because all teh guys showed up. Went to church..planned some tennis with hunter..came home. Heath came over around 2..we washed his truck cuz it was diiirrty. We did a GOOD job too..go us! Then we just layed around..he left around 5:20 and I ate dinner..and now im here bored...cuz hunter is hurting too bad to go play tennis.whatever.i still wuvs him. adios?  *One word thats all you said.Something in your voice caused me to turn my head.your smile just captured me.and you were in my future far as i could see.and i dont know how it happened.but it happened still.you asked me if i loved ya.If i always will.well you had me from hello.I felt love start to grow.the moment that i looked into your eyes.it was over from the start.you completely stole my heart.and now you wont let go.you had me from hello.inside i built a wall.so high around my heart i thought id never fall.one touch you brought it down.the bricks of my defenses scattered on the ground.and i swore to me i wasnt gunna love again.last time was the last time i let someone in.but you had me from hello.*
      
</post>
<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Last night..was hell. I swear Im psycho. Heath gets online and starts talking to be about what were supposed to do tonight. The other day I told him my parents would be gone so we couldnt do anything here. Well, he must have forgotten because we start talking and hes like lets rent a movie. I agree and its settled. Well, since I had told him about my parents I assumed we were watching it at his house. He calls later on and asks what time he should be here. I was like...huh and explained again. And he starts up with.."then why did u say thats what wed do"? And so this whole big argument starts up over this little thing. We kinda settled it but we couldnt talk about anything else. It was awkward so I freak out and tell him Ill call him back. I get down here and start talking to Bek..she doesnt make me feel any better because all she says is "thats not the way to get Heath to like you" so I talk to Hunter and I love this kid. He makes me feel better..tells me to stop being stupid and call Heath back and apologize for going crazy over nothing. Plus he promises me that me and him will do something tomorrow. So..I call Heath back..he doesnt answer?..I leave him a vm and my voice keeps cracking so I sounded like a total man. In the middle of it, he beeps in. We work stuff out and talk like normal so Im happy again. We get off the phone at 2..were depriving each other of sleep..no joke. I get up at 9:30 because Dad wants me to go run with him. I go run a mile and a half. Come back..shower..nap. Now Im here..trying to work out plans for tonight since I have zero. Dad wont let me car date..how ridiculous is that? Its almost as if he thinks were actually going on a date in the car? I dont understand why he cant comprehend in his head that the only part that has to do with a car is getting where we are going? It really makes NOOO sense to me at all. But whatever My cousin is coming in a month and 8 days. My birthday is in 9 days...all I want is to be able to car date?hahahaha..or a laptop? Both preferably...yup thanks. Marni comes home in 2 weeks and 5 days..apparently she met a guy! Go Marnz! Hasta Lavista?
      
</post>
<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today was a lazy day..I got up at 12 and did nothing. Everyone seemed to already have plans so I got back in bed and watched Radio. Heath and I kinda texted each other back and forth but not too much. I sat around allll day..so I dont have much to talk about on that subject but I did just get off the phone with Heath for the night due to the fact that Im about to go to the movies with Sara and Emilee and hes going camping tonight and wont have service. I might spend the night with Sara..who knows?  So..I leave for Mexico in 7 days. I really dont even know what to say about that. It doesnt even make me mad anymore..mainly just sad. I dont want to leave here for that long. Things are good right now, Im happy with where I am, with Heath, with my friends, and I dont want to go and then come back and things be different. Heath said "he'll find someone else" while Im gone, I know hes kidding, but I still dont wanna be away from him for that long. I havent seen Hunter in what seems like a year. My birthday is 2 days after I leave, so I wont be doing much celebrating but I guess I wouldnt be doing much anyways, after you reach a certain age the parties arent too great anyways, which if you think about it, is really depressing. Its almost like people stop caring that its the day you were born 15 years ago but oh well..shit happens. Anyways I get back on July 4th and Im really hoping that I get back before the fireworks. If I do I promised Nikki that we'd go sit up on her hill like we did last summer. Today I wrote Nik this email of this song that really reminded me of her. It made both of us think about last summer and how it was me and her..and the rest of the world was just there, but didnt matter to us because we had each other. No one got in the way of anything we wanted to do or anything we wanted to say. It was Me and Ben..and her and whatever guy shed chosen for that week.Haha. And it was us..and us..was perfect. Nothing could ever compare to last summer, I just wish it was easier not to compare everything to it and start to hate everything because its not as good.  I just went upstairs about 10 seconds ago because I had on this nice shirt to go to the movies in and then I realized, I dont have to look nice because I dont have to impress anybody anymore. I have my Heath and Heath makes me happy. So here I am..In my ripped jeans, my John Mayer shirt, and my flip flops..happy..and ready to go to the movies.  And now Im stopping because..I just am..and I like being just me.
      
</post>
<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      okay...so right now, im in this mood..and I dont know which one it is yet and that bothers me beyond belief. Anyways, today I wake up to a call from Marni at 10:45,I could have killed her. But,it really didnt matter due to the fact that Tina and Heath both sent me texts at 11. Myers and Emilee got here around 12:15. Heath came a little later and then Rowdy and Sara came around 3:30. Between Sara falling face first into the water, Myers and Emilee screaming WHEETLE for some unknown reason, and Rowdy and Sara getting stuck in a tube, the day was pretty good. Well,minus the part where I got destroyed by all their little comments..ud think Id be usta it by now. Then we all go to Sara's and sit around there. I actually felt different around Heath today..like a good different..it was fun..AND were becoming experts at the whole "dodging the parents" thing..just so we dont kicked out of another house again...hahaha wow. ANYWAYS...Now..im bored..and I dont have shit to do. Trevor is making me angry because of his little hunter comments but whatever.  My dad found the pics of me and heath sleeping at Beks..he asked questions..but believed me when I told him the truth..thank goodness. Heath was gunna come over saturday to meet the rents but theyre goin to some luau so maybe ill just go to his house..then he can come over some other time. I guess well figure it out.. im done writing all this pointless stuff..i think im gunna go...kill myself..
      
</post>
<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Its soooo hot outside. I think Im dehydrated. I just got in from laying out for an hour and I think im gunna die. Thanks..Im being a drama queen but u know u love me. Soo..Heath didnt call last night? But he sent me a text "Im not gunna be able to call tonight but ill call ya tomorrow,have a good night and sleep good". At least he was nice enough to do that. He hasnt called today yet either..Im getting worried but its only 3:54 so its all good...i think? New subject. I leave for Mexico in 10 days. Im not happy about this. I just realized that for four nights,Im going to be sleeping in some POS cabin in some POS campsite with a bunch of people I dont know. Then Im gunna go work my ass off for three days for some damn mexicans that cant build their own fucking houses. Gal Im sucha great Christian. The thought of going just puts me in this not so good mood. But Im going to church tonight to pray for forgiveness of my sins? thanks. But when i get to church..theyre gunna talk about Mexico some more...and its gunna put me in this even worse mood which will be fun so hooyah.  When im on this little trip..were staying in Texas..if i dont have phone service..im gunna be a little upset considering I wont be able to talk to heath for a whole damn week. If I come back and things are different Im gunna be sooooo upset it wont even be funny.  IM IN A BAD MOOD NOW...GOOD JOB...HOLLER
      
</post>
<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Alrighty...I just had the best two days that Ive had in a long time. Lets see, yesterday I got up around 11, watched Crossroads cuz Im a fag, called Bek around 1:30,got ready,she got to the house around 3:30 or so,we went and saw Dad,ate at McDonalds,got in a noodle fight at walmart "GIRLS PLEASE LEAVE THE STORE",went and got Em,went to sno biz, went to Beks. We sat around there for a while and around 7:30 Mikey and Clint got there. They brought the movie Van Wilder and we watched it. Around 8,Heath and Robbie get there, we all sit around talking and kinda watchin the movie. After 2 hours of naked women and the guys throwing pizza rolls into the fan, everyone finally settled down and we watched O Brother Where Art Thou. Heath finally warmed up to me and we cuddled just a little bit. Around 11 all the guys left but Heath said he was gunna go get his truck,get zach,and come back. So he got back around 11:30. Emilee Bekah and Zach left us alone minus an occasional underwear tossing and flashlight shining,so we watched John Q. After that was over we just kinda laid there in the dark and talked. Then around 2 Zach made him leave. Me Bek n EM tried to go to sleep but it just wasnt happening for us due to the fact that we talked about damn nigg** chickens and Emilee kept saying "IF YOU BONE MY UTERUS I THINK IM GUNNA HAFTA DIE". We finally fell asleep around 5am and awoke to a call from Mikey at 10am telling us he was coming over for breakfast. Heath called a few minutes later and said he was coming too. Mikey left around 12:10 for basketball and football practice so Bek Em Me and Heath went to Castillos for lunch and Robbie met us there. We left and went back to Beks. We just layed around the house for forever then ended up finally leaving around 7 after Beks mom found me and heath on the couch :s *definitely embarrassing*! We go into town,walk around walmart for some unknown reason,go to Dairy Barn *heath bought mine :)*, sit there for forever then we all leave and split up. Me and Heath had no where to go so we ended up goin over and sittin in his truck at the senior activity center? hahahahaha! We talked for about an hour,played the "get to know u game" and took gay pics until Bek and Em came and got me and brought me home. I got here, took a shower, and now im here..doing shit..waitin on Heath to call since he said he would :). As you can tell, Im definitely happy and I definitely like this kid. Im not gunna mess this one up because i really hope this is the guy im finally gunna date. Anyways...I definitely havent talked to Marni much at all, makes me sad but I guess shes having fun, which is good. I dont think Ky or Jamie have talked to them either so oh well.  I think,or at least hoping, that tomorrow im gunna have some ppl over to swim cough*bekemheathmikeyclint*cough! ga im a loser..anyways..its 10:33 and im outta here...holllllaaaa
      
</post>
<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ive definitly tried to write this 3 different times but cant ever seem to get it done..but Im gunna do it this time so here goes..Im about to scream because our fag guests are annoying the shit out of me and they just need to go to sleep...facing idiots.hahaha. Anyways..so I get to Applebees last night with David Em Laura and Myers. Mitch Coby and Lauren showed up too and ate at the table next to us. It was fun. Around 8:30 Aaron B called Amanda up and told her that him and friend were coming to Athens and for us to meet them at 9:30 at the Dairy Barn. We got Mitch to take us there but we saw Blake Derrick on the way and they felt the need to race. So we go all the way down to Heil because "thats where the central folk race". Blake totally smoked us considering Mitch had 6 people in his car. They quit that and we finally make it to DB. Well Aaron shows up a little later and hes brought his friend Paul with him and let me tell you..the kid is HOTT. So we all sit there and talk for a little while then Me Myers Aaron and Paul leave and they take us to Myers house. Aaron made Paul sit in the back with me and he was so funny. He said something about having x-ray vision and i was like.."okay Superman" so then we started talking about SuperHeroes..but it got interrupted due to the fact that some faggot pulled out right in front of us and we camethisclose to wrecking. We were so freaked out. So Paul hops up and starts yelling out the window..FUCK YOU MOTHER FUCKER! hahaha it was soooo funny. Then he tries to get Aaron to turn around so they can kill the guy because "Pauls blood is flowing" but Aaron wont. So great. Then Paul finds his "doo rag" and puts it on and goes..."GUYS ITS STONER TIME" hahaha. It was so funny. Then Kenny Chesneys *Back Where I Come From* comes on and he starts singing..and wow..thats what I figured out that I loved this kid. He was so sexy. So Im all about this kid and we were gunna do something with them today but they had baseball so me and Myers ended up sleeping til 1,she showered,we get ahold of Blake and he takes us to my house so I can shower, get done there and we go ride around for forrrrever. It was crap. We go back to Myers and sit there til we hafta leave cuz the family hasta celebrate her Dads bday. Me Blake and LJ go to etowah to pick up Beau and take him to Jamichaels. Then we go cruise around again because were losers like that and then go back to Myers for about 30 minutes. LJ brings me home and I sit around here til 9:30 when Dad decides to drag the whole crew to Sno Biz. I see Charlie there though so its not all that bad. I go home and get a voicemail from Bekah saying that Im spending the night with her tomorrow because Heath is coming over and wants to meet me. So Im kinda hoping that I get to spend the day with Paul and the night with Heath and see which one I like. The thing is though..Paul hasnt showed interest in me yet really and Heath has. I might not even have a chance with Paul so Im kinda worried about what Im gunna do but I figure if I just sit back and let things happen itll go how its supposed to..so well see! So my first day without Marni wasnt totally bad. Im hoping I can stay busy while shes gone so I dont get bummed out again. I know shes having fun though, but me and Jamie are gunna walk to Hendersonville,NC now so im outta here.  *I wasnt looking for a lifetime with you.I never thought it would hurt just to hear "I do" and "I do". And I do a number on myself and all that I thought to be And youll be the one that just left me undone. By my own,hesitation And for the million hours that we were Well Ill smile and remember it all then Ill turn and go. While your story is completed mines a long way from done. Well Im on a champagne high. Where will I be when I stop wondering why? On a champagne high. Id toast to the futer but thatd be a lie. Spring turned to summer But then winter turned to mean. The distance seemed right. At the time it was best to leave. And to leave behind what I once thought was fine and so real to me. And while Im still gone on a quest for your song, Im at your celebration.*
      
</post>
<date>12,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hey guys..Thought Id go ahead and write even though, knowing me, Ill end up writing again later on tonight. Im bored. Today I got up at 8..went to soccer til 11. Came home, went outside and played with the dog for a little while. Came in, took a shower, then WhipDaddy came and got me and took me to Marns so I could say goodbye for real this time. We were supposed to stay for like 10 minutes but ended up staying for about 3 hours but we had fun. We all got in Andrew's bed and watched tv..and you know thats always fun..so yeah. Then..it was time for her to leave. I wasnt gunna cry..I really wasnt..but then DR hugged me and I lost it. So I like..made myself actually leave and cried in the car but hey its all good. Nathan and I went to Mexi Wings and he bought me my cheese dip since I didnt feel like eating and he made me anyways. Okay so I did tell him to go somewhere but I wasnt all that hungry after crying but whatever. Anyways, I got home and was informed that the gang was going to Applebees at 7:15. So now, Ive got about 10 minutes to fix my hair until David gets here to pick me up so I guess I better go. But before I do..I gotta tell ya..Im supposed to meet this Heath kid from central and Im reallly excited cuz apparently hes adorable so thats fun. Bekah is trying so hard to find me some one..bless her. Haha. But yea..gotta jet..   *Well He said whats the problem baby, Whats the problem? I duno well maybe Im in love,love think about it everytime I think about it..cant stop thinkin bout it...Turn a little faster..the world will follow after..because everybodys after love..were accidentally in love..* </post></Blog>