<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      haiz... bad timing... wanted to change something in my blog template. and.. then.... agrrh... accidentally clicked on the.. edit changes... and.. i didn't save properly. so... now.. i have to redo all .... everything... and i have no time to really do this anymore... sigh... tt's so sad... argh...  then... a bit happier stuff... eh... got my new phone! =) samsung? x430.. i think... haha.. though it's not the phone i really wanted... but nvm... ahaha... still like it... too bad its white in colour... i wanted silver de... haiz... nvm lor.. then..haha... but the phone like... a bit harder to use... hm.. used to my nokia phone le... haiz... nvm... haiz.. now my blog really sucks... sad... nvm... will get it done up... hm... hopefully by end of next month... haiz... going to do some hols assignment... not going to finish chem and physics de.. today try to finish english and geog... but geog alot!!! gtg... 
    
</post>
<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      haiz... didn't update yesterday. keeping it short. got pple say entries too long... okok... anyway, i got not much time to crap... going to rush out all the hols assignment this week.  ok... yesterday, went to marina... waited for raisa for 1/2 hr. was late. reached marina mrt at 915am i think. then took the shuttle bus.. then reach. eh... actually.. dunno why need the bus. walk can le... then... had to touch up the cart, get the shirts for the pple... oh my... my class took 24 Ls and 3 Ms... haha... then had the kids... then lunch... well it;s kinda horrid.. but... hungry.. so eat. then... when the cart was being judged, my class sang 'teko tan'...  with one of the old  songs... haha... funny. then weijia went to ride the kart.. -_-"" the pedal of the bike came off... gosh... and he pedalled  with his feet... wat a joke... ahahahahhaa....  then... had to look after this kid.. dunno who in charge de... then no one cared about her. then in the end, PJ told me to look after her. oh well... haiz.. didn';t have the intention to look after kids de lor. then nvm la.. just do lor... but... argh... the kid was.... well kinda spoiled... sigh... but no choice. then had to ride the cart with her... oh man... then the kart... argh... the thing that turns the direction... was bent... so... if i wanted to go straight, i had to turn left. oh well... haiz... then... cut my feet... sobs... nvm... then we build the house... sOOOOOOO nice... but didn't get any prize. sad rite... haiz... nvm lor... only got 3 prize... if we also take, then swiss took all the prizes le... of course cannot rite... ahahaha...   then... we changed out of their shirt... haiz... the shirt is lousy... after that got this blue blue thing sticking onto me... argh... hahah.. then my class we... sort of hanged around the place... played with the spider web thingy, and the swings... hahaha.. fun... then about 20 of us when to eat together.... went suntec.. hahaa.. then after that, went to buy pen for my daddy... father's day... =) hahaha...that weijia owe me $$ for the pen he bought.. hahah... haiz... but i lost one of my pens... dunno lend to who lei/... haiz... then lose it... sad... nvm...  ok... not a very short entry anyway... then... today... lazed around ba... i didn't go for the physics thingy... then tried to do work... but it was sooo hot... haiz.,.. then my sis doing project with her friend, so i can;'t do work in the study. haiz. then under the heat.. didn';t do much... sigh... nvm... ahaha... gtg.. do work!!! 
    
</post>
<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sigh... today went for band... early in the morning... sian... woke up at.. 8... then had to rush to sch... haiz... last nite too late slp le....  ok... yesterday..  class outing was nothing... argh... haiz... sigh... it became... waste time outing instead.... early in the morning i went to sch, did cip... the cart thingy... only got a few pple la... haiz..... xianglong,joseph,teckming,chengjoo, me, shurong, mingjie... sigh... sometimes, i wonder why i bothered, but i did anyway... so, ya... the cip... hahahaha... the cart quite nicely done... only got one thing... argh... i had to sew???? oh well.... yup... we did the folds thingy... hahaha... quite ok le... then also spray painted the bike... haha... oops.. and my white sch shoes has silver paint on it now..... and i just washed it... but it looks really dirty now... sigh... oh well... then i started to fold stars... ahahaha.... then some of them went to buy lunch... the stuff we did were really.. boring, and in the end..... we sat down there telling lame jokes..... man... very cold ones.. while doing our work...  then when to lot 1 meet the pple... class outing? well... only got junxian, xianglong, zhenyong, meili, zihui, yiwen, me, yiling... wei zhong, edward ps us... then.... saw elvin... then he dun wan to go... so... we actually wanted to go east coast there...... but.... too late le..... so we stay at lot one rot... then the boys went to eat the sushi thingy... haha... then we gave them an hour to eAT, then, we went to wait for yiling... and rot at the mrt station for an hour... then we went to find the boys... then had to think of where to go...  we went to buy sweets... and dunno why.,.. but jun xian decided to buy all the sour sweets... -_-""" oh welll.... hahaaa... then we went to take neoprints... girls only... haha... then.... saw someone i think yiling knows.. then... want to siam off..  then i went to the arcade to look for the boys... then when i came out, they were down the escalator.. then... got this guy wanted to know yiwen i think..... hahahaha... then we all siam off... to the other mall..... last time the popular there... then.... sat down there...... and rot again.... -_-""" haha... then we decided to go orchard...  then... yup... we went orchard, but meili, and zihui went back home... then we went to hereens.. then take neoprint again... ahahha.a... the boys took with us... =) ahahah... so funny lor... then we go cut the pictures until small small.. ahahaha... then give them.... =p then went for dinner, at cineleisure.. hhahah.. the boys walk the place while we eat... then they came back looking for us... haiz... ahhaha... they all broke after the sushi... and i think xiang long was getting hungry when he looked at us eat... ahahhahahaha..... =) then.... i want to go back le... haiz... then yi ling, and yi wen stayed... so.... i went back with xl, jx, and zy... oh well... then on the bus... haiz... haha... hear jx and xl crap... hm... hahah... then they two alight le...hm.......&gt;.  tml have to go the marina thingy... should i go?.... haiz... sian... haiz... go do work la...so sian..... 
    
</post>
<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      sigh.. yup... very disappointed.. class outing had to be cancelled.. too many pple cannot go.. sigh... was looking forward to it de... sigh...  disappointed... in another thing.. sigh... really very.... just call him XX ... sigh... well... he is a great friend of my... very very very good friend... kind... understanding? haha... then... always willing to listen to all my problems and stuff... a very wonderful friend and person... though sometimes insensitive... sigh... but today... at least.. now... feel so mad at him..... argh...  dunno wat more to say... he... haiz... well... just because someone was pissed at him, he cannot help call the person about the outing... sigh... wat the hell... oh well... sigh... then... was very pissed la... in the end had to call the person myself... then i think i said something... then.. he was like.. WAT! and said that he had to go... haha... dun believe it... but then... he might have blocked me or something... who cares.... i told him that i didn't want to fight with him... cherish this friendship de... someone who is really one of my great friends.. but thenn... just tt i told him wat i thought about the wasy he was behaving, then become... like tt... sigh... isit because i can't understand? or... sigh... nvm,... sorry if you are reading this... but i doubt he will... he won't care anymore..
    
</post>
<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This will be sort of like... about my life in band... like.. dedicated to SwiSS WiNdS ? sigh...  Tay actually let us play for serenade... then...now... sec 4s can only go for sat afternoon band prac. but like tt, we only have 1 pathetic practice before the concert.... ? how to? for us to pass out too... wat the... it would be... totally throwing SWISS's reputation down the drain! sigh... then... we are ' kicked' out of the bandroom when we try to go some other days.. sigh...   sigh... swiss winds... haiz... why?... SerEnAde is very important to us... esp the sec 4s..   that's when we pass out... the day.... that.... the day... that we.... leave the band... never to step into the bandroom, as an actual member anymore... we become guest, visitors... ex seniors... and then... slowly.... our voices, playing, faces, each... slowly... is being eroded away... slowly... we will become the forgotten... the forgotten batch... of seniors... from 2001-2004.... the days we spend together are now merely in our memories... somewhere... deep... at the back of our heads.... how many of us... can actually take this memories out? from the storage tank? how many of us can still do it... after the many years have passed... and the feeling slowly... almost naturally disapear... before you know it... and when we try to find the feeling back... its like... too late...  sigh... things will change... and when it does... the changes are great.... so great... that it takes you in surprise.. and you have no way to escape... to fight... all you can do... is to retreat... and retreat... and retreat.. and when you try to fight back once again... it causes you to fall back more...  sigh...   sigh... so tired of all this.. we always fight... but problems keep coming... and coming... one wave after the other... each time getting stronger.. forceful -er and... and its drives us further... and further away... away from where we want to be... and going to where they think we want to be... is it fair ? no.... but then again.... is there anything in the world, that is really fair ?   soon... all this... everything... will become memories... sigh... then... why hurt us now? .... sigh..   Band. the place where i gone through alot, sometimes, hate it, but still... love it.. the place where i 'grown up' in... the place i made my most important friends, and learned important things and skills tt i will not find in the textbook and classrooms... a place where we enjoy the music together. a place we stuck through thick and thin. a place we saw the different sides of a person.. the place which taught us things we will never learn in exams,class, remedials, lessons. watever. a place, where i will never forget in my whole life.... 
    
</post>
<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      sigh... read someone's blog... suddenly... sigh... can understand how she feel... feel  like crying... but... even she is not... sigh... living in the same house... we are suupposed to be knowing wat each other feel... but... she gone through that much... and i didn't know... probably i was too busy with my own life again.. sigh... holidays.. but then... its the same as having sch at home... rushing out hols assignment... which... for me... cannot be finished.. sigh... dunno la... can't slp... argh... 
    
</post>
<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      new to this... i am blog idiot... can't expect much.. =P trying to make it more presentable... 
    
</post>
<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OMg... yup.. i think i am falling sick...  think i caught a cold or something.. &gt;.  so in the end.. i had to take 2 panadol pills before i go to sch... reach class... !! so COLD!! ok.. maybe its just me.. then.. had to finish some admin stuff.. then ... sigh... had headahce throughout the day... esp in the afternoon... sigh.. my mother suggested that i go home during recess.. but thought i would be alright... sigh..  then took the emath mock... sigh... my headache was really really very bad at that time.. i think can't even get 80% this time.. how to maintain my 92%? cannot le la.. the words and numbers were like... dancing in front of me half the time.. sobs... sigh....  doing that math paper is really tiring... after that...my braincan practically just crash... sigh... didn't have the strength to carry my books and walk.. argh.. felt so much like calling my mother.. but daddy not back yet... can't drive me home.. sigh...  then reached home.. when they saw me.. they just told me to go and slp.. but ... i can't slp lei.. so bloody tired.. sigh... head HURTS!!! its not fun being sick.. argh.. 
    
</post>
<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       What's love? When you are together with that special someone, you pretend to ignore that person. But when that special someone is not around, you might look around to find them. At that moment, you are in love.  Although there is someone else who always makes you laugh, your eyes and attention might go only to that special someone. Then, you are in love.  Although that special someone was supposed to have called you long back, to let you know of their safe arrival, your phone is quiet. You are desperately waiting for the call! At that moment, you are in love. If you are much more excited for one short e-mail from that special someone than other many long e-mails, you are in love. When you find yourself as one who cannot erase all the messages in your answering machine because of one message from that special someone, you are in love. When you get a couple of free movie tickets, you would not hesitate to think of that special someone. Then, you are in love. You keep telling yourself, "that special someone is just a friend", but you realize that you can not avoid that person's special attraction. At that moment, you are in love. While you are reading this page, if someone appears in your mind, then u are in love with that person.
</post>
<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sigh.... i am really tired... how?... so many things happened lately... i can't help thinking...  can't help thinking... sigh... so tired of thinking... and yet... i still do... i guess its human nature.. so sick of everything.. Life, school, homework, thinking, books, stress.. and also SF...  basically everything... its like.. i dunno... i think i am having too many characters? in class.. with my friends... then... alone... each is a different me... and things i say, do, are all so different... so tired... all this "roles" playing in my head.. sigh...   now so distracted.. thinking of many things... but everytime... when i am alone... ahaha... i can't escape from all those images... they just flash through my head... sigh... i wish i can stop thinking... but apparently... no...  too bad for me isn't it... sometimes.. i really convince myself its not going to work, not worth it... blah blah... but then... my mind does not think of that for long... argh!!!!   focus? sigh... i thought of too much things... events... days... too bad... i am really tired... tired of thinking of you? i am... you know who you are? haha.. no you don't..  wat the hack? i am talking nosense again... he doesn't even know.. well it's better that way right... save the embaressment? haha... sigh... i am going crazy again... &gt;. talking nonsense.. dun bother about it...  
    
</post>
<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      sigh... today never go to school... so bored.. listening to my mother scold my sister because she anyhow practise the piano...   sigh... today got 3p of chem, 4p of math.. and 2 p of english... then still got ss, history and geog remedial... sigh sigh... how??? miss so many lessons... actually wanted to go sch de... but was so tired... then homework also didn't do... sigh... feel horrid.. PHEW..   argh...stupid bees... argh... cause got one tree below my house got beehive.. then the pest control people came... and then my mother went to fetch my sis... and saw the people... so ask me go close window... then i close lor.. how i know there's a bee on in the room already... then i didn't see... accidentally step on it..!!!! argh... then i was like.. yuck! wat's that.. and i got so freaked out.. then actually got check my feet ok a not one... then see like nothing... then go on typing in my Od and Blog... sigh... then later my mother ask me keep something.. then feel that my feet there got something.. !! sigh.. its the bee sting.. !!! argh.. then i took it out lor.. then like nothing happen liao.. so i go on typing in my blog and Od lor..   who knows.. *phew.. that my stupid leg hurts like hell when i finished asking raisa wat homework we have to do.. so i didn't do any homework... went to see the doctor at 9.30pm... then i waited and waited.. and waited... until its 11pm.. *yawns.. then its finally my turn... i was the last patient.. sigh... then the doctor had to take out the other half of the sting... cause i didn't pull it out completely... how unlucky could i get... he had to take it out... !! somemore without anestatic?(how to spell??) *phew.. OUCH!!!!!!!! HELP!!! and its so bloody cold in the room.. the air con was blowing right into my face... Gr... sigh... then he bandaged my foot.. until... its SOOOOOOO BIGGG!!! that i couldn't even fit into my slippers.. *phew. sigh... then afetr thati still had to get injection...ouch... until now my arm's still hurting.. then still got medicine.. argh... the antibotics is like... 2 tablets and 3times a day... argh.....sigh... then reach home... so tired... then go sleep liao..   didnt do homework at all... then i woke up at 5am... then fell asleep again.. too tired.. so today i didn't go to school.. sigh... hm... can someone tell me what's going on in school today???   
    
</post>
<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       yup... today we celebrated racial harmony day...    haha... my whole class wore the costumes.. haha.. so proud of my class... they all look great in it... hahaha... unlike me lor...look  so freaking ugly... &gt;. some of them stilll look chinese to me... esp the boys... ahhaa... though almost all of us wore malay costumes.. ... but they say i look like chinese malay.. &gt;.   then my class and 4e3 tied for the competition... cause we had everyone wearing the costumes.. la la la... so proud of my class.. haha... then... ms tan went to take the voucher.. represent our class... ahaha... then we all stood up and cheered... ahhaha... so fun...    well... then... we were supposed to have CME... ahhaa.. Mr Ngoh let us take photos instead... so we used the period to play.. and take photos... ahaha.. we carried the bench out... and got our teachers to take picture with us..haha.. went off to find ms tan, mr kamal... and also mr wee!!1 ahaha.. so the 4 teachers took photos with us...  WHao!!! ahahahaha... happy, sha la la la... its so nice to be happy... sha la la la... hahahah... i siao le...    really glad my class is so... together? hm.. i hope we can all study together too..    4e2, jia you!!!!! ADD LOTS OF OIL!!! HAHA.... =)    mad liao le la.. &gt;.  
    
</post>
<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Suddenly...    Tears just formd in my eyes... 
</post>
<date>07,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      sigh... tired of everything... really...  oh man... can't i have a BREAK??????? really so tiring... i feel like dying... wat the Hell???  sigh... dunno wat's wrong with me... sigh... keep feeling out of sorts... dunno la.. life sucks.. *phew*  sigh... tired... of everything le... keep gett ing all this rubbishy mood swings... then suddenly got influenced by others easily... &gt;.</post></Blog>