<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I dreded work all day but it really wasent that bad....im thinking about calling in sick tomorrow:) i need a day off lol well im going to bed im so tired byes  :::goodnight:::  :::lots of Love:::
     

    
</post>
<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wow PMS! thats all im gonna say! lmao no no but really i was in bit of a mood today and i appoligize Charlie and to n e one else i made mad:(   I love you all  Well im going to bed didnt do much today i woke up at 3.....well talk to yall later     &gt;&gt;
     

    
</post>
<date>27,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok I am a fuckign retard to even mention drinking!   I DONT WANT TO DRINK ANYMORE!   SORRY GUYS  I had to work today, it wasent that bad of day we were slow so we all just went in back and talked most of the time lol. I worked with ALL the people i love working with Melissa, Brandon, Paul, Markita, and even Rob. i work alot this week! 22 fucking hours! cant wait to get past this week!   Oh well...... Im going to bed because im tired.    &gt;&gt;thank you:) XOXO    &gt;&gt;  &gt;&gt;
     

    
</post>
<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I really want to just drink tomorrow night....i just need to blow off some steam! i dont know what from IM NOT MAD AT ANYONE OR N E THING i just i feel like drinking! i havent done it since my brothers GRAD Party so...yeah.... I got hit on today at work it was horrible and i dont want to talk about it!   i came home and my internet still wasent working even though the guy came out today to fix it. Me and my mom tried to fix it ourselfs but we just messed it up more so we finally called tech support and got it all fixed thank god:)! i hate when i cant get online it bugs the shit out of me!  well i had a good night after work:) thanks i love you  i think im going to bed i gota work tomorrow 11-3 !! AHH  well goodnight  ::: &gt;&gt;:::
     

    
</post>
<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Thank you so much for the wonderful night:)  you made me feel 100% better  i wrote a poem.....  Pond To Heaven  Clear midst in the fields Where yellow and white Lilly's grow I see a face in the pond reflecting what is not me it wasn't but a man behind me who I did not know.  He touched my shoulder Gazing at the water ripples as I touch it I turn around and close my eyes and fall back Deep into the pond my soul floats to the top.  I blow out my last breath  Looking up to the top of the water;the waters edge so long I see his face once more as I close my eyes and part I hit the bottom.He is jumping in after me, but I am gone.  Well im so tired and i gotta work @ 4 tomorrow:( god i dont want to!!!! well goodnight everyone! Love yall!  &gt;&gt;&gt;Malocups 

    
</post>
<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Im feeling alot better now.......we talked  no more hurting:)  I love you and im sorry.......      :::printing out pictures:::   I'll write more later
     

    
</post>
<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i had the worst morning of my life....     :::i hurt myself today:::   to see if i still feel i focus on the pain the only thing thats real  ::HE:: hates me now :(    I hate this..............        :::Crying all day::: 
     

    
</post>
<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      OMG! 4 hours of work and im pooped......and guess what i just fucking found out........AHHHH! man i got a 22 hour week next week.....tuesday i work 4:30-7:30 Wed 5-9 Fre 11-7!!! IM GONNA DIE! and Sat 12-8 IM GONNA DIE!!!!! omg im seiroulsy gonna die.....i barely made it through today! just four hours.....eight hours is gonna b worse!! OMG! i wanan quit NOW! oh well i guess i'll make it. Make more money:) thats always a plus so yeah....oh well....i think im gonna go take a shower or something and then lay in bed or talk online.....didnt have to bad of a day....just for chest pains since 3 in the mornin HOW FUN! oh well ill live BYES  ~*</post></Blog>