<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      HiHi i just got bacjk from Becky's, i stayed the night there last night,it was fun! Then before i came home i made her her own xanga. I feel lonely, i dont feel like i have anyone to talk to. I hate that feeling. Im talking to kt and paige, paige was telling me how kt went to the burnsville mall yesterday and invited her the day before and she said she couldnt come, that made me feel really bad. Cause when i talked to her she said she didnt know where she was that day. :( uughh, i feel like shit, i feel [once again] like i have no friends because everyone lies to me, :( but then again i dont deserve any friends, i dont deserve to live 
    
</post>
<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      HiHi i just got bacjk from Becky's, i stayed the night there last night,it was fun! Then before i came home i made her her own xanga. I feel lonely, i dont feel like i have anyone to talk to. I hate that feeling. Im talking to kt and paige, paige was telling me how kt went to the burnsville mall yesterday and invited her the day before and she said she couldnt come, that made me feel really bad. Cause when i talked to her she said she didnt know where she was that day. :( uughh, i feel like shit, i feel [once again] like i have no friends because everyone lies to me, :( but then again i dont deserve any friends, i dont deserve to live 
    
</post>
<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I went shopping yesterday in burnsville, it was fun, i got lotsa clothes and stuff. I wish kt coulda been there, it was kinda lonely without her  :( and she's still grounded so she cant hang out either :( I called natalie to bring her with , but she didnt answer so i left a message and she didnt call back so i called again and her mom answered and gave the phone to natalie i was like "hey didnt you get my message?" and she said "ya i just didnt want to talk to you" so i sadi "oh thats okaaayy then i guueeess, so i take it you dont want to go?" and she was like "not for 2 reasons 1. i have plans with dylan and 2. i hate how you always plan things last minute". so i got off the phone and left.She made me feel like shit again but like usual she doesnt give a fuck, that made me so sad yesterday that in the car on the way there i was actually planning on killing myself by o.d.ing on the way home. But while i was at the mall i just sort of transformed my saddness into anger and now, well now i just hope she dies and sont give a flying fuck about what the dumb ugly worthless bitch thinks. Read her xanga about me, its really interesting... http://www.xanga.com/home.aspx?user=thatwasmyshoe </post></Blog>