<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today... I learned how to update my profile... add a few pictures. It was all very fascinating.  I hope to add my travel journals soon.  I am very excited about all that I can do with this online journal!
    
</post>
<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    This is the wannabe giraffe urlLink   
    
</post>
<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    This is Me! urlLink   
    
</post>
<date>13,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       This is not the day I was born. This is the day I decided to begin a blog.  There are many things that I would like to record so that I never forget.  I always write journals when I go on vacation.  I have found that a few people like to read them, and one person suggested I make a blog journal.  I thought, hmmmm why not?!?  This will be the place I can share with the world some of my most personal thoughts.  I find myself laughing at the idea, if they are so personal - why would I want to share them???  I suppose that maybe I really do want to share them, but maybe fear that people might not want to actually read them!  This journal  for myself will be sort of a therapy for me... a diary, a map of my thoughts, a way to better understand myself... take a journey inward... I can look back after a while of writing it and see how I have changed... who I have become... Maybe along the way I will have given something to others, perhaps a laugh or two, maybe some inspiration, motivation or needed strength....  Whatever it is I give to anyone just know that these are thoughts from my heart... ideas from my mind and observations from my eyes.... the way I see the world.
    
</post>
<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Ahh..... Exhaustion is a definate these days! In fact, so much so that my days run together in a confusing sort of blur. I just finished my women's studies exam.... I had my African Literature class this evening and I worked today.... I am not writing this to evoke pity, I am just trying to remember the events of my day.... Tho... anyone offering sympathy will be much appreciated ; ) My classes are very interesting, I only wish I hadas much time to devote to themas I would like. 
  
  John's family is visiting and I am constantly reminded that I am missed at home.... Asked why I am soo intent on getting my degree? I only can answer this with "It's important to me". That answer is too vague though, but I am not sure that my ambitions would be easily understood. 
  
  I feel thankful for the privalege of being able to learn.... It is a gift that not all people are able to partake in. I love the challenge. I love learning new things. Yes, I realize that learning does not have to be only in a classroom... I think daily life gives lots of opportunity to grow as people, learn new things. I try to take advantage of learning by learning anywhere, everything that I can. But the reason I like being in the classroom soo much is that it provides structured guidance to explore things that otherwise you may never have heard of... The classroom exposes you too many different perspectives on one subject all at once.... As each student is a unique contributor.  
  
  I may never get rich from my studies... That is not my goal... In fact, I believe wealth to be a trapping. People get too caught up in material possessions anyway. A constant theme I see over and over in my studies is actually about that very subject. It seems man is a greedy creature that exploits and rules with a selfish heart. This is not true of all mankind of course (Thank God), but it seems that power can corrupt even the most selfless. 

    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Many have asked about my failure to update my world....  I plan to very soon... I have a nice excuse tho.  I began school this week.  My days and nights have been filled with endless pen, magnets and mousepads during my work day at Bic.  My afternoons have been occupied by Russia...  How sad the Russians have had life!!  African American literature, I am reading about a slaves journey from motherland Africa to plantation life....  and then my online women studies course.... which is definately interesting.  I still like men even ; )  I will be posting again soon...  When I am a bit more awake......  Good Night All.
    
</post>
</Blog>