<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So what if I couldn’t drive??! It’s not like it is a crime to not to know how to drive? I mean, it’s not like I am troubling anyone by asking them to give me a lift, right?? Right??!! Well, ok.. maybe in some cases when I go partying with my friends… but then again, they offer to pick me up.. I didn’t force them, did I? Did I?? Malaysia has lots of public transports to choose from.. so, why the worries??   Consider this…    Men prefer their women to be more independent. You are independent if you know how to drive. I do not know how to drive.    Can someone tell me where’s the validity to the above statement?? Can anyone see the logic?? I don't think so.. but even if there's a yes among you people who read this.. I'll say, "Screw the men!" It's not my problem if they couldn't accept the fact that I can't drive!     
      
</post>
<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I hate my company.   I’m miserable and it’s all my bloody inconsiderate boss’s fault.  Although I also blame my I’m-24 hours-busy-bf and all his smooth talks that for some reasons stop my questionings on his lack of attention towards me lately. I point my finger of shame at J for telling me that I can be pushy when I choose to be, my ‘so-called’ dedicated lecturer who was supposed to provide me with the information on the 2 important major courses I’m taking this semester so as not to land myself with another super stupid C+ and the entire family of Hitz FM for playing all the wrong songs at the wrong time.   I find the following people and creatures guilty of conspiracy to inflict misery upon me: my handphone for giving me trouble in typing texts, the taxi drivers for repeatedly taking the wrong routes when I repeatedly with my sweet looking face telling them, “Please take the Pusat Sains Negara route and turn into your right after the traffic light”, my missing brown sandals for not showing up although it has been nearly two weeks now, my totally chubby legs and most of all the boy bands in general for their I-can’t sing-but-thanks-to-my-good looks-performances…   I positively loathe men who approach the forever-so-romantic-in-the-head-women with their you-are-so-beautiful-pick up lines in order to get into their pants!!!     
      
</post>
</Blog>