<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I get to come home soon! T_T I miss you all! Well..most of you. *shifty glance* I'm REALLY going to miss German guys though, I mean.......wow. They are NICE!! I wish Wendy were here to share the glory with me. U_U In Scotland my friend, in Scotland. We shall admire the guys there, together. For love, FOR LOVE AND FOR PEACE!!! That boy had really nice eyes..I mean er-uhm &gt;_ Aaanywho, I like it here muy mucho *nod nod*  not as nice as Ireland, I don't really feel at home like I was there, and the fact that none of us speak German, French, or Dutch, doesn't help any...Mom's talking about going to Spain, so my Spanish may actually be of use, since Joe is the only other one that speaks it. But we're going to Scotland first! *wink, nudge, elbows Wendy* Then Japan W00t!!! Umm..I guess that's all for now, I mean I'll end up talking to you all, you can ask your questions and whatnot then. *nods* Pies for nows.
    
</post>
<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      At my grandma's &gt;_&gt;;; slowest computer I swear. Anyway, bored out of oblivion. Keep thinking about the plane &gt;_0 oooooh  how I hate planes!! T_T Don't make me go! :cry cry: Ummm...what else? I had ice cream! yey!! I never get Ice Cream, so if you know when my birthday is, or you see me on X-Mas, get me ice cream, I'll love you forever. X3 Aaand yesh. Think I'll stop now, just know that I was very bored when I wrote this. That is all.
    
</post>
<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      okokokokok this is my last quiz post thingy...for awhile. ^_^ I just got all excited when I got it:   Dragon: Dragons are very mysterious creatures who often live alone in caves with hoards of gold. You keep yourself from others and contain many armoured plates for defence. However,  you will be kind to others if they are kind to you. You are very thrifty and rarely waste any money.   I'm a mysterious creature!? Who knew? o.O;;
    
</post>
<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yeah..interesting I know, but I couldn't resist alright?   You are a Siren. More adventurous than all with a voice like no other you sit on warm rocks and sing to the moon and sea. Yet sometimes shipwrecks find you and raving men want you. You are a bottle of talent and power. What the unknown is you seek to find, and a lover. You have the moon and stars as freinds. There are a very few of you, what a rare find.
    
</post>
<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This thing is damn cute. I want one!!! T_T   
    
</post>
<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      AAAAGH!! I love quizzes ^_ Anywhoosy, I thought this one was right, comment! Tell me what you think!! ...or something!    You have a Calm Soul! Being calm and cool is what you do best. You collected thoughts and always positive attitude make you very bright and logical. When theres a problem, you know how to approach it, and solve it. Your friends rely on you on their problems, and your shoulder for their crying. You are peaceful, and enjoy nature and freedom. You rarely get angry and hardly scream, which makes you good with kids. You seem to be in tune with the world and if anything goes wrong, you always bounce back.   
    
</post>
<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was hoping I'd get water, this was totally unexpected @.@ I think it hit right on the mark though, you wouldn't picture me as a sad and lonely type would you? ^_^ How little I have told you my friends...    You're Element is Night. You're a loner who is very creative but will never show your work to anyone. You may smile a little but sadness or loneliness surrounds you and others can feel it when they're near you. You have a dark or unusual beauty that makes you mysterious and you probably have a lot of secrets that you've never told anyone. You're beauty is intriging and unorthidox but the real thing that makes you special is your eyes. Something in them makes them like "Diamonds in the Rough"    
    
</post>
<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      And now, for a random picture of my cat!!     Awww the cute blind-ability awwwwwww...
    
</post>
<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If this man isn't a god, I have no idea what he is. I've read a lot about him and listened to as much of his music as I can get my hands on, concluding that he truly is an incredible person. Not to mention insanely good looking &gt;.     XD gotta love that Zorro look.
    
</post>
<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well hmmm lessee here...in news, which rarely happens, I'm going to Germany on the 20th should be back by the 4th of July, and if I'm not, don't worry, I will be back. n_n Here's a fun little riddle for the few of you that actually read this: I shed my second tear, into the cup of cheer, But look not in any cup, the answer's written here! My first is in blood and also in battle, My second in acorn oak, and apple, My third and forth are both the same, In the center of sorrow and twice in refrain, My fifth starts eternity ending here, My last is the first of last...Oh dear! If I told you the answer then you would know, 'Twas made in the winter of deepest snow. ~Brian Jacques
    
</post>
<date>15,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yes, this is my blog thingy. It's oh so interesting as you can see &gt;_&gt;;; Hopefully I can get the hang of it soon enough and entertain you all...
    
</post>
<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Aww! You wished me a Happy Birthday right here in my own blog! That was sweet of you. I would have responded sooner if I had actually been home, but I kinda ran away on my birthday ~_~ I just got home a few hours ago, and I wouldn't have come back if it weren't for violin! T_T Stoopy parents always ruining my life. But thankuuu again Micky! (&gt;^_^</post></Blog>