<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       1. My favorite new slang word for "doin it": French Omelette.  It's an omelette with meat inside.  AN OMELETTE WITH MEAT INSIDE!  2.  If I were to have a band, I would name it "Post No Bills", just to stick it to the man.  Or "Uterine Lining".  3.  My Pret A Manger lunchbag has a slogan on the side: "This Bag Has Enjoyed A Previous Life!"  As what?  Another bag?  That doesn't sound very enjoyable.  Although I have been entertaining thoughts of my bag having been a very flamboyant Courtier in 18th Century France.  urlLink     
    
    
</post>
<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink     What better way to memorialize "The People's Princess" than with a "People's Super Awesome Fun Slide"?    A Memorial Waterslide/Open Sewer for Diana has opened in Hyde Park, much to the astonishment of those refined gentlepeoples of the British press (read: cause of her death).    Well, I hear that isn't half as bad as the 9/11 Bumper Cars.  And yes, that joke could have been 100 percent more tasteless/funny.   urlLink  Controversial 'Waterslide' Commemorates Princess Diana     urlLink  See Picture of It Here    
    
    
</post>
<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink     An angry mom in Macon, GA. got a little aggressive towards America's Creepiest Mr. Mice Guy.  She accused the Chuck E. Cheese mascot of not paying enough attention to her child, and as a punishment, pelted the mascot with piping hot pizza.  Good move, asshole.  That's his whole thing, that he LOVES pizza, so what do you do?  Throw pizza at him!    How do you discipline your child?  By stuffing his mouth and ass with Snickers bars?  God, I HATE idiots.   urlLink  Angry Mom Flings Pizza At Chuck E. Cheese Character     
    
    
</post>
<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hangs Self.  WARNING:  The site is called Vegan Porn, but I'm pretty sure it's work safe.  God almighty, I hope it's work safe.   urlLink Man Hangs Himself After Being Exposed As Bird Rapist  
    
    
</post>
<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'll make this quick.  To Ball Park franks, the hot dog company that promotes their horse meat with a YUGE man saying the word "Girthy" over and over again, girthy girthy girthy, all the while drooling on himself and then closing this spectacle by taking big, meaty bite of your weiner:  Let me be frank.  I get seriously physically ill every time I see this.  A quick Google search:   urlLink  Apparently I'm not alone.    To Centrum, and your new "CARB ASSIST" vitamin.  During your commercial, you twist the bottle around dramatically to reveal the title.  For about 2 solid seconds, I thought you had a new product called "CARB ASS".  And while I would be in your prime demographic for said product, I really don't appreciate being spoken to that way, by you, by your family, by all of your friends.  I see the way they look at me, and I'm not going to take it anymore.  Now get out! 
    
    
</post>
<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink     A little busy this morning, so for the time being, take a gand at these haunting and suprisingly lifelike mannequin heads.  The first one says "I can't afford a  urlLink facelift or a razor . And I may very well murder you slash grind on you in a Berlin disco," while the second one says "Ello!  I star in a multi-million dollar  urlLink cinematic franchise !  I was an  urlLink ugly kid , but in this last movie, I was  urlLink pretty hot .  Catch ya later!"   urlLink  SCARY MANNEQUIN HEADS     urlLink     
    
    
</post>
<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink Fans, you asked for it, you have it.   As reported previously, Mary-Kate Olsen has been sent to rehab for her voracious cocaine appetite.  What follows are some gift ideas to send to MKO in her time of need.   urlLink      1.   urlLink Tissue Box Cover   Lilting and feminine, she'll think of you every time she reaches for an Egyptian Cotton disposable hanky.  Every recovering coke head's first choice. (trust me.) ---------------------------------------------------------------  urlLink      2.   urlLink Skip It   A.k.a. "The Ball and Chain of My Childhood", this is the perfect sport to keep those with "the shakes" occupied and happy for hours.  Now, when she's "hopped up", it'll have a  totally  different meaning.  And I'm sure she'd appreciate that. ---------------------------------------------------------------  urlLink      3.   urlLink Vazline   Keeps those nostrils moist, not to mention those teeth gleaming for lurking, blood-hungry paparazzi. ---------------------------------------------------------------  urlLink      4.   urlLink The Taboo Broadway Soundtrack   Because nothing says "Put Down The Fucking Coke" better than a shitty Broadway musical about Boy George and drug addiction.  She has to learn her lesson somehow. ---------------------------------------------------------------  urlLink      5.   urlLink Razor Scooter   Stop cutting up white lines, and start scooting your way back to health!  It'll really bring out the kid in her.  Not to mention these things are  so  hot right now. 
    
    
</post>
<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink     As most of you know, American's beloved doppleganger, Mary-Kate Olsen,  urlLink recently checked into a hospital  for what my sources have confirmed is an eating disorder.  This sexy-rexy may be a billionairess, but she is still going to need some cheering up.  Below are some suggestions that might make this little anorexic who has everything feel a notch or two better.  ---------------------------------------------------------------  1.   urlLink 6-Ply Cashmere Turtleneck   If there's one thing this little stick-bug is gonna need inside that dreary hospital, it's the warmest sweater money can buy.  Watch as she pulls the sleeves over her hands while cupping a hot water with lemon.  She may be sick, but she looks damn good! ---------------------------------------------------------------   urlLink      2.   urlLink 18K Gold "Hang In There" Necklace   Here's the perfect way to let Mary-Kate know "Hey! You'll pull through this!  Just HANG IN THERE!  Don't die on us, ok?" ---------------------------------------------------------------   urlLink      3.   urlLink Butter   To ensure her survival.  ---------------------------------------------------------------  urlLink      urlLink  4.  Gorgeous Thick Human Hair    No nourishment = major hairloss.  Skip out on that  urlLink bedazzled doo rag  and opt instead for this luscious wig, perfect for those glamorous Hollywood outings and group therapy sessions.     UPDATE***UPDATE***UPDATE***UPDATE***UPDATE**             urlLink It's cocaine.   It's not an eating disorder, she's in rehab for a rabid cocaine addiction.    Instead of tossing the above list to the wind, apply it to a friend or loved one who is undoubtedly riddled with self-hate.  And stay tuned for an updated guide...   
    
    
</post>
<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Sheep Vest and Crotch Shot  A city in Australia plans on pumping Barry Manilow tunes, as well as other soft-core favorites, into crime-riddled underpasses and areas where drug dealers and other mufflegaggers tend to hang out.    The crime may go down, but I guarantee the suicide rate will go up.    urlLink Barry Manilow - Crime Fighter   
    
    
</post>
<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink     ...for even drawing this comparison.  The eery resemblance between  urlLink Craig Kilborn  and  urlLink Chris Burke . 
    
    
</post>
<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink     Ladies, are you tired of meeting too many men, and then never knowing which ones ones are keepers and which ones are goners?  Try this handy little guide from the "Glamour Magazine" of the Florida Panhandle, the Pensacola News.  In Dee Dee Ritchie's Pulitzer Prize winning article,  urlLink  "Judging a Man by His Cassarole"  , Dee Dee explains the ins and outs of your man's culinary dabblings.  Of Tuna Casserole:  Do I really even want a man who likes tuna casserole? As much as I love tuna, of the sea rather than of the can, I cannot gag down a bite of this dish. If a man eats your tuna casserole, it must be love because his taste buds are dead. It's a great litmus test.   I once made the mistake of judging my man by how long it took him to shower.  Over 10 minutes meant that he was obsessed with his body and himself, versus paying attention to me, talking to me, bathing me, combing my hair, telling me how nice I look, etc.  If the shower was over 10 minutes - he was OUT THE DOOR!  In the end, I had a very meaningful relationship with a man who I knew cared for me, but his body fungus had me saying "Smell Ya Later!"    
    
    
</post>
<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink     As I'm sure most of you now know, right now, in America, three babies are named ESPN (pronounced Espen).  One couple even plans on naming their second child ESPN 2 (pronounced, I believe, as Espen Douche).    As a result, ESPN plans on filming a documentary about these tykes, because if there's one thing ESPN fans love, its watching semi-retarded parents clean a dirty diaper.  The more I think about it, the more I like the idea.  Yeah, that's it, naming my baby after things I'm a fan of!    My first child will be called "Babaganoush", followed by "Snackwells", "Camel Ultra Lights", and my beautiful little girl, "Abortion."    Seriously, though, I will be happy to name my child "CBS".  All it's gonna take is for Les Moonves to drop that slut  urlLink Julie Chen , pick up a phone, and make it happen.    urlLink  Couple Names Son ESPN   
    
    
</post>
<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink     America is in desperate need of a funny fat woman.  Roseanne Barr (big fan) is passe,  urlLink Rosie O'Donnell  is obviously the worst (not counting  urlLink Another Stakeout , which is primarily funny thanks to the genius comic stylings of Dreyfus/Ethtebeth), and  urlLink Mama Cass , while never necessarily a comedienne, is most definitely dead.  Then it occurred to me... Whatever happened to  urlLink Edie McClurg ?    Edie McClurg was an icon, one of many faces that has faded post-1989 ( urlLink Rick Moranis  on Line 2).  And why?  McClurg's brand of humor was unique, from syrupy sweet southern charm to a two-faced bitch on wheels.  From Grace, the plucky secretary in  urlLink Ferris Bueller's Day Off , to Bonnie Brindle, on  urlLink Small Wonder , to the annoying yet loveable Patty Poole on  urlLink "Valerie"  cum  urlLink "The Hogan Family" .    And how is Hollywood using this genius?  In straight-to-video thrillers such as  urlLink To Kill a Mockumentary  and the 2003 sleeper bomb  urlLink Fish Without A Bicycle  (which I hear is almost as good as  urlLink Goddamn, Parrot, That's A Sweet Ride! )  Well, I, for one, am appalled.  From hereforth hencewith, I propose banding together to form the "I Needie More Edie" Campaign.  I'll be the President.  The t-shirts alone will clearly be snatched up by Urban Outfitters, and my talk show circuit run would be ginormous (Can anyone say  urlLink Livin It Up with Ali and Jack ? I can.)  Who's with me?  Write to MichCollinz-mail@yahoo.com, and let's make something happen, yes? 
    
    
</post>
<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink     For those of you workin' a day job (holla!), I highly suggest plugging your company headphones into your computer to get a listen to this hilarious commercial out of the East.       urlLink  Kill Bill Commercial    [via  urlLink Engadget ] 
    
    
</post>
<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink     Brace yourselves.  It's gonna be a  long  week.  An Iranian woman claims that she has given birth to a frog, reports newspapers in Iran.  Doctors speculate that the woman may have been impregnated whilst swimming in a dirty pool in Iranshahr, in Southeastern Iran.  I bet the Club Med there is  really  suffering.  Apparently, though, this woman isn't alone.  The BBC reports that in the long and rich history of amphibian-human impregnations:  One of the most famous was the 17th Century case of Catharina Geisslerin, known as "the toad-vomiting woman" of Germany.     And I thought that time I harfed up a live baby chick was bad!  It was definitely cuter.  I would LOVE to see this couple on Judge Joe Brown, or any other inane daytime Court drama:    "Ya Honor, his baby is 3 years old.  He does not pro-vide for me.  He was never there for his son!"    Cut to:  The other podium, where a live frog sits, defenseless and silent.  "I mean, look at him!  He cannot even hold. a. job.  And he's bad in bed!  Worthless, Ya Honor.  WORTH. LESS."  Cut to:  Frog.  Looking hurt.     urlLink  Iranian woman 'gives birth to frog'    
    
    
</post>
<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink     urlLink Scott Peterson  and  urlLink Ben Affleck : Separated at Girth  For an even better pic, check out Peterson (aka  urlLink "The Nadia Comaneci of Liars" ) on the cover of the  urlLink Post . 
    
    
</post>
<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink     The Uncanny Similarities Between  urlLink Michael Jackson  and  urlLink Adam Brody  
    
    
</post>
<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink      Zing!  Seriously, Wimbledon has really fallen through the cracks here in the U.S.  I've heard little to no coverage -- other than the  urlLink Venus Williams scandale .  Less of Michael Moore, More Action on the Court.  Thank you for your time.   urlLink  Wimbledon News   
    
    
</post>
<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink     While working at a sporting goods store in Johnson City, NY, a 23-year-old man found a spider, doused it in lighter fluid and threw a match at it, in an attempt to kill it.  The fire quickly spread to the surrounding merchandise, and burnt half the store down.  No word on how the spider is recovering.  I totally hear this guy's pain.  I am psychotic about bugs!  (play a clip of Country John from the Real World SF singing "True Story!")  One time, I killed a small spider in my bathroom, first by dousing it in perfume (thanks for nothing, Dolce and/or Gabbana), then by unloading half a bottle of hairspray on it and freezing it to death.  Then there was the time I killed a roach using bug spray, and airlifted it to my toilet using double-sided tape stuck to the bottom of a small grocery bag, a la  urlLink Jamie Lee Curtis'  helicopter stunt in True Lies.   urlLink  Worker Trying to Kill Spider Starts Fire    
    
    
</post>
<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink      Look, Arnold.  I'm a fan.  Grope all the women you want, spout slurs against jews, I just can't help but liking you.  I've always found your antics to be sweet, endearing, and overall unthreatening.  But you are  really  cutting it close with this one.    Arnold wants to repeal a state law requiring shelters to keep stray dogs and cats for six days until they're put to sleep. The new law would give the lil' pups and kits only three days until their little souls float up out of their bodies, cartoon style.   urlLink But stray's really do serve a purpose!   I think all Arnie needs to soften up and reconsider is a warm chai latte, a cashmere throw, and a little movie I like to call  urlLink The Adventures of Milo and Otis .  And seriously - can someone please massage Bob Barker's heart back to the "ON" position so we can get a spokesperson up in this peace?     urlLink  Schwarzenegger Wants Strays Killed Faster        
    
    
</post>
<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink       
    
    
</post>
<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       From the files of "I'm Gonna Be Sick.  No Really.":    urlLink The Smoking Gun  reports that a Judge in Oklahoma has been disrobed, so to speak, for using a male enhancement pump, shaving and oiling his nether region, and pleasuring himself.  Pretty standard stuff.  Pause, 2, 3.   All while sitting on the bench .  My god -- can you imagine?  "Keep that up (pump, pump), and I'm gonna put you (pump, sigh, pump) in CONTEMPT (pump) of the (hiss, hissss) COURT!"   urlLink  Here Comes The Judge      
    
    
</post>
<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink     My regular New York Post hocker on the Upper West has been MIA.  The result?  I've been gouging my eyes out using the fragmented sentences that make up AM New York (Named New York's Worst Newspaper 2004 by  urlLink You Can't Make It Up .)  I remember with fondness the funny headlines and celebrity snapshots.  The feel of the pulpy paper in my hand.  My blackened fingertips, calloused and cut, my biceps stringy and hard from the heft of its news.  Horses Cloned Via D.N.Neeeiiigh?  You said it, Posty.  Following is a link to an article from a few years ago describing in pitch-perfect Post prose a man arrested for stalking Serena Williams.  An excerpt:  In the interview, Stromeyer said his wealthy family and friends helped him finance his stalking, and he charged $15,000 on his HSBC credit card. "Please thank the bank," he said, smiling. "I couldn't have stalked without them."   He calls tennis "the game of kings."   "It is a graceful game that reveals the personality of the players," he said. "Serena is a dancer. She is the ballerina of tennis."   He said he fell in love with her two summers ago when he first saw her playing on TV. "She has this perfect tuft of hair. I had to watch her in person," he said.    There's nothing I can add to make this any funnier, so just read the whole thing, will ya?    urlLink I'm a Sweet Stalker   [via  urlLink Chelsea Peretti ] 
    
    
</post>
<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink     In what may be the most cringe-inducing article of the week,  urlLink ABCNews.com  reports:  Somewhere in Germany is a baby Superman, born in Berlin with bulging arm and leg muscles. Not yet 5, he can hold seven-pound weights with arms extended, something many adults cannot do. He has muscles twice the size of other kids his age and half their body fat. DNA testing showed why: The boy has a genetic mutation that boosts muscle growth.   Something tells me this kid would kick Tobey Maguire's ass in an alley fight.  Now that I think of it, I'm guessing an average 5-year-old would kick Tobes' ass.  Poor Tobey.  Poor, weak, lisping Tobey.  I mean, did you guys catch his interview on  urlLink Leno  the other night?  He speaks  so.  slowly.  It's like seeing a turtle watching Meet Joe Black in rush hour traffic.  THAT'S HOW SLOW IT IS!  Oh god. 
    
    
</post>
<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink     A Grace only a mother could love.  Some of you may have noticed that my usual manic, zealous, speed-driven postings have been lacking this morning.  Well, there's a good reason for that.  I went to the  urlLink Grace Jones  concert at  urlLink Crobar  last night. (Not to be confused with  urlLink Grace Jones , of  urlLink That Dawgone Dog  fame.)  Did I say good reason?  Make that  urlLink utterly retarded  reason.    For those of you wondering, Ms. Jones looked hagulous.  Following a two-hour delay (an anonymous source witnessed the hulking stallion take a mighty drunken fall down some stairs), she came out and served, bitches.    To make a tedious story longer, I'm on little sleep, and at a desk job where "the shakes" and "honking" are considered inappropriate office behavior.  So, in honor of this morning, I've set up a couple of links to keep my readers refreshed, whilst I crouch under my desk to grab some shut-eye right by the balls.   urlLink  Hungover.net     urlLink  William Hung     urlLink  Suicide and Prevention     (You'll Need This)   
    
    
</post>
<date>23,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Readers,  CNN.com is reporting that eveybody's favorite form of postage, the food stamp,  urlLink is in need of a facelift.    They're doing away with paper booklets, and upgrading to spiffy plastic swipecards.  They're also renaming it.  Oh, the possibilities!  Come up with some names you'd like to see replace "Food Stamp", and I'll publish the winners sometime in the next day or two.    And no, Apple and Coco are not real names.  Send your entries to:  michcollinz-mail@yahoo.com  Management   urlLink  Renaming Food Stamps   
    
    
</post>
<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink      Snicker inducing site from the catch phrase that had American saying,  urlLink "You're the Man Now, Dog!"   Pictured above:  "Sean Connery", winner of the Setter category at an Icelandic dog show, being lady-handled by  urlLink Louise Fletcher , of  urlLink One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest  fame.  Thanks to photog Kickie Boman for the pic.    urlLink You're The Man Now, Dog!  
    
    
</post>
<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink      Locals in a small Nepali village in Kathmandu (Pronounced "Cat Man Doo") are in a tizzy due to the overproductive secretions of one of their Gods.  No, not R. Kelly (zing!).  Rather, the deity has been sweating, a sure sign of doom.  Natives have been in a praying frenzy, sacrificing goats hither and tither, and bracing for the worst.    [T]he last time the Lord Bhimeshwor idol "sweated" was in January 2001, six months before Crown Prince Dipendra shot dead his father, King Birendra, and eight other royals before turning the gun on himself in a drunken rage... The deity also reportedly sweated in 1932 before an earthquake killed thousands of people.   That seems pretty serious.  The last time an idol sweated here in the States, millions of teenage girls ran out and bought Clay Aiken's album, "The Faggiest Mile."  A tragedy indeed.   urlLink  Anxious Country Prays to Placate 'Sweating' Deity     
    
    
</post>
<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    GOD, it's a slow news day. 
    
    
</post>
<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Somehow less addictive.  A chain of restaurants in China has been shut down after authorities found cooks mixing opium poppy in their soup.  The soup becomes addictive, guaranteeing repeat customers.  Not to mention the added bonus of your bowl talking to you, and your chair swallowing your soul.  "This could eventually lead you to drug abuse in serious cases," said national health authority spokesman Wei Tao. (ed note: for added fun, try singing his name to  urlLink The Surfaris' "Wipeout" )  While they're at it, they might want to scan the operations over at the Crystal Light factory.  I'll never forget a couple of years ago, waking up in the morning, and not finding an ice cold pitcher of Pink Lemonade waiting for me.   I would crawl up the walls!   I've since broken that habit, replacing it with the much less addictive alternatives of cigarette smoking and peanut butter.   urlLink     
    
    
</post>
<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink      In an effort to keep more New York ladies  urlLink looking their best , and more New York City men  urlLink masturbating in public , the MTA has rekindled a 35-year-young tradition of electing a "Miss Subway", a beauty pageant I'm hoping is limited only to  urlLink Mole People  and that dummy made of pantyhose that tangoes in Times Square.  On second thought, why stop there?  I think each New York City institution should elect a pretty face to represent it on billboards.  Why, there's Miss Empire State Building, Holly Arbuckle!  And look, over there, Miss Dead Frozen Homeless Man, Sally Finkleton!  Gasp!  Could it be??  Ms. Pubic Hair In My Knish, Madelyn Johnson!   urlLink  New York to Revive Subway Beauty Contests   
    
    
</post>
<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       This is a new feature here at YCMIU.  Rather than toast the celebrities who were birthed today, I've chosen to honor all those celebs who kicked the proverbial bucket of champagne wishes and caviar dreams today, June 23.    Today's Celebrity Deathdays are:   urlLink  Maureen O'Sullivan (87)     urlLink  Jonas Salk (80)     urlLink  Fleming Danty (43)     urlLink  Dorothy Dix (92)     urlLink  Aurania Rouverol (68)   
    
    
</post>
<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Happy Annual "Kittens In Your Nightmares" Day! 
    
    
</post>
<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       This is  exactly  the kind of news that makes this unpaid, self-employed job worthwhile.  CNN.com has reported that two inmates, one with a prosthetic foot, the other a fake leg, escaped from a "special needs" prison cell last weekend.  (If I had to go to prison, I'd be all for a "special needs" cell, a 4 by 4 concrete dungeon replete with melaleuca oils and hot stone therapy for my "special needs.")  Their names read like the back-up band for some 90 year old fiddle player: William Clay Bohanan, 40, Berl Keith McKinnie, 38, and Billy Leo Potts Jr., 39.    Luckily, two were caught.  I'm guessing they forgot to disguise their fake limbs with new shoes or a bandana tied around it, Punky Brewster stilo.   urlLink  Inmate with prosthetic limb at large       
    
    
</post>
<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink      Have you ever been noshing on Pringles, when the next thing you know, you find a powdery ranch image of Jesus staring you in the face?  Miracle?  Coincidence?  Chips in a cardboard tube?  That's crazy!  Thanks to Freddy, a longtime paranormal junkie and fan of all things totally fucking mad, there is an online documentation of various "Jesus Is In My Oatmeal" sightings.    What is perhaps the craziest is this little optical illusion, which I have posted above.  For starters, this is obviously a  very   loose interpretation of what Jesus looks like.  It's more like the result of a sweaty night of passion between Vincent Gallo and Skeletor.  Back to the magic of optics.  Freddy instructs:  Concentrate on the four little dots in the middle of the picture for about 30 seconds. Then close your eyes and tilt your head back.  Keep them closed...you will see a circle of light.  Continue looking at the circle...  WHAT DO U SEE?  Wait... Wait a minute... Gasp! There it is!  Someone with  way  too much time on their hands!*   urlLink  Freddies Paranormal Horizons    *Today's winner for the "Pot Calling Kettle Black" Award.      
    
    
</post>
<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Great!  (I pull out a gun, and blow my brains out.)  Here's a terrible joke, accompanied by an even worse mp3, read by what I can only guess is an illiterate Italian man.     urlLink  An Italian in Malta   
    
    
</post>
<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink      Look, if I had a 20 foot turd growing out of my head, I'd want to win an award too, ok?   urlLink  Man Goes for Guinness Longest Hair Record   
    
    
</post>
<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink      Sigh.  Probably. 
    
    
</post>
<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       A boat carrying 42 African migrants accidentally wound up on the shore of a nude beach in Spain this past Monday.  Telemundo was there to catch all the action, as the exposed bathers approached the heavily clothed Africans to see if they needed help.    One thing that caught my eye was this paragraph, just thrown into the article with no apparent explanation:  The migrants included four babies, including one just 11 days old. A group of bathers was shown gathered around one of the infants, gently counting the fingers on one of its hands and coming up with six.   A six fingered baby!  I used to have a history teacher armed with a sixth toe, which she would proudly model for us in a pair of 80 year old Aerosole sandals, the same color as her pasty, blue-lined foot.  Looking back, it was probably just an overgrown bunyon, but at the time, this sixth toe was all I had to focus on during painfully dry lessons of Western Expansion (to this day, my least favorite part of American History.)    But a sixth finger!   Think of all you could do!  You could play a 12 string guitar with ease...  Or type 200 words per minute!  You could frighten little children away, but then win back their affection by inviting them into your car for some free candy!    Man,  urlLink what I wouldn't do  for a sixth finger.   urlLink  African Migrants Wind Up on Nude Beach    
    
    
</post>
<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink      Have you guys checked out the  urlLink Cat Fancier's Association  lately?  Anybody?  No?  Well, take a deep breath and relax, because I check up on it hourly.  It's only three notches away from being my homepage, after the  urlLink American Idol  site and  urlLink www.BurningBoys.com .   Moving on, check out the Breed of the Day, the Ragamuffin.  Not just a cat, the Ragamuffin is also a companion, something to come home to...    When you first see a RagaMuffin from a distance - you will find yourself in awe. There lies a gorgeous, massive cat with large expressive eyes that are just begging for you to come closer. You will not believe its sumptuous color, its soft coat or the substantial size of its body.    Someone break out the hose!!  I've already got two of these little guys on backorder, cause I'm freaky like that.  I think I'll call one of them "Void" and the other "Filler."  Thanks to  urlLink C. Peretti  for the CFA link.   urlLink  CFA BREED PROFILE:  RAGAMUFFIN      
    
    
</post>
<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink      Do you know what time it is?  3 blood-curdling shrieks to quittin time!  Leave it to the Lord Co. Center (slogan: Repentance is Futile) to give us this years must have stocking-stuffer, the screaming Jesus clock.  (Check out the sound bites they have sampled on the page.)    Now, if someone could only find me a Kvetching Moses watch, we'd be in business.   urlLink  The Screaming Jesus Clock   
    
    
</post>
<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink      Today is a historic day for aviation enthusiasts.  This morning,  urlLink man's first privately owned rocket made its way into space.   Now, an 89 year old Trinidadian man is finally able to leave his apartment, thanks to a repaired elevator.  Newsworthy?  Maybe not.    I should add, however, that the man has not left his apartment  in eight years.   Eight years!  I've donated dozens upon dozens of eggs in that time!  So while I've been rolling in ovarian dough, this poor man hasn't seen the light of day.  Boy will he be embarassed when his kids come looking for him in 20 years!   urlLink  After Eight Years, Man Takes Elevator to Freedom   
    
    
</post>
<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink      This elk really crossed the Finnish line.  A toddler was slightly injured as a local Finnish elk busted through his window, crushing the boy's bed, but only scratching his cheek.    The boy's mother knew there was something wrong when she opened up her bedroom door and "was shocked to find the beast in her bed."  That's the same way I felt when Gary Sinise decided to surprise me with a post-work  urlLink "Afternoon Delight."    urlLink  Close Call for Toddler as Elk Crushes Bed    In a related story, my birthday isn't too far off, gentlemen.  Not that I expect you to get me anything.... we've only just met!!  But you know what they say:  the way to a woman's heart is through her black, corroded lungs.   urlLink  Genuine Elk Foot Ashtray    
    
    
</post>
<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink      What's one part "Aww!", three parts "Ha!", and a pinch of Vom?  Dogs in lederhosen.  Also, huge, middle-aged bosom.  But don't fret lasses!  The manufacturers have also made "Dirndls for the bitches."  Sigh - at least we know how Snoop Dogg's back-up dancers will look on his latest tour "Better Poon Her Than Later, Hozens."   urlLink  German Dogs Get Their Own Lederhosen   
    
    
</post>
<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink      Let's start off this beautiful week with a little ditty out of Europe's loveable kitten of a country, Germany.    Locals have been keeping their eyes and bananas peeled in the hopes of catching one lunatic in Berlin.    A camouflage-clad German man wielding a samurai sword attacked at least seven hikers in forests west of Berlin, performing sword tricks before ordering them to leave the woods, police said Friday...  The man pushed two elderly people off their bikes and, flashing his sword, shouted at them to leave the forest. He later tried to drive a young couple out of the woods.  This seems like just the type of enforcement we need here in New York.  Imagine how nice Central Park would be without all of those performance artists and  elderly   people.  And babies.     urlLink  German 'Samurai' on the Loose in Woods Near Berlin   
    
    
</post>
<date>18,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink      900 Degrees/ in the Mediterranean Seas with all the Grand Mommies/ Screaming "Help Me, I'm Dying!"  A solution:   urlLink  Italy Plans to Keep Old Folks Cool in Supermarkets   
    
    
</post>
<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink      Dr. Gigolo at your service.  A doctor was fined for convincing a patient that the only way to cure her pelvic pain was playing a little game of "Hide the Medical Sausage".    And I quote:   Hopkinson said the woman told officials that Smith told her massaging her ``trigger points'' would alleviate her pain. Eventually, he said, the therapy involved sexual intercourse.     That is horrible.  Totally disgusting.  *cough cough*  Uch, I think I'm coming down with something.  And my luck!  I'm going on vacay to Oregon tomorrow!!  Hey - wait a minute...  (insert smiley faced emoticon here).   urlLink  Doc Charged State For Patient Sex   
    
    
</post>
<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink      Michelle's Page of Animal Oddities Continues...  Whiplash, a 17-year-old Capuchin monkey, rides a border collie and herds sheep at the Old Fort Days Rodeo on June 5 in Fort Smith, Arkansas.   Don't worry, I've got the ASPCA on line 7. 
    
    
</post>
<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Which I believe is just myself?  Hello?  Am I right?  Just a quick plug:  I'm doing stand-up tonight at the reliably funny 8 O'Clock Show at the Boston Comedy Club.  It starts at 8, I should be going on at around 9 p.m.    The show is free with a student ID, with a two drink minimum.     The Boston Comedy Club  82 West Third Street between Sullivan and Thompson    
    
    
</post>
<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink      I happened upon this movie a few years ago, during an early morning viewing on Cinemax.  And what a goddamn treat.  John Travolta must live in a bubble.  And by "bubble", I refer to the plastic shower curtain lazily hung in the middle of his parents' living room.  Note how the "bubble" also has a huge open doorway, with a tiny fan blowing out the "germs."  How do we know there's a fan?  There are three pastel ribbons barely blowing out of the doorway, proving said airflow.  Also, Travolta spends the entire movie in a wifebeater and retro basketball shorts, because "ees really haht in dis bubb-le."  You don't know the half of it, Johnny!   WARNING: SPOILERS!  At one point, Travolta has a great idea - a portable bubble!  He maps out a diagram on some lined construction paper with a huge black crayon:  It's a stick figure, in a space suit, with a huge box strapped to its back, and a helpful arrow labelling it as a "Battery Pack."    Cut to:  The end of the movie where Travolta graduates wearing a 6 foot long oven mitt/lobster costume, and a smart looking mortarboard.    An interesting fact about this movie:  The woman playing Travolta's mother,  urlLink  Diana Hyland ,  was actually his lover in real life for many years.  She past away from cancer when J.T. was still in his prime.    On a serious note:  I would suggest watching this movie on mute for the first time.  The dialogue is genius, but watching these antics with no sound.... there are no words.  Also, the DVD is only $5.99 at Best Buy!!  (Possibly because the disc is made of matzah and recycled pickle jars.)   urlLink  The Boy in the Plastic Bubble     
    
    
</post>
<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Americans, be on alert:  Osama Bin Laden may be residing in our "friendly" neighbor to the north, Canada.  The perfect plan.  The. Perfect. Plan.  A taxi driver in Montpellier tried to run over a pedestrian he mistook for the bearded terrorist himself.  I can understand the confusion -- I hear they have an  amazing  Turban Outfitters there.  Zing!  See this link -- the article is definitely pee-in-pants material.   urlLink  French driver targets pedestrian he mistook for bin Laden!   
    
    
</post>
<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink      Readers,  I am in bad need of a good grooming.  Those who want to donate the the "Make Me Look Pretty Again" Fund can e-mail me at MichCollinz-mail@yahoo.com  I am only half-kidding.  Raindrops on Roses, Michelle 
    
    
</post>
<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Well, that ol' whore Madonna just won't quit.  She's changing her name to Esther, like a good mystic/jewish girl should.    If she really wants to re-tramp her image, she should go the whole kit and kaboodle and change her last name to "Prynne", while having a mammogram performed live on stage during "Borderline."  Then we, her faithful listening audience, can tack on a well deserved Scarlet "W.U.H." to her cardy = Washed Up Hag.   urlLink  Madonna reinvents herself as Esther   
    
    
</post>
<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink      Take a gand at this slightly used cosmetology school mannequin.  So many questions...  namely, what's the deal with the vice that comes along?  I've heard the phrase "It hurts to be beautiful," but this is ridiculous!!  What a country!   urlLink  COSMETOLOGY MANNEQUIN! STAND INC. MEDIUM LEGNTH HAIR!!!    
    
    
</post>
<date>17,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink  urlLink       Relax!  Some of my best friends are racist!  No, seriously, relax.  Click on below link to read the most misleading headline of the day...   urlLink  Donkey DNA Shows African Asses Were First Tamed    
    
    
</post>
<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink      A colt-blooded killer.  Check out how one horse terrorized a small farm in Arizona with his teeth and a mission:  Last Horse Standing.  I can already see the Lifetime TV Movie starring Maria Shriver as Henry, the loveable murdering horse, and Tori Spelling as Horses 1, 2 and 7.  Don't worry, Celine D.!!  You'll star in your own horse movie one day, I know it.     urlLink  Officials: horse-slashings case solved     UPDATE:   Priya, a friend and loyal reader, adds:  Among the horsefaced, you have forgotton their queen - rene russo.  She has been able to mask her horsiness with excellent lighting and killer tits - something tori spelling and the others can only dream of.  
    
    
</post>
<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'd like to wish a warm happy birthday to today's B-list and foreign celebrities!  Eff Entertainment Tonight, these ladies and gentlemen of screens small and tall deserve their moment in the sun.  Happy Birthday to:   urlLink  Greg Kinnear (41)     urlLink  Santiago López Castillo (60)      urlLink  Reginald Barlow (138)       urlLink  Thomas Haden Church (43)     urlLink  Þórðarson Garðar Bachmann (18)   
    
    
</post>
<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Here's a nice, artsy way to kill time at work.     urlLink  SCREENTOYS    Another idea?  Sometimes I pluck hairs out of my ankles.  Anything that threatens my speed in the water. 
    
    
</post>
<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Yoy! 
    
    
</post>
<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       This website caught my attention for a number of reasons.  For starters, I love goats, dammit.    For enders, on what other website would the sentence  urlLink  What should I do to care for the dam after kidding?     make any sense???  Some highlights include:   urlLink  How do I keep my goat healthy?    and a handy page of links by  urlLink  "Duh Goat Man"  .   
    
    
</post>
<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Jews rejoice!  For any of you unsure readers out there, it's official:  We really are running the media!    Take a gander at the Lox Networks latest fall programming.  It'll have you screaming  Gevalt! , just like the time your yarmulke fell off at the Fleetwood Mac reunion concert.   "Joe Minyanaire"   A good-looking young man goes to an Orthodox singles event and tells girls he meets there that he davens every day. Watch their reaction when they find out that he hasn't been inside a shul since his bar mitzvah in 1986 and spends every morning and afternoon at Starbucks!   "American Sheitel"    Viewers vote for the woman wearing the best-looking head-covering.   "The Rhea-Al World"   Rhea and Al Goldberg, married 55 years, are thrown together in a house in Miami Beach for a week with no TV. If both survive, they move on to the next installment: an hour-long trip in a Cadillac with no air conditioning. The excitement never ends!   "Don't Meet My Folks"   Three Jewish men take their girlfriends home to meet their parents. But watch out-one of the girlfriends is a shiksa! Parents try to guess which son is in an interfaith dating situation so they can throw him out of the house and threaten to sit Shiva for him. 
    
    
</post>
<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Good morning World! 
    
    
</post>
<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
            urlLink       
    
    
</post>
<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       First the Holocaust, then David Hasselhoff, now this.  A shriveled 81 year old German man was found not guilty of rape this past Tuesday when he proved that his "gavel" wasn't "bang-worthy" (you guys following my puns here?)    Apparently, nurses betrothed his wang with an "Erectometer", which, I'm guessing, hardly reacted.  Thanks to the esteemed Dr. Gabriel Liedman for the link.   urlLink  Suspected German Rapist, 81, Fights Potency Check    
    
    
</post>
<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       In a project Halle Berry can only  dream  of being a part of, feline-phile Mike Stanfill decides to serve the Quaker Oats man a steaming bowl of "In Your Face" with these hilarious pictures of cats looking at cats looking at cats....   urlLink  The Infinite Cat Project   
    
    
</post>
<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Walk, nay, RUN to your video store to pick up a copy of the 2003 sleeper bomb   urlLink Flavors .   If not for director Krishna D.K.'s vision, then at least to support YCMIU's Name of the Day,   urlLink Jicky Schnee .  
    
    
</post>
<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       K, I admit, the title's a stretch.  Things like this make me emotional.    Check out the following link to this doll on ebay.  Marvel at the elegance of the delicate prose.  Savor the refined quality and beauty of the porcelain face.  Then whack off to the upskirt photos.   urlLink  Beautiful "Toulouse Latrec" MIB w/hangtag    
    
    
</post>
<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       We'll begin this blog using a source that delivers real punch-to-the-groin journalism:  The AOL News Ticker.    I am seriously considering changing my given name to Lethal Homebrew, then blinding five people with my fists and fists alone.     urlLink  Lethal Homebrew Kills 13 Iranians   
    
    
</post>
<date>16,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hello Fans and Readers,  This is a little introduction to what I hope will become the blogging world's "new sensation" INXS-style except without all the suicide.  Maybe just some threats.  This blog is devoted to tracking down the most random and weird things found on the internet.  Articles that make you laugh.  Products that bring the query "What in the fuck?"  Things about old people.  The yoozh.  Feel free to e-mail me if you find anything truly bizarre or hilarious.    Doodles, Michelle        urlLink       
    
    
</post>
<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Readers,  This blog is coming to a 10,000 hit milestone, hopefully by the end of the weekend.  If you get a moment today, and you're a fan, don't hesitate to send out an e-mail referring people over here or even linking me on your own site (to which I'll return the favor).  It's a thrill seeing how many people access the site each day, and like a crack baby to a pipe, it's addictive.  Bright Copper Kettles, Michelle 
    
    
</post>
<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink  Woman In France Fired Over Writing Book Called "Hello Laziness: How to Survive in the French Corporate World Without Doing Any Work"      urlLink  Anti-Semitic Undertones Land Her Handsome Severance Package   
    
    
</post>
<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
         urlLink Irvin S. Yeaworth, Jr.  , director of cult classic  urlLink  "The Blob"  ,   urlLink is dead at 78 .    urlLink  Rosie O'Donnell Still Alive and Well.      urlLink Fat Jokes Deemed "Not Funny" by Angry Fat Guy.      urlLink Really ,  urlLink they   urlLink aren't .  
    
    
</post>
<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink       It's a long story, but something I saw on TV last night had me Googling "Presidential Pets" this morning.  And that's when I discovered the fascinating world of Presidential Pet Names and Breeds.  For example, did you know that   urlLink Teddy Roosevelt   had a pet guinea pig named "Father O'Grady"?  And while he wasn't toussling about with his wife's spaniel, Emily Spinach, he was probably out playing with his lion, hyena, wildcat, coyote, five bears, two parrots, zebra, barn owl, snakes, lizards, rats, roosters, and raccoon, to name a slew.  Believe it or not, unknown President   urlLink Rutherford Hayes   ended up making a difference in America -- by bringing over the first pair of Siamese Cats.  It would be only a few years later when his beloved Chinese kittens would play joke, and put pee-pee in his coke.  Loner  urlLink  James Buchanan   wasn't fucking around either:  when he wasn't vetoing a bill or causing a Civil War, he could be seen cuddling with his herd of elephants from the King of Siam and playing frisbee with his Bald Eagles.  Want to learn more?  Cart yourself over to the   urlLink Presidential Pet Museum   in Lothian, Maryland -- don't forget to swing by the gift shop!  Cause I'm not saying I didn't get any meaningful birthday gifts (one can never have enough   urlLink fart spray  ), but   urlLink look   urlLink at   urlLink this .     
    
    
</post>
<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'm currently reading a book by comic Dave Gorman called   urlLink Googlewhack! Adventure  , which will be released in September.  Googlewhacking is where you plug two words into   urlLink Google  , without using quotes, and receive only one response.  That response cannot be a word list, and both words must be in the dictionary.  I've spent the better part of my day trying to find a Googlewhack, and came up empty handed.  However, I did find two words that received NO responses from Google.  Therefore, I have nominated this very blog to be a Googlewhack.  Buckle up!    urlLink Sousaphone   urlLink Mulligatawny     UPDATE:   urlLink Googlewhacking Mission Accomplished.   
    
    
</post>
<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Police are searching for a man who has been  urlLink  stealing Port-O-Potties from soccer fields in Indiana  .  They describe the man as   urlLink 5'11", mentally ill, and smelling like an airplane toilet  .  They have also released a picture of the suspect, posted below.  Please call 911 with tips.   urlLink     
    
    
</post>
<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
         urlLink Just when you think you can't sink lower than    urlLink  Kangaroo Jack  ... 
    
    
</post>
<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink    Above, newborn baby "Custard Poopsalot"  I was in the Strand the other day, aka "8 Miles of Litter Box Liner, Half a Block of Books", when I happened upon a book called " urlLink Cool Baby Names ."  Being about 5 months pregnant with a "food baby" (no doubt the result of my recent obsession with nutty brown rice), I couldn't resist.    What. A. Treat.  Why name your child "Nicole" or "Kevin" when "Nyquoile" and "K'Vynne" are available?  Why spend your valuable time actually raising your child to be unique, when naming it Unique is so much easier?    Another source for fucking your kid up for good,  urlLink  CoolBabyNames.com  , has broken down their cool names by category:   urlLink  Shakespeare Names    urlLink  Gems, Minerals and Metal    urlLink  Sports Names    Wow!  I never would have thought I could name my kid after a sports star!  Meet my my son Abdul-Jabaar Schwartz.  And Shakeseare names??  I can hear the bone-on-bone schoolyard pummeling  already .    Some other possible categories:   Entertainment Awards Names:   Oscar, Emmy, Golden Globe, Razzie, Palme D'Or.  Feminine Hygiene Product Names:   Always, Monistat, Kotex, Vagisil  Euphemisms For Gay Sex Names:   Fudgepacker, Turdminer, Asspirate (pronounced Oss-pi-ra-tay),  urlLink Santorum   You can thank me later.  
    
    
</post>
<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink     12-year-old Ilana Wexler may not be a household name (save for her own, where word has it she's up for Homecoming Queen of her home-schooled class, population: Ilana Wexler).  But it looks like her popularity is on the rise.  Deeming the Spelling Bee Circuit too "bloodthirsty", tiny Ilana, clad in a purple cardigan and humongous red Jewfro, has chosen the road less mudslung: politics.    She's already started a website,  urlLink Kids For Kerry , which aims at taking money pre-teens normally use for pornagraphy, drugs and abortions and applying it to a better cause - helping John Kerry get to the White House (Amen).    Her hard work has paid off.   urlLink  Ilana was asked to speak at the Democratic National Convention in Boston this week  , and brought the crowd to their feet.  On Dick Cheney:  When our vice president had a disagreement with a Democratic senator, he used a really bad word.  If I said that word, I would be put in a timeout. I think he should be put in a timeout.  BOOYA!  In your face, Dick!  Put that mutha-fucka in a time-muthafuckin-OUT!  I am standing on my feet and clapping as I write this.  What's in store for Ilana's future?  After growing out of her "awkward phase", she'll wait around for approx. 10 years to find a man that likes her for "her brains."  She'll sleep on a mattress made of money, and will undoubtedly be more successful than me.  Sidenote:  Why isn't  urlLink  Jaleel White   running for Senate?  He could take   urlLink Obama   to school. Two times.  Front and Back Note:  Yes, I am fully aware the title makes no sense.  K My A. 
    
    
</post>
<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink      Sorry about lack of postings today.  I'm extremely busy planning a three week trip to the French Riviera.  Did I say French Riviera?  I meant rehab.  I'm busy planning a trip to rehab.  Forever yours, Jay Kaye. 
    
    
</post>
<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink     This morning brought on a grand discovery, a website called   urlLink Who's My Daddy  , where the famous lineage of many popular celebrities is exposed, thusby negating their so-called "talent" and allowing us to wallow in the pleasure of their  urlLink  undeserved fame  .  Well, I'm not one to brag, but if offering up my own celebrity lineage increases my chance at fame, then I guess I'm left with no other choice.  So here it is.  I am the child of   urlLink Julie Newmar   and  urlLink  Bootsy Collins  .  It's true.  Not many people are aware of their brief but fruitful romance.  I am all too aware.  Their fame cloaks me in a shadow of doubt:  Do I deserve this wealth?  This mansion, this champagne fountain, paid by three parts soul, one part funk and a couple of catwoman costumes?  Who are my real friends?  Do they like me for me, or are they just out for some of my Bootsy-licious fortune and fame?  Point being, if any of you casting directors or literary agents out there want to get your hands on some priceless pop-culture DNA, please contact me.  [Link via  urlLink Gawker  via  urlLink Chicha ] 
    
    
</post>
<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink       urlLink 'SEACREST' OUT IN SOME MARKETS    Above, a little celebrity math:  Seacrest + wig + drug addiction = Farrah Fawcett 
    
    
</post>
<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink     Believe it or not, there are some things  urlLink so tasteless  even I won't blog about them.    This item walked that very line, but like an obese man on a tightrope, lost its balance, and here it is.    Italy held their  urlLink  annual Ms. Chubby contest   this week, and crowned its winner with a tiara made from sausage links and Sno-Caps.  Giovanna Guidoni, weighing in at 416 pounds, literally took the cake, becoming 2004's official Miss Cicciona (which translates to "Uch, God.  No, Really, I Feel Sick.")  Fat jokes aside (of beef), did you know that there are forums online promoting anorexia?   urlLink  Pro-Ana sites   are springing up all over the net, instructing girls on how not to eat, what diets really keep your weight below 85 pounds, and listings for upcoming auditions.  Also of note,  urlLink this twig ,  urlLink this wall , and  urlLink flies fucking .  Somehow all more interesting than anorexics. 
    
    
</post>
<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink     What do you get the  urlLink  Courtney Love   who has everything?  Howsabout this  urlLink  I Had an Abortion   t-shirt?  I bet my mom  wishes  she had one. 
    
    
</post>
<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink     I was 30 minutes late to work this morning, thanks to some electrical problems at Chambers Street.  Subway Announcer:  The train is being held at the station.  I think:  Mmmm...  I bet it's nice being held at the station.   If anything in this city needs a little TLC, it's the subway.  A home/bathroom to many a gypsy and tramp, littered with garbage, hitting a person now and again... these things can be very traumatic for a train.  All it needs is to be held a little while.  But please.  Not on a Monday morning during rush hour.     
    
    
</post>
<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink     I'm not sure if you guys were aware or not, but Sunday nights on Turner Classic Movies is Silent Sunday Cinema.  A friend of mine and I tuned in.  Maybe because the only other options were  urlLink  "The Abyss"   (love) and  urlLink  "All I Want For Christmas"   (LOVE!), both epics in their own right, but movies I know all too well.  The movie was called   urlLink "Safety Last"   (I chuckle as I type), starring the adorable antics of  urlLink  Harold Lloyd   as "The Boy" and some floozy as "The Floozy".  Most of you are probably aware of the famous picture of some old timey guy hanging off of a clock, a still taken from this movie.  Please, for all that is sacred, try your best to get a copy of this film.  I cannot remember the last time I laughed so hard.  Some clips:  An officer named STUBBS, a drunk caught in a volleyball net, and physical comedy that makes Robert Benigni look like Al Gore! (a very wooden political figure, for those of you not aware.)     Perhaps the only cringe-enducing scenes involved overly racist stereotypes:  a Black servant who looked absolutely possessed, and a Jewish jewelery dealer whose greedy hand rubbing and blackened teeth made   urlLink The Passion of the Christ   look like  urlLink  Shoah  .  But for a movie made in 19-tickety-two, it didn't come as that big of a surprise.  For more info, check out this  urlLink  CNN article about Lloyd  , as well as a recent  urlLink  biography   written about him.         
    
    
</post>
<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink     Those wacky Japanese are at it again!  This time, a clothing company has created knife-proof clothing to protect Japan's schoolchildren from the likes of blade-wielding day-glo vampires thirsty for that sweet salty-eye-brine, or something like that.  Those Japanese.  Are Pretty.  Wacky.   urlLink  Sign of the Times: Knife-Resistant Garb for Kids   
    
    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Let's start the morning off on the wrong foot, shall we?  It's raining outside, it's dreary, I've got a stool-load of work to do, and I'm pretty sure I'm out of tampons.  Bodily functions aside, my hair looks terrific.  And I'm covered in strange dog hair (I don't own a dog).  SO!  Rather than delve immediately into "funny" stories about dogs dressed like ambulance drivers and monkeys on rollerskates, let us warm our hearts instead.  First off, an ex-crack addict and homeles man has donated $10,000 to an art gallery.  After receiving a large inheritance from his deceased mother (which reminds me, I need to call Aaron Spelling to reschedule our "date"), the newly rich ex-convict wanted to express his gratitude to the gallery after they allowed him to sleep in their doorway, no doubt while gallery owners sold canvases covered in black and white shit-smears for hundreds of thousands of dollars.   urlLink  Ex-Crack Addict Gives $10K to Art Gallery    Also, a divorced American soldier fresh from the sandpits of Iraq has struck gold in the Assachusettes lottery, winning $200,000 a year for life.  He plans on spending the money on "his kids' college education and [all the whores and booze money can buy.]"**  **Actual quote: Getting himself out of bankruptcy, but c'mon, we all know what that's code for.   urlLink  Soldier Home From Iraq Strikes It Rich In Lottery    Finally, in keeping with the theme of "money", we have  urlLink  Zoot Money  , pictured below.  I don't know what this guy's famous for, but somethin' tells me it has a lot to do with baby-makin' music.   urlLink     
    
    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
         EMOTICONS THAT WOULD COME IN HANDY    WHILE MESSAGING MY FRIENDS FROM THE OFFICE     ;</post></Blog>