<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>19,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Wooohooo!!! My first blog log....! I didn't know it's THAT easy...
     

    
</post>
<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Let me not to the marriage of true minds Admit impediments.  Love is not love Which alters when it alteration finds, Or bends with the remover to remove: O no! it is an ever-fixed mark That looks on tempests and is never shaken; It is the star to every wandering bark, Whose worth's unknown, although his height be taken.   Love's not Time's fool, though rosy lips and cheeks Within his bending sickle's compass come: Love alters not with his brief hours and weeks, But bears it out even to the edge of doom. If this be error and upon me proved, I never writ, nor no man ever loved. (Sonnet 116)    Love looks not with the eyes, but with the mind, And therefore is winged Cupid painted blind. (A Midsummer Night's Dream, 1.1.231-2)    She never told her love,  But let concealment, like a worm i'th' bud, Feed on her damask cheek. She pined in thought,  And with a green and yellow melancholy  She sat like Patience on a monument,  Smiling at grief. Was not this love indeed? (Twelfth Night, 2.4.115-120)     I love thee so, that, maugre all thy pride, Nor wit nor reason can my passion hide. Do not extort thy reasons from this clause, For that I woo, thou therefore hast no cause But rather reason thus with reason fetter, Love sought is good, but given unsought better. ("Twelfth Night", 3.1.151-6)     Love comforteth like sunshine after rain... Love's gentle spring doth always fresh remain. ("Venus and Adonis")    
     

    
</post>
<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink MTV   作詞:徐河娜  作曲:朴誠日(for新村music)  編曲:朴誠日  對白:成詩京    Baby don't you know it's for you   你的臉讓我開始感到迷惑 所有的疑問迷失在空中  像寶貝般呵護的帽 沒有太大的變化  寒冷的冬季氣候 就像我們分手的那天  這是一場鬧劇 沒有什麼感覺(保重..真的很對不起)  你是否還衣然眷戀著不知道何時能撫平的傷口 哦~~ 分手的那天是我先轉過身 你會不會恨我  是不是我真的太壞 不要走 這種沒有骨氣的話 我裝作聽不見  在心中不停喃MY Love  心痛的喘不過氣來 ohh   像漫畫一樣 我們一見面就吵不停 像拉德與愛莉一樣每天..........  只有嬴才能讓我的心得到平靜 ...ooh (對.....我對不起你)  你是否還衣然眷戀著不知道何時能撫平的傷口 哦~~ 分手的那天是我先轉過身 你會不會恨我  是不是我真的太壞 不要走 這種沒有骨氣的話 我裝作聽不見  在心中不停喃MY Love  心痛的喘不過氣來 ooh   **坐在樓梯口等待你 我期盼能夠再次擁有  不停地祈求著不知現在你還是不是一個人  你會不會恨我 我是不是真的太壞  不要走 這種沒有骨氣話 我裝作聽不見  在心中不停呢喃MY love  心痛的喘不過氣來~ooh no no wowo no wowowoooh  裝作聽不見在心中不停呢喃MY love  心痛的喘不過氣來ooh    아마도 사랑이겠죠 - 장나라     Baby don't you know it's for you   귀찮게만 느끼던 그대 얼굴  차창밖을 지나 멀어져가요..  마치 보물처럼 아끼던 모자.  변한게 없네요...   벌써 코끝 시린 계절이 왔죠,,  우리 헤어지던 그때처럼  조금 우습지만 그럴듯 했었죠...  (잘가.. 정말 미안해..)   그대도 힘들었나요  서로가 언제 가야할지를 몰랐었죠..  처음하는 이별 나 먼저 돌아서 버렸죠..   내가 미웠겠죠..내가 나빴어요  가지말라던 그 용기없던 말을 모른척했죠..  작아지던 목소리 MY LOVE~~  내 맘 아프게 하네요..   만화처럼 우린 만나면 싸웠죠..  톰과 제리처럼 매일을..  항상 이겨야만 편했던 내 마음..  (그래.. 내가 미안해..)   그대도 힘들었나요  서로가 언제 가야할지를 몰랐었죠..  처음하는 이별 나 먼저 돌아서 버렸죠.   내가 미웠겠죠..내가 나빴어요  가지말라던 그 용기없던 말을 모른척했죠..  작아지던 목소리 MY LOVE~~  내 맘 아프게 하네요..   낮은 계단위에 앉아  날 기다리던 모습이..  다시 찾아왔으면 해요..기대해보지만  그대 곁엔 누군가가 있네요..   내가 미웠겠죠.. 이제 용서해요..내가 나빴어요  가지말라던 그 용기없던 말을 모른척했죠..  작아지던 목소리 MY LOVE~~  내 맘 아프게 힘들게 만드네요..   모른척했죠..  작아지던 목소리 MY LOVE..  내 맘 아프게 하네요..   urlLink  
     

    
</post>
</Blog>