<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
            Last night worked late in the office till 9.30, but thanks to msn to keep me company. Had a nice long chat with him. Cute n interesting fellow, really enjoyed the 3hours chat.. shared alot of stuffs together..      Suddenly gto a call from mum, told me ah boy;s feet is swollen and is on his way to see doctor.. Can sense mum is crying n worried.. Boy is mum's favourite, that s why i can understand her anxiety..      Reached hme about 10 , went to see ah boy.. wahh siahh his feet is really very badly injured.. goin for x ray today.. hopefully there's nothing serious.. if nt will be very jia lar...             
</post>
<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
             断点 静静地陪你走了好远好远连眼睛红了都没有发现听着你说你现在的改变看着我依然最爱你的笑脸连这条旧路依然没有改变以往的每次路过都是晴天想起我们有过的从前泪水就一点一点开始蔓延 我转过我的脸 不让你看见深藏的暗涌已?shy;越来越明显过完了今天 就不要再见面我害怕每天醒来想你好几遍 我吻过你的脸 你双手曾在我的双肩感觉有那么甜 我那么依恋每当我闭眼 我总是可以看见失信的诺言全部都会实现我吻过你的脸 你已?shy;不在我的身边虽然你不在我的身边我还是祝福你过得好一点短开的情线 我不要做断点只想在睡前 再听见你的 蜜语甜       
</post>
<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
            Wu Tian Jian Wei Ni Bu Ku Ming Tian De An Wen..Wei Ni Bian Jian Jiang Xiang Xin Ni De Yan Shen..      Used to sing this song together with me in the car..remembered the time we used to spent together rollerblading, chit chatting at east coast "The rock", our rooftop, bumper boat, haunted house, runway and our peaceful home in seletar and many more..      Got to get used to the new life now... watever is gone now will never be back.. Thank you for all the sweet memories and moments we have once shared..Whenever i look at the precious moments figurines, i will think of you..each figurine i have definetly carries some special meaning.. how m i goin to forget you..Will you still think of me when you walked past precious moments store next time?      Remembered all those songs i burned for you? I always ask you to listen to the lyrics, cos the songs says all..We shared a few "Jing Dian" like.. Wu Ding, Zhi Shao Zou De Bi Ni Zao, Yong Qi, Love Me, Wang Le Yin Chang..      Nw can only try to be "Siao Sa" and let you go..       
</post>
<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Whew, after this morning's struggle i finally managed to set up my 1st post! Yeah! Thanks to you ah! My dear! HAha! Feeling abit drained out after the 3 days cruise, so sinful at the buffet! Food and more food! Jus cant resists the seafood and the delicious crayfish! Yummy!!!! Sis is away for 2 weeks, kinda missed her presence in the room..  Mum was so lucky last week, struck lottery twice on Wednesday and Sunday. Not great amount but still its better than nothing..  Had long chat with audrey onboard the past 2 nites..talked bout family, love life, friends and work..she is troubled too over her love life over sam and lawyer..hopefully she will get passed it soon..So envious of her parent's lovey dovey manner..after so mnay years of marriage, they still looks like their newlywed..Will i be like them down the road?  Results will be out soon i guessed..haiz dun know can scrap throught or not.. driving test also coming nt mth..havent learn proper parking n nt even go into circuit yet..wah piang really siao liao!  
    
    
</post>
</Blog>