<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    me and my lil' brother at regal 18 urlLink   
      
</post>
<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    me and lil' sister at Brian's house urlLink   
      
</post>
<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    me... chillin' urlLink   
      
</post>
<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    The girls singing karaoke!!! urlLink   
      
</post>
<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    My SCHOOL!! urlLink   
      
</post>
<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Kristie!! a good friend of mine urlLink   
      
</post>
<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Omar, Hector, and Andy's back (bowling night) urlLink   
      
</post>
<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    My brother and Sister playing on the snow at NOrth Carolina urlLink   
      
</post>
<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    The first filipino bead flag I made. urlLink   
      
</post>
<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Logan pulling the straps of his book bag (when breakdancing battle at Stratford) urlLink   
      
</post>
<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Martin with a tampon tucked in his ear urlLink   
      
</post>
<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    me............. urlLink   
      
</post>
<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    me and Marjorie at her house urlLink   
      
</post>
<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    My ex Andy (we're good friends now) urlLink   
      
</post>
<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    me eating my birthday cake (Oriental Mindoro) urlLink   
      
</post>
<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    me and layce at their driveway urlLink   
      
</post>
<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    me...  urlLink   
      
</post>
<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Me at Daisy's house (going to the gym with Bay) urlLink   
      
</post>
<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    me without make-up... I look bad on this pic urlLink   
      
</post>
<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    me at stratford's bathroom urlLink   
      
</post>
<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    me at deb's room urlLink   
      
</post>
<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Felipe Dylon at a soccer game at Brazil urlLink   
      
</post>
<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    my brother with a hooter chick urlLink   
      
</post>
<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Me and Pussy urlLink   
      
</post>
<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    This is my cousin's cat... she calls it Mingsimings but me and my friend Savannah call it Pussy.  well anyways on this picture as you can see Pussy was eating the Bulgarian flag that I made for Daisy urlLink   
      
</post>
<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    My future husband!! urlLink   
      
</post>
<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    My school urlLink   
      
</post>
<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    My future husband!! lol hahah urlLink   
      
</post>
<date>20,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      this morning was horrible... i wanted to go to the damn flea market but my lazy ass uncle won't give us a fuckin' ride!!!  I mean that's why he's living with us so he can provide us some sort of transportation since my mom doesn't know how to freakin' drive.  I mean i know ain't wiser than she is...  but come on now my dad has been teachin' her for like 3 or more months now... and then she blames my dad for not being able to teach her better??? she's the one who don't wanna listen to my dad.  she doesn't like being told what to do.  I mean this shit is all her fault.  She's the one who wanted us to move... she spent a bunch of money just movin' to this trashy trailer.
      
</post>
<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Go to my website:   urlLink http://malandi.azn.nu  
      
</post>
</Blog>