<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Mokuba tossed a half eaten slice of cold pizza back into the take out box and made a sour face.  “Yuck” he muttered to himself as grabbed a can of grape soda off the elegant oak end table next to the couch. Noa glanced at the open phone book on his lap as he dialed the phone. “I hope Duke answers” Mokuba chuckled as he sipped his soda.. Noa sank back into the sofa as the phone began to ring. {High Rollers, Duke speaking.}  Noa took a deep breath and tried hard to not laugh. He covered the mouthpiece with his hand.         “It’s Duke” he whispered to his younger half brother as he pressed the speaker phone button. Noa cleared his throat.   “Hello, is Mike there?”  {Mike who?}  “..Rotch” Noa replied, covering his mouth to prevent himself from laughing. {I’ll ask, hold on.......Hey! There’s a guy on the phone looking for Mike Rotch, Has anybody seen Mike Rotch today?} Mokuba covered his face with a pillow and burst out laughing. It took a massive amount of Noa’s will power to not do the same. {Sorry dude, no dice. I can’t find Mike Rotch anywhere......uh.....what the fu-HEY! Who the hell is this!} “Oh, sorry, wrong number!” Noa laughed as he abruptly disconnected the call.  Mokuba sat up laughing hysterically and wacked Noa over the head with a pillow. “You’re crazy Noa! That was hilarious!” Noa caught the pillow. His eyes were teary from laughing so hard. “I’ve never done that before, that was fun.” Mokuba picked up the phone book and took a few deep breaths as he looked up a name. After he had regained his composure he dialed a number.  “You thought that was funny? Check this one out.” he whispered away from the mouthpiece.  Noa sat at the edge of the sofa watching Mokuba enthusiastically. Mokuba’s eyes flickered with mischief as a person answered. He quickly pressed the speaker phone button so that Noa could listen in. {The Pizza Place, How may I help you?} a male voice answered. Mokuba grinned at Noa as he cleared his throat.  “Uh, yes, my name’s Harry, Harry Blubauls, with whom am I.uh... speaking to?”  Noa covered his mouth with the pillow and snickered into it. To disguise his voice, Mokuba had lowered his voice and made himself sound like a really dumb hillbilly.  {This is Roy} The man on the other line answered. Mokuba winked at Noa. “I’m uh....cawlin’ ‘bout a pizza. My brother and I had ordered one of your fancy ass super supreme cheese pizzas earlier this afternoon, and uh..... that shit ‘dun made us sicker than dogs! Weez just spent two hours in the hospital thanks to yar rotten nasty shit rich folk food! I want my money back you scumbag!” {You got the pizza here? Are you sure?}  “Skuze me? Are you cawlin’ me stupid? I’ll tell you what mister! My momma din’t raise no dummy! I know when when I’m gettin’ screwed, and you folks ‘dun screwed me bigtime!” {I’m not calling you stupid sir, I’m sorry. We have six other locations around the city and I was just asking if it was possible that you may have visited one of the other establishments.} “You really think I’d call the wrong damned pizza joint? I’m insulted!” {I’m sorry sir, I didn’t mean to mock your intelligence.} “I sure as hell hope you ain’t! If you are......oooh......I’d send my cousin’s over to your stank ass place and have them teach you’s a lesson! Now, how’s about you givin’ me my money back for selling me an overripe pizza?” {I’m sorry sir, I can’t do that} “What! I’s just spent the past two hours retching up the most disgusting things out of every orifice because of your food, and you won’t gimmie my money back? I’m callin’ my lawyer! I’m not asking you to pay the hospital bill here! The colors that were shooting out of me! Lordy it was hideous! Blues, and greens, and reds.......chunks of turquoise! I thought I was dyin’! I saved that shit as evidence!”  { Yeah, but sir....}           “Yeahbuts living in the woods you dufus. Now I want my money back, no yeah buts ‘bout it boy! Have you ever had your stomach pumped? You know what them there doctors do to you when you get your stomach pumped? They stuff this tube up through your.....oooooh! I can’t even think about it! The pain! It was terrible! I hope you all burn in hell for what you dun to my brother and I! Neither of us’ll be able to fuck for at least a month! You ever gone without sex for a month?”  Noa couldn’t help but notice how ‘good’ Mokuba was at this. He handled the call like a professional actor. The goofy voice he was using sounded nothing like his own. He continued to badger the confused pizza place worker until the guy finally hung up on him. Mokuba and Noa laughed hysterically after the call. The two of them were in tears from laughing so hard at their antics.  “I just had a really good idea.......I’m calling Duke again.” Mokuba grinned.          ************************************************************  	Ryou could feel Malik’s warm body snuggled tightly next to him. He could feel every breath Malik took rising and falling against his back. The air in the room was warm and still. Ryou could smell lingering sweet scent of the oil Malik had rubbed into his skin the night prior. Almost all traces of his sunburn were gone now, in fact, after staring at his arm for a while, Ryou thought he looked a little tan. He glanced over at the night stand at the alarm clock and looked at the time. It was only a little passed seven o’clock. David had mentioned to Ryou that he was coming to pick them up around ten, so Ryou had plenty of time yet to exercise what he’d read in his Kama Sutra book. Ryou slipped quietly out of bed and went to brush his teeth. Morning breath was something he didn’t want to share with Malik. After brushing his teeth and running a hair brush through his hair, Ryou snuck back into bed with sleeping Malik. He looked over Malik’s angelic face and smiled. Slowly, Ryou peeled away the blanket covering Malik’s waist. He wanted to wake Malik up his own special way. Ryou kneeled between Malik’s legs and lowered his head. Ryou wrapped his hand around the base of Malik’s shaft and using the blade of his tongue, began to lick upward. Ryou licked up one side and than down the other.  Malik moaned lightly in his sleep. His hand twitched slightly as Ryou kissed and nibbled lightly on the sides of Malik’s growing arousal.  Ryou loved watching Malik’s face. He looked up at Malik as he took the head of Malik’s shaft into his mouth. He moved it around in his mouth using his tongue, stimulating Malik even though he was sleeping. He watched Malik make an array of amusing sex faces as he engulfed   the entire length of the Egyptians growing manhood.   Malik moaned again as he started waking up to Ryou’s surprise.  Ryou’s stopped half way as Malik’s eyes opened and started sucking vigorously. Malik dug his fingers into the sheets below him and sucked in a deep breath between his teeth. His entire body stiffened as Ryou sucked him rock hard. “That’s...amazing....Malik whimpered between clenched teeth. Ryou slid his lips upward and kissed the tip tenderly. “Morning Sunshine” he chuckled as he massaged the rigid shaft in his hand with his thumb.  “Yes......” Malik shivered as Ryou wrapped his lips around the tip and began to flick his tongue over the bundle of nerves. Malik’s senses were exploding with need. He trust his hips upward in hopes to gain more contact with Ryou’s soft lips. Ryou gripped firmly onto Malik’s hip with his free hand as he stroked him with the other. Malik reached over and laced his fingers in Ryou’s white hair.  “You’re so hot Ryou Bakura.” Ryou chuckled as he took Malik’s entire length into his mouth. The vibrations of his laugh sent shivers through Malik’s body. Ryou could feel the pressure building inside Malik, so he slowly pulled his lips away. Malik whined in protest from the loss of contact with his lover’s mouth. Ryou grinned as he licked his finger and slowly inserted it into Malik’s rear entrance. Malik’s whines turned into whimpers as Ryou prepped him for what was yet to come. Ryou inserted a second, and than a third finger , eliciting an even louder whimper from his writhing partner. Ryou stopped and  looked up at Malik’s face.                 “I’m not hurting you, am I?” Malik bit down on his bottom lip and clenched his eyes shut.  “A little bit......but don’t stop.....it’ll feel better soon.”       Ryou pulled his fingers out of Malik and rose to his knees.  Malik brought his legs up and wrapped them around Ryou’s shoulders. He crossed his ankles behind Ryou’s head. Ryou slowly pressed himself inside of Malik, taking his time to make sure he was giving as much pleasure as he was receiving. He slowly began to move in and out of his needy lover. Ryou threw his head back and cried out as Malik’s tight heat wrapped around his arousal. He quickened his rhythm and thrust deeper into Malik. Malik squeezed his eyes shut and rocked his hips against Ryou’s. “Oh Ryou, that feels so good! Harder, harder!” He moaned as Ryou repeatedly struck his prostrate, sending shockwaves of pleasure through his lithe body. Ryou grabbed Malik’s ankles and ran his hands slowly down Malik’s long legs. Malik continued to squeeze his ankles tightly together around Ryou’s neck. Ryou lightly raked his fingernails down Malik’s chest, leaving light red welts in the wake. Malik’s body twitched with his pending orgasm. He grabbed two fist fulls of his creamy blond hair and growled under his breath. “Fuck me hard, Ryou, HARDER!”  Ryou plunged his himself harder and deeper inside of Malik to the point where he could barely breath. He stroked Malik’s throbbing manhood vigorously to help draw out his release. Ryou’s body couldn’t handle anymore and with one final deep thrust, he screamed Malik’s name as he spilled his essence inside of the blond. Malik felt his body tingle as his release shot out onto his chest.  Ryou leaned over and eagerly started licked the salty fluid off of Malik.  “Mmm, Malik......” Ryou moaned as he licked up the last drops.  Malik pulled Ryou up into a passionate kiss, tasting the salty left over remnants of their passion on Ryou’s soft, supple lips.   “I love you Ryou” Malik said softly against Ryou’s lips. Ryou smiled brightly and nipped at Malik’s lower lip. “And I love you, Malik Ishtar.”  ************************************************************** 	Tristan stared into the intense emerald eyes gazing back at him. A thin film of sweat covered his forehead as he and Duke fought for dominance in an old fashioned arm wrestling match on top the pin ball game. Duke let out an agonizing growl as Tristan let out a final grunt and slammed Duke’s hand down. “HA! I win!” Tristan grinned triumphantly. Duke rubbed his knuckles and made a sour face. “Yeah, yeah. I let you win, Taylor. Next time I won’t let you off so easy.” Tristan rolled his eyes as he made his way behind the bar and poured himself a mixed drink.  “If that’s what you want to think, buddy” Tristan chuckled as he picked up a white dish clothes and wiped off the bar. Duke propped his chin up with his hand on the pin ball game and groaned. “I could really go for a buzz right now.” Tristan sipped his mixed drink and sighed. “You just got high an hour ago, dude.” Duke scratched his head. “Oh yeah.......I guess I did.” Tristan looked at the clock and groaned.  “I wonder when that new bartender you hired is going to show up. I was really hoping on getting out of here by five o’ clock so I could talk to Boom Boom Blackmore about selling me his 1972 Chevy Monte Carlo with the 454 engine and duel four barrel aluminum intake. The one that throws flames out the exhaust.” Duke perked up and joined Tristan behind the bar.  “You mean Boom Boom the smelly old hippie that lives in a parked school bus out in the woods?” Tristan nodded his head. “Yeah man, he said he’d cut me a good deal. I told him I’d meet him in the beer tent before the races tonight.” Duke shrugged his shoulders. “I can stay here tonight, you go ahead. I know how much that car means to you.” Tristan’s face lit up with excitement. He threw his arms around Duke and kissed him on the lips. “You’re the best, dude. Thanks!” Duke grabbed a bag of cheesy popcorn off of a rack next to the cash register and pulled up a seat behind the bar. “No prob. I’d rather stay here tonight anyway.” Tristan grabbed his jacket off of a hook on the wall and pulled it on. “Mind if I take your Harley? My Honda is running like shit.” Duke grabbed a chocolate bar from the candy rack and tore the wrapper open with his teeth. He pointed to his set of keys that were laying on top of a shelf beneath the bar. “Go ahead, just don’t fuck it up man. I just had it detailed.” Tristan grabbed Tristan’s keys and headed out the door quickly. “Don’t worry, I’ll bring your baby back in one piece. Later dude!” “Yeah, later” Duke sighed as he got up from his seat and walked into the newly added kitchen located through a door behind the bar.  “Hey Duke, you’re sure looking all bummed out tonight, is something the matter?” Geraldine, more commonly known as Jeree, the top notch cook Duke had hired to run the newly added dining area, ask sweetly. Duke poured himself a cup of steaming hot fresh coffee and smiled at the friendly middle aged woman who wore white-blond hair up in a cute little pony tail. “It’s nothing Jeree, I’m just a little tired tonight.”  Jeree patted Duke on the back and smiled up at him.  “Aw, I wish I could help you out, but I don’t know jack about mixing drinks.” Duke pulled the smaller woman into an affectionate hug and laughed. “Don’t worry about it sweetheart, you just stick to doing what you do back here. I have yet to hear any complaints about your cooking.” Jeree blushed because of Duke’s compliment and lightly chuckled. As Duke took a sip of his coffee, the phone began to ring. Jeree winked playfully at Duke as she started walking toward the storage room. “If you need to talk honey, I’ll be here.  Duke nodded his head as he went to answer the phone. “I’ll keep that in mind” he answered her before he picked up the receiver.  “High Rollers, Duke speaking.” **********************************************  	Malik and Ryou cuddled up next to each other and relaxed after their little early morning  romp between the sheets. They knew they had to get out of bed, but they didn’t really want to. The warm sun laid out a choppy blanket of light over them as is crept in through the window blinds. Malik stretched his arms above his head and yawned. The sun reflected off his gold wrist bands and cast funny shapes on the ceiling. He chuckles as he made the reflections dance around on the ceiling. Ryou watched Malik’s little light show and giggled at Malik’s commentary. “Come here my little orb of light, don’t run away from me!” he laughed as he made one circular reflection chase the other. “AHHH! Noooo! The darkness is taking me! Help! Help! Ahhhhh! ” he continued on playfully as he flicked his wrist and made one of the orbs of light disappear. Ryou reached up and grabbed Malik’s hand. He brought it up to his lips and kissed Malik’s knuckles.  “You’re so cute Malik, but we better get our lazy rear ends out of bed before my father returns to pick us up.” Malik propped himself up on his elbows and nodded his head. “I hope I can remember how to get out to that oasis again.” Ryou sat up and swung his long legs over the edge of the bed.  “I’m sure you will. If you don’t, Marik will remind you.” Malik nodded his head as he watched Ryou pull on a white button up shirt. “M’hm.....hey, did that stuff I bought you work on your sunburn?” he ask curiously as he admired his perfectly bronzed legs. Ryou looked back at Malik and smiled. “Yes, it worked phenomenally! It doesn’t even feel as if I was ever burned. Thank you very much, Malik.” Malik waved his hand in front of his face and shrugged his shoulders. “It was nothing.” Ryou pulled on a pair of shorts and sat down on the bed to put on his socks and shoes.  Malik quickly gathered his own clothes and put them on. Just as Malik and Ryou finished dressing, Ryou’s father knocked at their hotel door.  “It’s open” Malik yelled as he put in his earring. David walked into the room looking very tired. He hard dark circles under his eyes, and he looked like he was lacking greatly in the sleep department. Ryou walked up to his father and gave him a big hug. “Hello father, are you feeling alright? You look a bit disheveled this morning.” David rubbed his eyes and sighed as he sat on the bed. “Just sleepy. Are you boys ready to go?” Malik and Ryou nodded their heads as they gathered their belongings. David looked on the floor next to the bed and noticed a book had fallen under the bed. He picked up the book and read the title, “The Kama Sutra.” A big grin swept over his face and he handed it to Ryou. “I don’t think you’ll want to forget this, son.” Ryou took the book from his father and blushed as he stuffed it into the bag he was carrying. Malik burst out laughing. “No Ryou, you can’t forget that! We need that for later!”  ***********************************************************  	Yami stared at his son’s angelic face and studied it from every angle. There was no doubt in Yami’s mind that this was his son. The baby boy had the same crimson eyes and defined facial features as he did. Yami could also see the Ishtar in his son, Solon resembled his uncle Malik quite a bit. He had bright blond hair that was exactly the shade of his uncle’s. As much as Yami didn’t like to think about it, he and Malik were related, and there was no way to deny it. He held his small, sleeping son close to his chest and listened to the delicate child breathing deeply in his arms. Yami closed his eyes and sighed. He knew his time with Solon was limited. Isis was only visiting, and had plans to leave the next day with Solon back to Egypt. It bothered Yami that he’d already missed out on the first five months of his offspring’s life. He felt strongly compelled to try to be part of Solon’s life. He wanted part in raising him. He didn’t want his son feeling neglected by his father. Yami knew he only had one option if he was going to a major part of Solon’s life: to go back to Egypt.  Yami opened his eyes and glanced over at Yugi and Isis. They were both sitting at the kitchen table looking at photographs. For the first time in months, Yami opened up their mind link.  //Aibou......I need to speak with you about something.// //What’s wrong?// Yugi replied casually through their link. //I’d rather talk with you about it tonight after we go to bed. Do you think you could wrap things up down here?// //Yeah, sure Yami. Anything you want.// Yugi responded. ********************************************************* 	On the drive out to the oasis, David explained to Malik and Ryou what he knew about early Mesopotamia. Ryou brought up the information Bakura had mentioned about a king named Malik, and his father acknowledged the validity of the existence of the ancient king, though it wasn’t common knowledge. The only reason he’d heard of the ancient king was because he’d been fortunate enough to be part of an excavation team digging at Nineveh that found some ancient cuneiform tablets containing the name back in the 1960's. After a long drive out into the desert, they finally spotted the oasis. David parked the truck they were riding in under a tree and they all piled out. David followed Malik and Ryou as they sprinted toward where they had seen the stone markers. “Over here, father!” Ryou waved excitedly.  David rushed over and gaped at the ancient stones. “Simply amazing” David gasp as he ran his fingers over the headstones. He looked at the ancient writing and studied it.  “Hey Malik, come here please.” Ryou shouted. Ryou looked up after he didn’t receive a response and noticed Malik was nowhere in site  “Malik?” Ryou called out again, a little louder this time. “Over here!” Malik finally answered as he came running out from a cluster of trees. He quickly made his way over to Ryou. “Sorry, I had some business to attend to.” Malik chuckled. Suddenly David looked up with shock written all over his face. “Father, what is it?” Ryou ask curiously. David just shook his head from side to side. “I don’t believe this, these tablets contain both Sumerian and Babylonian words. This site may be helpful in finding what connected these two ancient civilizations.” Malik cocked his head curiously as he crouched down next to Ryou. “Who were the Babylonians?” David chuckled as he brushed off some sand covering a partially hidden tablet buried in the sand. “They were a very rich civilization who had a lot of interaction with the Egyp- oh my, what’s this?”  David brushed off the rest of the sand from the ancient tablet and stared at it in amazement. “I don’t believe this! This tablet is written in cuneiform!” Ryou and Malik both poked their heads over David’s shoulders and looked on as David did his best to translate the ancient words for them. “I think it says, ‘Light reveals darkness, morning ends the night.......” David stopped suddenly. “Damn, I’ll have to bring this back to camp to translate it all. Can you boys help me carry this back to the truck?” Ryou and Malik nodded their heads and they leaned over to help David lift the heavy stone tablet out of the desert sands. Suddenly Malik fainted for no reason at all. David and Ryou set the tablet down and rushed to his side. “Malik!” Ryou shouted as he kneeled next to his fallen friend.  Malik wasn’t responding though.  David quickly scooped Malik up and carried him back to the truck. He laid him down on the front seat. Ryou hovered over Malik nervously as David an back to retrieve the stone tablet. Fortunately, Malik regained consciousness after a couple of minutes. “Where......what.......?” he moaned as he opened his eyes.  “I love you Malik, I was so scared.” Ryou exclaimed as he kissed Malik’s forehead. Malik slowly sat up and put his hand on his head. “Ryou? What happened? Everything suddenly went black, and I can’t remember a damn thing.”      

						
</post>
<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I noticed Aff.net is running extrememly slow, so I'm posting chapter 8 here for those of you who are not in the mood for waiting all damn day for the story to load. WARNING! YAOI!!!! Don't like, don't read!!!  Disclaimer: I don't own Yu-Gi-Oh!!  Faded Pictures    	Joey’s heart felt as if it were going to leap out of his chest. Tiny beads of sweat pooled up on his fore head. He hadn’t seen Seto this upset in a long time, and he knew he had to find a way to calm him down. It wasn’t going to be easy soothing Seto, but Joey had an idea. “So where were you all night, Wheeler? Care to enlighten me?” Seto glared angrily. Joey hung his head and sighed. “I don’t have an excuse, Kaiba. I should have called and let you know I was knocked unconscious after Bandit Keith and his asshole friends jumped me. I’m sorry Seto, I didn’t mean to worry you.” Seto’s harsh glare softened as he tipped Joey’s chin up gently with his hand. He looked over the blond’s cuts and bruises and quickly turned away. The elevator doors opened and Seto stepped out. Joey stepped out behind Seto and followed the CEO into his office.  Seto’s desk was cluttered with stacks of contracts that needed to be signed, prototypes for new gaming devices, and crumpled up papers. He sat down in his cushy blue executive chair and buried his face in his hands. Joey found himself feeling rather awkward at the moment. He wasn’t sure whether it was best to leave Seto alone or try to talk to him. His sixth sense told him to talk to Seto, so Joey cleared his throat.  “Uh, Kaiba?” he asked in a demure voice.   Seto lifted his eyes and groaned. “What?” he stated flatly. Joey scratched his head. He realized he hadn’t thought about what he was even going to say. “Well, I, uh...I um.....” Seto made a sour face. “Get to the point already” he snapped sharply. Joey could feel his skin crawling at the hint of harshness of Seto’s voice. He took a deep breath and prayed he wouldn’t say something stupid. After a few moments of thinking, Joey took a deep breath and said what was on his mind. “I’m really sorry. I want to make it up to you.” Seto rested his chin in his hand. He looked up at Joey with half attentive glance. “Don’t even bother. Go lay by your dish and leave me alone.” Joey bit his bottom lip and swallowed hard. This wasn’t going to be easy. “I’m trying to be nice here, but you ain’t makin’ it easy! Damn Kaiba, what crawled up your butt and died? Seto got up from his comfy executive chair and steadied himself with his hands on his desk. He glared sharply at Joey. “I think you better go now” he growled. Joey slammed his fists down on Seto’s desk and glared back at Seto. His fuse was lit now, and there was no holding back. “NO! I’m not gonna go! I know you’re pissed off because I didn’t come home last night, and I know you’re probably pissed because Mokuba moved out, but I don’t give a flying fuck! You’ve been a real bitch to live with ever since that shit with Yugi happened six months ago! Why can’t you just lighten up!” Seto grabbed Joey’s shirt collar and pulled the blond face to face with him. “NEVER talk to me like that again. You’ll regret it if you do.” Joey grabbed Seto’s hands and yanked them away from his neck. He stepped back and snarled. “You know what Seto? You’re an ASS! If you don’t start being nicer, you’re gonna end up ALONE-Just like your stepfather! I don’t need this shit, fuck you ya big dickhead!” Seto clenched his fists tightly and slammed them down onto his desk. Papers flew off and fluttered to the floor. Seto stared down at his unorganized mess on his desk and took a few deep breaths. He stared reminiscently at faded picture of him and Mokuba he had sitting on his desk in a gold frame.  After a few moments he looked up at Joey with remorseful blue eyes. “I’m sorry, Joey. You’re right, I’m being an ass. I don’t know what’s come over me.” Joey took a brave step in Seto’s direction and held his hand out. “C’mon Kaiba, I think you just need a break. Let’s go down to the rec room and shoot some pool.” Seto looked over his desk and sighed. “I can’t Joey, I have so much work to do.” Joey grabbed Seto’s hand and yanked him toward the office door. “You’re work can wait. You’re only human Kaiba, you can’t work 24 hours a day, seven days a week and not take a break.” Seto had to make a quick choice: Go to the rec room and shoot a few games of pool with Joey, or have his arm ripped off by Joey and work in his office.  Seto made the obvious choice of following Joey.                                      ****************************  	Malik climbed into the bathtub with Ryou and sat facing his white-haired lover. He glanced at the book laying on the floor and grinned at Ryou. Ryou’s eyes filled with curious lust as Malik reached out and ran his long, tan fingers through Ryou’s wet hair.  “Has anybody ever told you how beautiful you are?” Malik ask in a low voice. Ryou bit down on his bottom lip and looked into Malik’s dazzling lavender eyes. “Only my mother” he replied softly. Malik reached over and picked up the bottle of healing ointment he’d bought and pulled out the cork. He poured a small amount into his hands and rubbed them together. “I hope this helps.” he smiled as he gently ran his ointment covered hands over Ryou’s burned shoulders.   Ryou closed his eyes and tilted his head back. The ointment began to sooth his body the moment Malik touched him. “Gods Malik, that feels so good” he sighed with relief. Malik slowly ran his ointment slicked hands down Ryou’s arms and massaged the substance into Ryou’s skin. He brought Ryou’s hands up to his lips and dotted soft kisses on Ryou’s knuckles.       “I love you too much to let you suffer” he purred lovingly as he poured more slippery ointment  into his hands.  Malik rubbed the lotus scented all over Ryou’s back and chest, taking his time and making sure to cover every inch of Ryou’s sunburned upper body.  Ryou moaned with pleasure as the special ointment soothed the excruciating pain his sunburn had caused him. He whimpered lightly as Malik’s hand passed over his left nipple and down his chest.  “I love when you touch me, Malik.” he sighed lightly. Malik smiled as straddled Ryou’s hips and pulled him up against his chest. He ran his hands down and up Ryou’s back and held him close. “I love how you feel. You’re so perfect in every way.” Ryou melted in Malik’s arms. He couldn’t believe how quickly the ointment had taken effect. His lower body still burned, but his upper body was feeling better than ever. He rested his cheek on Malik’s shoulder and sighed. Malik kissed Ryou’s shoulder and gently eased them both back into the cool water. Ryou giggled as Malik cleverly turned them both around so that Malik was now under Ryou.  “What are you up to, Ishtar?” he ask curiously. Malik looked up at Ryou with a mischievous grin. “You’ll see.” Malik quickly grabbed the bottle of ointment and poured a bit more of it into his hand. He rubbed his hands together and brought them down onto Ryou’s lower back, stimulating Ryou’s Muladhara chakra. Ryou quickly figured out what Malik had in mind.  “You’re such a little sneak.” Ryou giggled as Malik massaged the oily substance into his skin. Ryou reached down and cupped Malik’s cheek with his hand. He slowly lowered his lips to Malik’s. Malik moaned lightly into Ryou’s kiss. He arched his back and began to rhythmically press his hips against Ryou’s in up and down movements.  He needed to feel closer to Ryou, his body burned with desire. He ran his oil slicked hands over Ryou’s rear and brushed them lightly over Ryou’s slender thighs. Ryou nipped at Malik’s lower lip and moaned as his lover’s warm touch caused his senses to soar. “Need you......in me......” he breathed heavily as Malik stroked his thighs.  Malik lightly feathered Ryou’s skin with his fingertips as he brought his hands upward.  “In time” he responded to Ryou with a sparkle in his eyes. Malik reached up and ran his wet fingers slowly down Ryou’s oiled chest. Ryou closed his eyes and threw his head back. Tiny droplets of water dripped from the ends of Ryou’s hair down onto Malik.  Malik caressed Ryou’s sides as he slowly brought himself up into a sitting position.  He wanted to make love to Ryou, but there was only one problem: the cold water.  Getting hard was next to impossible for Malik at this point. He nipped at Ryou’s shoulder and kissed his way up to Ryou’s ear. “Ryou, baby......let’s dry off and take this into the other room.....” “M’k” Ryou sighed as he and Malik stood up. Malik grabbed two towels off the rack next to the bathtub and handed one to Ryou.  “Don’t forget the book!” Ryou grinned as he wrapped the fluffy white towel around his waist and stepped out of the tub. “Don’t worry, I’ll remember.” Malik smiled as he dried off. Once he was completely dried off, he tossed his towel onto the floor and hurried out by Ryou.  “Ready or not, here I come!” He laughed as he dove onto the bed- Kama Sutra book in hand. Ryou giggled as Malik pounced on top of him. Malik opened the book and grinned. “Okay, lets see here....erogenous zones....hmm...” After reading over the pages for a few moments, Malik kneeled  next to Ryou and brushed Ryou’s hair out of his chocolate brown eyes. “Tell me how this feels” he ask as he leaned over and began to lightly kiss Ryou’s neck.  “Mmm....good” Ryou moaned. Malik than began to lick and kiss his way around Ryou’s neck as he stroked Ryou’s thighs with his fingertips. Ryou closed his eyes and rested his hand on Malik’s shoulder.  //Hey Stupid!// Bakura yelled through his mind link with Ryou. //Not now, yami, go away!// Ryou mentally snapped back.  //No! I must show you something immediately!//  “Stop it!!” Ryou growled out loud.  Malik stopped what he was doing and looked at Ryou a little shocked. “Huh?”  Ryou’s eyes snapped open and he made a sour face. “I didn’t mean for you to stop! The spirit of the Millennium Ring won’t shut his mouth!” “Oh” Malik responded as he went back to what he was doing to Ryou.  Ryou closed his eyes again as Malik’s lips worked their way down his chest. Malik gently nipped at Ryou’s right nipple, eliciting a moan of pleasure from his partner. //You ungrateful brat! When I’m talking you’ll listen! This is important!// Bakura snarled. //It can wait. Can’t you see I’m in the middle of something here?//   Malik took the head of Ryou’s manhood into his mouth and teasingly licked at the tip. Ryou grabbed hold of the bed sheets and sucked in a deep breath through his clenched teeth. He thrust his hips upward in an attempt to gain more contact.  “Oh gods, Malik!”  Malik giggled playfully and he crawled over Ryou and situated himself between his writhing lover’s legs. //Bitch// Bakura snorted through his link with Ryou. “You are so annoying!” Ryou accidently shouted out loud. Malik stopped what he was doing and sighed. “You’d better see what Bakura wants. If he’s anything like Marik, he won’t shut up until you listen to him.” Ryou groaned loudly. As much as he wanted to ignore Bakura, he knew it was practically impossible. He looked at Malik with somber eyes. “I’m sorry Malik, I promise I’ll be quick.” Malik shrugged his shoulders and opened up the Kama Sutra book. “No big deal, I’ll just read” Ryou kissed Malik on the cheek and smiled. “You’re the best, Malik.”                             *************************************************************          Yugi laughed until tears streamed down his cheeks. His face was red from laughing so hard. He gasped for air as he watched Yami tangle himself up for the third time in a roll of scotch tape. “You should just let me wrap the present, Yami!” he giggled. Yami glared at the roll of tape and the gift wrap laying in front of him. “Curses on the person that invented this! Fine Yugi, you finish wrapping this! I’ll go bang my head up against the wall.” Yugi hopped off the sofa and grabbed a pair of scissors off the carpet next to Yami. “Yami! Don’t do that! Stay here, I’ll show you how it’s done.” Yami groaned as he laid back on the carpet. He closed his eyes as Yugi went to work. Yugi had the gift wrapped in almost record time.  He smiled brightly as he handed it to Yami. “See? It’s easy!” Yami opened his eyes and looked at the perfectly wrapped present.  “You forgot one thing, aibou.” Yugi cocked his head. “What?” Yami picked up a shiny red bow and peeled the sticker off the back. He took the gold wrapped gift from Yugi and proudly plopped the bow in the center. Yugi shook his head and laughed. “Perfect. You do good work, Yami. We’d better finish cleaning the house now, Isis and your son will be here soon.” Yami took a deep breath and let it out slowly as he got to his feet.  He extended his hand to Yugi and helped him up. “Thank you for helping me, aibou.” Yugi nodded his head and brought Yami into a warm embrace. “Anytime you need me, I’m here for you.” Yami patted Yugi’s back and sighed. “I feel like such a burden to you. No matter how hard I try, I still can’t get used to having my own body again. It’s just so odd.” Yugi pressed a light kiss on Yami’s cheek and smiled. “Don’t sweat it, I’m sure you’ll get used to it. I like you better this way.”  Just as the words left Yugi’s mouth, there was a knock at the back door. Yami’s eyes got huge and stood still. “That must be Isis! I can’t wait to see your son! This is so cool!” Yugi smiled brightly as he went to answer the door.  Yami walked slowly over to the sofa and sat down. His nerves were getting the best of him. He was shaking like a leaf on a tree as he waited. Seconds later the sound of a baby crying echoed through the livingroom. Yami bit down on his bottom lip as he heard the sound of footsteps growing nearer. Yugi entered the livingroom first, followed by Isis.......who was carrying their crying son. “Greetings, my pharaoh.” Isis smiled. Yugi’s eyes were sparkling with excitement as he lead Isis over to Yami. Yami looked up at Isis and the baby. “Hello Isis, may I.....hold him?” he ask gingerly. Isis nodded her head. “Of course, he’s your son.” Yami reached up for the boy, who was wrapped in a soft white blanket and crying his little crimson eyes out. As soon as Yami cradled him in his arms, the boy looked up and ceased to cry. Yami smiled down at his son proudly. Yugi poked his head over Yami’s shoulder and giggled. “He looks just like you! How cute!” Yami chuckled lightly and looked up at Isis. He patted the on the sofa next to him. “Have a seat” he smiled. Isis sat down and folded her hands on her lap. Yami looked at her curiously. “What did you name our son?” Isis reached over Yami’s arm and ran her finger down the baby’s cheek lightly. “Solon, Solon Atemu Ishtar.” she responded lovingly. (Pronounced So-len/ long “o” )	 Yami nodded his head and looked back at the now smiling bundle in his arms. “Solon Atemu Ishtar...... hello, my son.”  ************************************************************  	Bakura was extremely keyed-up. Ryou sat across from him completely absorbed. It wasn’t so much the subject Bakura was yammering on about, it was more the way he was saying it. Ryou rarely saw Bakura so passionate about something that didn’t have anything to do with revenge or sex. Ryou took a mental note to mark the day on the calender. He even considered making it a holiday.  Bakura recited the words to Ryou that he’d read from the book from memory. That was one advantage to the afterlife- the skill of remembering everything.   “According to the new ensi[1], Malik’s reign was brought to an abrupt end when he never returned to his country. One can only speculate as to what became of him.” Bakura recited. Ryou nodded his head. “M’hmm...very interesting. Now can I go?” He was so absorbed in trying to think of a good name for a holiday honoring Bakura, he hadn’t heard a single thing Bakura had just said. Bakura lowered his eyes and smacked Ryou upside the head. “You haven’t heard a single thing I’ve said, have you?  Condescending little shithead!” Ryou rubbed his cheek and stood up. “I heard what you said, you think what you found in that book has something to do with those graves in the desert. You could be right. I have an idea. How about you go into my soul room and look for more books to read. Maybe there’s some with old pictures or something. Actually, start with a dictionary. Look up the word “blighter.” While you’re at it, contemplate what it would mean in the sentence, “My yami is a blighter. I’ve got somewhere else to be now, okay?” Bakura stood up and crossed his arms. “Fine. I’ll talk to you later.” Ryou nodded sharply and left Bakura’s soul room.   	Ryou opened his eyes and looked around the hotel room. He found Malik sound asleep with the Kama Sutra book laying over his face. Ryou gently took the book off Malik’s head and looked down at his sleeping angel. He bit his lip and sighed. Malik was out cold.  Ryou sat up and started reading the page Malik had left off at. It was entitled, “The Three Orders of Men.” He found the title catchy, so he started to read. 	After an hour or so went by, Ryou put the book down when he noticed Malik kicking the covers. The sleeping Egyptian restlessly tossed and turned. Ryou scooted over to the edge of bed to avoid getting kicked and turned off the light. He closed his eyes and went to sleep. The Kama Sutra would have to wait until morning.    [1]ensi: term used to refer to a patron deity or a ruler; Sumerian origin  ****************************************************************	  Since AFF.net’s outage screwed up my schedule, I’ll have respond to reviews when I post on Monday.  What I’m planning is to post updates for this story Monday/Wednesday/Friday. Monday I’ll also post “My Pet Yami.” (Let’s cross our fingers AFF stays online!) If there’s ever a problem with AFF in the future, I’ll post updates here at my blog site. (http://theishtargate.blogspot.com/)  Big huge thanks to my totally awesome beta reader, Xeno!!! *hugs n’ kisses*   In the next chapter.......... 	Yami goes to Egypt, Ryou and Malik will finally get some alone time to try some Kama Sutra, and Duke and Tristan do something very naughty on a pin ball game. David Bakura will explain the history of the ancient stone tablets, and Malik faints afterward.    ***************************************************************** (Very short) My Pet Yami Preview!!   Yami’s crimson eyes burned with anger.  “I will never listen to you!” he growled in a stern voice. Bakura looked back at Marik and rolled his eyes. He turned back to Yami and grinned evilly. “Yes you will, my pet. You have no other choice!” Yami lowered his eyes and clenched his fists tightly. “Drop dead thief!” “HA! Already did, pharaoh!” Bakura chuckled.    “Encore!” Yami retorted vindictively      

						
</post>
<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Everybody needs a back up plan, right? Well here's mine:  Anytime AFF.net servers are down, I'll post my story updates here. These include, "Carved in Stone," "My Pet Yami," and "Somewhere Between Heaven and Hell."  I might just go ahead with posting them here no matter what, but I have to read the rules and see if I can do that.(Considering the nature of their content *evil grin*) Once I have enough material I'll splurge and buy my own website. Sound good?  

						
</post>
<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Very short blog today. (why?)  Because I have to work on my story "Carved in Stone." even though AFF.net is down. I'm suffering from yaoi withdrawls since the site went down Sunday. Talk about annoying!! Bastards..... I know it's not AFF that's responsible for the outage, so today's FU award goes to NEXCESS. They claim it's faulty hardware that killed AFF, but come on- three days now? I can install all new components on my computer and it would take me (at the most) half a day. This three days with no AFF is bullcrap.  I chose to call this blog "Discordia Unleashed" because Discordia was the goddess of chaos in Greek Mythology. I'll blame Discordia for AFF's down time for the simple reason that she can't sue me for defimation of character. (*grin*) 

						
</post>
<date>21,June,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   In the King James Bible it says that Noah was a descendant of Seth, (son of Adam and Eve) and that he, his wife, and his 3 sons (Shem, Ham, and Japheth) and their wives were the only survivors of The Great Flood. So who TODAY descends from who BACK THAN? Let's think about this.  Shem had six sons; Elam, Asshur, Arphaxad, Lud, and Aram.       "Elam is the ancient name for Persia, which is itself the ancient name for Iran. Until the time of Cyrus the people here were called Elamites, and they were still often called that even in New Testament times. In Acts 2:9, the Jews from Persia who were present at Pentecost were called Elamites. The Persians are thus descended from both Elam, the son of Shem, and from Madai, the son of Japheth (see above). Since the 1930s they have called their country Iran.   It is interesting to note that the word ‘Aryan’, which so fascinated Adolf Hitler, is a form of the word ‘Iran’. Hitler wanted to produce a pure Aryan ‘race’ of supermen. But the very term ‘Aryan’ signifies a mixed line of Semites and Japhethites!  Asshur is the Hebrew word for Assyria. Assyria was one of the great ancient empires. Every time the words Assyria or Assyrian appear in the Old Testament, they are translated from the word Asshur. He was worshipped by his descendants.  ‘Indeed, as long as Assyria lasted, that is until 612 BC, accounts of battles, diplomatic affairs and foreign bulletins were daily read out to his image; and every Assyrian king held that he wore the crown only with the express permission of Asshur’s deified ghost.’10  Arphaxad was the progenitor of the Chaldeans. This ‘is confirmed by the Hurrian (Nuzi) tablets, which render the name as Arip-hurra — the founder of Chaldea.’11  His descendant, Eber, gave his name to the Hebrew people via the line of Eber-Peleg-Reu-Serug-Nahor-Terah-Abram (Genesis 11:16–26). Eber’s other son, Joktan, had 13 sons (Genesis 10:26–30), all of whom appear to have settled in Arabia.12  Lud was the ancestor of the Lydians. Lydia was in what is now Western Turkey. Their capital was Sardis — one of the seven churches of Asia was at Sardis (Revelation 3:1).   Aram is the Hebrew word for Syria. Whenever the word Syria appears in the Old Testament it is a translation of the word Aram. The Syrians call themselves Arameans, and their language is called Aramaic. Before the spread of the Greek Empire, Aramaic was the international language (2 Kings 18:26 ff). On the cross, when Jesus cried out, ‘Eloi, Eloi, lama sabachthani’ (Mark 15:34),13 He was speaking Aramaic, the language of the common people." *  Ham's descentants migrated south and established the land we've come to know as SUMER. Ham had four sons, Cush, Mizraim, Phut, and Canaan.        "The descendants of Ham live mainly in south-west Asia and Africa. The Bible often refers to Africa as the land of Ham (Psalms 105:23,27; 106:22). The name of Noah’s grandson Cush is the Hebrew word for old Ethiopia (from Aswan south to Khartoum). Without exception, the word Ethiopia in the English Bible is always a translation of the Hebrew word Cush. Josephus rendered the name as Chus, and says that the Ethiopians ‘are even at this day, both by themselves and by all men in Asia, called Chusites’.9  Noah’s next grandson mentioned was Mizraim. Mizraim is the Hebrew word for Egypt. The name Egypt appears hundreds of times in the Old Testament and (with one exception) is always a translation of the word Mizraim. E.g. at the burial of Jacob, the Canaanites observed the mourning of the Egyptians and so called the place Abel Mizraim (Genesis 50:11).  Phut, the name of Noah’s next grandson is the Hebrew name for Libya. It is so translated three times in the Old Testament. The ancient river Phut was in Libya. By Daniel’s day, the name had been changed to Libya (Daniel 11:43). Josephus says, ‘Phut also was the founder of Libia [sic], and called the inhabitants Phutites, from himself’.9  Canaan, the name of Noah’s next grandson, is the Hebrew name for the general region later called by the Romans Palestine, i.e. modern Israel and Jordan. Here we should look briefly at a few of the descendants of Ham (Genesis 10:14–18). There is Philistim, obviously the ancestor of the Philistines (clearly giving rise to the name Palestine), and Sidon, the founder of the ancient city that bears his name, and Heth, the patriarch of the ancient Hittite empire. Also, this descendant is listed in Genesis 10:15–18 as being the ancestor of the Jebusites (Jebus was the ancient name for Jerusalem — Judges 19:10), the Amorites, the Girgasites, the Hivites, the Arkites, the Sinites, the Arvadites, the Zemarites, and the Hamathites, ancient peoples who lived in the land of Canaan.  The most prominent descendant of Ham was Nimrod, the founder of Babel (Babylon), as well as of Erech, Accad and Calneh in Shinar (Babylonia)."*  Lastly we will take a closer look at Noah's third son, Japheth. Genesis tells us that he had seven sons.  "The first of Noah’s grandsons mentioned is Gomer. Ezekiel locates the early descendants of Gomer, along with Togarmah (a son of Gomer), in the north quarters (Ezekiel 38:6). In modern Turkey is an area which in New Testament times was called Galatia. The Jewish historian Flavius Josephus records that the people who were called Galatians or Gauls in his day (c. AD 93) were previously called Gomerites.1  They migrated westward to what are now called France and Spain. For many centuries France was called Gaul, after the descendants of Gomer. North-west Spain is called Galicia to this day.  Some of the Gomerites migrated further to what is now called Wales. The Welsh historian, Davis, records a traditional Welsh belief that the descendants of Gomer ‘landed on the Isle of Britain from France, about three hundred years after the flood’.2 He also records that the Welsh language is called Gomeraeg (after their ancestor Gomer).  Other members of their clan settled along the way, including in Armenia. The sons of Gomer were ‘Ashkenaz, and Riphath, and Togarmah’ (Genesis 10:3). Encyclopaedia Britannica says that the Armenians traditionally claim to be descended from Togarmah and Ashkenaz.3 Ancient Armenia reached into Turkey. The name Turkey probably comes from Togarmah. Others of them migrated to Germany. Ashkenaz is the Hebrew word for Germany.  The next grandson mentioned is Magog. According to Ezekiel, Magog lived in the north parts (Ezekiel 38:15, 39:2). Josephus records that those whom he called Magogites, the Greeks called Scythians.1 According to Encyclopædia Britannica, the ancient name for the region which now includes part of Romania and the Ukraine was Scythia.4  The next grandson is Madai. Along with Shem’s son Elam, Madai is the ancestor of our modern-day Iranians. Josephus says that the descendants of Madai were called Medes by the Greeks.1 Every time the Medes are mentioned in the Old Testament, the word used is the Hebrew word Madai (maday). After the time of Cyrus, the Medes are always (with one exception) mentioned along with the Persians. They became one kingdom with one law — ‘the law of the Medes and Persians’ (Daniel 6:8, 12, 15). Later they were simply called Persians. Since 1935 they have called their country Iran. The Medes also ‘settled India’.5  The name of the next grandson, Javan, is the Hebrew word for Greece. Greece, Grecia, or Grecians appears five times in the Old Testament, and is always the Hebrew word Javan. Daniel refers to ‘the king of Grecia’ (Daniel 8:21), literally ‘the king of Javan’. Javan’s sons were Elishah, Tarshish, Kittim, and Dodanim (Genesis 10:4), all of whom have connections with the Greek people. The Elysians (an ancient Greek people) obviously received their name from Elishah. Tarshish or Tarsus was located in the region of Cilicia (modern Turkey).  Encyclopædia Britannica says that Kittim is the biblical name for Cyprus.6 The Greeks worshipped Jupiter under the name of Jupiter Dodanaeus, possibly a reference to the fourth son of Javan, with Jupiter a derivative of Japheth. His oracle was at Dodena.  Next is Tubal. Ezekiel mentions him along with Gog and Meshech (Ezekiel 39:1). Tiglath-pileser I, king of Assyria in about 1100 BC, refers to the descendants of Tubal as the Tabali. Josephus recorded their name as the Thobelites, who were later known as Iberes.1  ‘Their land, in Josephus’ day, was called by the Romans Iberia, and covered what is now (the former Soviet State of) Georgia whose capital to this day bears the name Tubal as Tbilisi. From here, having crossed the Caucasus mountains, this people migrated due north-east, giving their tribal name to the river Tobol, and hence to the famous city of Tobolsk.’7  Meshech, the name of the next grandson, is the ancient name for Moscow. Moscow is both the capital of Russia, and the region that surrounds the city. To this day, one section, the Meschera Lowland, still carries the name of Meshech, virtually unchanged by the ages.  According to Josephus, the descendants of grandson Tiras were called Thirasians. The Greeks changed their name to Thracians.1 Thrace reached from Macedonia on the south to the Danube River on the north to the Black Sea on the east. It took in much of what became Yugoslavia. World Book Encyclopedia says: ‘The people of Thrace were savage Indo-Europeans, who liked warfare and looting.’8 Tiras was worshipped by his descendants as Thuras, or Thor, the god of thunder."*      *(Taken from, "The sixteen Grandsons of Noah" www.answeresingenesis.org)    My conclusion??? I don't have one- I'm still thinking...give me a few days.      

						
</post>
<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Ever have a building explode only a few hundred feet from your house? Well, I did, and holy motherfucker! It's scary as hell!!!!!! My hubby and I were changing a light bulb in the bathroom when we noticed our dogs acting like blithering idiots. They sounded their alarm (woof woof woof!lol) but we just told them to shut the fuck up as usual. They're always sounding false "alarms." Anyway....after the 3rd time we told them to shut up, we heard this loud "KABOOOM!!!!!!" outside. Needless to say, I ran into the hallway and looked outside.  All I could say was "Holy fuck." The entire sky was black with smoke, and people were running everywhere. My hubby right away assumed his workplace finally blew up, (its across the road from the place that actually exploded)so we both ran outside. He ran to where the smoke was coming from, and I walked out and started talking to the neighbors.  Thank God, it wasn't his workplace. This town would have been one giant desolate crator had it been. *shiver* Come to find out a trucking business was the cause of all the exposions (there were many, it sounded like a kick ass Independance day celebration outside,lol) Anyway, life was very crazy Wednesday night after that. I had to see the 50 foot flames for myself, so afterward my hubby and I dropped the kids off at my ma's house and watched the business burn. (I'm a bit of a pyro, oh well, LOL) Gotta love the action in small town USA.....lol 

						
</post>
<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   *******This isn't the whole chapter, but I'm posting it anyway. Why? Cuz I feel like it, no reason really.....maybe. *grin* I'll add the Ryou/Malik section later today.(Maybe there's a lemon I'm holding back here)??? This is also un-edited, in fact I haven't even read it over since I typed it out. Hopefully I'll have this chappie complete AND edited once AFF gets it crap together and is online again. I'll also have the next chapter of "My Pet Yami" up too.*******    Ja ne!  ************************ Night of Questions   	Serenity flipped her long brown hair off to one side to cover her face and smiled politely. “Oh no Duke, thanks but no thanks. Your brownies look really yummy, but I’m not very hungry.”      Duke picked up another special brownie and took a bite. “You don’t know what your missing, sweetheart. These are awesome.” “I’m sure they are.” Serenity laughed weakly. .                           Duke popped the rest of brownie in his mouth and took a swing of beer to wash it down. He got up off his seat and reached for Serenity’s hand.  “Come with me, sweety, I’ll show you around. First I’ll introduce you to Jeree, she’s our cook. Than I’ll take you in back to the coolers where we keep the soda and beer and whatever.” “Cool!” Serenity smiled brightly as she followed Duke into the kitchen. 	After Duke had shown Serenity around her new place of employment, they sat back down behind the bar. A woman with long curly black hair pulled back into a pony tail and deep brown eyes pulled up a bar stool and lit up a cigarette.   “Is a new protege?” she ask with a quirky grin. Duke automatically poured the scantily clad woman a drink and chuckled. “Ha-ha, cute one Darla. No, she’s not a new dancer, she’s bartending part-time.”  Duke looked over at Serenity and winked. “I couldn’t hire a little princess like Serenity to dance, her brother would kick my ass!” Serenity covered her mouth and giggled. “Joey wouldn’t kick your ass, I wouldn’t let him. I’m all grown up now, Duke. My big brother doesn’t really have a say in what I do anymore.” Duke held his hands in front of himself defensively and shook his head. “I’m not willing to take any chances......I’ve seen Joey fight....and that son of a bitch fights dirty!” Darla blew out a puff of cigarette smoke and laughed. “From the looks of it little princess here is quite a fighter too......nice eye, honey.” Duke looked at Serenity and reached up to move her hair out of her face. She stopped him before he could reveal the secret her beautiful long hair was hiding.  “I fell......off the bed.....it’s nothing.” Serenity said quickly as she turned away. Darla got up out of her seat and shook her head. “Sure, hon.......I’d believe that if I was blind. Listen, I got a show to get ready for. You two have yourselves a fun time listening to the rants of the local drunks tonight.” “And you have fun getting groped by the local pervs. Now go make us some jing, baby.” Duke winked back. “Nice meeting you, Darla was it?” Serenity smiled politely. Darla extended her hand to Serenity and smiled. “Nice meeting you too, Serenity. Just a word of caution before I go: Watch out for Duke’s wandering hands.”  Duke rolled his eyes as he got up off of his barstool. “Hey now! Be nice or you won’t get that raise I promised you, sweetheart!” Darla mashed out her cigarette in an ashtray in front of her and grinned. “Guess that means we’ll be seeing your skinny ass dancing on stage than, eh?” “Yeah! Uh......No! Oh you, get out of here.” Duke snickered in response to his hired dancer.  *************************************************************** 	Yami lifted off his black t-shirt and tossed it into the hamper. He unzipped his jeans and pulled them over his hips while Yugi brushed his teeth. “Yugi?” Yami ask as he slipped his jeans over his ankles. “Yeah, Yami?” Yugi replied as he rinsed his toothbrush off and set it next to the sink. Yami approached his light and wrapped his arms around his slender waist. He looked at their reflections staring back at them in the mirror behind the sink. “I don’t know what I’d do without you, aibou.” Yugi tilted his head back into the crook of Yami’s neck and smiled. “Awe, Yami.” he giggled. Yami slipped his hands under Yugi’s untucked t-shirt and gently caressed his light’s sides.  “You blow my mind Yugi Motou.” Yugi’s cheeks blushed red. He stared at Yami’s reflection wrapped around him in the mirror. “I do? How’s that?”  Yami tilted his head to the side and rested his cheek on top Yugi’s head. He wrapped his arms protectively around Yugi and pulled his back against his body. Yugi closed his eyes and sighed lightly. Yami pressed a light kiss Yugi’s hair. “Let’s go to bed.” Yugi gave Yami a quick nod as the walked out of the bathroom together and down to their bedroom. Yugi sat on the edge of the bed and watched Yami light a candle that was on the dresser. The pharaoh turned on some sexy fuck music before returning to his hikari. He stood in front of Yugi and held out his hand. “Aibou....my love.” he sighed as he gazed into Yugi’s candle lit violet eyes. Yugi reached out and took hold of Yami’s hand, pulling him down into a kiss.  “My yami...” he moaned as their lips met.  Yami gently pushed Yugi back onto the bed and crawled on top of him. He lifted Yugi’s t-shirt and brought his lips down against Yugi’s soft skin. He slowly kissed his way up from Yugi’s navel, savoring the sweet taste of his hikari’s flesh. Yami cleverly unbuttoned Yugi’s jeans and unzipped them with one hand, as he traced his finger around the pink area around Yugi’s right nipple. Yugi rested his arms behind him and moaned lightly from Yami’s touch. Without taking his lips off of Yugi’s stomach, Yami eased Yugi’s t-shirt over his head and tossed it aside. He kissed his way up to Yugi’s nipple and licked it until it perked up. He than gently nipped at the flashy nub with his teeth, eliciting a pleasure filled whimper from his hikari. Yami continued to tease Yugi with his tongue, causing his hikari to grow hard very quickly. Yami reached down and wrapped his warm fingers around Yugi’s erection, slowly stroking it. Yugi rocked his hips in rhythm to his yami’s motion. “Yami......I love this....more.....” Yugi moaned as he brought his arms around and gripped Yami’s bare shoulders. He lightly dug his nails into the smooth flesh below.  “If it pleases you, it pleases me.” Yami purred as he nipped Yugi’s collar bone lightly with his teeth. Yugi ran his hands over Yami’s back, taking in every ounce of pleasure his other was giving him. Yami released Yugi’s erection and grabbed a tube of lube they kept on their nightstand. He flipped open the cap and cleverly squeezed out some of the clear gel into his hand. He coated his fingers with the viscous substance as kneeled between Yugi’s legs. Yugi instinctively brought his knees up to allow Yami easier access to his rear entrance.  Yami slowly pushed one of his fingers into Yugi’s tight channel. Yugi’s body instantly tensed up and squeezed around Yami’s intruding digit. Yami rested his free hand on Yugi’s knee and kissed the inside of his hikari’s thigh. “Relax......I know this is a little painful, but I promise I’ll do my best not to hurt you, aibou.” Yugi bit his bottom lip and nodded his head. “It’s okay” he said softly. Yami slowly began moving his finger in and out of his hikari’s tight warmth. Yami’s heart was pounding like a hammer. He and Yugi had only slept together a handful of times since his return from Bakura and Marik’s control. He could count the number of times they’d been together intimately on one hand. Yami loved sharing himself with Yugi, but he still found himself fighting demons in his mind. He clenched his eyes shut tightly and tried to focus on Yugi, but no matter how hard he tried, he couldn’t forget the pain he’d caused his other only a few months ago. Yugi grunted as he fisted the white bed sheets below him.   “Oh yeah, Yami....oh gods yeah!” Yami wanted to make love to Yugi so badly he could taste it.  Only one thing was preventing him from sharing his love with Yugi: Yami couldn’t get hard. No matter how hard or fast he stroked himself, his manhood wasn’t responding. Yugi took notice of Yami’s predicament tried to make him feel better. “Yami.....if you don’t want to do this we don’t have to. I don’t want you to feel you have to sleep with me.”  Yami crawled off of Yugi and turned onto his side and brought his knees to his chest.  “I’m sorry, aibou....I feel like such a failure.” he whimpered quietly as he curled into a ball. Yugi crawled up next to Yami and laid back with his arms behind his head. “It’s okay” he sighed as he pulled the covers up to his waist and rolled over. Yami closed his eyes and tried to fall to sleep, but the he felt horrible for screwing things up. He couldn’t sleep. After a few minutes of laying silently next to Yugi, Yami could have sworn he heard Yugi sniffle.  “Yugi?” Yami ask quietly. “What” Yugi replied a little more harshly than he intended.  “Please don’t be mad at me. I love you.” “M’hm.” Yugi replied with a little hint of sarcasm. Yugi wiped the tears from his eyes and sat up. He pulled his legs to his chest and rested his chin on his knees. “You know how I told you that you need to tell me how you feel?” “M’hm” Yami nodded as he rolled over onto his side facing Yugi Yugi stared down at his toes and sighed. “Well, I think this is one of those times. Do I.....um....not turn you on anymore?” Yami sat up and shook his head. “Aibou, I can’t believe you’d think that. No, that’s not it at all. This has nothing to do with you, I swear on the Book of the Dead!”  Yami’s voice cracked as it trailed off into almost a whisper.  Yugi glanced over his shoulder at Yami and bit his lip. He didn’t know what to say next. He felt  empty inside......again. He’d already lost one love in his life, had he lost another?  ****************************************************  	Seto parked his Lexus in the underground garage and turn off the key. He looked over at Joey who had fallen asleep on the short drive home. “Wake up, Wheeler. We’re home.” Seto chuckled. He found it amusing how Joey could fall asleep just about anywhere. “Huh? Wha?” Joey mumbled as he opened his eyes. “We’re home. Do you need me to carry you in, sleepy-head?” Seto joked as he opened his car door. “Oh, cool..” the blond yawned as he reached for his door handle. Seto walked around the car and helped Joey to his feet. Joey leaned his cheek on Seto’s shoulder and sighed contently.  “Thank you” Seto rolled his eyes and lead Joey to the elevator. He pressed a button that took them directly to the floor of Kaiba Corps in which they resided together.  “Come on Wheeler, I’ll take you to bed.” Seto smiled as he lead his drowsy partner down the hall. By the time they reached the bedroom they shared, Joey was practically sleeping on Seto’s shoulder. Seto wasn’t surprised that Joey was so tired. They’d had quite an action packed night at Noa and Mokuba’s. While Seto went over legal forms regarding the Holographic Duel Transmogrifier (HDT for short) and discussed what needed to be done at Kaiba corps while he was away with Mokuba and Noa, Joey kept himself busy by playing tennis against Serenity for a few hours. Seto remembered back to the days when he was young and he and Mokuba used to sneak down to the indoor tennis court and play a game or two. It was risky, but Seto was willing to do anything to spend time with his little brother and get away from his studies, even if it was only for a short game of tennis.  Seto sighed as he began removing Joey’s clothing for him. After spending time with Mokuba, it only hurt Seto more that his younger brother no longer lived with him; even if Mokuba was a bit of a trouble-maker. After he’d stripped Joey down to his boxers, Seto covered him up with a blanket. “Sleep tight, pup.” He whispered as he pressed a gentle kiss on Joey’s forehead. “Don’t go” Joey mumbled sleepily as he grabbed onto Seto’s sleeve. “I’ll be back later, I have some work to finish up.” Seto responded as he tried to pull away from Joey’s grasp. Joey opened his eyes a crack and refused to release his grip on seto’s jacket. “No.....I want you to stay with me tonight, please?” Seto bit his lip. He wanted to stay, but he knew he had work to do. He looked down at Joey and sighed. “Wheeler, I don’t have time for this. I really need to get those forms Mokuba and you completed faxed out, and I have a stack of paperwork to go through besides.” Joey still held tightly onto Seto’s sleeve.  “Please Seto? It’s been so long since you’ve spent the entire night with me. It gets pretty lonely sleeping by myself.” Seto let out a frustrated growl and reluctantly sat down at the edge of the bed. “Wheeler, running a business isn’t easy. I have deadlines to meet, you know.” Joey stuck out his bottom lip and pouted. He looked up at Seto with his best puppy eyes. Seto couldn’t resist saying to  those big brown begging eyes. “Fine, how does this sound: I’ll stay with you all night if you allow me 10 minutes to go fax the forms. I’ll bring the rest of the paperwork to bed and go over it while your sleeping. Is that acceptable?” Joey nodded his head. “Promise you’ll be back in 10 minutes?” Seto nodded his head. “You have my word.” “Well get a move on than!” Joey grinned as he let go of Seto’s sleeve. Seto quickly went to his office and sent the faxes. He knew he had to keep his word to Joey, so he scooped up some work that needed to be done and started walking out of his office. He picked the Holographic Duel Transmogrifier (HDT) off of his desk and stacked it on top his pile of papers and quickly returned to Joey. “That was 11 minutes” Joey smirked as Seto entered the bedroom. Seto rolled his eyes as he set his armload of work down on the oak end table next to their bed. “Wheeler, shut up and move over.” Joey chuckled as Seto sat on the edge of the bed. The CEO removed his shirt and shoes and slid into bed next to Joey. “Seto? Can you hold me?” Joey ask pleadingly. Seto wrapped his arm around Joey and scooted closer to the blond, pressing his hips against Joey’s backside.  “Mmm....you’re so warm.” Joey purred as he pressed himself back against Seto. “This is nice” Seto smiled as he kissed the nape of Joey’s neck.  Joey sighed contently as he lay in Seto’s arms. The steady beating of Seto’s heart lulled him back to sleep very quickly.   “Love.......you....” Joey mumbled as he drifted off to sleep.  	After he was sure Joey was sound asleep, Seto sat up and switched on the lamp next to the bed. He picked up the HDT and looked his new money-maker over. Even though he’d seen how the device worked, he’d never actually tried it himself.  He picked his briefcase up off the floor and pulled out his recently modified duel deck. He looked over his cards and smirked at his all-powerful assortment of monsters, traps and magic cards. His curiosity got the best of him, so he placed the cards in the slot and put the HDT helmet on his head. What could it hurt to give it a try? ******************************************************   

						
</post>
<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~* a/n: The Sumerian words used in this chapter were taken from various notes on Mesopotamia that I’ve taken over the years. I never bothered to write down the reference crap way back when, so I can’t tell you exactly what texts (or who) they came from. For all I know I might have screwed up when taking notes- some of the translations may not be perfect. In a million years when I’m fluent in every language I’ll correct any mis-translations. Good deal? *dorky grin* Also, the words Yami says to Solon are taken from The Book of the Dead. So unless modern transcriptions are wrong, I’m 99% sure of their translation. *~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*~*   	Back at camp, David and Ryou carried the heavy tablet into David’s tent. Malik wanted to help them, but Ryou wouldn’t let him. Malik’s little episode at the oasis had him a little apprehensive.	Instead, Malik went off with David’s assistant Ramose to dig around in the sand for artifacts. The site they were at had only  revealed one ancient treasure so far, a kohl stick. Kohl sticks were used to line the eyes of the ancient Egyptians, so the site was most likely a typical Egyptian settlement. Nothing too spectacular.  Malik was spending more time slathering himself in coconut tanning oil laying out in the sun than he was digging. He’d grown up around this kind of stuff, so it didn’t really trip his trigger. Ramose didn’t seem to mind Malik’s laziness, it wasn’t like Malik actually had to do anything. This trip was more of a vacation for him, rather than do work. He wasn’t getting paid, so why do anything? 	Meanwhile, Ryou watched  his father work diligently  transcribing the cuneiform written on the stone tablet in one of the tents. Some of the symbols had been completely worn away, and some just partially. It made transcription a very grueling process.  Even though Ryou was interested in learning what the tablets said, the transcription process was as boring as boring could get. “Father, would you be offended if I joined Malik outside?” Ryou ask politely. David took off his eye glasses and set them down next to him. He rubbed his tired eyes. “I don’t mind, son. Just don’t forget your sunscreen.” “Smashing! Thank you father! I’ll see you later!” Ryou exclaimed as he ran out of the tent. David nodded his head. “Take care of yourself, son.”  Ryou sprinted out of the tent and took off running. David sighed as he put his glasses back on. “Ah yeah, back to work.” He picked up his cuneiform reference book and began searching for a specific symbol he was having trouble with.   “This is going to take forever.” He mused to himself as looked through the table of contents.               Ryou found Malik sound asleep basking in the hot Egyptian. He was sprawled out on his stomach on top of a white beach towel. Ryou walked over to where Malik was sleeping and gently shook Malik’s shoulder. “Hey baby, wake up, I could use a little company.” Malik shifted around a little and started to mumble. “Inanna barra!” [Be gone Inanna!] Ryou raised an eyebrow and started to giggle as he crouched down next to Malik.  “Inanna?” Malik clutched the white beach towel tightly between his fingers as his dream grew more intense. “Geme xul! [evil slave girl!] Maskim! [fiend!] Edin na zu! [Go to the desert!] he spat angrily. Ryou scooted backwards a few inches and watched as Malik began to cry in his sleep. “Inanna.......kanpa lu-gal Malik.” [Inanna, remember King Malik] //What the hell is he saying?// Bakura cut into Ryou’s thoughts. “Banana campa glueball Malik?” Ryou repeated incorrectly as Malik began to settle a little. //Be serious, I should hurt you for being an idiot. I’ll wait until later for that though.  Let’s listen and see if he says anything else.” Bakura snapped back. Ryou sat back in the sand. He watched as Malik continued to sleep restlessly under the hot sun.  *********************************************************** 	Duke sat behind the bar twiddling his thumbs. The bartender he’d hired still hadn’t shown up, and Duke was getting very bored. The bar was basically empty expect for Duke and Jeree. It was only 6 o’ clock though, and most of the tavern’s patrons didn’t start showing up until after 8' clock. Duke still had two more hours to burn until the night livened up. He traced the mouth of his beer bottle with the tip of his finger. The friction from his finger moving around the rim of the bottle made a high-pitched whistling noise. Duke lit up a Marlboro light and stated up at the television on the wall. “Duke?”  Jeree ask curiously as she poked her head out of the kitchen door. “Yeah?” Duke responded as he turned around. The bleach blond middle aged woman looked around the empty bar and looked at Duke compassionately. “I take it the new help you hired hasn’t shown up.” she stated sympathetically as she walked up to Duke. “Nope. She must have said ‘fuck it’ and found a better job.  Jeree patted Duke’s shoulder and grinned. “Well Duke, you know what they say....you win a few, you lose a few. And if all else fails, bake some brownies.” Duke chuckled absently as he stared up at the television on the wall. Suddenly, he had an idea. He looked back at Jeree with a mischievous grin. “Do we have enough ingredients in back to make some brownies?” The blue eyed woman nodded her head. “I’m pretty sure we do, why do you ask?” Duke got up off his chair and affectionately put his arm around the much older woman. “Jeree, my dear, I think you should show me how to make brownies.” Jeree smiled enthusiastically and nodded her head. “I’d love to!” Jeree exclaimed as she pulled Duke into the kitchen.  **************************************************************  	Yami kissed Solon’s forehead lightly and smiled down at his young son. “Thank you for bringing him here, Isis.” he smiled as he cuddled his baby boy. Isis smiled sweetly and nodded her head. “I wasn’t sure if you wanted anything to do with him after the way things turned out.” Yami traced his finger lightly along Solon’s lower lip and sighed. “I’m sorry about that Isis. I had every intention of moving to Egypt with you, but things just got out of hand.” Isis looked down at her shoes to avoid eye contact with Yami. “Yes, I know. I’m very sorry about my brothers actions. He and the tomb robber had no right to treat you the way thy did.” Yami patted Isis’s shoulder. “You’re brother may not be as bad as you think. If it wasn’t for him sneaking me food, I probably would have died. That Bakura is one twisted son of a bitch. He taught me a lesson though, that’s for sure.” Isis took a deep breath and continued to stare at her shoes.  “Malik......I haven’t talked to him in almost a year. Sometimes I want to call him and see how he’s doing, but I never can find enough courage to even pick up the phone.” “That’s a shame” Yami grimaced as he gently rocked his son in his arms.  Isis bowed her head. “I miss Malik. I regret treating him so badly. I wish I could take back all the cruel things I said to him before he moved out. I admit, I was out of line.” Yami slowly got up off the couch. He was careful not to disturb his sleeping son. “You should call him” Yami stated frankly in almost a whisper. He walked with Solon cradled in his arms over to blue bassinet and laid him down carefully. Yami laid a blanket over the child and kissed him on his little round nose. “Tra en Nefer-ua” [Young and beautiful one] he whispered in ancient Egyptian against the baby boy’s bronze skin. Solon let out a contented sigh as he drifted off to sleep. Yami left his sleeping son and walked back over to Isis. He sat next to her on the couch and took her hand.  “If you want, I can talk to Malik for you.” he smiled. Isis raised an eyebrow. “You? Talk to Malik? My brother.....Malik Ishtar. The same Malik that held you against your will for an entire month and made you go through all sorts of terrible things. Are we talking about the same Malik here?” Yami chuckled lightly and nodded his head. “Yes, we are, Isis. You must remember it was Marik that was part of Bakura’s scheme, not Malik. Yugi is good friends with Ryou, so it won’t seem strange if I call over to their house and ask to speak with Malik.” Isis bit her lip nervously. “Oh pharaoh, I don’t know.......I don’t know if that’s such a good idea. My brother doesn’t just forgive and forget very easily.” Yami picked the cordless phone up off the table and began to dial Ryou’s number.  “Let’s find out.” he smiled as he finished dialing. Yami listened to the phone ring 4 times before the answering machine picked up. As he was hanging up, Yugi walked into the living room and joined Yami and Isis. He was licking an a chocolate ice cream cone he’d just made himself in the kitchen. “Who was that?” He ask Yami curiously as he flopped down in a big. Yami set the cordless phone down on the coffee table and sighed. “I was trying to call Malik, but there was no answer.” Yugi licked his ice cream cone again and laughed. “Of course there was no answer, Yami. Malik and Ryou are in Egypt with Ryou’s father.” “What? Why are they in Egypt?” Yami ask curiously. Yugi nonchalantly continued eating his ice cream and glanced at Yami. “They went there to find a way to trap your soul in the Millennium Puzzle forever so we don’t have to hear your ‘heart of the cards’ speeches’ anymore.” the petite hikari answered seriously.  “WHAT!?!” Yami shrieked loudly. Yugi put his finger up to his lips. “Shhhh.......you’ll wake Solon, Yami!” he whispered in a slightly heightened voice.  Isis covered her mouth and chuckled at the pharaoh’s reaction to his hikari’s wisecrack. She could tell Yugi was only joking. “I’m kidding Yami, relax, jeez!” Yugi giggled playfully. Yami didn’t seem as amused at Yugi’s witty little remark. He got up from the couch and went into the kitchen without saying a word. “I guess I hit a soft spot, eh Isis?” Yugi chuckled.  Even though Isis didn’t understand why Yami had reacted to Yugi’s comment like he did, she still found it a little funny. Yugi got up out of his chair and sat next to Isis. He leaned over and very quietly whispered in her ear. “I think I pissed him off.” he smirked. “I’ll go talk to him and get his royal crankiness back in here.” Isis nodded her head. Yugi excused himself and went into the kitchen to talk to his rather upset yami. Since Yugi had been released from the psychiatric ward, he’d become a lot bolder. He’d learned not to hold his feelings inside. His intrepidness wasn’t easy for Yami to deal with, and on occasion Yugi said things that bothered Yami. The pharaoh incarnate didn’t care for arguing, so he’d leave the room whenever Yugi’s comments would bother him.  Yugi walked into the kitchen and spotted Yami staring out the window by the sink. Yami didn’t bother acknowledging Yugi’s entrance. He stood still with his hands in his pants pockets looking outside.   “Yams? Did what I said out there upset you?” Yugi ask softly as he stood behind Yami. The sulking pharaoh closed his eyes. “Sometimes I wonder what you think of me, aibou.” Yugi rolled his eyes and laughed. “I was only joking back there, Yams, you should know that. Did you really think I would have kept something like that from you if it were true? I love you too much to do something like that.” Yami sighed as he turned to face Yugi. He tried to look Yugi in the eyes, but found it difficult.  “I know that. It’s just sometimes I wonder things. When you take a shot at me, it makes me wonder if you even care how I feel, or if our love is even real.” Yugi hesitated as he contemplated what Yami had just said. He felt his heart drop to the floor. “Y-Yami.......you have doubts about how I feel for you? But....I love you with all my heart, haven’t I proved that to you already?” Yami shifted his weight from one foot to the other anxiously. He wasn’t sure how to respond to Yugi’s reply. Something had changed inside Yami since his traumatic experience of being ‘Bakura’s bitch’ for a month, and he’d found himself second guessing everybody around him. The constant nagging feeling that people were taking advantage of him hindered his trust. Even though Yugi had proved time and time again that he loved Yami unconditionally, the thought that Yugi was only using him crossed his mind several times a day.  “Aibou.......I don’t know of any words to express what I want to say to you.” Tears began to pool in Yugi’s violet eyes. He shook his head and grabbed Yami’s hand. Yugi small fingers trembled as they linked with Yami’s.	 “Are you trying to say you don’t feel the same about me? Are you saying you don’t love me anymore?” Yami wiped a tear from Yugi’s cheek. He loved Yugi, he just didn’t believe that Yugi whole-heartedly loved him back.  “No aibou......that’s not what I said. I love you completely, there’s no doubt in my mind of that.” Yugi’s hand continued to tremble, but he was able to hold back anymore tears. He rested his cheek against yami’s chest. “Than what are you trying to get at, Yami? I’m confused.” Yugi whimpered against Yami’s tear stained white button-up shirt. Yami took a deep breath and let it out slowly. He wrapped his arms around Yugi and held him close. “If you could only live the book of my life, aibou, you’d understand. We used to be so close, but after all that’s happened, I just can’t seem to get back to where I was before.” Yugi wrapped his arms around Yami’s waist and rubbed the small of Yami’s back with his hands. “If our relationship is going to work out, you need to talk to me, Yami. You can’t talk in riddles. You have to tell me things straight up.” Yami gently kissed Yugi’s forehead. He tipped Yugi’s chin up with his finger and gathered the courage to look into Yugi’s moist eyes. “Aibou......promise you’ll never leave me?” Yugi nodded his head. “I promise Yami, I’ll never leave you.” An obscure smile spread across Yami’s face. He ran his fingers through Yugi’s tri-colored hair. “I need to hear you say that more. After what happened to me I don’t always find it easy to trust.” Yugi wiped the remaining tears from his eyes with his sleeve and took a deep breath.  “I think we need to get away for a while Yami, just you and me.” Yami cocked his head. “Where would you like to go?”Yami ask curiously. Yugi shrugged his shoulders. “I don’t know, maybe we can fly to California and get married or something?” Yami’s eyes shot open as big as saucers. “Are you serious?!?” Yugi covered his mouth and chuckled. “Not really, but it’s the thought that counts, right?” Yami rolled his eyes and messed up Yugi’s hair. “You need a spanking, aibou. It’s not nice to trick your yami.” Yugi giggled as he leaned up and placed a kiss on Yami’s cheek. “Aibou’s like spankings from their yami’s.” Yami wagged his eyebrows and laughed. “Maybe tonight.....if you want.” “IF I want? Duh, Yami, of course I want! Hey, I just had a great idea! We should go with Isis back  to Egypt! It would be a nice little vacation for us, and you’d get to spend more Solon!” Yugi suggested excitedly. Yami cocked his head and thought about what Yugi had just said. It didn’t sound half bad. “I like how you think, aibou. Let’s do it, let’s go to Egypt.” Yugi smiled brightly and threw his arms around Yami. “Let’s go tell Isis! This is gonna rock!” ************************************************** 	Duke sniffed the pan of fresh brownies and licked his chops as Jeree pulled them out of the oven. He couldn’t wait to try one, especially since he’d slipped his own special ingredient into the mix prior to baking. “Damn Jer, they smell awesome! When can I have one?” Duke ask as Jeree set the hot pan down on a cooling rack. “After I cut them.” she smiled as she pulled a knife out of the drawer. Duke was practically salivating on the cook’s shoulder as she cut the brownies into squares.  Once she finished slicing through the fresh baked treat, she grabbed a napkin off the counter and handed one to Duke. The raven haired dice master quickly ate his “special” brownie. He looked at Jeree curiously when he realized she wasn’t taking one for herself. “Oh my god Jeree, these are the best! Aren’t you going to have one?” Jeree shook her head and laughed. “No thanks, Duke. You think I didn’t see what you added to the batter? I’ll never be able to do my job back here stoned out of my brain!”		 Duke grabbed another brownie out of the pan and grinned. “Than you won’t mind if I take these up front with me, right?” “I don’t mind at all, just save me one for after work, okay?” Duke kissed Jeree on the cheek and grabbed the pan of brownies. “Of course I’ll save you one, sweetheart. It’s the least I can do for the best cook around.” 	 	After eating half the brownies, Duke kicked back behind the bar and started reading the newspaper.  He was startled from his reading when somebody came running into the bar. “I’m so sorry I’m late! Please don’t fire me! I really need this job!” Serenity pleaded as she approached Duke. Duke looked up from the newspaper. His eyes were glossy and he was wearing a big grin. He laid the newspaper on the bar and started to giggle. “Did you ever notice how people always die in alphabetical order? Isn’t that weird?” he mentioned as he pointed at the obituaries. Serenity looked at Duke like he was wacked out. “Are you okay, Duke?” she ask curiously, taking a second to glance at the half eaten pan of brownies. “Better than ever, babe. You hungry? I have some special brownies that taste absolutely great!”   

						
</post>
<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I don't own Yugioh  This is a repost of crazy little one shot I did a long time ago. I found it amusing and decided to share it here. Ja ne!  **********   “So what’s your idea again?” Bakura mused as he tied his sneakers.  “Sky diving. I heard from one of my rare hunters that it’s better than sex”  Bakura rolled his eyes  “NOTHING-can beat sex.”  “We shall see” Marik grinned as he pulled on his coat.  They took ff on their motorcycles to a small airport just outside of town to get the ball  rolling. A few days later that had finished all the necessary classes and were prepared for  their first jump.  While they were strapping on their gear, Bakura looked over at Marik nervously,  “I’m not so sure about this”  “You’ll be fine Bakura. Don’t sweat it.” Marik grinned.  “I’ll break you’re fucking face if something goes wrong” Bakura snapped back.  “Oh shut it, don’t be such a pussy........hey, I have an idea. It’ll make this jump even better.”  Bakura looked up at Marik with a patronizing gaze.  “I dread to hear this.......but go ahead.”  Marik grinned mischievously.  “I’ve always wanted to try this....but I don’t want to do it alone....let’s take this jump in  the buff!”  Bakura’s eyes got huge,  “SAY WHAT! Are you bent, man?”  “What? You got something to hide? what can it hurt? I heard it’s a major rush,  pleeeeeease Bakura? Would you do it for a Scooby snack?”  Bakura rolled his eyes,  “Shut up, I’ll do it. But you owe me one. This is insane.”  Marik smiled proudly.  “That’s my bro.....”  They purposely strapped their gear under their clothes and headed on board the small  plane.  The air craft took off, and when they were at the right altitude, the instructor started  sending people out the door.  Marik and Bakura were the last to go.  “Are you going to jump or what?” the instructor ask firmly.  Marik gave Bakura one final sneaky grin.  “Yes sir, we’re ready.”  “1....2....3....JUMP!” The instructor counted.  Marik flung himself and got suck out into the open sky.  “YEEEEEEEEEAHHHH!” He yelled as he began descending.  Bakura jumped out seconds after him.  “Oooooooh FUUUUUUUCK!” he screamed as he was free falling.  Marik gave the signal and they both started pulling off their clothes. By the time they had  to pull their parachute cords they were butt naked.  Their adrenaline was sky-rocketing as they floated downward....in all their manly glory.  Without warning, a strong wind gusted and pulled them off course.  “Oh oh.....this isn’t good” Bakura groaned as they blew further and further off track.  They couldn’t make out what was going on below, but they could tell there was a large  gathering of people.  “Marik? I think I might have to kill you once we land.” Bakura yelled  Marik grinned, but it was obvious he was having regrets of taking this jump without any  clothes on.  As they neared the ground, they were able to make out more of what they were going to  land in the middle of, and it wasn’t going to be pretty.  Seconds later they reached solid ground again, but not on the grass. They landed in the  middle of a runway....right in the middle of a Victoria’s Secret lingerie show. They  scrambled out from under their parachutes and were met with the eyes of hundreds of  spectators.  “You are so fucking dead Ishtar!” Bakura growled as he got to his feet.  Cameras were snapping pictures all around them, and reporters were zero-ing in on them  with their video cameras.  “Shit.......let’s fucking run for it man!” Marik yelled as he unclipped his landing gear.  They both ran off the stage and headed straight for home. As luck would have it, they  were only a few blocks away from Marik’s, so they grabbed a couple jackets they saw  laying on some chairs and ran for it.  After running all the way to Marik’s, they threw open the door and ran into his room.  Marik borrowed Bakura a pair of jeans and a shirt to wear while they laid low. They  turned on the television to kill some time. A couple hours later Marik’s sister Ishizu  walked in with a bag of groceries.  “Hey you two...did you hear the big news around town?”  They both played stupid.  “No, what’s going on?”  Ishizu opened a bag of chips and sat down on the couch next to them.  “Some crazy sky divers landed right in the middle of the big Victoria’s Secret show  downtown today. Word has it they were completed nude!” she laughed.  As she finished speaking, the news came on.  “Today in Domino, two young men caused quite the disturbance at the Victoria’s Secret  gala.......you are seeing footage of their grand entrance.” The newscaster chuckled as  Marik and Bakura’s faces were shown on live tv for all of Domino to see. Ishizu just  about choked on her chips when she saw her brother on the television.  "Oh my gods.....that's YOU! and BAKURA!"  Marik held up his hands infront of him.  “Uh.....I guess”  Guilt was written all over his face.  "Anzu Masaki was at this show, and she claims to know the two individuals who pulled  this stunt off” the newscaster continued.  Bakura and Marik gaped in horror as Anzu gave out their names.  “That bitch is dead.....she is SO dead!” Marik hissed.  “Let’s go kill her NOW! And once we get rid of her....I'm going to kill YOU!” Bakura said adamantly to Marik.  The two of them took off in a homicidal rage looking for Anzu.....with full intentions of  doing very horrible things to her.   

						
</post>
<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   okay, I don't own Yugioh blah blah blah.   The Countdown to Death  		  	Yami carefully folded the letter to Yugi and slipped it into a white envelope. He looked around the office he’d hidden himself in since Bakura and Marik had left for a way to get the letter to his hikari. He noticed a wood mail holder hanging on the wall with the words “outgoing” and “incoming” on separate slots.  Perfect.  He peeled a stamp off of the roll he’d found in the desk drawer and pressed it onto the corner of the envelope. “Aibou” he sighed somberly as he looked out the window. Yami’s thoughts were quickly diverted as the sound of chains clinking against leather rattled outside the office door. “I’ll look for the little fuck in here, you go check in the basement.” Marik yelled from beyond the closed oak door. “He’d better hope you find him, because I’ll rip his fucking eyes out and shove them up his royal ass! And don’t think I won’t!” Yami heard Bakura shout back venomously. The gold knob on the door rattled and slowly turned.  Yami bit his lip as Marik shoved the door open. His hands began to tremble very slightly. He took a deep breath as Marik stared him down.  Marik grinned ambiguously as he quietly closed the door. He was careful not to spill a bottle of beer he was carrying. Yami kept a close eye on him. If he made any sudden moves, Yami wanted to at least be able to defend himself from the more masculine Egyptian. To Yami’s relief, (and surprise) Marik reached into the pocket of his long black leather jacket and pulled out a small bag of sour cream and onion flavored potato chips. “You’re so pretty when you’re scared, pharaoh. Here, catch.” He smirked as he tossed Yami the unopened bag of chips. “You better eat those fast, Bakura’s really bent out of shape over you  not coming when he called you downstairs.” Yami ripped open the bag of chips and stuffed a fist full of them in his mouth. He continued to keep an cautious eye on Marik though.  “How are those new piercings doing? Are they causing you much discomfort?” Marik ask as he walked over to the window. “I....don’t..feel....a thing.” Yami responded between bites. The potato chips tasted way better than they should have. He managed to consume the entire bag in less that a minute. It had been many hours since he’d had anything, so he’d eaten the chips a little too fast. Damn it. He should have saved some for later. It could be quite some time before he’d get anything to eat again.  	The chains on Marik’s leather jacket clanged together as the Egyptian the came walking toward Yami. He wore a blank expression on his face, so Yami couldn’t tell what Marik was thinking. It made him a bit nervous. Unlike Bakura, Marik was unpredictable. Bakura was always an ass. He’d lash out at Yami at every given chance. Yami had noticed Marik had moments where he , dare say, seemed to be somewhat nice? Seemed to care? Seemed to feel remorse? Was this one of those moments? “I know I said eat fast, but damn pharaoh, you practically inhaled those. Here, you can have the rest of this.” Marik laughed as he handed Yami his half drank bottle of beer. The salt on the potato chips had made Yami very thirsty, so he took the beer from Marik and chugged it down before Marik changed his mind.  Marik chuckled lightly and sat on the heavy oak desk. “Whoa pharaoh, slow down. That’s beer you know.” Yami polished off the entire contents of the bottle in one breath. He didn’t care what it was, he hadn’t had anything to drink since he inhaled a few pints of bath water earlier that morning. Yami set the empty bottle on top the desk and looked up at Marik. “Can I ask you something?” Marik shrugged his shoulders. “Go ahead” Yami shifted around uncomfortably. The fresh ampallang piercing he’d received was feeling rather uncomfortable. He still hadn’t figured out how to stop the barbell from vibrating.  “Is there any way to turn this thing off?  Yami ask pleadingly and he motioned downward with his hand. Marik nodded his head. “Yes, Would you like me to show you how?” The look in Marik’s eyes unnerved the pharaoh. He wasn’t sure if this was one of Marik’s nice moments, or if it was one of his demented cruel jokes. Yami swallowed hard as he nodded his head. “I’d appreciate that.” Yami closed his eyes as Marik hopped off the desk and kneeled in front of him. His heart raced as Marik’s hands got closer to his sore manhood. “This might feel a little weird, but it shouldn’t hurt.” Marik mused as he did something to make the piece of jewelry stop vibrating. Yami let out a sigh of relief as the vibrating ceased. Marik looked over the fresh piercing and smiled. “It looks nice, does it hurt much?” The tip of Yami’s shaft pained him quite a bit, but Marik didn’t need to know that. “No” Yami answered sternly. Marik lightly kissed the head of Yami’s manhood and got to his feet. He didn’t say another word. He just stared at the thin pharaoh ambiguously.   	 The sound of the door being kicked open and hitting the wall caused both Marik and Yami to jump back. “There you are, you stupid, piece of fucking shit wannabe god!” Bakura growled evilly as he stepped into the room. He had a wild, insane look in his eyes that sent chills down Yami’s spine. Bakura lunged forward at Yami and wrapped his fingers around the pharaoh’s throat. Yami choked for air as Bakura squeezed his windpipe. Yami’s face began to change to red, and than to purple as he gasp for air. He tried to wiggle himself free from Bakura’s death grip, but he was once again over powered. Bakura’s rage and hatred for Yami was fueling his strength. The tomb robber’s chocolate eyes glowed with anger.  “I hate you pharaoh......I’ll never forget the life I had to live because of you. It’s only fitting that a man you mistreated so badly is the one who squeezes your last breath from your pathetic body.” Yami continued to struggle, but it was of no use.   Everything went black. 		  ******************************************************************  	Yami had no idea how much time had passed since he’d blanked out. All he knew was that there were  thick  metal cuffs securing his wrists and ankles to a cold metal chair and that his neck throbbed with intense pain. He slowly opened his eyes.  The entire room was dark except for a candle burning in the corner. The sound of footsteps echoed down from the ceiling above Yami’s head. A quite a bit of noise accompanied the footsteps. It sounded like there was a struggle going on in the room above him. Yami knew by the musty smell that he was in the basement. The footsteps above him began to grow quieter. The creek of an opening door, followed by the clacking of two sets of boots hitting wood began to worry the helpless pharaoh. The voices he heard confirmed his fear. 		  “Here, hold this while I find the light switch, Ishtar.” Bakura’s voice echoed through the darkness.  “Hey look, I just wrote my initials in blood on your wall!” Marik boasted moments later.  “Oooh, you’re so talented.” Bakura snorted back.  	Yami cringed as the foot steps stopped outside the door to the room. The last time he’d seen Bakura, the thief had choked him senseless. Yami prayed to the gods that Bakura was in a better mood now. His neck felt bad enough already.  The door opened slowly and a bright beam of light hit Yami in the face, temporarily blinding him. “Looks like he lived.......damn it.” Bakura scoffed as he handed the bright flashlight off to Marik. The thief was also carrying a brown cardboard box. He walked over to Yami and set the box at the pharaoh’s feet. Bakura stood in front of Yami wearing a sadistic smile.  “We brought you some gifts, would you like to see them, pharaoh?” Yami hated the way Bakura called him “pharaoh.” The sacrilegious tomb robber never referred to Yami as pharaoh unless he was mocking him. Yami wasn’t going to honor Bakura with a response. It wasn’t worth what energy he had left. Marik walked behind Bakura carrying the flashlight. He shined the light up at his own face. The way the light illuminated his face made him look more evil than usual. Yami couldn’t help but notice he had fresh blood splattered on his face and in his hair. Yami’s crimson eyes shifted over to Bakura. The tomb robber was sifting through the brown cardboard box. Oddly enough, he didn’t have any blood on him.  “Let me give the pharaoh my gift first.” Marik insisted. Bakura pulled a long black jewelry box out and handed it to the Egyptian. Marik traded Bakura the flashlight for the rectangular box. He grinned wickedly as he stood before the pharaoh. “I thought of you when I saw this. I think you’ll like it.” Yami watched cautiously as Marik opened the box in front of him. He was relieved when he saw it was only a black leather collar.  Marik pulled the collar out of the jewelry box and held it up for the pharaoh to see. Two thin gold chains dangled from a gold ring attached to the front of the collar. Yami only moved his eyes when looking the “gift” over. The rest of his body remained perfectly still as Marik leaned over and fastened the collar around the pharaoh’s bruised neck. Marik’s hands felt like ice as they touched Yami’s skin. “Definitely an improvement, wouldn’t you say, Bakura?” Marik smiled proudly as he stood back and looked at Yami’s new jewelry. Bakura purposely flashed the bright light of the flashlight in Yami’s face again. “Attach the chains” he snapped coldly. Marik smirked at the pharaoh as he reached for one of the shorter gold chains. “You are going to look so hot.” he purred as he connected the chain to the gold ring in Yami’s tender left nipple. Yami hissed through his teeth as Marik gave the chain a little tug. Bakura looked up and chuckled at the pharaoh’s discomfort. “Fucking little pussy.” he jeered. Marik took a second shorter gold chain between his long fingers and clipped it onto Yami’s right nipple, but this time he did it very gently. Marik traced his finger around the swollen flesh, causing Yami to flinch. “You are one sexy little bitch, pharaoh. ” Marik lustfully purred. Yami tilted his head up toward the ceiling and bit his lip.  “Tell me what is going to happen to me.” Yami spoke in a weak voice. No matter how hard he tried to be strong, his voice continued to fail him. “You want us to ruin our surprise, pharaoh?” Bakura chuckled as he connected a black wire to one of the legs of the metal chair Yami was being held in. “Well you can just forget it!” he hissed as he attached a red wire to the opposite leg of the chair. Yami swallowed hard as Bakura hooked the wires up to a box that was about the size of a 5 gallon fish aquarium. The numbers 00.00 appeared. “Haha!” Bakura laughed evilly as he adjusted the numbers to read 24.00.  “Oh shit!” Marik suddenly exclaimed. Like a bolt of lightning, the blond yami took off on a dead run up the basement steps. Bakura set the timer down in front of Yami and grinned wickedly. “This is it, pharaoh. The time has finally arrived for me to take my ultimate revenge on you for everything that you’ve ever done to me!” Yami glared at the tomb robber as he watched Bakura press a red button. The numbers on the timer began to count down backwards. “What’s the meaning of this, thief! What are you up to!” Yami demanded. Bakura stood before the pharaoh incarnate and ran his deathly cold hand along Yami’s cheek bone. His chestnut eyes flickered with malicious intent. “Do you have any last words, mighty god of Annu?”[1] Yami was in no position to argue with the thief, so he just glowered back into Bakura’s evil chocolate orbs. “Fine, you have no last words.” Bakura snapped as he slapped Yami across the face. “You have exactly 24 hours to think about all the evil you brought into this world, all the lives you ruined, and all the trouble you brought about. When the timer attached to your chair expires, all of your worst fears will be reality. Enjoy the darkness.......pharaoh.” Yami swallowed hard, but didn’t respond to Bakura’s threat. His crimson eyes burned with fear and anger.  Bakura laughed insanely as he began walking out of the dark room. “Xer Xu em Xennu kekui! Hahaha!” [2]  ******************************************************** 23.00 “I can’t believe I’m letting you do this to me........I just can’t believe it.....” Yami thought to himself as he sat in the cold, dark basement. The minutes seemed like hours, and hours felt like days as he watched the numbers counting backward on the timer. Yami’s mind began to wander as the darkness and silence began to play with his mind. He was trapped. There was no escape from whatever fate the evil tomb robber had bestowed on him. The last few words from the wily white haired hooligan echoed through Yami’s mind. “......all the evil you brought into this world, all the lives you ruined, and all the trouble you brought about........” “I never brought evil into the world! ” Yami shouted to himself out loud. The word “evil” kept running through his mind. What was evil? Where did it come from? How thin was the line between the two greatest forces in the world? Yami had always tried to do what he thought was good, but was it really good? Or was good actually evil, and evil actually good? Who was the judge of what was right and wrong? Had he been mislead his entire life? What made “good” so good anyway? Yami thought back to what his father had inadvertently done to Bakura’s village. If his father was supposedly good, why did evil come from his actions? Nothing good came from the making of the Millennium items, only more pain and sorrow. And now that pain and sorrow had spilled into the 21st century. Yugi’s nervous breakdown wasn’t a “good” thing, and Yami blamed himself for it happening. If he never would have made Yugi break up with Joey, Yugi probably would have been just fine. After much thought, Yami came to the conclusion that there really wasn’t a difference between good and evil. Only differences in points of view. Bakura had seen his entire family get boiled alive, so was he actually in the wrong for wanting revenge? After all, he was only human at the time of Kuru Eruna’s demise. Not only was he human, he was a young, impressionable child who’d watched his entire world get ripped away from him. To Bakura, good was evil.    19.00  The time continued to pass by slowly. The house was silent except for the constant ticking noise coming from the timer attached to his cold metal chair. He’d contemplated good and evil already, and found no definite answer. There was no way to determine what was actually good and what was actually evil. It was useless to think about it any longer. Yami stared at the only focal point visible in the room, the digital timer. The seconds ticked away right before his eyes.  He had no clue what would happen after the time expired.  What was inside the box? A bomb? Was he going to get blown to smithereens? Would demons crawl out of the box and drag him to hell?	   14.00  Only 10 more hours left until Yami would discover his fate. He decided it was time to pray to Osiris to have mercy on his soul in his second afterlife. The more Yami thought about it, the more he believed that the box contained something that would end his existence.    8.00		  Thoughts of Yugi were the only thing keeping Yami sane by this point. Yugi’s bright smile, Yugi’s sparkling violet eyes, Yugi’s tender touch. All three of those things gave Yami a little comfort in what he believed were his last few hours.     1.00  Only one hour left. The end seemed inevitable. There was no way out. Yami had accepted that he was going to die. He felt he was ready to go to the next world even though he didn’t feel it was his time. There was so much more he’d wanted to do before his final hour. There were still many loose ends he hadn’t taken care of. The child he’d created with Isis for one. He was leaving behind his legacy before they could meet. He didn’t even know if the child was male or female yet, and it pained him to think of the child growing up without ever knowing its father. What was worse though? Never knowing who created you, or knowing them and losing them? Yami’s eye lids began growing heavy. He’d been up for 24 hours straight thinking about anything and everything, and his mind was exhausted.          “Xer Xu em Xennu kekui” he sighed as he drifted off to sleep.    5........     4.........   3.........  2.........  1.........                             TBC..................................    [1] As you may know, Atemu’s (Atem, Tum, “the closer,”) main cult center was in Heliopolis. In ancient Egypt, “Annu” was the word for Heliopolis.   [2] Ancient Egyptian for “light has fallen into darkness”(literally-Hath fallen light into the darkness)   

						
</post>
<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Okay, so I just took a quiz (which Yugioh character will knock you up-lol!) and this is my results-   You slept with...Ryou Bakura      because...He had something you wanted   LMFAO! Yeah, I know, HIS YAMI!!!  Just felt like posting that......hahaha  Hey, just curious, anybody got any hot yaoi pix of Hiro and K from Gravitation? Damn those two are hot together.......Thank you Deb for getting me hooked on K! Fuck is he HOT!!!  

						
</post>
<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   (Unedited)  Hellraisers Chapter 1- Hells Angels   Bakura followed Ryou down the wide stairs that lead into the basement of the church. He fumbled with the pack of cigarettes in his pocket, wishing he could light one up to calm his nerves. "I can’t believe you’ve dragged me into this sacrilegious dump!" Bakura growled into Ryou’s ear. Ryou covered his mouth to try to keep himself from laughing. He knew Bakura would rather cut his arm off than go near a church, but Malik and Yugi somehow convinced their yami’s to go, so it was only expected that Bakura be there too. Anzu’s idea, she said it would be good for everybody to go and none of the hikari’s wanted to argue with her- the friendship and morality speeches took too long. "Marik and Yami have to go too, so just try to grin and bare it, please? It’s not like this is a service, it’s just youth group, and it’s only for the summer." Bakura glared at the carpeting under their feet. "Well don’t expect any miracles. Making me go to this place of myths and fairy tales isn’t going to change what I believe." Ryou’s giggle accidently escaped as they stepped into the youth group room a couple minutes late. Everybody was already seated and listening to a man about 30 years old talk. There were two open chairs next to Malik and Marik, so Ryou and Bakura gravitated their way. The man talking up front continued with the announcements; "and we’ll be helping out with the decorations for the missions banquet after the service on Sunday........" Bakura could already tell this wasn’t going to be easy. The way the mans voice just droned on and on was almost enough to make him snap. He glanced over at Marik and grinned when he saw that the spiky haired Egyptian was holding the flame of his white BIC lighter under Yami’s butt and burning the loose thread off the former pharaoh’s jeans. Bakura started to chuckle, but Ryou quickly brought his laughter to a halt with a quick jab to the former tomb robber’s ribs. "Fucker" Bakura snarled under his breath, loud enough for only Ryou to hear. Ryou held his finger up to his lips and glared. Bakura rolled his eyes and crossed his arms as he sunk back in his seat with his legs spread apart, casually picking the loose threads from the hole in the knee of his jeans. Yugi, Yami, Jou, Anzu, Honda, Shizuka, and even Mokuba Kaiba were sitting amongst the large crowd of young people. It was just weird. He stared at the pattern on the carpet as the man infront babbled on and on...... Bakura felt like taking a nap. Nothing useful was coming out of this man’s mouth. Help here, help there, lend a hand over there......Bakura just wasn’t into it. Bakura was just about asleep when he felt something hit him on the forehead and fall into his lap. He quickly snapped his eyes in the direction the folded piece of paper came from. Marik was looking at him expectantly. Bakura opened the neatly folded note that Marik had thrown at him. It was written on the back of a flyer for Spencer Lake Bible camp. ‘Meet me in the bathroom 5 minutes’ was scribbled very poorly onto the blue paper. Bakura nodded his head. He watched Marik whisper something in Malik’s ear and than get up and leave. Bakura waited a couple minutes before doing the same. Bakura walked into the closest men’s bathroom and found Marik pretending to use the facilities. "I’m glad it’s you, I thought Malik might have caught on" Marik grinned as he pulled a flask out of his black leather jacket. "Nice shirt" he grinned at Bakura, who’s black t-shirt had "Here today, Gone to Hell" written in bloody looking letters over a cracked skull. Bakura’s eyes lit up like fireworks. Maybe this wasn’t going to be so bad after all! Marik always knew how to make a crappy night a little easier to deal with. "I know" Bakura winked back. Marik took a drink of the clear liquid and handed the flask to Bakura. "This place fucking sucks" the Egyptian grumbled. Bakura took a big gulp of the liquid, which he could tell by the smell was vodka, and nodded his head. "You fucking said it. I can’t believe the things we do for our pathetic hikari’s." Bakura took another quick drink and handed the flask back to Marik. They both heard footsteps nearing the bathroom door, so they turned around quickly and pretended to be taking a leak. "Ra-damned brainwashing bastards......" Yami grumbled in a low, angry voice as the door swung shut behind him. "Pharaoh?" Marik mused as he tried to inconspicuously screw the cap back on the flask. Yami stalked over to the sink and turned on the taps. "I can’t believe the lies they tell here." Yami groaned as he splashed his face with cold water. Bakura snorted coldly as he shoved his hand in his pants pockets. "I thought you’d love it here- all these goody-goody’s under one roof." Yami glanced over his shoulder at the former thief and narrowed his eyes. "I must admit Bakura, I’m surprised that their so called god hasn’t struck you with one of his lightning bolts." "Fuck you and you’re little attitude" Bakura hissed in response. Marik unscrewed the cap of the flask of vodka and guzzled the rest of it down. "Look, we’re all in this together, so I suggest we try to get along for the time being" he growled. Bakura crossed his arms and grunted. "I suppose your right" Yami dried his face with a paper towel and nodded sharply. "So how do you suggest we get through this without sending them all to the Shadow Realm?" Marik replaced the cap on his flask and put the empty container in his pocket. "I haven’t thought of that yet, but I’m sure we can think of something." "Go figure" Yami groaned as he walked out the door. Bakura rolled his eyes. "I still hate that little bastard" Marik nodded his head. "I know, but he’s in the same boat as us this time. Imagine how he feels, he’s the creator god and he’s in a place where they’re trying to convince everybody he’s not." Bakura started to snicker as he looked at his reflection in the mirror. "That’s good for that little pompous runt" Marik pulled a piece of gum out his jacket pocket and broke it in half. "Here, chew this, they won’t smell the alcohol on our breath." Bakura took the gum and popped it in his mouth. "You mean we have to go back in there?" Marik nodded his head slowly. "I’m afraid so, c’mon, I’ll walk in with you" Bakura reluctantly followed Marik out of the bathroom and back into the meeting. The man had finished talking and the group was now watching a video about satanic messages in rock music. Marik and Bakura returned to their seats, greeted by nasty looks from their hikari’s. "What took you so long?" Ryou ask in a hushed voice. A snakey grin spread across Bakura’s face. "I had to do my business, need proof?" Ryou made a sour face and looked back at the movie playing on the television. Bakura smirked victoriously and pulled a little knife out of his pocket. He discretely started carving a pentagram into his metal fold up chair. After the movie, the man who had bored Bakura to the brink of tears returned to the front of the group. "Now we have a special treat for you all! We’re going to walk over to the old age home and sing for the elderly! Won’t that just be totally keen?" The man exclaimed. Yami looked back at Bakura and rolled his eyes. Bakura nodded back, he knew exactly what Yami was thinking. The group got up and started heading for the door. Anzu was the first out the door as usual. "This is going to be great!" She squeaked excitedly as she ran up the stairs. Bakura and Marik exchanged sickened glances as they walked behind the group. The man who was leading the meeting walked up behind the two and put his hands on their shoulders. "Ready to spread some joy?" he ask with a big grin. Bakura made a sour face, as did Marik. "Get you’re hands off me or I’ll put a spell on you" Bakura snarled evilly as he jerked his arm away. "And than I’ll banish your mind to the Shadow Realm!" Marik growled. Ryou, noticing his yami wasn’t behind him, rushed to Bakura’s side and started pulling him away. Malik saw Ryou take off, than noticed Marik wasn’t behind him, and duplicated Ryou’s reaction. "My uh.....brother just, um.....got out of prison. He’s been in since, um.....he hasn’t been around the general population" Ryou lied as he pulled Bakura away, scolding the yami with his eyes. "Uh...same here" Malik nodded as he whisked Marik away. "This isn’t easy for any of us, okay? Just settle down now," Ryou growled under his breath as they followed the group out, "Please?" Bakura crossed his arms and grunted. "You are in for the beating of your life tonight" Yami overheard Bakura’s threat and jabbed the former thief in the ribs with his elbow. "You’ll do no such thing..unless you’re looking to get mind crushed" Bakura narrowed his eyes. "Just go fuck yourself" he glared. Yami gave Bakura the "I’m not kidding" look and ran his fingers over the Millennium Puzzle, indicating to Bakura he was serious. Bakura stuffed his hands in his pockets and rolled his eyes. "Whatever" The large group of young people, ranging in age 13 to mid twenties in age, walked down the sidewalk towards the nearby old age home. Bakura swore he smelled cigarette smoke, but thought it was just his mind playing tricks on him. Seconds later he felt a tap-tap on his shoulder. Bakura turned his head and saw Marik walking close behind him. The Egyptian glanced down at his hand and than back at Bakura. Bakura looked down at Marik’s hand and realized he was passing him a half smoked cigarette. "You’re the best" Bakura smirked as he discretely took a long, satisfying drag. "I know, you can thank me later" Marik winked. Bakura turned his head away for a minute and grinned. He secretly had a little crush on Marik, but didn’t think it would be a good idea to tell anyone, not even Ryou. Marik was just his friend, nothing more, and that’s how it needed to stay. The two yami’s lagged behind the group passing the cigarette back and forth as they walked to the old age home. The weren’t in any hurry to go sing songs to old people. After only five minutes into the singing, Bakura had enough. He quietly slipped outside to get away. The first thing he did was light up a cigarette. Smoking was a habit he picked up from Marik after Ryou and Malik started hanging around each other more. He didn’t care if people thought it was gross, it helped him to calm his nerves. As he walked around the brick building, Bakura heard voices around the corner- male voices. Not wanting to draw attention to himself, Bakura leaned back against the wall and crept quietly closer to see who it was. He was relieved when he heard Marik’s voice. "I’m so glad to be out of there. I’d rather have lose an arm than sing that ‘Amazing Grace’ again." "You can say that again" Yami sighed. Bakura was about to say hi to them, but as he turned the corner of the building, he found Marik pulling Yami into a smoldering kiss. Bakura quickly pulled back out of sight. That WASN’T what he was expecting to see. His heart dropped a little after seeing his chances with Marik were slim to none. "Gods Yami, I wanna fuck you so badly" Marik moaned. Yami just giggled in reply. Bakura swallowed hard, than took a long drag of his cigarette. "Oh, yeah, I almost forgot; Could you and Yugi give Malik and I a ride back home after this stupid meeting? Isis dropped us off, but said we’d have to have the church van bring us back- and there’s NO WAY I’m riding back with those heretic bible thumpers!" "That’s fine, I’m sure we can squeeze the two of you in" Yami purred in Marik’s ear, nipping at the Egyptian’s earring playfully. Marik started to laugh. "You are such a little tease Yami, I wish you’d let me fuck you." "You know my rules" Yami replied. Marik let out a long sigh. "I know, no sex until marriage, but that doesn’t mean you can’t give me a little head every now and than." Yami pushed Marik’s hair behind his ears and started licking his neck. "Oh Marik, cut it out, yes it does. Now quit griping and kiss me." Bakura sucked down the last drag of cigarette and tossed the tar stained filter to the side. //I’d let you fuck me// he thought to himself as he walked back to the door he’d snuck out of. He didn’t want to go back inside, but he didn’t want to stay outside after seeing what he saw either. At least inside he could scare old people by making his eyes glow, or make his hair spike up into horns during "Holy, Holy, Holy." That would definitely make the night a little more enjoyable. "Osiris will be busy tonight!" he laughed as he walked back inside. He sided up to Ryou wearing a cheshire grin. "Where were you?" Ryou whispered into Bakura’s ear. A snakey grin spread across Bakura’s face. "I had to do my business, need proof?" Ryou made a sour face and looked away. After returning to the youth group room back at the church, the youth pastor made a final announcement before he dismissed the group. "This Saturday is our annual trip to the Wet Wilderness Water Park. The van will be leaving from here at the church at 7am sharp! Don’t forget to bring your own towels, sunscreen, and some money for food and whatever else you may want. If you still need to sign up, see me or my wife after the meeting." A chorus of excited talking erupted. Ryou turned to Bakura with a big grin plastered on his face. "We have to go! Wet Wilderness is the biggest waterpark within a 500 mile radius!" Bakura reluctantly nodded his head. "Fine, we can go.....but you’ll owe me bigtime! Got that?" Ryou threw his arms around Bakura and squealed excitedly. "Thank you, thank you, thank you!" he said quickly. Bakura rolled his eyes as he peeled his gushing hikari off of him. "Yeah, yeah. Now let’s get the fuck out of here. I’m beginning to feel queezy." "After I sign us up! Wait right here!" Ryou instructed his yami. "Oh for fucks’ sake," Bakura groaned as Ryou bolted away. "Hey sexy" Marik grinned as he approached Bakura from the left. Bakura rolled his eyes as he stuffed his hands into his pockets. "Pfffft, whatever" he responded sarcastically. Marik ran his fingers through Bakura’s hair and grinned. "You’ve got really nice hair" he purred in a seductive tone. He sunk his nose into Bakura’s long, spiky white hair and inhaled deeply. "Mmm, your hair smells good too, what do you use?" Bakura could feel his face grow hot and his knees got weak. Marik could be quite the charmer sometimes. Bakura recalled what he’d seen behind the old age home and shook his head. "Toilet water, now get the fuck off of me. Don’t you have a boyfriend?" Marik started to laugh as he pulled away. Yami joined them seconds later looking aggravated. "We’ll have to wait a bit before we leave, Yugi’s signing us up for that stupid waterpark trip." Bakura rolled his eyes. "Ryou’s making me go too, tell me Yami, why can’t I beat the little bastard again?" Marik playfully punched Bakura in the arm. "You need to lighten up, at least your hikari lets you smoke in the house. Mine has a sister who’s just a big psychotic nag." "I don’t know, I think you’re sister is kind of cute" Yami snickered. Bakura made a sour face and turned to leave. "That’s just...ewe.....more than I really needed to hear. Excuse me, I need to go puke. Do me a favor, tell Ryou I’m walking home." Halfway back to their apartment, Bakura heard a car pull up next to him. Assuming it was somebody thinking of mugging him, Bakura pulled out his pocket knife and prepared for a fight. "Hey yami, hop on in! We’re taking a ride out to the country in Yugi’s grandfather’s car!" Ryou shouted. "Yeah, get your ass in here!" Marik chimed in, banging his hand on the outside of the car door. Bakura turned around and found his hikari hanging half out the front window waving him over. "There’s room back here with us." Marik grinned as he opened the back door. Bakura made a sour face as he slid in next to Marik. Yami, who was sitting on Marik’s other side, had his shirt off and the zipper of his jeans left wide open. Marik had a fresh bright red love bite on the side of his neck. It made Bakura want to throw up. Ryou turned to his yami with a big grin. He handed Bakura an empty glass bottle. "You’ll be needing this" he snickered. Bakura looked at the bottle curiously. It wasn’t big enough to throw up in, so what could Ryou have meant? "Where in the hell did you get a bowling ball!" Malik exclaimed as he looked on the floor by Ryou’s feet. Yugi started to giggle. "It’s my grandfather’s" Bakura sat as close to the door as possible. Marik and Yami were all over each other, and what they were doing was just shy of actual sex. Both of them were moaning and making very disgusting slurping noises. Bakura opened his window and stuck his head out. "Can I smoke in here?" he ask Yugi. "Sure, as long as you ash out the window" Bakura reached into his pocket and pulled out a cigarette and tried blocking out the scene next to him. They drove out into the country, where houses were few and far between. The road was dark, and little furry woodland creatures repeatedly ran out infront of the car. "I really need to use the bathroom, can we pull over?"Ryou ask politely. "No!" Malik chuckled, "I got a better idea!" Yugi had turned up the radio, so Bakura couldn’t hear what Malik whispered to Ryou. All he could make out was the two hikari’s shifted around and giggling. Ryou looked back at Bakura with a big grin. "I’d close my window if I was you" Bakura made a face. "Why?" Ryou held up a glass juice bottle like the one he’d handed Bakura earlier, but Ryou’s was filled with some kind of liquid. Bakura could only guess what the liquid was. He quickly closed his window. Ryou opened his window and patted Malik’s shoulder. Malik look at Yugi. "Hey, drive a little slower past that mailbox." he instructed their tri-haired driver. As they passed the mailbox, Ryou chucked the bottle out the window. It hit the mailbox and shattered into tiny pieces. "Ace in the hole!" Ryou cheered as he high-fived Malik. "Nice shot" Bakura snickered as he unzipped his jeans. "Now it’s my turn!" After driving around causing trouble for an hour, Yugi announced they had to get home. Grandpa gave him an 11' o’clock curfew. Bakura and Ryou were the first to get dropped off, their apartment was the closest. On their way up, Ryou seemed to be glowing with happiness. "What the hell has you so Ra-damned happy?" Bakura grunted as he fumbled for their house keys. "You’re not going to believe this!" Ryou blushed. Bakura rolled his eyes. "Try me" he groaned as he opened the door. "Malik as me out! Can you believe it?" Bakura bit his lip. This couldn’t be happening, could it? Bakura felt a lump growing in the back of his throat. "That’s great" he managed to squeak out without sounding like it bothered him. "He’s coming over tomorrow night, I can’t wait!" Ryou exclaimed as he flopped onto the sofa. "That’s just dandy" Bakura mused to himself as he stripped off his shirt and headed into the bathroom for a cold shower. "Just fucking dandy" he sighed as he closed the door.                      

						
</post>
<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Yami watched the tomb robber’s every move from down on the floor. The restraints around his ankles and wrists weren’t very tight, but they were far from comfortable. Even though his situation didn’t look very promising, Yami clung tightly to Marik’s philosophy about laughing away pain. Yami forced himself to be brave in the face of eminent danger and instead of fighting Bakura’s games, he’d go along with them as much as he could. Bakura made sure to keep the atmosphere of the room was ominous and dark. A single black three-wick candle was providing just enough light for Bakura to see where to walk. The faint scent of something else burning lingered lightly in the air. After whipping Yami’s rear end until the carpet below was speckled in blood, Bakura had left Yami to go plug something into the wall. A quick flash of light illuminated the thief’s white hair making it glow purple, followed by an eerie buzzing. He giggled evilly and turned the device off. Bakura walked back to Yami and knelt down infront of him. He was holding the device behind his back and smirking. "If I could easily snap your neck with a single twist, but that would be too easy, wouldn’t it?" the thief ask hypothetically. Yami scrunched up his nose and glared into Bakura’s wild eyes. "I could start this house on fire and leave you to burn too, but that would also be too easy, wouldn’t it?" the fiend continued. Bakura snapped his fingers. "I know, I could mummify you- the old-fashioned way! HAHA!" Yami knew that Bakura liked playing mind games. He was notorious for psyching his victims out until they’re minds would crack. No doubt this was his intentions right now. Yami wasn’t about to allow Bakura’s tricks to weaken his mind. "What makes you think that torturing me to death will change anything, Bakura?" Yami ask seriously. Bakura chuckled lightly as he tipped Yami’s chin up with his index finger. "Change? I don’t wish for anything to change. I’m happier right now than I’ve been in many millenniums! I’ve achieved ultimate power.....ultimate power over YOU! HAHAHA!" Yami narrowed his eyes. "And just what does that prove? You’re a bully who likes to pick on people smaller than you?" Bakura glowered down at the brutally honest pharaoh and clenched his fists. "You better watch your mouth, pharaoh. I know you’re not as honest and holier-than-thou as you try to portray to the world. I may have done some nasty shit to my hikari, but I can honestly say I never pushed his friends away. You on the other hand........" "You turned Ryou’s friends into dolls, you wicked thief.... or have you forgotten that?" Yami spat. Bakura shrugged his shoulders. "Hmpf, so? I kept his friends close, didn’t I? I didn’t impregnate the first woman who blew me a kiss and push Malik out of Ryou’s life now did I? You live a double standard life, Yami, can’t you see that? I’ve always been honest about what I was after. You lied to Yugi for your own selfish want. How close are you with Yugi these days, huh? He put his life on the line for you time after time, and you repay him by taking away the one thing that meant the world to him? That’s just a trifle -evil- wouldn’t you say?" Yami’s heart was pumping fast. Bakura’s words infuriated him! "Bastard! That’s not how it was!" he growled venomously. Bakura was tickled pink by Yami’s reaction! He fell to his knees laughing. He used one hand as support, still holding the other behind his back. "Oh my! Have I hit a sore spot? Have I angered the wanna-be creator god? Oh that’s rich!" Yami was breathing heavily. Had he not been restrained he would have punched Bakura’s teeth out. Maybe even ripped out his pretty white hair....... "Just shut up Bakura, SHUT THE HELL UP!" Bakura took a deep breath. He waited a few seconds before he got to his feet. "As you wish" Bakura snickered as he brought the device he was hiding behind his back into full view. It had a black handle with a long glass tube attached. Bakura pressed a button on the device. The tube started to glow purple and emitted a menacing buzzing noise that made Yami’s skin crawl. The thief’s eyes glowed with malicious intent. "I think I prefer living in the 21st century opposed to ancient Egypt. These pathetic mortals have come up with some fun little inventions." Yami swallowed hard as Bakura turned him over. Every muscle in Yami’s body felt like they were being pinched in a vice. Only contortionists were suppose to bend like this. The effects of the aphrodisiac were still in working their magic on Yami’s fully erect hard on too, which made the pharaoh feel like a total dork. Bakura held the strange device just above Yami’s chest. "It’s a violet wand, in case you’re wondering. It converts standard household current into high-frequency, high voltage up to 30,000 watts." Bakura touched the tube lightly against Yami’s flat stomach. Myriads of small sparks started flying around. Yami tried to wiggle away, but with no success. The sparks felt like bee stings all over his stomach. "Heh Heh.....I love technology." Bakura chuckled wickedly as he watched Yami squirm. Yami closed his eyes tightly and tried to think of laughing. He tried to laugh out loud, but nothing came out except for a whimper. He tried hard to lay still as Bakura ran the wand across his body. He wasn’t sure what Bakura was up to. "I think we’re ready to move on now." Bakura announced after bathing Yami in sparks for a few minutes. Bakura turned off the wand and set it aside. He reached into his pocket and pulled out a set of keys. He flipped Yami back over and unlocked his restraints. Yami’s legs and arms dropped to the floor. Bakura flipped him back over and straddled the pharaoh’s hips. "You’re in for the wildest night of your afterlife, Yami-kins." Yami laid totally still as Bakura got off of him and picked him up. He carried Yami over to the bed and laid him down. The tomb robber pushed Yami’s legs apart and kneeled between them. "I want you keep your legs spread and hug your knees to your chest.......and don’t refuse, I’ll lock you up again....or worse" Yami reluctantly did as Bakura ask him. Bakura got off the bed and retrieved one of the bags containing some of the new toys. He pulled out the battery powered anal spreader. "I want you to look me in the eyes when I do this to you. Don’t take your eyes off of mine no matter what I do." Yami nodded very slightly as he looked into Bakura’s eyes. He took a deep breath as Bakura lowered his head and started running his tongue down Yami’s shaft. Yami involuntarily moaned as Bakura’s tongue grazed his scrotum. Bakura smirked wickedly as they maintained eye contact. Yami bit his tongue hard to remind himself not to do that again. Bakura wetted Yami’s rear entrance with his tongue, causing Yami’s shaft to twitch. The thief grasp Yami’s manhood and stroked it as he lubed up his backside with saliva. Yami still kept his eyes focused on Bakura’s, but it was becoming hard. He didn’t like Bakura seeing that he was kind of enjoying this a little. Bakura slowly inserted the metal spreader. Yami bit his lip as the cool metal slid into his canal and began to expand. Bakura snickered as he turned the device on, sending waves of electricity through Yami’s hind end, instantly stimulating his prostrate. Yami closed his eyes and started to moan. The current was just enough to send him into sexual euphoria in mere seconds. "Yami, you broke eye contact....you know what that means?" Yami opened his eyes and focused back on Bakura: "It won’t..... happen... again" Yami panted as Bakura got off the bed. Yami whimpered in protest, his shafted throbbed for some attention. "Don’t move......understand?" Bakura instructed him firmly as he rummaged through one of the bags. Yami held his position, whimpering intermittently as he felt his release pooling in his gut. "I’d love to hear you moan a little louder, pharaoh." Bakura chuckled as he returned to his position on the bed. "And I think I have just the toy to do the trick." Bakura inserted a thin, white vibrator into Yami’s rear and wrapped his lips around the pharaoh’s needy member. Yami drug his fingernails into the bed sheets below him and cried out. "Bakura!" Bakura sucked Yami’s entire length into his mouth, tasting the first drops of pre-cum oozing from the tip. He stroked Yami’s shaft vigorously and he teased the pharaoh’s prostrate gland with the vibrator. Yami’s threw his head back and screamed loudly as his climax peaked. Bakura pulled his mouth away and stroked the pharaoh’s release out of him. Beads of sweat had formed on Yami’s face. He continued to grip the sheets tightly as his heart rate slowly returned to normal. Bakura pulled the vibrator out of Yami and tossed it aside. He turned the vibrations off and pulled the other metal instrument out of Yami and chuckled. "That was certainly special now, wasn’t it?" Yami nodded his head as he released his legs. "I’m glad you enjoyed it, because now it’s my turn to have some fun." Yami swallowed hard as Bakura covered his eyes with a fuzzy black blindfold. "I’m going to enlist a little help from the shadow realm for my latest game." Bakura informed Yami as he pulled his duel deck out from his pocket. "Chain Energy!" Bakura shouted. Glowing rings surrounded Yami, restricting his upper body movements. Bakura picked the burning candle up from its spot on the headboard of the bed and slowly tipped it over, spilling hot wax out onto Yami’s stomach. Yami cried out in pain as the super hot wax burned against his skin. Bakura started to laugh. "If you can tell me what the cause of your pleasure or discomfort is, I’ll be happy to move on to the next item." "Hot candle wax" Yami whimpered as the wax began to cool and dry onto his skin. "Very good" Bakura replied as he put the candle back. He peeled the wax off of Yami once it cooled completely and moved on to the next item in the bag. "Can you tell me what this item is?" He ask as he ran melting cherry popsicle over the area he’d just dumped the wax. "Ice?" Yami ask nervously as the coolness eased the discomfort. Bakura chuckled evilly as he licked the popsicle. "Nope, guess I’ll have to make this easier for you to guess. Spread your legs." Yami bent his knees, as requested, as waited anxiously for Bakura’s next move. He grunted as he felt something cold and wet get shoved up his ass. "Any guesses, pharaoh?" Bakura giggled as he moved the popsicle in and out of Yami’s tight heat in a tedious fashion. Yami arched his hips up and moaned as a chill coursed through his body, "It’s.....a....popsicle....." "What flavor?" Bakura snickered as he watched the melting red liquid drip from Yami’s warm canal. "I don’t fucking know!" Yami cried out. Bakura pulled a tiny remote control out of his pocket and pressed a red button. The collar around Yami’s neck activated, giving the pharaoh a sharp, quick jolt of electricity as punishment. Yami yelped in pain. "Every time you answer wrong, this is what you’ll get." Bakura smirked. He pulled the icy treat out of Yami and held it over the pharaoh’s lips. "Taste" he said firmly. Drops of red cherry flavored liquid fell onto Yami’s lips. Yami licked them off. "Cherry" Yami said quickly, turning his head away from the popsicle. Bakura snickered as he tossed the melting item onto the floor. The thief positioned himself between Yami’s legs and placed a pillow under Yami’s lower back, raising the pharaoh’s hips. He was already rock hard, so he pressed his thick shaft halfway into Yami’s cherry stained ass. The chilled inner walls of Yami’s canal caused him to moan loudly. Yami duplicated the moan as Bakura began to move inside of him. "You feel so good pharaoh" Yami clawed at his sides trying to free himself from Bakura’s chain energy restraints. He wanted to grab Bakura by his hips and pull him into him all the way, but it was of no use. Bakura just laughed as he teased the pharaoh with his manhood. "You want more?" the thief ask with an evil grin. "Yes!" Yami gasp as he bucked his hips upward. "Beg me for more than!" Bakura snapped back. Yami screamed with frustration. "Please Bakura, I’m begging you! Fuck me right or don’t fuck me at all!" Bakura made a sour face and pulled out of Yami. He lifted Yami's blindfold so that the pharaoh couls watch his next move. "You call that begging? Pfffffft.........Marik does a better job than you in his sleep! I think I’ll just have to entertain you with more toys before we go any further. Tell me pharaoh, what’s your favorite color?" Yami looked up at Bakura and made a face. "Favorite color? I don’t know, black?" Bakura nodded his head as he pulled his pants back up. "Nice choice, black is my choice of color too, it’s funny how we think alike sometimes, isn’t it?" Yami only nodded slightly in response. He waited anxiously as Bakura sifted through his bag of sex toys. "Oooh, yes! I forgot about these!" Bakura exclaimed as he pulled out a pair of black leather studded wristbands. A half smile spread across Yami’s face, he couldn’t disagree- the wristbands were really cool looking. Bakura snapped the bands around Yami’s wrists and went back to digging through the bag. "Mm, this will do, as will this, and oh yes, I mustn’t forget these!" The thief mused to himself. Yami took a deep breath and let it out slowly. The items Bakura had pulled out were not torture devices, they were articles of clothing: something Yami hadn’t had since his first day of servitude to the thief. Bakura put a black leather biker cap with a silver chain on Yami’s head and ran his fingers through Yami’s blond bangs. "You look simply divine......my little sex object." the tomb robber purred. "I love how you look in black leather." Yami chuckled lightly, was a compliment? Bakura place a pair of round framed sunglasses with mirrored lenses over Yami’s eyes and slid off the bed. He stood over Yami wearing a cheshire grin. "One last accessory and we’ll begin your....heh......sexacution." Yami watched Bakura intently as the thief laced up a pair of black leather combat boots. Once the boots laced, Bakura grabbed Yami’s ankle and smirked. "You’ve got cute toes, pharaoh......you know that?" Yami was feeling a little weirded out by Bakura’s comment, but accepted it. "Thanks" he replied quietly. Bakura slipped the boots onto Yami’s feet and tied the laces tight. "Now we’re talking....hahaha." the thief laughed as he pulled a little silver ring with a thin, seven inch long, tapered metal rod attached to it. Yami swallowed hard. There was only one place that it looked like it would go into perfectly.... Bakura chuckled evilly as he set the silver colored apparatus on the bed and started taking off his clothes. Yami shivered nervously as Bakura crawled back onto the bed with a tube of lube in hand. He squeezed an ample amount into his hand and picked up the metal ring with the rod (about as thick as a straw) attached. He spread the lube over the cool metal. "I think you’re going to enjoy this pharaoh." he grinned wickedly as he held up the device. Bakura reached between Yami’s legs and distributed the remaining lubrication on his hand on Yami’s shaft. Yami closed his eyes. He thought he knew exactly what Bakura was going to do.....he waited....and waited...... "Owe, fuck!" Bakura snarled. Yami opened his eyes. He was surprised to find that Bakura had inserted the metal rod into his own arousal, and the ring fit snuggly under the head. The thief’s eyes were watering. "I’ve never used one of these Glans rings before, it’s a bit- strange feeling." he whimpered as his manhood adjusted to the metal intrusion. Bakura waved his hand in the air and the magical binds restraining Yami quickly disappeared. He covered Yami’s petite body with his own before Yami could try to escape. He pressed his cold lips firmly against Yami’s and forced the pharaoh into a deep kiss. Yami didn’t struggle or refuse the thief. He allowed the tomb robber to take what he wanted, after all- he was still wearing an electric collar that Bakura could activate at anytime. Bakura explored the warmth of Yami’s mouth with his tongue, heightening Yami’s senses. Yami reached up with his hands and wrapped them around Bakura’s shoulders, pulling the thief a little closer. Bakura pulled his lips away for a moment to catch his breath, but Yami wasn’t about to let him stop. He yanked Bakura’s head back down and forced Bakura’s mouth back against his. Bakura moaned loudly and dragged his fingernails over Yami’s shoulders. . Yami cried out into their kiss and bit down hard on Bakura’s lower lip. Bakura’s eyes got huge! He was shocked at the pharaoh’s sudden reciprocation. Yami actions only fueled Bakura’s fire. Bakura raised his hand and slapped Yami across the face, instantly leaving a red hard print. Yami forced himself to look un-phased. He grabbed two fists full of Bakura’s tousled white hair and yanked it hard. Bakura growled as he grabbed Yami’s hair and did the same. He tried to pull away to say something, but Yami cleverly wrapped his legs around Bakura and flipped him onto his back, pinning his shoulders to the bed. Bakura looked up at his own reflection in Yami’s mirrored sunglasses and stared in shock. Yami placed his index finger over the thief’s lips and smirked. "Don’t be scared" he chuckled darkly as he twirled a lock of Bakura’s hair between his fingers. "I’m not!" Bakura hissed back as he struggled to regain the top position. Yami shook his head. "Wouldn’t your game be more fun if we .....shared the pain?" Bakura narrowed his cold, cruel eyes. "What do you got?" Yami grinned as he reached for the vibrator Bakura had used on him earlier. Bakura glanced at the white, buzzing object and grinned evilly. Bakura nodded his head sharply. "Let the battle for dominance began than, pharaoh! I’m curious to see how creative you are!" Yami licked his lips and smiled boldly at the tomb robber. "Indeed....let the battle for dominance begin!" ************************************************************  

						
</post>
<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   *because AFF is fucked again, here's chapter 7 for ya'll;-)  Tolerance Theory   Seven days came and went, and Yami was surprised to find himself still sane after enduring 168 hours with Tea. His ears were constantly ringing, but he hadn’t killed himself, so that was a good thing........wasn’t it? Bakura wasn’t very happy with the results of his avenue torture, but it didn’t matter, he still had more play time with his pet. He couldn’t fathom how Yami had survived seven days locked in a room with "Gorgon," as he had dubbed Tea. Just hearing the word "friendship" coming out of her mouth made Bakura want to throw up and isolate himself in the Millennium Ring for a few thousand more years. A yami can only handle so much mushiness. After sending Tea home, Bakura surprised Yami by allowing him out of the basement to take a shower and get something to eat. Yami had just stepped out of the shower when he heard Bakura shouting at Marik. Not wanting to interrupt the spat between the two quarreling rogues, Yami knelt down and peeked out from under the closed bathroom door to better hear what all the commotion was about. "I’ll be back later, don’t do anything stupid, Ishtar. That means NO making out with my pet. You just stay the hell away from him, he’s mine tonight! You hear me?" Bakura growled. "Loud and clear. Now get the fuck out of here." Marik hissed back. Yami heard the front door slam, than all was quiet for a few minutes. He dried himself off with a towel and ran a comb through his hair for the first time in what seemed like forever. He looked into the mirror and gaped at his sickly reflection staring back at him. Webs of tiny, swollen red veins had spread over the whites of his eyes. His lips were cracked and bleeding slightly. He looked nothing like a former pharaoh. His appearance depleted significantly in a very short time. Yami wrapped the towel around his slender waist and noticed how thin he’d become. He could almost feel every rib in his body. A knock on the bathroom door startled the frail pharaoh, causing him to jump. "Pharaoh? Are you okay?" Marik ask curiously through the door. Yami slowly reached for the doorknob and turned it. He pulled the door open and found himself looking up into Marik’s dangerous indigo orbs. "Im fine, where did Bakura go?" he ask a little hesitantly. Even though Marik had been sneaking food and showing a glint of compassion towards him, Yami didn’t want go as far as considering him a friend just yet. The fact remained that Marik was in cahoots with Bakura, making him an unlikely alliance. "I don’t know, he just said he was leaving. My guess is that he’s going to the cemetery to meditate." Marik said with a little chuckle. Yami screwed up his face and stared at Marik through shocked eyes. "He meditates? In the cemetery? That’s definitely different." Marik leaned back against the doorframe and shrugged his shoulders. "I know what you’re thinking: you’re thinking Bakura’s not playing with a full deck." Yami nodded his head. That happened to be exactly what was going through his head. "You’re very perceptive, Ishtar. Tell me something, didn’t Bakura say were weren’t suppose to talk to me while he was away?" Marik crossed his arms and looked down at Yami. "Like I give two shits about what that bonehead says. Bakura doesn’t control me." Marik reached into his belt loop and pulled out his Millennium Rod. "If he tried to he’d find the Millennium Rod so far up his ass, he’d taste it." A cold chill ran up Yami’s back as his eyes focused on the pointed end of the rod. Marik shoved the rod back in his belt loop and started to laugh. "C’mon pharaoh, the cranky old thief only said that I couldn’t go near you, he said nothing about you coming near me. How about you follow me into the back yard. There’s something there you may find interesting." Yami cocked his head curiously. "What is it? He ask as he followed Marik. "You’ll see" Marik smirked as he lead Yami out to the back patio. Yami was a little unsure of Marik’s motive for coaxing him out, but went along with it. The sun had just set and stars were flickering above their heads. The full moon provided them just enough light to see their surroundings. Marik lead Yami over to a small picnic table with a lit candle placed in the center. "Have a seat." he said to the towel clad pharaoh. He didn’t say the words as a command, but more like a request. Yami sat down across from Marik and stared at the candles’ light dancing in the darkness. "So Marik, any idea what the tomb robber has in store for me tonight?" Yami ask, morbidly curious. Marik propped his chin up with his hand and chuckled. "I think he’s planning on filleting you alive and turning your carcass into new livingroom furniture." Yami’s jaw dropped open and his eyes got huge. It sounded like something Bakura would actually do. He was always sick and twisted that way. Marik snickered at Yami’s reaction. "I’m only joking, pharaoh. I honestly don’t know what he’s got in mind for you. It’s not like he and I sit around having friendly conversations. Bakura does his thing, I do mine." Yami let out a relieved sigh. Having his skin cut from his flesh was not on the top of his afterlife agenda. Marik reached over the table and ran his fingertips down Yami’s cheek. He sighed as he pulled his hand back. "Why don’t you ever give up and die?" he ask. Yami cocked his head. "Excuse me?" he gasp. Yami hadn’t expected a question like that! Marik got up off the bench he was sitting on and walked over to the edge of the deck. He put his hands on the wooden ledger board and looked up into the star speckled night sky. "Bakura and I have done everything to drive you over the edge, yet you are still undaunted." Yami thought for a minute before answering Marik. ‘Why don’t you give up and die’ wasn’t something he was asked everyday, and it required a little more thought. "Let me ask you this, Ishtar. Why don’t you and Bakura ever give up and die? A world without evil would be a much better place." Marik looked back at Yami. His long, blond hair was blowing in the gentle breeze. He didn’t look angry, but he didn’t look very pleased with Yami’s answer. "Yamis’ like Bakura and I don’t die because we laugh at everything- unlike you who thinks everybody has to be serious all the time. That’s why I don’t understand how you’re still around. You’ve always got a stick up your ass." Yami crossed his arms and grunted. Marik shrugged his shoulders and sat down on a lawn chair next to the picnic table. "If it wasn’t for laughter, I probably would have died when Bakura slit my throat in that shadow game three weeks ago." Complete shock spread over Yami’s face. He vividly remembered watching Bakura slit Marik’s throat, but it seemed too vicious to be reality. "But....but...I thought....I thought that was a horrible dream...We were playing a shadow game?"Yami gasp. Marik looked back at Yami and shook his head. "Pharaoh, I assure you, Bakura’s dark games are very real. You were out cold for an entire week after that shadow game." Yami swallowed hard. Marik’s words sent shivers down his spine. He couldn’t believe he’d been unconscious for an entire week either. "Are you cold?" Marik ask casually, noticing Yami’s quivering form. Yami nodded his head. "A little" he responded as he rubbed his bare shoulders. Marik didn’t need to know he was actually scared shitless thinking about the reality of Bakura’s evil. "Come sit on my lap, I’ll keep you warm" Marik offered with a wink of his eye. Yami rolled his eyes. "I bet" Marik smirked devilishly and waved Yami over. "I’m serious pharaoh, I want you to come over and sit on my lap." Yami looked at Marik quizzically as he got up off the bench and stood infront of his former nemesis. Marik patted his lap. "Right here" Yami gingerly took a seat on Marik’s lap. "Yeah, that’s it" Marik grinned as he protectively wrapped his muscular arms around the pharaoh’s upper body. "Don’t worry, I won’t bite’cha........not yet" he purred into Yami’s ear. Yami bit his lip. He wasn’t quite sure, but he sensed Marik was coming on to him. The way Marik touched him felt so good. He wasn’t being forceful, but he wasn’t playing a submissive role either. The Egyptian’s strong hands caressed Yami’s arms as they moved down his body. "Marik.....what if Bakura returns?" Yami ask nervously. Marik ignored Yami’s question and gently nipped at Yami’s earlobe. His hands wandered under Yami’s towel, feathering the silky smooth skin underneath. Marik wrapped his hand around Yami’s shaft and slowly stroked the sensitive organ. Yami moaned lightly as he felt himself growing very aroused by the soft touch of the other. Marik managed to loosen the towel from Yami’s waist, exposing the pharoah’s naked body to the elements of the night. Yami could feel Marik unbutton his pants and press his hardened arousal up against his lower back. Yami began to tense up. He recalled the savage way Marik had taken him against his will during the first week of his servitude to Bakura. It was one of the most unpleasant sensations he had ever felt. The thought of it sent a wave of fear coursing through his body. "Pharaoh? Is something the matter?" Marik ask in a cracked low voice. Yami closed his eyes and rested his head back on Marik’s shoulder. He shifted his eyes upward and focused on Marik’s face. "I’m a little on edge. I’m sorry." Yami waited nervously for Marik’s response. Two things were possible right now: possibility number one- Marik would get angry and rape him until he couldn’t walk. Possibility number two- Marik would be understanding. By the ambiguous look on Marik’s face, Yami couldn’t tell quite yet. Marik scooped the diminutive pharaoh into his arms and got to his feet. He carried Yami back in through the patio door and into the livingroom, where he laid him on the couch. "Stay put. I’ll be right back" Marik said firmly. Yami waited anxiously for several minutes before Marik finally returned. "I locked all the doors and windows in the house. Can we continue where we left off now?" The Egyptian ask with grin as he sat on the couch. Yami smiled back at him. Maybe Marik wasn’t so bad after all. Yami was about to crawl back onto Marik’s lap when Marik suddenly grabbed him by his hair and pulled him away. "Uh-uh pharaoh.......not so fast." Yami froze in place. His hands began to tremble as Marik gazed into his eyes. "I think you should go on top.......I want to see what you’re like when you’re in action." Marik continued. A big smile spread across Yami’s face. Marik’s willingness to submit to him proved that the Egyptian had definitely changed. For now at least.  ******************* Bakura returned hours later carrying three big shopping bags with the words "Toyz 4 Boyz" written in bold red. He placed the bags next to the couch and glared at Marik and Yami. The two of them had fallen asleep together watching documentary on the history channel about mummification. "Cuddle time is over" Bakura hissed as he pulled a small glass bottle out of one of the bags. Marik got up and sided up to the demonic thief. He rubbed his eyes and focused on the bottle in the thief’s hand. "What’s in that?" he yawned. Bakura handed him the bottle. "It’s Yohimbinum. It will maintain and increase sexual performance in my little pet." "Cool" Marik nodded as he read over the label. Next Bakura pulled out a double rigid iron restraint. Yami swallowed hard as he caught sight of Bakura’s latest investment. "How’s that used?" he whimpered. Bakura smirked evilly. "It holds the captive's wrists firmly in-between his ankles. There is not much room for movement, and in whichever position the captive is being placed, he is certain to stay there." Bakura set the item on the floor and reached into the bag again. Yami’s face went white when the spirit of the ring pulled out the next item and held it up. "This is an electro-charged anal spreader, pretty self explanatory I think" Marik reached into a different bag and started to laugh. He waved a little pack of candy infront of his face, "Pop Rocks? You bought candy, Bakura? Has anybody ever told you that you’re very strange?" Bakura rolled his eyes and pulled out another item from one of the bags. It was a small white box. Marik tossed the candy back into the bag and grabbed for the box in Bakura’s hands. "Gimmie" he said as he started ripping the box open. "Holy shit! I can’t believe you found one!" The blond exclaimed as he held up a remote controlled electroshock collar. Yami gaped at the wicked looking device. "Oh fu-" Before he could finish his sentence, Marik cut him off. He’d already dropped the collar and grabbed another item. "Bakura? Why did you buy whipped cream in a can?" Bakura scowled viciously back at Bakura and slapped his hand. "You’re beginning to get on my nerves." Marik ignored Bakura’s threatening doomgaze and continued snooping around. Yami curled up on the couch and hugged his knees to his chest. He didn’t really want to see what else Bakura had brought home. "Since you are already undressed you’ve saved me some time, runt." Bakura smirked wickedly, electro-shock collar in hand. The thief handed Marik the collar. "Put this on him. We’ll test it out in a bit." Marik took the collar from Bakura and nodded sharply. Yami could tell by the look in Bakura’s eyes that there was only more pain and humiliation ahead. The thief laughed evilly as Marik secured the new collar around Yami’s neck. Next Bakura handed Marik the bottle of Yohimbinum. "Make him drink all of this, I’ll be back in a few minutes. I need to set up the room" Yami and Marik watched Bakura go upstairs. When the thief was out of sight, Marik opened the bottle. "Drinking the entire bottle would be dangerous. You drink half, and I’ll drink half, okay?" Yami nodded his head. "Thank you, Marik." The Egyptian guzzled down half of the liquid and handed the rest to Yami. The two of them waited in silence for Bakura to return. Yami knew whatever the tomb robber was up to, it didn’t spell out anything good. "Pharaoh?" Marik ask quietly. Yami looked up at Marik curiously. "Yes, Marik?" Marik crossed his legs and grinned. "Are you scared?" Yami made a funny face and started to laugh. "Yeah, but it’s turning me on!" Marik looked down between his legs and nodded. "Me too" The aphrodisiac they had consumed had worked itself into their systems quicker than they expected. By the time Bakura returned, Yami had Marik pinned to the floor in the "69" position. His lips wrapped around Marik’s throbbing shaft, and Marik’s around Yami’s. Bakura rolled his eyes. "I’ve seen enough! Gah! Marik, why do you keep fucking this up!" he growled as he grabbed a pillow off the couch and flung it at the horny duo. Yami began to moan loudly as he body convulsed with his release. Yami’s moans sent just the right amount of vibration to Marik’s manhood, causing his release to erupt seconds later. Bakura smirked evilly as he rushed over to Yami and grabbed him my his hair. "Now that you’ve had you’re fun, it’s time for me to have mine. You’re coming with me." Bakura yanked Yami up and started dragging him by his hair toward the staircase. Marik got up to follow, but Bakura froze him in place with the powers of the Millennium Ring. "You’re not invited." the thief hissed as he pulled Yami up the stairs. Bakura shoved Yami into a bedroom and locked the door behind him. He quickly locked Yami into the double rigid iron restraint and stood over him laughing. The pharaoh’s hands and feet were locked securely behind his back in one of the most uncomfortable positions imaginable. Fortunately for Yami he was very flexible. Bakura held up a flogger and cracked it in the air. "You think you’re behavior will go unpunished? I don’t think so! Tonight you’ll experience something so profound, I’m sure you’ll never forget it. Welcome to the world of extreme BDSM, pharaoh! It’s just you and me tonight........no Marik to save you’re scrawny ass! I hope you’re prepared for this......HAHAHAHA!" Yami buried his face in the soft red carpeting on the floor. He took a deep breath before twisting his neck to look over his should at Bakura. "Bring it on! HAHAHA!" Yami boldly laughed back. Bakura lowered his eyes and brought the flogger crashing down on Yami’s exposed backside. Yami was jolted by the unexpected pain, but something Marik had mention stuck in his mind. "Yamis’ like Bakura and I don’t die because we laugh at everything." Yami began to chuckle. To his surprise, the pain seemed to vanish. Bakura struck him again......and again.......and again. Each time Yami laughed harder, only fueling Bakura’s sadistic rage. "We’ll just see how much you’re laughing after I’m through with you. I’m curious, how much pain can you tolerate before I break you’re spirit? My guess is that you’ll be begging me to stop in less than an hour, shall we test my theory?"  

						
</post>
<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Mí Amor, Azul Ojos Dragón Blanco "My Love, Blue Eyes White Dragon" ***** (Heh..long disclaimer......I don’t own "Like a Virgin," "I Remember You," "Don’t Close You’re Eyes," and "Body Talk," Madonna, Skid Row, Kix, and RATT do. I don’t own the Coke company either, but I do own a twelver of the stuff. *cheesy grin* //.......// means the radio is on A/N: My Spanish isn’t perfect, sorry! I ask my Spanish neighbors for help, but they can barely understand English. Not a good combo. LOL) *****  Duke searched everywhere he could think of for Tristan, but came up empty at every corner. He wasn’t extremely worried until the first rays of the sun crept up the horizon. Tristan was always good about calling if he was going to be late, but Duke’s cell phone never rang once. The only radio station coming in somewhat clear was having a marathon of 1980's and early 1990's ongs. If Tristan’s disappearance didn’t drive him insane, hearing "Like a Virgin" again just might. "I Remember You" by Skid Row was on at the moment, and it was coming in crystal clear as Duke drove down a deserted section of highway. A light fog hung just above the road. Duke was trying hard to swallow back his fears, but the song wasn’t help his situation. Duke pulled over to the side of the road and got out of his car. He slammed his fists in the roof of the car. "DAMN IT TRISTAN! Where the fuck are you!" He shouted into the morning air. The only sounds he could hear besides his heavy breathing were birds and the radio. // I paint a picture of the days gone by, when love went blind and you would make me see. I'd stare a lifetime into your eyes. So that I knew that you were there for me, Time after time, you were there for me.  // Duke felt like crying, but he forced himself not to. "Damn hairbands" he growled under his breath as he wiped his eyes and got back in his car. Duke continued to drive down the quiet country road. He was nearing a small town known as Bikuriville. It was a long time rumor around Domino that a ghost haunted the woods that surrounded Bikuriville. "Don’t Close You’re Eyes" by Kix came on the radio just as he drove. // There's no one there to hold you, no one hears your scream You live life up and down, your nightmare's are your dreams .// Duke groaned again as the woods grew darker. "GAH! Domino needs more radio stations...." Just as he got midway through the creepy forest, Duke noticed a light coming from the woods. His first instinct was to stop and check it out, but once he was halfway across the road, a thought hit him. Maybe it was the ghost? Duke stopped dead in his tracks and started twirling his bangs around his index finger. "Owe....fuck.....is there somebody there?" a low, raspy voice croaked from the area of the light. It was definitely a human voice. Duke ran up to the light and let out a relieved sigh. "Tristan!" What the hell happened, man! You crashed my bike!" "Tell me something I don’t know, moron. I’m in pain here, mind getting me to a hospital or calling an ambulance?" Tristan retorted sharply. Duke grabbed his cell phone out of his belt clip and nodded. "Oh, yeah, good idea." Duke’s reception was extremely poor in the woods, so he had to go out into the road to see if the reception was any better. After telling the 911 operator and making sure an ambulance was on the way, Duke looked around. He swore he had heard a baby cry. He didn’t spend much time thinking about it though. He quickly rushed back to Tristan’s side. "So what the hell happened tonight?" He ask curiously. Tristan took a deep breath and let it out slowly. "There was a woman.....she ran out infront of me.......I swerved...." Tristan started coughing and closed his eyes. "Where’s......ambulance." he groaned. Duke cupped Tristan’s bruised cheek with his hand and sighed. "Shh.......they’re on their way." Both men waited in silence for the ambulance. The woods grew lighter as the sun rose into the sky. The ambulance arrived shortly and whisked Tristan to a hospital in Domino. Duke walked back up to his car with plans of following the ambulance. Once again he swore he heard a baby crying. He dismissed the thought and got into his car. "Body Talk" by Ratt was coming in a little fuzzy as the morning fog moved out. // Body talk I know your body talk You make my body talk When you're next to me // Duke rolled his eyes. "Oh great, now I’m horny."  ************************************************* "Sexo caliente en México" Joey recited from a book as Seto, dressed in a black bathrobe, joined him for breakfast. (Hot sex in Mexico) Seto’s hair was sticking up and he had dark circles under his eyes. Saying he looked like crap would be an understatement. His attitude matched how he looked. Joey was sitting in his underwear and had a pair a white socks on. He seemed to be in a decent mood. "Mi perro habla espaZol?" Seto groaned. (My dog speaks spanish?) Joey scrunched up his nose and made a face. "It was the Duelist Kingdom dream again, wasn’t it. The one where Pegasus sealed your soul in a card with Grampa Motou’s. That dream always makes you a crabby bastard in the morning." Seto propped his head up with his hand and groaned. "Don’t bring that up again, got it Wheeler? It was just a rough night, nothing more. By the way, who was it that called earlier?" Joey set down his Spanish book. He looked a little apprehensive. "It was, uh...Yugi." "What did the little geek want?" Seto yawned, not really sounding very interested, as he picked up the newspaper. Joey picked up his book and started flipping through the pages again. "Uh, nothing really. He was just wondering if we would want to come over and see Yami’s kid before they leave for Egypt, or something like that." Seto blew his bangs out of his eyes and laughed. "I still can’t believe the little freak reproduced. Technically speaking, would the freak child be Yugi’s, not Yami’s? Considering the time frame and all?" Joey scratched his head. "Uh.....run that past me again? You lost me right after ‘technically speaking.’" Seto rolled his eyes and stood up. "Think about it. I don’t have time to explain. Mokuba and Noa are suppose to be here at 8 o’clock sharp, so that gives me exactly 17 minutes to grab a shower and get some clothes on." Joey grinned impishly and tossed his book on the table. He got up and grabbed Seto’s arm before he could leave. "I’ll think about it later, right now I’ve got something else on my mind." Seto tried shrugging Joey off of him, but it wasn’t working. "Wheeler, I don’t have time for this. My brothers will be here soon, and I highly doubt they would appreciate walking in and seeing us............ you get the idea." Joey stood infront of Seto and looked up into his big blue eyes. "Every second you keep talking is another second wasted, and Seto Kaiba never wastes time, right? I say you shut up and kiss me." Seto cleared his throat and made a face at Joey. "I’m serious, I don’t have time for....umph!" Joey went in for the kiss before Seto could finish his sentence. "Jo......ey........no.......time....." Joey cupped Seto’s cheeks between his hands and slipped his tongue into Seto’s mouth. Seto moaned lightly as the blond’s tongue explored his mouth. Joey reached under Seto’s black robe and began stroking the CEO’s semi-soft manhood. Seto quick grew hard in Jjoey’s hand and before long was thrusting himself into Joey’s grip. Once Seto was fully erect, he turned Joey around and grinned. "You’re going to regret this, you know." Joey shrugged his shoulders as he stepped out of his underwear. "Try me." he laughed. Seto untied his robe and tossed it on the floor. He noticed a plastic bottle of maple syrup on the table and smirked as he coated his fingers with the sticky substance. "With pleasure......" Seto remarked as he pushed his finger into Joey’s tight heat. Joey let out a small whimper as Seto’s long finger stretched his entrance. Seto added a second finger and than a third. "Oh Dios! Seto! Más!" Joey begged. (Oh God Seto More) Seto withdrew his fingers and obliged Joey’s request. He slowly pressed himself into the blond’s maple syrup coated entrance and gave Joey a minute to adjust. "Esto buena?" Seto grunted as he pushed deeper into the blond. "Yes....love it......Don’t stop, por favor" Joey moaned as he gripped onto the table. Seto slowly began to move in and out of Joey, making sure every stroke sent Joey’s senses over the edge. Seto knew he had to be quick though! He slammed into Joey once he was sure it wouldn’t hurt him. Joey’s eyes got huge from Seto’s sudden burst of energy. At the pace Seto was setting, it didn’t take long before both of them were at their climax. Their bodies shook with their releases. "Mí amor, mí azul ojos dragón blanco" Joey sighed as Seto’s release spilled into him. "Mí amor, mí mal perrito" Seto smirked as he pulled out of Joey and tied his black robe back together. (My love, my bad puppy) Joey picked his underwear up off the floor and smiled up at Seto. "Thanks for taking the time to do that...Even if it was quick, I still loved it." "Time is of the essence, Wheeler. Now I only have 4 minutes to take a shower and get dressed." Seto winked as he walked away. "I’ll make you pay later for holding me up." Joey rolled his eyes and chuckled. "I’ll be waiting." ********************************************** Mokuba rubbed his eyes as he walked out of his bedroom. Morning had came and went and it was now early afternoon. The youngest Kaiba smirked proudly and he strolled casually down the eloquently decorated hallway. Seto would have gone ballistic had he slept in so late living back at Kaiba Corp. Here there was nobody to answer to except himself. Now this was living in luxury. He could do what he wanted, when he wanted, where he wanted to do it, and with whomever he wanted to do it with. It was the perfect life! Nobody telling him what to do anymore and life was good.....almost. Mokuba found himself extremely hungry. //Pizza!// he thought to himself. Mokuba was so preoccupied by his new found total independence and hunger pains that bumped right into Serenity. She was walking backwards out of her bedroom carrying a two baskets of laundry; which of course went flying over her head. Mokuba quickly jumped out and caught one of the baskets, the other over-turned in mid air and landed on his head. Serenity covered her mouth and giggled as she knelt down to help Mokuba out. "Crap. Sorry Serenity! I wasn’t watching where I was going. Hey, where’s Noa at?" Mokuba ask curiously as he sat up and started helping Serenity pick up the clothes. Serenity shrugged her shoulders. "I’m not really sure, he left before I woke up." Mokuba tossed an armload of shirts in the basket, noticing one of them had traces of blood soaked into it. He didn’t pay much attention to it though and tossed it in with the rest of the dirty clothes. "Oh yeah? What time was that at?" he ask. "I got up at 8:30" Serenity replied as she tossed the last sock into the basket. "Hmmm, I wonder where he went." Mokuba mused to himself as he picked the clothes basket up off the floor. "Isn’t there here a servant that takes care of laundry?" Serenity nodded her head. "Yes, but Noa said that if I’m going to live here for free, I have to work it off." Mokuba started to laugh as he followed Serenity down the hall. "Work it off? Nobody but hired help is suppose to work at this house. Maybe what my brother meant was work off by having sex with him." Serenity wanted to tell Mokuba the truth about Noa and his abusive ways, but she just couldn’t bring herself to do it. Noa would be furious if he ever found out! The thought of how upset Noa would be struck fear into her rapidly beating heart. The things he would do to her sent a shiver down her back. Serenity forced herself to laugh along with the youngest Kaiba. "If I sit around on my butt all day I’ll look like Jabba the Hutt! Besides, I like doing nice things for Noa. That’s what girlfriends do, you know." "Only in fairy tales! Every girlfriend I’ve ever had expects me to kiss HER ass! Damn! I must be doing something wrong. Why can’t I find myself a pretty little sweety like you?" Serenity giggled nervously as they walked into the laundry room. The smell of dryer sheets perfumed the air. Mokuba rubbed his nose and sneezed. "WOW! That felt fucking good!" he laughed as he set the basket of clothes down on the table against the wall. Serenity scrunched up her nose and made a silly face at Mokuba. "You’re weird, you know that? It’s hard to imagine you running your brother’s company." Mokuba placed his hand firmly on his hips and shifted his weight to one side. "It’s 49% mine, and if Seto get lynched off by snipers, it’s all mine. I could run that company with my eyes closed." "Is that what you were doing? You slept right through your alarm clock and failed to show up today." Noa chimed in as he passed by. Mokuba smacked himself on the forehead and groaned loudly. "OH SHIT. I bet Seto went ballistic." Noa tossed his black leather briefcase on the table and chuckled. "Not really. I got the distinct impression that he got laid last night. Get this, I saw him SMILE!" Mokuba blinked his eyes a couple of times and cocked his head. "Say what? Seto smiled and I wasn’t there to see it? All the planets aligning up happens more than Seto smiling! Life is so unfair." Noa smirked as he stretched his arms."I could really go for a pizza. Say we all go over to High Roller’s and pay old Dukey and Tristan a visit?" Mokuba nodded his head eagerly. His eyes lit up at the mention of food. "Yeah, that sounds good. Can I drive?" Noa rolled his eyes and laughed. "I don’t care. Just give me a few minutes to change my clothes and we’ll leave. Serenity, mind coming up with me? I need you to help me with something." Serenity closed her eyes and took a deep breath. "Yes, I’ll be up there. I just need to get these in the wash machine." "I’ll do it for you Serenity. I’ll fall over dead if I don’t get some food SOON. I’ll do anything to hurry things up." Mokuba said quickly. Serenity bit her bottom lip. She glanced between Noa and Mokuba and forced herself to smile again. "Uh, okay...thanks, Mokuba." she said softly. Mokuba began tossing clothes into the washer, not paying any attention to their color, and groaned. "Please hurry, I’m about ready to start eating my hand off." "Lovely" Noa chuckled as he pulled Serenity out of the room. ******************************************************* Duke waited around the hospital all day drinking coffee while he waited for Tristan to get fixed up. He’d been awake for over 24 hours straight, and his lack of sleep was catching up with him. The events of the prior night seemed like a dream. Duke still hadn’t seen Tristan since the ambulance had brought him in, and Duke was eager to find out what had caused his significant other to total his motorcycle. By 4 o’clock in the evening the doctor’s had Tristan fixed up. He had a slight concussion, a broken arm, a fractured collar bone and multiple cuts and bruises. Once Duke got Tristan home, they finally got the chance to discuss what had happened. Tristan held an ice pack against his sore head as he laid down in bed. Duke sat on the bed next to him and sighed. "Man Tris, You had me really worried. You can’t imagine the things that go through your mind when someone you love is missing." Tristan reached over and took Duke’s. "I’m sor..."he began. Something felt like it clicked in his head. A clear mental picture of Duke pounding the roof of his car on the verge of tears flashed through his mind. All the pain Duke had felt flooded Tristan’s mind. "..ry? What the hell was that?" he finished. Duke cocked his head. "What was what?" Tristan shook his head and groaned. He was probably having hallucinations from all the drugs that had been pumped into him during the day. "Nothing. I think need to get some sleep." Duke leaned over and kissed Tristan’s cheek. "Okay than. I’ll be bartending with Serenity tonight, so if you need anything, call me." "Okay" Tristan sighed as he began falling asleep. ******************************************************* Yami and Isis walked into the dining room in the back of the tavern and found an open table next to Mokuba, Noa and Serenity. "Hey Yugi! How’s it going?" Mokuba ask loudly. Yami rolled his eyes and sighed. "Do I look like Yugi?" Mokuba stared for a minute at Yami and realized his mistake. "Oh, damn, you’re right.....you always look pissed off. I should have known it was you." The younger Kaiba snickered. Yami looked back at Isis and crossed his arms. "Are you sure you want to eat here? Isis nodded her head. "Yes, I’m sure. I must speak with Duke before I leave this country." Yami turned back to Mokuba and faked a smile. He than picked up the menu laying on the table infront of him and started reading. "I hope Yugi will be okay with Solon." he mused as he pondered what to order. Isis looked up from her menu and chuckled. "Yes, I’m sure Solon and his new "Ma ma" are just fine. Yami rolled his eyes and continued reading the menu. Two more people walked into the dining room and took a seat nearby. Yami happened to glance over at who it was. Seto and Joey. "Shit" Yami growled under his breath. "Ready to order?" Duke ask as he walked up to Yami and Isis’s table. "I think I’ll just have breaded mozzarella sticks and a Coke." "Alrighty, and you?" Duke ask as he turned to Yami’s companion. Isis lowered the menu and bowed her head. "Hello Duke......." she said in a serious tone of voice. "Isis!" Duke gasped as he dropped his pen. ******************************************************* 

						
</post>
</Blog>