<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      After a quite hectic Friday night I decided to head out of the craziness of COM Fest as well as Pride to the Drexel East. Sigh. This was to relax in air conditioning (as my apartment is fan-only) and to see the hyped movie 'Fahrenheit 9/11,' by Mr. Mike Moore.   Thank you, thank you, thank you. I cried, and laughed and cringed. I am thankful that someone has that much drive to give the American people a lesson on the reality of democracy and government.   In regards to this drama filled weekend I would like to say that some people never change. The cheaters continue to cheat while the leeches continue to suck. Upsetting. Oh well, at least I only have to see them once a year. 
     

    
</post>
<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Work is good - although this ‘blogging’ may become a bad habit. Something to keep an eye on during the 9-5 hours.  I would like to thank Tracie for bringing the Wal-Mart story to my attention. I would also like to congratulate her on reaching me before NPR did. Quite impressive!   I still do not quite understand this lack of equal rights (in this instance it is represented through a monetary value) when comparing men and women. I don't vow to be an intense feminist who achieves joy through a cacophony of statistics and chants, but I do believe in equal rights. As a woman I have never thought that I was lesser than my male counterparts. Yet, upon entering the architecture field I am becoming more aware of these ‘Good olde boy’s’ clubs and other such underground male business organizations.   But – I also have noticed this discrimination within the female community against other females. Eg. I was at a site last week doing some field verifications with a tape measure and a woman walked up to me and asked if I was making new drapery for them. Now, just because I have a tape measure and am wearing a skirt does not mean that I cover windows with dancing floral patterns. I find this sad.   Back to work.  Also for those unaware: Tracie's blog is - http://www.livejournal.com/users/tmz438/  Check it out - she's a smart political girl! 
     

    
</post>
<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Sigh. After many months of putting off the task of publishing my life I have decided to join the ranks of political activists as well as idiotic twelve year old kids.  I am not quite sure what this will achieve world peace or stop the war in Iraq but I suppose it becomes another way to express guilt, happiness as well as frustration publicly. I cannot think of a better way to be passive agressive. How thrilling.  My sudden desire to partake in this current pet-rock-like fad is that due to a lack of self control in the copy cat mentality. Tracie, a good friend from the back 'home', Chagrin area has, just joined the fad too. I am quite naturally jelous of Tracie and her vicous post against the Wal-Mart that I have decided to create what you could call a Blog-Editorial on her posts. Hell, everyone needs an editor. Get ready Tracie - this will be fun!  I will be selfish also writing about my own worldly concerns. So, sit back and fall asleep as the everyday and mundane becomes spelled out to the point of exhaustion! 
     

    
</post>
<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I found this on another blog and just had to put a link to it....    urlLink http://www.veryverygay.com/elijahwood/ewivvg.html  
     

    
</post>
<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    A hott picture of Joe and I at an undisclosed location... ok, ok - it's the new school of Architecture.  Posted by  urlLink Hello  
     

    
</post>
<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This weekend was packed with many mixed events. Due to the plethora of activities I learned a lesson that I never knew existed. This shocked me greatly as I generally am told or aware of the lessons that are available to learn. We learn to blow out candles before we leave our apartment, we learn to not whistle in public as it is not a very ‘lady-like’ thing to do and we learn to curtsy in front of royalty. Yet, I never knew that I could be very bad at something and still enjoy it immensely.   I always thought that we enjoyed what we were naturally gifted at. I suppose I confused the idea of pride with enjoyment in that I took pride in my accomplishments because I was good at them and naturally excelled. For example; you enjoy playing a trumpet because you can play Taps and people recognize the tune. I on the other hand realized that I love to dance and am incredibly bad at it. I am not a budding young gay boy who can exclaim his emotions with the thrust of a leg or arm – I am a bad dancer that loves to move regardless of the ramifications and misunderstandings of my jolting and hopping.   So what are you doing next weekend? Want to meet at the nearest club?  
     

    
</post>
<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         I just returned from close to a day spent at O.U. Yes, it was an executive road trip. It was moments like today that I love my job. I got to root around the attic of Ellis Hall as well as walk around the roof and decipher visual clues as to why things are failing and leaking. I like to think of it as a combination of Architect, Archeologist and Detective. Ok, ok – so it’s not the same as solving who stole the peanut butter, but the roof is leaking for a reason. It was fun, even though the building is a structural mess and will be a bitch to deal with. Hopefully we can sort it out and restore it to it’s original prestige. Red clay tiles and all!                So it is     5:08     and I have only been in the office for an hour or two. Not bad! I love it when days fly by.                 Next week is my 23 rd  birthday. There is no real cultural significance of turning 23 other than maybe equating it somehow to your 21 st  birthday. An example of this could be, “Happy 23 rd  Birthday – You have been legally able to drink for two years in the     U.S.    ” or “Congrats, you’re more of an adult than you previously were.” Regardless, nothing has changed other than the distance I am to crow’s feet. But, on the other hand I feel that I have accomplished quite a lot within the last year.                -         I have graduated from OSU with a degree in Architecture.                -         Became a Vegetarian (except last week when I accidentally ate chicken at Happy Greek.)                -         Went from Staples employee – Admin. Asst – Graduate Architect within the space of 5 months during a bad economy.                -         Got a new car.                -         Moved in to my own apartment.                -         Started working out religiously and being as healthy as I can (minus the smoking.)                -         Read a lot – Atlas Shrugged and Fountainhead (the two largest accomplishments.)                All in all I am pretty happy about things. Hopefully they will keep on going well for the next year and the years to come, as we only get older, slower and shorter.                Now – a decision to make – go drinking at Larry’s or go to swim practice? Hmmmmm…..    
     

    
</post>
<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
                              After quite the hectic and crazy weekend that we all had I am back at the work station and slower than ever.                 The weekend was packed with fun including a hott party on Miranova’s 18 th  floor with an untouchable view of the fireworks. Thanks goes out to Sky for throwing the great party and giving me a reason to dress up and look good. As for the rest of the weekend, well it was good – especially the part where a friend was whipped and paddled in front of a large crowd. Any more of this craziness would have been invalid.                 So here I am sitting in front of the Ohio Book of Building codes trying to figure out the ‘Occupant Load Actual’ after three days of fun and games. As a result my normal motivation is considerably lacking and it has harmonized itself without standard time.                 Joe and I managed to sneak in a photo shoot at an undisclosed location and came away with some great shots. I am quite happy with them and hopefully will publish a couple on here.                 Regarding the rave review I had given last week about a swim practice I had attended – well, I attended practice number two last night and left with another great feeling of accomplishment. A swim meet is coming up in October and gives me a potential goal to reach. I have no doubt in my training and swimming abilities to be ready for the meet (it’s in     Ft.   Lauderdale    ,     FL    ) but meets in general have always terrified me. The nerves beforehand become uncontrollable to the point of nausea and shaking. Is it worth putting myself though the turmoil for a sense of accomplishment? Or should I just focus on the immediate health benefits I receive from swimming regularly? It’s something to ponder for the next few months or so.                      
</post>
<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
                                   Yawn… oh lordy. Why oh why do I continue to have fun on a weeknight?! I went to Skully’s last night and had more than a good time. I don’t regret it - although leaving at       1am       wasted from a club with work the next day isn’t too smart. There was a great group of people there, lots of drinking and dancing… who hoo.          I can’t really function too well – sentences are tough to correspond.           It’s noon – Hopefully I’ll be out of here in no time – out to lunch which will take around an hour and a half and then a couple more hours of work…….. poopy.      
</post>
<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It is 10am and I am the only one here at work. A pleasant way to start the morning off.  Yesterday, after a long, drawn out day of drafting (or as I like to call it vector data entry) I decided to make the most of a perfect summer evening and partake in an outdoor swim team practice.   I had no idea how much I could love it again! After being physically and mentally abused by unforgiving high school coaches I thought that the idea of swimming and enjoyment could not coincide in the same phrase. Wrong. The drive it takes to swim during timed exercises is beyond personal choice. The endurance and effort promoted is only something that can be emitted by having a fitter and faster teammate slapping your feet due to your weak arms and burning lungs. After the hour long rush is over it then takes your last drop of adrenaline to actually hoist yourself out of the pool and find your safe warm towel.   I have decided to seriously reconsider routinely swimming on a team. Sure it is $5 a practice, but when you equate that to a couple of glasses of wine at the Burgundy Room is seems quite menial.  Overall, I feel great today even though I didn't make it to the gym this morning. The swim practice high is still resounding with me over 12 hours later. Not too bad for five bucks.  
     

    
</post>
<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
                                  After months of trying to put it off – I finally bought tickets for Sarah McLachlan in two weeks. This will be the 5 th  time I have seen her in concert. Could my lesbianism be showing through here? Regardless, I am very excited. I hope that she sings ‘Vox.’ That has to be my favorite song ever by her.                 Back to work – I am plotting out the final sheets for a project. Yay, I am so glad that it is done!      
</post>
<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
                                  So, everytime I sit down to blog my boss comes in and decides to check my drawings etc. This generally ends in AutoCAD v. 14 not working correctly (not surprising since the world is now on V. 2005) resulting in us hunting all around the computer for an answer. This of course means that I have to quickly close any blog that I am writing with the erasure of a half processed thought and statement. Quite frustrating!!                I suppose that I could always dive into the cold water and just publish them without spell checking, and rereading my thoughts… but who wants to read something sporadic? I have never been into free verse.                Well, I think that Todd (boss) will be coming soon. Better edit it before I can’t!     
</post>
<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
                                   I have been listening to BBC Radio 4 all day. The stations subtitle is that of ‘Intelligent Speech.’ Who wouldn’t want to listen to that? I am obsessed with a show called “in our time,” by Melvin Bragg. He is quite good at carrying on an interesting, in depth conversation with people who are at the top of their fields while making himself sound like he knows what he is talking about. It is very good.                     I always wonder why I have to listen to foreign radio to get a good show to listen to.                     Regardless, I listened to a show about Proust. When these college professors and literature intellects talked about his 3000 page text they made it sound great. So I have decided that this is my new goal – after I finish my Nevil Shute novel. I can’t wait.                    Apparently Proust writes about memory and the different ways we process/don’t process moments. For example, if we can’t remember what happened a couple of years ago then maybe we are also unable to remember events from other lives and worlds. Fascinating. So, if we do remember an event then maybe some of our random thoughts could have happened also.                     Something to cogitate.      
</post>
</Blog>