<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Today was awesome day. To start my day off, I woke up at 7:00 to clean my room. It actually took me 3 1/2 hours to clean it. Then I got ready and walked to the high school to pick up Dan Shyles at 11:30. We watched Disturbing Behavior, hung out in my room listening to music, and walked to Rita's.  Here comes the only bad part of my day. I was forced to go on a walk with CJ and her friend Chelsea. With them being how they are, it was really nasty. They were really huggy and tickled each other a lot. I got over it with paying attention to the passing cars....and the guys driving them.  Here comes the really good part. I went over to Mike's house since I promised Becca that I'd come over. Mike and I decided to go on a walk. I told him everything, and were friends again! YAY! He's even talking to me on the computer again!  All in all, it was a wonderful day. Tomorrow is off to work again. At least its only a 4 hour day. Then to Dann's house to talk to his mom. That will be all for now. Lots of love. 
    
</post>
<date>22,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Let's start with last night. I was outside making Swirl(my hermit crab) a ladder to climb on. Meaghan saw me and when I was done I went down to her house. By the way, that would be Mike's house too. He didnt know I was there, only knew that David wanted him to come out. Not really, it was all me. He saw me, and didnt say a word, the whole night. If I was on the porch, he went over to David's house. If I was over there, then he went to his house. I was going to talk to him, but I was afraid to. So, I got nowhere last night. Besides his other sister, Becca, knowing everything. Do you really hate me that much Mike? Why? Fuck. I'm gonna start crying. Listening to "So" by Static-X isnt helping much either.  Today was a 8 hour work day, 11-7. It was so dead I was sitting in the back room for hours. Easy 40 bucks though. Great thing was that I sold $100.75 in product today. Michele, the other receptionist, is happy to get that in a week! Tracy D., the assistant manager, had me take out her client's foils then wash her hair. It's only the first day into my second week and I've already washed someone's hair! Michele has been working for over a month and she hasnt gotten to yet. I feel special kind of :)  Once I was done my shift, Ashley was going to dye my hair, but it picked up a lot so she didnt have time. I was hoping she would since Dan is coming over tomorrow, I wanted him to see it. We're screwed, as in my mom, brother, and I. My father cant pay the rent, Meenan Oil, Peco, or Verizon. So, our landlord is taking us to court and we may be evicted. Fun, aint it?  Oh, and this girl that I never want to talk to,(long story, dont ask), is trying to talk to me again. She wants me to go on a walk with her tomorrow. Usually, if I want to go on a walk, I actually like to ENJOY it.  Dan Shyles is coming over tomorrow to watch a movie....this should be interesting.  Dude, I think I'm going to have to make my "list" again. This should be tons of fun. Why must being 14 suck so badly? </post></Blog>