<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      weee walllked down the streeet my heart you would sttteall.  hello! or shall I say, "HOLA!" i'm talking to Jenna, my old old friend. we used to be best friends, and we drifted. well, she decided it would be cool to ditch me. saaame thing. anyway, she told me that you don't realize who you are until you hang out with different people, which i guess is pretty true. i never realized. hhmh, something to think about. tonight was pretty fun fun. went to the D ST meeting, always a good time. We've been to nearly 5 or 6. Best one is when we all walked to mcdonalds. can't beat that. Jimmy was there, which is a rare rare thing. Dan and Augie were there too. We mostly talked to Tasha and Aaron, got to know them better. I knew Tasha before, but they are really awesome.    hello my name is your TV   after all THAT fun was over, me, hill, and lauren went to lauren's hizzouse. we were so bored that we played Sims on her brother's play station 2. we made a lesbian couple, they fell in love. ahhhh, computer graphics in love. at least SOMEONE is getting some. anyway, i'm tired. i should go to bed. much love you.      
      
</post>
<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      all meaning....no one. since i just created this masterpiece i like to call my 5th online diary. yes. my fifth. i found a picture of my brother today. one of him making this face he did all vacation. i think i was in fifth grade. good memories. i saw Dodgeball today, what a movie. what.a.movie. i laughed quite a bit. i find stupid humor like that hilarious. just my quirky sense of humor. no one gets it except for lauren and occasionally liz. I think Cheap Seats on ESPN classic is the greatest television show ever, (next to Bug Juice (you know the show on disney about kids at summer camp) and i made my mom watch it with me one time, she laughed like once. while me, i was laughing hysterically.    crash into me, baby.   it feels good to be home. the fire just sucked, being out of the house for that long was ungodly. i don't think i could handle like being in a band, going on tour. never being in the same place twice. or like my sister, she lives in Alaska for christ sake. well, i guess that how it is, you go into the Air Force, you get stationed places that suck. Alaska, on that last. Woot! I haven't even talked to her since Mother's Day, which is not cool at all. I need to call her, tommorow sounds good. Tommorow also equal D street team meeting, yeehaw! I hope it's not like packed, it usually isn't but it's at 7 (which is later) and all the college kids are home. Whoopty Wah. it's almost three, i should go to bed. later kids.  </post></Blog>