<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Good weather today... this morning when i was out of the house on my way to sch... i thought to myself, wad a nice day, im not gonna let anything spoil my day. It reminded me of Hong Kong... really.... the weather there when i last went back was exactly like this... except that it was much colder and comfortable. Man i missed that place... hope i can go back soon. My mom promised to go back with sis and me after my alevels... so happy... at least i have something to look forward to after Alevels.  Hmmm.... i really dun like ppl who like to compare ppl. I think that everyone is unique in their own ways... can't compare. Im who im... i can't change!!! Damn... this really spoil my day. And do i get angry easily? No lor... i dun. Wadever lah.  Today suck. 
      
</post>
<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Here's a pic of Raul... he's advistising for Pepsi  in Europe area... and gez wad... F4 is advistising for Pepsi too =D urlLink   
      
</post>
<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Orh... just got to noe from chih chwen that Portugal beat England in penalties. Argh!!! Not that i support England, they're not bad... Rooney is good... but Portugal can't win!!! Coz i hate them for kicking Spain out in the group stage. Orh...... when spain got out... i was sooo depressed, they're suppose to be good, better than Greece at least. But frankly, they suck... they played so badly in their matches lor... and Raul played badly as well. Actually the reason why i support spain is becoz of him... hahaha coz i think he's very handsome and good!!! Yah but he's not in form recently... dunno why... never scored for soooo long already. The newspapers were all criticising him... feel sad for him... but i think it's his fault ah... perhaps he doesn't make a good captain. U see... he is Real Madrid captain, and Real Madrid is not doing very well... and now Spain team. Orh... i think he should just stick to his role of being a forward... get someone else to be the captain. Then he can just concentrate in scoring goals.   Yay... that's wad i think ah... hehe=) eh... didn't noe it's quarter finals already eh... coz i kinda lost interest in euro after spain got out. Hmmm but i think last night's match portugal against england was exciting since it got to the penalty stage to decide who will get through. haha. Maybe i'll just watch the finals... yeah... that's after CTs... hahah... 
      
</post>
<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Windstruck 2 urlLink   
      
</post>
<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Whoo... i finally noe how to ppost pic! yay... here's one more =D urlLink   
      
</post>
<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Windstruck urlLink   
      
</post>
<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I recently watched a MTV of a korean song... dunno wad's the song title though... not sure if the song is called kiss or the group that sang it is kiss. Okay wadever. Anyway... it's super nice and sad and touching. It makes ppl cry like hell. Maybe u all wud have heard of the story... it's about this guy and girl who love each other,,, and this guy is some photographer... then one day the girl accidentally spilled some acid (apparently used to develop photos) on her eyes... and lost her vision. Wad that guy did was to donate his eyes to her, so he himself became blind. Hur... so sad rite??? The worse thing is that he left the girl without saying anything after giving her his eyes. Soooo touching, Sobsob. Wonder if such a thing will really happen in real life... dun think so hur... i dun believe someone will actually be so wei da enough. but who noes? Haha. I still feel very sad whenever i think of the MTV now... plus the song is sooo nice... im sure my sis will agree with me... haha coz she cried when she watched it in her office... haha...  Orh... and there's a new Korean movie coming up... Ye Man Shi Jie(Windstruck). Oh i cannot wait to watch it... it's supposed to be the sequel to My Sassy Girl. And My Sassy Girl was super nice... very touching too... and i think the girl is super pretty... =) Argh okay i'll wait till after common test... im so jealous coz my sis is gonna watch it on saturday... =P  Okie... think i'll post pics of the girl when if figure out how to...... she's really very pretty... =)   Oh!!! Gez wad... I saw Pan WeiBo on TVee yesterday on Showbiz. He's publishing a new book... not sure wad it's about though. Cool... he's look sooo cute on tv... =) but he look nicer in real life! hahaha... hmmm he got this new hairstyle different from he's Microphone album hairstyle... hmmm look nice for a change... hehe... look more mature. hahahah!!! Wonder when the book is gonna come out in Spore? 
      
</post>
<date>24,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Oh i cannot believe it... i actually started a blog! Haha... seems quite fun yar... so i got myself one too.  Hahahaha... hmmm... i wanna complain ah... my holidays suck! The thought of having common test when sch reopen makes me sick. my revision is going suuuper ultra SLOW!  Slack too much at home lah... Now that i got SCV... keep switching on the TV, coz it's so tempting... but it makes me really happy when i see Zaizai and Will Pan on TV! hahah Yay!  So... revision at home is a bad idea... haha... but too lazy to go out, =P Getting worried... wad else, becoz of CTs!!! Argh... let me seee... friday, sat, and sunday, 3 more days to go...   OKay... gotta take my doggie for a walk... Argh... she's making noise again... she always does that when she needs to go do her buisness... haha... she simply refuses to shit on the newspaper... Well... she's so obedient rite? haha... 
      
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Here's the poster for Wilbur Pan and Zhang Shan Wei concert in August. =D Cool Pan weibo is sooo cute haha urlLink   
      
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Haha... common tests finally over... im glad... although i dun really feel anything. There's still school next week. Argh... at least i survived ct. Maths was the most terrible paper okie... one hour after the paper started i was still at question 3... and i have problem with almost every questions. Damn... this is bad lor... i think i lost about 35 marks... so an A is impossible already. Ah nvm lar... my maths is lousy anyway. =D  And today's Bio S was bad too... well but better than i expected lah. At least i have something to write, although i dunno wad i was writing most of the time. Bleah... haha. I was damn stressed whenever i looked at joseph lor. He was like next to me and he's writing so much. hur... damn pro. haha...I was trying so hard not to fall asleep. So many times i just feel like dropping my head and sleep! Damn tiring man... it was 2.5 hours. but at the end of the paper i was energetic again... Woohoo... Went shopping with Audrey later on... at orchard. We were talking about our sec school times... haha so funny. We laughed and laughed... make me so happy. Haha. Hmmm yeah then we shopped and shopped and shopped. Orh actually i wanna watch windstruck... but they only show it at lido at seven... arh... audrey has sch tml so i think i better not let her stay out so late. Hmmm nvm monday is Youth Day! Yay! I'll get her to watch it with me then.   Whoo hoo... Yeah... I shall make plans on wad to do for the next few days. I just realised i've got this bio s essay on cloning due next week. i'll just hurry up and finish it so i can go play!!!!!
      
</post>
<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    I found my motivation... that's wilbur pan. Really... everytime i see him i feel so alive... haha... it means something to me lar... keeps me going. Hahah very silly rite?  urlLink   
      
</post>
<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I realise i really have no more time already... just 6 more weeks to prelims practical exams and 8 more weeks to prelims!!! Man... this is bad lor... i think i cannot take it. I still have like super more to revise on, and judging from my common test results, i need alot more of that!!!  Damn sad, depressed, disappointed... bleah. My results are really bad. It's the worst since all my previous CTs... hmmm i dunno wad's wrong lah... i think i studied the most this time. Im super free during the holidays lar, stay at home qiao jiao everyday... haha, so there's really no reason for doing badly. But i REALLY dunno wad's wrong ah... i got back my chem paper, i nearly died of shock. 49 marks. Man i cannot believe it lar... later managed to find one more mark to add up to 50. Still bad eh??? Ay dun talk about math and phy, so much bloody careless mistakes... argh #%*@%#  Okie... bio and gp left, oh i am not sure if i can take it =P I MUST do something about it... i must aim for better, much better grades for prelims, if not i'll rather die. I must start planning... yar... reduce slacking time, computer and tv time......  I really feel like dropping s papers... my alevels results already suck... not fit to do spapers i gez. Not like i'll stand any chance of getting scholarship. Man... sigh.  I need to MUG... man... got many more bio essays to complete lar... damn stressed... okay i shall take it lightly...   ~~Mugger
      
</post>
<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      HahAha =D =D =D =D =D TK become autonomous!!! haha... very happy!!! =D =D =D =D =D really very happy... i was from there okie? Hee. Har... it really was an achievement for the school. =D =D =D sooo happy. Yay... TK Rox!!! 
      
</post>
<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The time now is 09:59... YuP... didn't want to do hw so came here to write something. Hmmm... life is back to normal hur... normal lessons resumed and all... Heh...   Monday was Youth Day... went out with Audrey. We wanted to catch Windstruck lor, but it was full-housed!! Orh i was soooo disappointed. I really wanna watch it =( We went to suntec quite late ah... and i met linlin there! Hahah she was catching that movie too... she said it was nicer than Sassy Girl. Oh man... how i wished i have watched it. Hmmm, so audrey and i walked around suntec and city link, then went for steamboat buffet at suntec conventional hall there. We were trying it for the first time... haha steamboat is always fun and the food is quite nice.   Then today went shopping at orchard with Sis and Xiachao. Today is wed, school ends super early now since cca stopped already. Hmmm... Mango got sale... but didn't get anything. My sis only got herself a zebra-like top... haha... very nice =D  Felt kinda guilty for spending the whole afternoon out. Argh... i'll go do some work now... tata! =)
      
</post>
<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        雨淋湿了世界 你站在我面前 爱得太深太想要    你的温度给我依靠 却不能要     放弃了也许才看得到 我从不是你的骄傲     我走进后乐园中 那迷失的一角 再一步就能触碰你的心跳    当我们以为的爱 不是一种荣耀 再深的爱也这样 失去了    你还在我身边 但我突然发觉     我们之间的画面只会变得越来越浅 不够永远     用生命也许才换得到一次机会深刻拥抱    我走进后乐园中   那迷失的一角 再一步就能触碰你的心跳     我努力往前奔跑直到天涯海角 却发现还到不了…    在我的后乐园中谁是我的依靠   我相信总有一天我会找到    用我的心去感受拥有爱的美好     我愿意世界为你 就这样 静止了…    
      
</post>
<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
         The week's finally over... I've been waiting so miserably for weekends. Dun like going to school... feel so stupid there .  Hur... sometimes realy feel like dying than to be in school. My results are bad. These few days are so depressing... feel very weak, coz i think i cried the most times these few days... feel like a water pipe lar, and somemore... aiya... forget it... gez that's too personal.     tsk tsk tsk... im too depressed to study lar. =( i need some sort of consolation?!?! I dunno wad i need lar... something to brighten me up. NOthing. NOThing. NOTHing.       =~~*Whereare u*~~=  
      
</post>
<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       回忆里想起模糊的小时候 云朵漂浮在蓝蓝的天空 那时候的你说 要和我手牵手  一起走到时间的尽头 从此以后我都不想抬头看 仿佛我的天空失去了颜色 从那一天起 我忘记了呼吸  眼泪啊永远不再不再哭泣  我们的爱 过了就不再回来 直到现在我还默默的等待  我们的爱 我明白 以变成你的负担 只是永远 我都放不开  最后的温暖 你给的温暖  不要再问你是否爱我  现在我想要自由的天空 远离开这被捆绑的世界  不再寂寞   ~~FIR 
      
</post>
<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>
</post>
<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      用我的晚安陪你 吃早餐  记得把想念存进扑满  我 望着满天星在闪  听牛郎对织女说要勇敢   别怕我们在地球的两端  看我的问候骑着魔毯  飞 用光速飞到 你面前  要你能看到十字星有北极星作伴   少了我的手臂当枕头 你习不习惯  你的望远镜望不到我北半球的孤单  太平洋的潮水跟着地球来回旋转  我会耐心地等 随时欢迎你靠岸   少了我的怀抱当暖炉 你习不习惯  E给你照片看不到我北半球的孤单  世界再大两颗真心就能 互相取暖  想念不会偷懒  我的梦通通给你保管  
      
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       喜欢用我的音调 唱出你的味道    这一秒 有种感觉甜蜜的发酵    一百种言语知道 爱有一个声道    才明了是你眼神传来的暗号        太多的幸福报到 拼凑爱的美妙    笑一笑 投入你怀里然后撒娇    不需要别人来教 把爱紧紧抓牢    这一秒 决定拥抱你给的美好        爱情是你独特的味道    在我的心中围绕    别人都不了只有你知道    因为你 世界不再单调    我的微笑 你明白就很好        你就像月亮绕着轨道    拥抱着地球闪耀在我的星球    写下惊叹号    有了你世界神魂颠倒    你的微笑 编织了每一个奇妙    
      
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      today. At least i think so...  i feel sooo happy...  It's a good thing to make ppl happy... yah... i wish i can make someone happy... =D 
      
</post>
<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I think i know the reason to my bad results... i just cannot concentrate these days... suck 
      
</post>
<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hur... bio s bio s bio s bio ass... suck big time! 
      
</post>
<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>
</post>
<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    Windstruck....... urlLink   
      
</post>
<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Lydia 迷离的眼眶  为何流浪 心碎的海洋   受了伤 连微笑都彷徨  Gypsin女郎 为谁而唱   你会看见雾 看见云 看见太阳  纪念和大地重复着悲伤   *他走了带不走你的天堂  风干后会留下彩虹泪光  他走了你可以把梦留下  总会有个地方 等待爱飞翔   Lydia 幸福不在远方  开一扇窗 许下愿望   你会感受爱 感受恨 感受原谅  生命总不会只充满悲伤  
      
</post>
<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Hmmm.... a nice day. Went back college for seniors' farewell. I love my section man... they're the best. My lao gong... my zhu ren... and my little baby ants... haha... they're simply the best. Feel very sad to leave them actually... but tian xia wu bu san de yan xi. I'll miss them!!! Haha...   1st chro rox... harmoc rules...   I went mad yesterday again... haha... very long nvr turn mad already... feel very happy after that =D       Then later rushed off to the Singapore Symphonic Orchestra concert at Esplanade... met up with eve and celeste and we kinda ran there... well... not really... coz the two ladies were wearing heels. Haha... for the first time i walked faster... haha. Anyway the concert was good... yar... this is the first time i went for concert at esplanade. The theatre is damn nice. Well... i saw it before in photos and all, but it's just different being really there. I was so fascinated when i stepped in... haha. And i was marvelled by the orchestra... they're good...    The concert ended at about ten, then we went for supper at Haagen Diaz... okay... expensive supper... but nice lar. haha... we took some photos like xiao zha bo-s... haha! Reached home nearly twelve... yar... bathed and went to sleep... 
      
</post>
<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Your element is Light: Innocent, beautiful, kind-hearted and pure. You are so sweet your almost angelic, you find joy in others happiness and cannot stand to see anyone in pain. You want to make everyone around you feel good about themselves and if someone is upset you can tend to become rather upset as well which means you are sympathetic and raise others above yourself. Being as kind and good-natured as you are people have most likely hurt you in the past but you pick yourself up every time. You may look fragile but you are stronger than most tend to see. Life is beautiful no matter how you look at it and you understand that people make mistakes, not everyone is perfect. You try to see the good in the bad which is a talent few posses, dont ever let anyone change you. You truly have a beautiful soul inside and a heart of gold. 
      
</post>
<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It's friday!!! Yay... friday is a slack day... lessons in sch very short, but gotta stay till 5 for bio s.   One more month to prelims... to death lar. Yeah... scared... very scared... *concentrate *concentrate... Thats wad i need most now... Concentration!!!  Im suppose to feel sad given the situation im in... but im not... not as much... haha. How come.??? hahaz... the things i say all very vague hor. haha  
      
</post>
<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      im whineyand flingsmy arms around too much hur.  Really... is that really the case?  Hur... fine, i have nothing to say.  No point being so nice also... this is wad i get... being referred to as irritating.  This is lousy!   
      
</post>
<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       I realised how vulnerable the human heart is to... hmmm external factors. At least mine is.   I am starting to feel sick, tired, wanna give up...       Ren shi shang bian de...      I really think so...   
      
</post>
<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Sigh... i very long nvr blog already... im in a state of burning out... i feel like im wasting every single day now... going to school, staying back in the library till eight thirty until daddy come fetch me home...  then eat dinner, bath... and go do more work. The worst thing is that no matter how much i do my work... they nvr seem to end. Argh... sooo scary leh. Sian... Tired lar. I was so tired on thursday... so i decided to go home and sleep. Friday was cool... national day celebration... the performance was nice... i always like watching such things... sooo cool. And terra won the NE trophy... terra was champion! Haha... we are not the last anymore... wah everyone were like sooo high lor... esp the guys in the class... the girls too... haha... damn fun. very funny lar... to see the guys singing so loudly... carrying linlin around during the interhouse game... haha... i almost fainted. hahaha...      Today is like another wasted day lar... went to cut my hair... eh didn't actually want it to be this short. I just wanna trim it... but it turned out... like this. Okay lar... i shall not complain... the lady boss who cut my hair is really nice... talked to me and asked about my life and all... sobz... no one actually bother asking me this question recently lor.       Watched windstruck already.   Finally. Nice. Very sweet. Very sad. The girl is so chio. The guy is quite handsome too.   But i still prefer my sassy girl. Haha...       Long weekend... one day is almost over... three more days... lalala... can't play... so sad... must mug... bleah...      Zhou Jie Lun's Qi Li Xiang is sooo nice lar... sooo sweet... =D   
      
</post>
<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      窗外的麻雀 在电线杆上多嘴 你说这一句 很有夏天的感觉 手中的铅笔 在纸上来来回回 我用几行字形容你是我的谁  秋刀鱼 的滋味 猫跟你都想了解 初恋的香味就这样被我们寻回 那温暖 的阳光 像刚摘的鲜艳草莓 你说你舍不得吃掉这一种感觉  雨下整夜 我的爱溢出就像雨水 院子落叶 跟我的思念厚厚一迭 几句是非 也无法将我的热情冷却 你出现在我诗的每一页  雨下整夜 我的爱溢出就像雨水 窗台蝴蝶 像诗里纷飞的美丽章节 我接着写 把永远爱你写进诗的结尾 你是我唯一想要的了解  那饱满 的稻穗 幸福了这个季节 而你的脸颊像田里熟透的蕃茄 你突然 对我说 七里香的名字很美 我此刻却只想亲吻你倔强的嘴  
      
</post>
<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       翻着我们的照片 想念若隐若现   去年的冬天 我们笑得很甜      看着你哭泣的脸 对着我说再见   来不及听见 你已走得很远      也许你已经放弃我 也许已经很难回头   我知道自己错过 请再给我一个理由说你不爱我       就算是我不懂 能不能原谅我   请不要把分手当作你的请求   我知道坚持要走是你受伤的藉口   请你回头 我会陪你一直走到最后   就算没有结果 我也能够随   我知道你的痛 是我给的承诺   你说给过我纵容 沉默是因为包容   如果要走 请你记得我       如果难过 请你忘了我   
      
</post>
<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I kinda waste the whole day away today... tried to revise on medical biotech... realised nothing gets into my head... okie... i give up... decided to go and write my testimonial which i gotta hand in soon if i wanna apply for australian universities.  I was watching TV while trying to brainstorm about every single thing i've done in nj... er... actually i really got not much achievements to mention... so i just write down every little thing that came to my mind. Man i feel damn bhb writing my own testimonial... i mean u gotta praise urself rite... i can't be writing stuffs like im mad or stupid or things like that... haha! Although i really have the urge to write im mad... coz i think i really am! Haha...  And i actually spent the whole afternoon doing this... at least i managed to type it on the com... well... i hope mr ong will accept it or something. My english is very lousy. Hmmm... watched NDP just now... man i really like the fireworks... they are so nice... so pretty. Haha... =) Im supposed to go watch it with a friend. But well... decided not to... coz will be very crowded and all... somemore i got family dinner at home. Yeah... next year maybe.  Fireworks are really so nice lor... they just come and go... yeah... hao jing bu chang zai... eh... yeah. haha...  Okie... i've to spend tml meaningfully... tsktsktsk... two more weeks to death.  
      
</post>
</Blog>