<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So yesterday I smoked Shisha (a.k.a. hookah a.k.a. water pipe) for the first time. It was an unplanned event entirely. A bunch of us went out to see Fahrenheit 9/11 and then wanted to go to Zen Cha, but it was closed. So next best thing? The Shi Sha lounge on High St. I've never smoked anything before, but since I know its really watered down tobacco, I admit, I have always been a little curious about shisha. It was rose flavored to boot, and the pipe (someone said its also called a bong, but I thought a bong was the smaller kind of pipe, whatever) was really pretty, so I tried it. Donny kept laughing at me when the smoke made it mostly out of my nose and the rest came out my mouth. Apparently I didn't smoke properly. But I did smoke a lot. I was in between Scott and Oren, so each time they passed the pipe back, I got another hit. Smoking twice as much as either of the guys didn't make a difference though. There was no buzz, no sting, no coughing. I think I would definitely do it again given the right group of people and a good flavor. And no, its not my gateway to more nicotine. I hate cigarette and cigar smoke. Its too acrid. I wonder though if the Smoke Free Columbus deal applies to Shi Sha. Especially since its a really weak smoke. I guess I wouldn't miss it if it did. Glad I tried though. 
      
</post>
<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm cooking for the mudphud dinner tonight and it smells like turkey in here.   Aside from that, I'm studying the specific mechanisms involved in constipation and diarrhea (both types), and watching my cat sleep.   Its times like these when I think, damn it'd be nice to have something else to do, but til then, I better really enjoy this! Really really.   Ciao peeps.
      
</post>
<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Check out the blogs of my friends. After all, they got me into this mess. :)   A man of rhyme and rhythm, and just the right words, my dear buddy from CWRU,  urlLink Shareef   Fellow OSU mudphud, favorite Iowan, traveling buddy, and partner in crime,  urlLink Aaron   Law student, shopping buddy, co-habitant of COJ coffeeshop, and professional cutie,  urlLink Chris   What's interesting is every one of these guys is politically inclined. I guess that makes up for my dearth of political commentary. Really, you'd think it would rub off on me by now, but so far all I have is a deep appreciation of Michael Moore's works and an interest in voter registration among minority communities (like mine!). Ah well, Enjoy!                   
      
</post>
<date>28,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      So this weekend I attended my first wedding of a close friend. Although Donny (my good buddy and wedding date) and I were too late to see her walk down the aisle, it was still totally surreal to see her up there, in that dress, taking vows, exchanging rings, and being dubbed a Mrs. for the first time. I think I was in a trance or something for those few minutes, and all I could think about was, "Are we sitting on the wrong side of the chapel? Oh SHIT. We ARE sitting on the wrong side of the chapel. Do I know anyone on this side? What was the groom's name again? What if the bride sees me on the wrong side? I think I just ruined her wedding. Oh DAMN." Donny and I made it out alive though. We even ran into an old friend of Donny's named Steve who also sat on the wrong side of the chapel (opposite us). I really liked Steve. Total cutie and really passionate about what he does with his life. Really outdoorsy kinda guy too. The reception was really long, but having Steve and Donny there made it go by much faster. Add to that the five high school friends I ran into. Apparently I was sitting next to one in the chapel and we didn't even recognize eachother (OH NO we're that OLD! and OH NO, she knew about our faux pas!). Other people I ran into were my high school orchestra stand partner and one of my best friends' sisters. It was driving me crazy how much PDA there was going on among this particular group of people. Lots of fiances and spouses, and they were all really reeally clingy. I don't like that at all. It shows a total absence of trust when a woman is hanging onto her SO's arm for dear life, or lips for that matter. In any case, dinner was excellent and dancing followed. Donny and I didn't get to waltz but we did get to swing, which was a ton of fun. An electric slide and Casper's mix later, and we were out with our complimentary jars of honey as wedding gifts "Sarah and Matthew Stuck Together June 2004."   Now all I need is my own honey to be stuck to. Yeah that's exactly what I thought at the wedding. Weddings have a funny way of making you want to hook up, even if you are living a perfectly happy independent life. I think I'll get over it...   
      
</post>
<date>26,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ok, I'm cheating. This is a recycled email-turned-post from February. But I had saved it for just such an occasion because I think its one of the most random emails I have ever written. Ok, definitely not the most random, but its up there. One of these days I'll actually write something current and put it up. But til then...    Here is the article a friend sent me that was all about sex clubs. Read it and just TRY to tell me that it doesn’t sound like something you’d totally think about trying just once for fun (but also never actually do it cuz its one of those, gee sounds sexy, I'll think about it, but umm NO).   http://www.nytimes.com/2004/01/11/fashion/11SWIN.html   And just because I was curious I looked up some caffeine stats. The MW of caffeine is 194 g/mol. There is on average 200 mg caffeine in a regular strength 8 oz cup o joe (100-120 mg in soda, 60 mg in tea). Thus, the average 8 oz cup o joe has about a 1 mM concentration of caffeine. Who knew?  And finally, someone asked me about migraines so I looked that up too. Migraine headaches are quintessentially caused by stress. Stress causes arteries that supply the brain to go into spasms, which leads to some platelet-clumping within those arteries and ultimately releases serotonin. Serotonin is a vasoconstrictor and causes other arteries to constrict, but this begins to limit blood supply to the brain. So what does the body do? Can’t shut the brain down… OoOOHHH noooo…the brain is very very important. So as a compensatory method, arteries begin to dilate all over the brain, from the initial source of the headache through the scalp and neck, and presumably supplies regions where pain receptors can be stimulated. And this, my friend, is what causes the pain of a migraine headache. ARE YOU EXPERIENCING STRESS?   http://www.mckinley.uiuc.edu/health-info/dis-cond/headache/migr-hea.html  Tata!
      
</post>
<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      "What about him?"  The hair, the hair, ohmigosh the hair! With that jacket? Eh. Something about that nose. He’s gorgeous. Go bang him. Oh wait, nevermind, he turned around and he’s not so cute anymore. Didn’t we see him once, oh yeah, we didn’t like him then either That one, mm mmm, that’s beautiful. He’s amazing. You’re staring Sandy. Yeah, and?  Nevermind.  I dunno, puke yellow doesn’t work well with me. I see it as more of a dark gold though. No? NO. Fine. Hot Daaaaamn did you see him? Them some gorgeous eyes huh. He affects me in ways you don’t sandy. Oh hey he looks reeeal good too.  Ohmigosh no, what are you thinking? Thinking straight again, sorry. Ewwwww!! Collective Ewwwwww!! Why are fags always hotter? Oh the agony the agony. What the fuck?  Now I’d take HIM home. Hey hey, over there, two o clock.  Oh yeah! Mmm hmmm. Definitely. Did you seeee that sweater he had on? YUUUUCK Oh wow, oh wow, hey don’t miss this guy. I was just about to point him out, he’s a cutie. Ok, this guy behind you, umm, try to turn around, don’t be obvious. I love that painting on the wall behind me. The one with the hottie in front of it. You’re staring. Must you always be so damn obvious? That shade of blue. Girl you’re getting your ass beat tonight. Haha. That hair. Ummmm… could use some help, but he has potential. Yeah I agree. He’s INTERESTING. He’s eye candy! He’s such a little fag. He doesn’t know it yet, but I’ll teach him a thing or two. Cute, but not blond enough for Kitkat. Yeah, whoever is? Ass-scoping should be done unabashedly and you my friend aren’t doing it! You’re staring again sandy. No I’m analyzing and I think, I give him a 7, maybe 8. Not so nice to look at in this lighting is he? Well forget that then. Don’t look now, but see him, yeah, him, right there in the blue shirt. Him? 3 o clock. No the one by the guy with the white hat on. Oh! him…hmmm. OH YEAH… oh YEAH.. Daaaaaaamn, yeah… he’s my favorite so far.  Now that* is a tight ass… oh but look what it’s connected to.. shit! How about that one kitkat? Damn Kitkat. Now that’s a hot fag. 
      
</post>
<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Tuta Tara (“broken star” which is what they call a shooting star in Hindi)  Sometimes it seems the broken sky is gathering at my feet And in my haste to avoid the mess, clean up the mess, or destroy the mess I forget to look up again And see the holes left in that sky, twinkling down at me A gentle reminder that not everything has fallen Not everything is shattered And in the larger scene, even as the debris collects below, Punching those holes out of the dark was necessary  To create the greater beauty that remains 
      
</post>
<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Mudphud  (about being md phd and why we love it even though other people find it scary)  A mudphud is a special kind of animal who is always Seeking relief of that inner itch to know or do something new	 The myriad jewels of knowledge and experience  That can ever be grasped or fathomed  In all of mudphudland, In all the world. All of them glitter as hopeful possibility on the road towards perfection To these highly capable creatures who are Fully talented, grateful, and aware that To whom much is given, much is expected. To observant mudphud enthusiasts, and there are many, This species of soul has never been observed Actually performing its required task of self-directed studying But the mudphuds are a secretive sort Who could never understand why learning is so easy for them, only that it is And that they love it, and they don’t care what judgment others pass of their own individualized education. In the mudphuds natural habitat of the library, a coffeeshop, or highly personalized personal abode, One may observe a range of mudphud dialogue, from intellectual procrastination to uberproductive idea exchange to regressive but necessary childish antics Wary of what is revealed and what is concealed about themselves Presented with interesting situations or options, in any sphere of life, they have never been observed to say No I can’t or No I don’t want to And they are never lying when they do this. Because somewhere inside there is a little spark for everything in the mudphud, and  They naturally want to build a fire for every spark of potential that they have. Some are so fascinated by the multitude of sparks they don’t know which fire to kindle first Others kindle flames as they come, seek the warmth of the blaze, and then move to the next, leaving the first one behind, Yet others take a middle path. Mudphuds as a species will always question themselves But perhaps all they really need to learn is that setting limits, making difficult and honest choices, does not suggest incapability, but strength of character In the end, deep down, these animals trust mostly themselves, and by the magic of intuition, Know exactly what they are all about and what they need to do.   
      
</post>
<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Crazyhoney bee  Lone honeybee zips from Fragrant flower to flower Neglecting none, sampling each one Unable to recall the distinct Image or aroma of the first Flower she passed because Its own nectar mixes with the next into sweeter Confection as she travels to Novel and enticing Patches in the delicate wilderness  The hive beckons for her Contribution to the blend, and of this She can proffer much. Her collection is Great in variety, but only Because she takes the Tiniest samples of each Of many, many, blooms before She starts out again on the mad chase For sweetness…  Only occasionally looking back With her wide open eyes With her episodic mind And remembers everything with gratitude. She cannot recall the path she  Took to arrive there but only That the trip was sweet and pure Beautiful and intriguing Just like her when the sticky honey Abundant and burdensome,  Spills and adheres to her motorized wings  Forces her to stop her bumbling And breathe it all in for a moment  It may be flighty and unstructured to the keen observer,  But it is fulfilling, purposeful and Colorful, the life of a lone honeybee 
      
</post>
<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ode to Sandy’s Round Tooshy Ass  The informative self-contained message at the visitors center Was played for you in all its sensational flaky glory Over the span of nine minutes it addressed all you needed With my boy Bob the Japanese guy to answer every major concern you could have had Especially regarding if you can touch me, feed me, or murder me in cold coral blood When you fear your own imminent death approaching Apparently you forgot all about me, after all I’ve done to bring beauty to the world Even after the catchy song and dance of oughts and better nots That you memorized and adored for all its inherent dorkiness And even sang as you thought about skipping down the street After all that, after all that You still wiped out my entire existence and that of my beloved family With your huge ass.  Extra golden brown and slightly firm as it was, It wasn’t worth the ultimate price, Sandy. And you let your thigh take out my cousins. I hope that hurt bitch. 
      
</post>
<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      "So Farsi So Good Blogging boom gives Iranian women a voice: "Take one exasperated Iranian woman. Add a computer. Hook it up to the internet. 'And you have a voice in a country where it's very hard to be heard ...'" Nice! Maybe that should be in our tour. "   My sisters are hooked up! I always get excited when I hear about Muslim women taking steps in the right direction. Speaking up, getting out, etc. I remember what it was like in Bangladesh a loong loong time ago, and women couldn't even go to the mosque with the men. I remember I got sneered at when I went with my dad, and I was only six years old! And what amazes me more is that these repressive rules weren't part of Islam as it was originally. I'd be happy to share resources if anyone is interested. And I'm way generalizing here, but its pretty fascinating what a little bit of superstition, an overactive and undereducated rumor mill, and some institutionalized dogma can do to entire cultures. Speaking of education, I still think women's education will save the world. Mothers are the first teachers after all.  
      
</post>
<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Chasing after shadows In a parallel universe My mind wanders in  The happily controllable mystery I’ve made in the reaches Of my mind lies a distant village Where the beauty of the day Wakes the sentiments of hearts	 And relationships are honored and doors Are left unlocked in seeming love Yet deep in every mind of every villager Lies the urge to know, to discover Something true about the village Or the mind in which it rests, far behind The windows that open to the world Where practicality and semblance Of reason rule over the expression Of purity of thought precious gems Which are made inside the dark behind The curtains which we only Truly peek through now and then   I break my own heart fifty times a day Building up innocent Expectations and being crushed anyway I am not naïve, I’ve only chosen not to play your game. How disappointing that people Do not trust each other, love each other, or connect With one another anymore? What is it we are so afraid of that keeps us further frightened And why rely only on pride to bring us happiness When the world contains enough simple beauty to do that on its own I do not want to lose myself in the cold when only I feel warm.   Someone told me they heard their father tell them these three words Only one time during their life What shame is there in affection and passion That we distrust it entirely and have eradicated it from the public sphere The inner anger and frustration of sons around the world Seeking mother figures and open hearts and selfless acceptance Has contaminated daughters too  And now it almost seems the world is flushed with the bitterness We once implored ourselves to hide beneath our smiles In the name of honesty and vulnerability with our inner negativity Have we not made ourselves More vulnerable than we started In the interest of being ourselves Have we not stunted our own growth Man has never been a purely angelic creature Yet so often we strive to lower ourselves to that level Instead of living up to what we were made for   When you don’t care or care too much I use my own heart as a ruler And I psychically predict the future of All our relations By the congruency of our hearts, moment to moment, The enigma of whether we are worthy to pursue In the grand scheme of the world Or if I am again better off alone and hidden As I was before I chose you to bring me out And only after much disappointment, guilt, Chronic self-beratement I am seeing better  How ineffective heart matching is In this world of constant dynamics Because I really cannot, No matter how I try or wish to Change you or improve you or teach you, Unless you ask me Allow me to know you And do not be afraid.   Why do matters of the heart frighten some people? Is it a sign of weakness to them? I do not understand. How else does one realize the true reaches of one’s strength If not through testing their vulnerabilities And reinforcing what they built A weak shield results when never taken to The battlegrounds of life And this is the shield that remains In the secure realm of home, while others  Fight the necessary struggles   This moment  In which I Move This, here, Is the very life I  Live and must This new virgin Moment that has Arrived Decked in splendor Novel beauty Has already Erased The one in which I started This thought And everything That lies before It and now And onwards Onwards to virgin moments   You are an enigma to those who Hold on to our self-control And being of us, I feel your Pain, of losing sight of yourself It was in those efforts to please  Yourself, seek yourself Taken out of hand in your way Of always being Out of control, out of here, now here, now there Nowhere Gone too far, too wrong, too gone And then you were pleased, you found your Semblance of truth, so you thought But you knew It’s the world that the rest of us Choose not to visit Out of perfectly sound reason It’s the song of the sirens You think it is your truth But let me tell you what is true For those who seek escape to eternal bliss To plastic paradise Ephemeral imaginings Unrealized hopes and dreams shattered and discarded In favor of a realistic fictional realm So inward you go, diving and diving, Pursuing the elusive When so much has always been right there in your reach Could you still be you, still be there, deep inside, somewhere The you that we loved and we know, who smiled and cared Illness creates geodes out of perfectly beautiful people But what illness is it if you chose it of yourself So much is said of cures, healing, treatment When the real disease is still what it has always been Disease of the heart At this point, I cannot tell if you are A victim or a burden or a coward or pathetic Even accepting pain as part of life, Of believing in positive reframing, courage And the development of pearls Uncertainty is certain and the gray times of life Are what get me brooding   I never asked for much  Of what I’ve been given Rarely complained about my cheese being moved Except once or twice All my unworthy tears for minor frustration and Self-created problems Dried up the wells That are so inaccessible now When I feel like I should need them most   Ripple effect of tears and frustration Shattered dreams gathered and reglued Old pains and mistakes Brooded over like a cycling record Shame and guilt and pain Needing resolution, with roadblocks In ever foolproof plan Only a fool could block them anyhow The core issues, seen differently in the six sided  Prism reflecting everywhere And nowhere is there clarity of focus A direction in which we all can look and examine While the True Core is missed entirely, surrounding us, Within us, carrying us, What pain can result when Someone does not think thoroughly of the consequences Of their actions And how frightening, self reflection, self-identification For those who are still around   Today I cry inside my heart For all the heart I spent on you The times I played my part So many times I’ve been the hero Rising above my victimization So angry at your puppeteering Of lives bound by the sanctity of family You play us like the characters Of your personal show The rescuer, the evader, the hero, the neglected, the needy How self-centered and manipulative You steal away our true roles The identities we were meant to have And that I was only able to find By leaving you   Porcelain doll woken rudely From slumber to terror In the home where nothing bad happens Her pretty eyes widen in shock A channel of tears pours down her cheeks Carrying in them fear, love, anger, disappointment So much sadness Who sees the porcelain doll? So fragile and tender When the world has become rough And all has turned hardened Who dries the porcelain doll’s tears? Lost innocence is a shame When it is to a young and precious Porcelain doll, crumbling in fear Beauty hidden by confusion   
      
</post>
<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      DTR and who am I of yours?  A lot of times I wonder how I present myself I only really know how I see me And never really how you see me But I do wish I could climb into your head At every moment that you are you And really find out when I am there And what fancies, colors, settings, and memories You have put me there with Because really, there is a bond Outside of us, but what is it inside?   It was amazing to see Everything I loved about The world The sunshine, stars, waves, Touristy people, attractive young men,  Sandy beaches, city life,  Culture, sunsets on the  Horizon, mountains, villages,  Childish song, and dance In a tiny speck of an Island in the greatest  Of the oceans All in four days with you. I can’t think of anyone else I could have created those particular Memories with Mahalo, my friend.   Freewrite on the beach  Five shades of blue Crystalline see through The odd sailboat The odd white foamy wave Total lack of hot men Except the gay one next to me I wonder why they call it diamondhead I love the natural distribution Of the palm trees As though they are not Artificial There to be seen but not there out of someones showmanship Beauty that doesn’t know it Fobiness extends everywhere and I don’t know hardly what to do with it I wish I could see a sea turtle Or lose this belly Ohmigod if I could lose this belly Battle of a lifetime I tell ya Maybe I could lose the flab and somehow use it to make the sun come out from behind the clouds again I love the slow rhythm of the waves hitting the beach   Sad day poem  There are times I feel I can’t keep up Or don’t belong It’s a world that I am not accustomed to that  Occasionally my companions are swept into And then I just want to go away And hide Or pretend it doesn’t matter if I’m there And I try to force myself to stick it out Be patient and dorky and dumb Fake energetic and happy Try to jump into the joke Because that is how I feel  And I know you don’t intend it But it is part of the dynamic And I love people too much To just leave them  But you know what I worry Sometimes that if I left Few would notice Or know me deeper than the surface It’s counterproductive and safe  To be social and antisocial at once And now it is written down   
      
</post>
<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      These are all some short poems I wrote in November 2003. They're all untitled at present, but if you can think of a good title for any of them, or revisions or changes, let me know.   I heard you cough as  You said nothing was  Wrong The familiar cough Of a familiar problem The cough a dying  Man releases Hoping his spirit will Flow out with the  Blood and phlegm Did you hear me When I said I loved You and did you know I meant it    My heart fluttered for my friend And it was as though I never recognized you Did you say I had grown up? Did I look into your eyes As we smiled and laughed And wondered curiously? How did you interpret our time was it like me? You were one of many who had lost respect for me And perhaps it is because  I had lost an ounce of respect for myself, For not living up to the standards that so many respected me for.   You dared me to break wide Open Even though I felt too scared I have worked so hard to Build layers of protection Around my fragile heart And your strength of  Spirit shattered those  Walls I am glad that you did Because I was not about To do it myself I am relieved     So your kid sister has grown up Or your confidant has changed I am sorry I inspired you So much that I let you down I knew all along deep down That “me” was too good to be true,  Too good to last for you For everyone who thought it And especially for me But I like who I am now I’m glad to be stronger A little wiser, a little more trouble I just adore challenging people Perhaps I always will And despite how I have changed I still love being around you, knowing you,  Sharing with you, laughing with you You must know how much I admire you The way you treat everyone you know With such friendliness and respect If I could only get past my fear of your judgment I could let you know me as I really am Sorry my friend… and thank you.   Whimsical determination Her iron will shines through her worry She doesn’t know how her Laughter revives us Those of us who live by her Smile and loving heart For such a tough shell There is a deeply tender Adventurous, imaginative spirit in there That doesn’t know her own strength  And possibilities Don’t you ever cry When your laughter is like a  Heartsong for us   We are only intimidating Because we dare to break the rules for ourselves And challenge who you think you are And what you think is possible    Vibrance radiating from The toughest shell It is like iridescence How beautiful, colorful, The shine dancing through the air The brilliance eludes many From seeing too far inside the ornament Which you can only do if you step close enough To the star that you no longer see the rays alone But the fiery source that produced them Admit your vulnerability Because that is what makes you perfect. 	  Sometimes it seems the broken sky is gathering at my feet And in my haste to avoid the mess, clean up the mess, or destroy the mess I forget to look up again And see the holes left in that sky, twinkling down at me A gentle reminder that not everything has fallen Not everything is shattered And in the larger scene, even as the debris collects below, Punching those holes out of the dark was necessary  To create the greater beauty that remains 
      
</post>
<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      As of September 2003   OK, this time I've really done it. I had totally forgotten about the little web "home" that Becky had so generously acquainted me with so long ago. She told me in 1996 that someday, when we're all reclusive people whose primary identities are found on the internet, it will be really nice to have some space to myself, like my own webpage. Well Duck you were right!  It looks like I haven't written since Junior year of college... um, thats a while, so I'll try to fill in main events right now.  The end of junior year came and went really fast. Through Spring, Summer, and Fall 2002, I was primarily devoted to my research in the Pehek lab when I wasn't in class. I managed to get 3 studies out of that lab: the SPUR study on D1 receptor specificity that took me to the Society for Neuroscience Conference in November 2002 (almost IMMEDIATELY after I was declared out of the severe stage of mononucleosis--see below-- I was on a plane to Florida! let's just say, never go to CityWalk unless you remember your ID! The only places we were able to go in were MoTown, MargaritaVille, and someplace else I can't remember. Although, dancing with the students from Alaska and Birmingham in the middle of the street for 2 hours was totally fun! So was getting reimbursed for the trip later!!), and then the Risperidone study took both Omar AND me to Colorado Springs (Can anyone ever forget the superposh BROOOOOOADMOOR Hotel? OOHHH GOOOOOOOD. or running into the other two indian/arab students from vancouver that were there and goin out with them for nearly the whole night (on Omar's heavenly bed, wasnt it)? or meeting the guy that invented Clozapine in person? perhaps driving "into the hills" during every spare moment, and watching EVERY STAR IN THE SKY SHINING above us from the pitch black heights of the Rockies! and then freaking out because the pot dealers brought their pickup to teh same ledge we parked our rental Camry! And finally, did I drive 10,000 ft into the sky? Up the tallest mountain in the continental US? in a RENTAL CAR? AWWWWWWwwww YEEEEAAAA baby!), and finally, I got to work on a really fast project to try to look at prolactin regulation of dopamine (American Cancer Society summer grant... that was the time Dan came by and nearly puked when he saw the rat guillotine). And all that fun was just from working in the lab! Let this be a lesson to those of you who think research is boring and for, dare I say it, NERDS.   but I still managed to have a life ON campus too. I TA'd BIOL 210 and 211, for Missy, who was once my own TA back in the day! Teaching is SO in my genes. My grandfather was a teacher, my dad is a professor, my uncles are professors, my other grandfather was a spiritual advisor. Its in my blood to teach people. I knew that academia was totally for me because of my TAing... and of course, I also got to meet all the cute little froshes and sophs. Admittedly, I had my favorites, and its been so cool to watch them "grow up" and start doing research of their own, get their own fellowships, etc. I miss em!  I also continued to work, at least peripherally, with ICDG and MSA (probably not as well-organized as I was initially), and RA both Glaser and Kusch (top of the hill buildings). I wasnt very good at either of these huge projects during senior year for several reasons. First of all, I got mono at the end of September, JUST after I submitted my AMCAS. So, I sat in bed, thinking I was dying, waiting for my spleen to rupture as I tried to breathe, propped up on 4 pillows for 2 whole weeks so that my throat wouldnt close on itself (it was SO swollen!), and surviving solely on ginger ale and Caprisun liquid calories. I dont think theres a single episode of The Wedding Story, Trading Spaces, or The Baby Story that I ever missed. For someone who never watched TV, I watched more than I needed to make up for it during those 4 weeks in bed, and the following 2 weeks "adjusting to light activities." So, in the meantime, my secondaries piled up skyhigh, and I scrambled to finish my coursework so I could still graduate on time (did you know mono counts as a student disability?). I actually took the midterm and final for my Pharm 430 class within ONE week of eachother!!  Second reason I was underinvolved Senior year was cuz of med apps. I applied to several schools, from what I remember, they were OSU, CWRU, Wright State, Northwestern, Vanderbilt, U Illinois, Boston U, NYU, U Michigan, Duke, and Wash U if I remember correctly. Aside from the "only in-state applicant schools" like MIch, Boston, and NYU, I got interviews at every school. I actually ATTENDED interviews at OSU, CWRU, WSU, UIll, and Wash U. I know I know, why would I cancel an interview at Northwestern or Vandy? Believe me I got slapped across the face by many a compatriot premed for being such a snot. But honestly, it was because I knew I wasnt going to make it into their MD PhD programs (I missed the deadlines for that application at those schools) and I had already been accepted to MSP at UIll and OSU and waitlisted at CWRU. Wash U was really tempting until I actually went to St. Louis. I didnt like it. And yeah, I lived in Cleveland for 4 years.. St Louis should be a step up eh? Whatever... Ultimately, I picked OSU.  It was good for me for a lot of reasons. I knew that an 8 year investment of time would require a lot of family support, and also perhaps more of my own support of THEM. So I wanted to stick close. As Westernized as I think I am sometimes, whether thats actually true or not, I still have the ingrained belief that its my job to take care of my elders in their old age. Its the least I owe them for all I've put them through... I mean seriously, I would have a really tough time trying to raise a kid like me! I'm always so damn complicated! Also of course, I liked the OSU program better than UIllinois. Funding and resource wise, social life and urban access wise, OSU had the goods and U Ill didnt (as much). The third and final reason I was underinvolved on campus was cuz I spent so much of my spare time either in the lab (I'm talkin weekends and evenins here!) or with the former BF Dan (yes, former... we'll get to that). When we spent time together during the SUmmer of 2002 living in Clarke tower, we had a great time. I could totally be myself, immature goofball that I am a lot of times when I let loose. He taught me how to swing dance, and I gotta admit, when a man knows how to treat a lady as a lady, and dance with her as a lady... dude thats impressive. We did the whole moonlight stroll thing, sharing our personal poetry with eachother, discussing our views of the world, etc. Then I asked him out (I'm always making the damn first move... can someone ask ME this time around?) and the rest is history. Coping through my illness, his LSATS, both of our application processes and interviews, my cousins illness and death, and pre-graduation craziness... in some ways, the point of the relationship got lost for me amidst the fun. I mean, who doesnt like having ready company thats always comfortable, easy to understand, and available for hugs? I'm a sucker for a hugger. OK, that sounds so weird, but if you can stop laughin at the statement, you know what I mean.  ANYWAY, it was only when we spent several weeks apart during summer that I realized that our relationship was built on some flimsy idealisms, my own stubborness to make everything work no matter what, and the CWRU environment (which indeed is a bubble, and anyone who has ventured out of CWRU knows this... its not a bad bubble.. its a bubble you miss.. but its not a bubble you can take with you when you leave). We broke up in August just before classes started here at OSU. We're on hiatus but trying to be friends, but I think we'll manage.  SO yeah, in May I graduated. In June I started the MD PhD program here at OSU, also called the IMSP. I'm doing my PhD in integrated biomedical sciences, which essentially means I have access to rotate through and/or do dissertation work in any lab at OSU that studies something relevant to human disease. Its a different program than traditional MD PhD programs because it involves taking some grad classes and some med classes simultaneously at all times, but in the end, you get the dual degree and usually even shave a year off the time. For the CWRUers, its something like the BSTP and MSTP program all mixed together.  So far things are going well. Its definitely taking some adjustment, a new place, a new bunch of people, a bunch of people from my past that I suddenly run into (and had lost touch with.. so where do we pick up now?), and new responsibilities. I have never been a drinker, but suddenly I'm in this place where everyone drinks when they go out, so believe it or not, I'm finally learning to be a DD (i.e. I have been). I discussed this with Saad the other day. No matter how bad things got at CWRU, alcohol-wise... it was nothing compared to down here. AND, nobody ever really drove much (beyond across campus... a whole 2 miles), IF EVER. So this whole analysis of drinking and driving is totally new to me. Does that make me naive, innocent, or clueless? Anyway, its one of those new things, I'll learn, and I'm fine with it as far as my end is concerned. I'd never make someone stop drinking if thats what thy really want to do, just like I'd expect them to never push me TO do it, because I really dont want to (i have my reasons...). If theres anything CWRU taught me, its to be tolerant, and be yourself.  I do love bootyshakin on teh dance floor, and people watching, and meeting people, and of course sarcasm and "those random connections" (all the way back to Peter's connections journal) gets the best of me ALL the time, so I've still managed to have a good time between study sessions (and even sometimes AT study sessions!) I gotta admit its hard here. As a mud phud, I dont quite fit into the MD1 class, or the IBGP PhD class, because my course requirements and schedule always differ slightly. Its easy to feel disconnected from both. Then of course, I'm THE female rep in our 4-person mudphud class. I can't reeeally complain because its such a small program and I assume the fellowships are more smarts-related than gender-related. There are two other women mudphuds this year but I've only met one. Natosha is great though, just further ahead in her career and in her life. We connect as women and friends, but its different than chillin with my fellow 20-something ladies. I mean, I've actually always gotten along better with guys, and when I count my closest pals, I'd say a good 70% are guys. But still, amidst all of this disjointed social life and scrambled academic schedule, I need some sisterhood ya know? What happened to my always reliable always fun always social activist dance-lovin posse of Soumzy, Samara, Hadele, Maheen, Yasi and Ro? Cooking together and bellydancing and playing powderpuff sistas "Fooooball" trying on outfits and guy-bashing and analyzing Trading Spaces and planning community service projects? I'm still in touch with everyone from CWRU, thankfully, and of course, I'm making my best efforts socially down here. Never really been afraid to go up to someone and start a conversation. Even if you're only 30% successful at keeping in touch with the person, its a better chance of finding cool peopel than if you say nothing at all. So yeah, I've met a ton of people, and theres definitely people I could go up to and make small talk, or joke around, or study with, or invite out for the weekend, and a handful I could even "talk" to about the things that I really* think about. But overall, this early in the game, I think I agree with Nupe when he said, "its like you end up making these really good friends, people who are always ready to hang out with, people you have fun with, have tons of inside jokes and history with, but when it comes down to it... how many could you tell your life story to? or talk to about the bad things, the sad things, the things that worry you?" I guess overall what I've been feeling lately is something between the thrill and contentment of being independent combined with the boredom and frustration of being alone. Its the pain and excitement of the lone adventurer starting on a hopeful journey..... I guess its time to call it a night. As usual, my best writing/venting is at 3 AM. Still hopeful though, and working hard to be the best damn Mud Phud Chick there is.  "I wonder what wonder the world will bring me today?"  
      
</post>
<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This has been such a crazy week...   sunday: drove 12 hrs from nyc to columbus monday: really fake celebration of the 1 yr anniversary after a big argument, but great food tuesday: got the infamous computer worm on the same day i was supposed to present my research for the summer to my boss, all my data was in my computer, really hectic time fixing things wednesday: parents came to visit, got my white coat, went out with friends, met people, finally broke up with dan thursday: postbreakup talk with dan, want to stay friends, went out with medschool class again, danced and got temp tattoo'd as "wild in the shower"  friday: lazy day, too sleepy for orientation, went out with med and law students, lost track of a friend, hit my shin on a table, and left early cuz i couldnt watch dan act stupid saturday: dan apologized, india fest, long nap, hurled a bowling ball at a cosmic bowling alley to relieve stress, met new people note: NO STUDYING! WHAT A WEEK!!  Post Note: Dan and I both need our friends right now.
      
</post>
<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      again, i havent updated anyone on things, so here we go.  1) i've moved to columbus. got pretty new furniture and set up the place so that all my friends can come visit. hint hint! 2) bought a used car. 98 camry. compared to dans screeching hyundai, this is by far better.. not just better, to me, it feels like a brand new car from teh dealership. i LOVE it. its so cool to say, hey i bought that myself. never did that before. 3)finally found a jean skirt! hehe. i know thats not that exciting to many of you, but realy, i have been trying to find a slitless denim skirt for SO long, and i found one finally! and it was for only ten bucks at lazarus! and its not like a bad quality skirt either, i just hit it lucky that day. yay! 4) have been at home off and on the past few weeks. my cousins are visiting since their father is currently seeking work. one is 8 months old, the other is 8 years old. the 8 yr old is a little, shall we say, rambunctious. shes got energy out the wahoo and i worry sometimes that shes ADD. she cant focus on anything for longer than 5 minutes. then she says shes bored. even when she begged me for days to take her to see finding nemo, and i finally did.. she complained the whole time we were in the theater! anyway, i've helped her learn to read a little by enroling her in our community summer reading club, and hopefully that should help her find some focus. she actually likes reading now, so it made me feel good to do that. as for her baby brother.. he's the cutest baby in the entire world! he's ALWAYS laughing and playing. its soo cute. and he said Maa (mother) the other day when he wanted his mom. learning to talk too! i think he'll be walking by end of summer because he's getting good at pulling himself up to a stand. aww... i miss him now. :'( 5) going to NYC tomorrow to see dan and his parents. super pumped. i love their family and the city too. i think this should be an awesome trip. my mom wasnt too ecstatic about it, and like with every other trip i ever go on, she tried to convince me not to get on that plane. also, shes uncomfortable that i am visiting dan. i tried to reassure her that his parents are there too but i think all her denial that i'm actually really dating him, and really serious about loving him, is finally sinking in. its a shock to her, but i have to stand my ground. any tips on how to stand my ground but still help her feel a little better? 6) i start school in two weeks. less than that actualy. orientatino is the 20th and classes for the PhD start the 23rd. i will be working in a cancer immunologists lab for my first rotation. again, i'm excited. august is the actual beginning of medical school for th rest of the MD students(only md phds start in summer.. so we get a head start befoe everyone else). i need to send them my measurements to figure out what size short white coat i will be wearing. i still cant believe theyre actually gonna let me wear one! ;P  well, thats all for now. take care everyone. HAVE A LOVELY DAY! :)
      
</post>
<date>25,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well let's see here. Current updates: I decided to go to OSU for MD PhD. Dan also decided to go to OSU after all, which is so exciting because we get to kind of embark on the adventure together, which is actually very nice to think about. WHats better than starting something new, different, and BIG, with the person closest to you, right? I am looking forward to suporting eachother through our professional educations. SOOO</post></Blog>