<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        im not happy na talaga dito sa office...parang ambagal ng oras...gusto ko nang umuwi...lot of things to do pero kahit isa wala akong gustong unahin hahaha...aftershock ng absences ko perhaps eheheh
     

    
</post>
<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        wehehehe! ewan ko ba tong si julia...sobrang happy na i-announce waistline ng low waist pants ko sa national TV during GMA's pre inaguaration ceremony at quirino grand stand...hahaha kala nya maasar nya ako wehehe...effort pa kafatid! it would take a lot para maasar ako eheheh  
     

    
</post>
<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        effort effort effort...working mother---u should have a million tons of this...  ...i dont have to convince you people---but i cant put the life of my kids at stake to please you!!!  
     

    
</post>
<date>30,June,2004</date>
<post>


       
        ...tears came flowing unendlessly...fears covering my humanity...IS THIS THE LIFE I HAVE TO PAY?  ...it's just an ordinary thursday morning.  everything was set in order--go to work, go to gym, doing some chores for my angels...simple outline for the week.  But one ring can change everything...a call from a very dear person...coffee in the afternoon...hard to cut the moments...dining in a fine resto...shopping spree...all plans has been wrecked with just ONE CALL...no regrets though, but what is the package behind the pleasure of being with him?...he brought me home late...that would be fine, foods for kids are individually packed...pasalubong are really mouthwatering...but, the first angel is somewhat quite...finding she's not feeling well...then the agony continues...  DONT PUT ME IN THIS TEST...
     

    
</post>
<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Catching Rainbows                  If I could catch a rainbow  I would do it just for you  And share with you its beauty  On the days you're feeling blue   If I could build a mountain  You could call your very own  A place to find serenity  A place to be alone   If I could take your troubles  I would toss them in the sea  But all these things  I'm finding are impossible for me   I cannot build a mountain  Or catch a rainbow fair  But let me be what I know best  A friend that's always there   This is a Hug Certificate!!              
     

    
</post>
<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My friend lives in Taal (small town in Batangas)  &gt; &gt; where trees and high  &gt; &gt; land  &gt; &gt; areas mostly surround it. One evening he went to  &gt; &gt; town (Batangas City)  &gt; &gt; for a movie with his friends. He was having a lot  &gt; &gt; fun before he  &gt; &gt; realized it  &gt; &gt; was getting very late. He quickly made his way home.  &gt; &gt; It was unusually  &gt; &gt; dark  &gt; &gt; and creepy that night.  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt; As he was walking, he was astonished to find an old,  &gt; &gt; creepy-looking  &gt; &gt; street peddler selling some books along the road. It  &gt; &gt; gave him the  &gt; &gt; shivers  &gt; &gt; when he noticed this pale old person staring at him.  &gt; &gt; The old person  &gt; &gt; said,  &gt; &gt; "Son, why not get a book .. it will keep you  &gt; &gt; company".  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt; My friend acted brave and thought why not. He had a  &gt; &gt; look at the old  &gt; &gt; man's collection ... his hair began to rise up on  &gt; &gt; end when he noticed  &gt; &gt; all  &gt; &gt; the books were related to the supernatural.  &gt; &gt; Nonetheless, he found one  &gt; &gt; that  &gt; &gt; was very interesting so he asked the old man, "How  &gt; &gt; much is this,  &gt; &gt; Uncle?"  &gt; &gt; The old person replied, "Well son .. that ' s an  &gt; &gt; interesting book...  &gt; &gt; its PhP 500. (pesos)"  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt; My friend was shocked and said "But ... but ..  &gt; &gt; that ' s so  &gt; &gt; expensive...  &gt; &gt; "The old man said nothing but glared at my friend  &gt; &gt; which freaked him  &gt; &gt; out. He quickly rummaged through his pockets and  &gt; &gt; found PhP 450.  &gt; &gt; "T-t-this's all I have " he said. The old guy  &gt; &gt; replied, "It ' s okay,  &gt; &gt; son.... you can  &gt; &gt; have the book for that price. " As my friend  &gt; &gt; hastily paid for it and  &gt; &gt; made  &gt; &gt; a dash for home, the old man called out to him and  &gt; &gt; said, " Son ...  &gt; &gt; whatever happens, don ' t you ever flip the book to  &gt; &gt; it ' s last page  &gt; &gt; ....remember these words ...or you will regret  &gt; &gt; it!!!!!!!!!!!!!"  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt; Reaching home, he quickly asked his parents, " Dad  &gt; &gt; ... mom...are  &gt; &gt; there any new booksellers nearby?" "Not that we know  &gt; &gt; of ... but  &gt; &gt; we've heard of a creepy old man that appears only at  &gt; &gt; night  &gt; &gt; during a full moon and then disappears just as  &gt; &gt; mysteriously.  &gt; &gt; Nobody knows who he is, or where he comes from but  &gt; &gt; many have  &gt; &gt; become victims in his wake... why son?"  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt; "N-nothing ... just asking", said my friend and ran  &gt; &gt; straight to his  &gt; &gt; room. Nervously, he opened the book and began  &gt; &gt; reading, all the time  &gt; &gt; remembering the warning the old man had given him.  &gt; &gt; But after a while,  &gt; &gt; he  &gt; &gt; grew tired and fell asleep.  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt; At midnight, as he was sound asleep in bed, a cold  &gt; &gt; gush of wind blew in  &gt; &gt; through his bedroom window which startled him and  &gt; &gt; sent chills down his  &gt; &gt; spine. He looked at his table and noticed the wind  &gt; &gt; had blown the pages  &gt; &gt; of the book to its last page!!!!! For a while, he  &gt; &gt; laid in bed - frozen  &gt; &gt; in  &gt; &gt; fear, but soon curiosity got the better of him. He  &gt; &gt; had to know what was  &gt; &gt; on  &gt; &gt; the last page.  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt; Slowly he got out of bed and carefully picked up the  &gt; &gt; book. As he  &gt; &gt; glimpsed at the last page, he let out a  &gt; &gt; blood-curling scream and  &gt; &gt; fainted...  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt; This is what he read on the last  &gt; &gt; page.........................................  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt; Scroll down (please)  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt; Retail Price: PhP 50.00 pesos  &gt; &gt; Promotional Price: PhP 25.00 pesos  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt;  &gt; &gt; aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh  &gt; &gt; !!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! 
     

    
</post>
<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
        SONNY AND I DIDNT TALK THE WHOLE DAY YESTERDAY!!! bakit sobrang miss ko na sya agad...he might be so busy or probably he was out with his barkada...one day ko lang sya hindi makausap, i found empty space agad...AM I REALLY IN LOVE?  
     

    
</post>
<date>01,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
        ...si batang si badeth nag-away! nobody here in the office thought they can come with such arguments...si batang well loved si badeth...si badeth well supportive kay batang...yet there are still mood off days when every one find it hard to understand each other...pressured with lots of works, bothered with personal problems...misunderstood every move..  but im glad...i've been a medium for their reconcilation! yahoo!!!  love ko sila pareho...  
     

    
</post>
</Blog>