<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Have you noticed that the only way an animated movie will do super good and be extermely loveable is if something tragic and sad happens?  Lets take that movie by dreamworks, Spirit.  Now that just had tragedy all over the place. 1st he gets captured then he escapes. After he escapes he gets REcaptured and falls in love with that pretty little horse Rain. Then Rain  falls over the side of a waterfall AND DIES!  After that, he's taken (he got captured AGAIN!!!) to pull a train over a mountain so they can run a railroad into his old home. Luckliy he survives  and discovers Rain has survived as well. Now, they run off into the sunset back to his homeland. That scene gives me a warm and fuzzy feeling inside the entire time I watch it. Did I mention that soundtrack ROCKS.  Next, we have Mulan. (I'm planning on making this my layout once I get a chance to)That soundtrack also rocks, I still love refelection to this day!!! Now, that was sad when she realized that her father would die if she went to war. So she cuts off most of her hair, dawns his armor and runs off for the armor. After she does that her father runs after her in the rain and falls. It was SAD!!!  Then there was Nemo. If you haven't seen Nemo yet, go!!! Go see it!!! The poor fish got fishnapped!!! NNNEEEMMMOOOO!!!  And, the all time SADDEST and BEST animated movie, the Lion King. I still can't believe they killed Mufasa. I cried the first time I saw that.  He was such a cool lion. And the way he died suck. Screw you Scar, SCREW you!!!!!  I loved Mufasa!  Now that I think about it....animated movies seemed to be much to sad for children. Just, to damn sad for the poor little picknees 
    
</post>
<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I was stock raving mad, ready to write a TON of rants today, but guess what happened? I forgot it lasts night. It got lost in the swirl of the Purgatory Arc I read last night. It was SO good!!! My goodness! I loved it! and its not even done yet. *cries* It leaves off in the worst possible place. Stupid purgatory arc! &gt; 
    
</post>
<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      HHHIIII!!!!! I know your watchingpeople,oO *shrugs* whatever I'm trying to write quick so I can update my story, then gowatch FairlyOddparent movie thingy. Ihave chaoter threeof Angel and Demons all up here in my noggin. That reminds me, I have toadd the linkat the side.  My computer STILL isn't ready. I need a roater. I wish I had some money to get it, cause Ijust got a brand new adobe photoshop and i'm DIEING to do soome icons. Here, in miami, its tax free week starting today. *rolls up sleeves* Time togo shopping,but once again, I'M MONEYLESS!!!! ;-; 
    
</post>
<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Being a woman sucks, times a million. Why wasn't I borne a boy, huh? I can't get over the fact thatfor a woman, a filmsy little shirt that looks like a scrap of fabric cost like $100 and some heavy material that would take decades to make cost like $20. Its not fair!!!!  If you add up the price of makeup, pads, tampons,headache tablets, cramp tablets, CHOCOLATE, and fluffy pillows, women are doomed to live in depth (And thats just what women buy in ONE month, FOR ONE WEEK! Its not worth it!)  I can't wait for menopause. Oh let me stop there before I start going on and on about child birth. I swear during the ordeal I would kill my husband, I would kill him and he would never touch my again.  Men, I just wanna say, you better watch out XD 
    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I have some very good, yet bad news, The so so: My aunt got in an accident last night and had to be air lifted to the hospital. Luckly she is very much alive. Things are kind of the same over here. Oh! last night I was gonna die cause I heard a tapping on the glass. I did the absolutely natural thing and ran like hell. My sister doesn't believe me though.   On second note, this house is starting to get to me. I close my eyes at night and wonder if when I wake up if things will be this bad? Also, I finally updated my fic, Angels and Demons. :-) I'm gonna start my next couple of chapters soon. I have this cool idea for a dieing scene that I am going to post right here, right about now....:  *He stood as soon as the dust cleared. He was hurting all over. But he had to see her. He had toknow she was okay. He braced himself and made his way toher body. She was turned on her side, skin coated in blood. What little skin he cold see was pale and lifeless.He touched her just a bit and lifted her into her arms in one swoop. He turned around and made his way to the city. The sun was setting in the distance.  Lite green eyes opens and stared into his own dark ones. "Hey there lover." She whispered  "Shush, don't say a word, everything gonna be alright."  "It beautiful isn't it?"  "What is?"  "The song, I can hear people singing" He looked down at her. She was smiling. A small beautiful smile.It was the first time he had seen her smile like that. "Mama's coming baby, mama's coming." She whispered before closing her eyes. He held her, for just one minute, before falling and letting himself die.*   Not so good, I know, it happens sometimes XP 
    
</post>
<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Right now my creativeness is going kabooom? Its sizziling up and i'm so afraid i won't be able to make a portfolio when the time comes. *cries* But besides that I'm bored. I've almost been down to the point where I am about to write a couple of fanfics. I haven't written a fanfic in YEARS. Maybe it'll do me some real good. 
    
</post>
<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I can't take it anymore. I'm running off to make some icons, i'll post here later (also I'm feeling very creative and unwriters blocked. Why the hell isn't m0y computer up for ths?????) *hits head against wall* 
    
</post>
<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just found out where I can download some lovely, lovely anime. Sadly,I have to wait till I get that thing in my room that allows two computers to be on a network. Till then all downloads are at a halt. Could you believe that at this VERY moment I could bepreparing to watch the 2nd Inuyasha movie??? or the 152 episode? or i could be watching bomberman. I'm gonna go look for my song, iris to put it on this thingy.        days till school: 27 days till birthday: 42  
    
</post>
<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I need some seriously new anime and manga. Screw Sim 2. I'm gonna go ask for money so I can run to the store to buy some seriously good manga. Or I'll borrow some from the libray. I was SO shocked when I realized that I could rent manga from the libray. Sadly out of order. Or maybe in order, I havent searched hard enough. I think i'll go back later. Maybe, somewhere, someway, I can download some lovely anime, like Naruto or the actual Inuyasha. (Mental yay dance)  On a second note look at this. Isn't it adorable:     hehehehehe!!  Days till school: 28 Days till birthday: 43 
    
</post>
<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hello!!! I'm getting ready to watch Def Poetry thingy in a minute. I just saw the 4400. IT WAS GOOOD! I love 4400. The days was a disappointment cause it was boring. Hopefully, desperate housewives and lost shall not follow in its footsteps.    As accordancewith the laws of teenagers (I swear I shall draw thisup by tomarrow)I begin my countdowns starting now:    Days till school: 29  Days till birthday: 44   
    
</post>
<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I'm looking and just now noticing how they've changed the place to edit stuff. Kind of freaky cool. Of course i'm writingin arial, cause arial is my favorite font. Online, i'm currently playinga game of water fight with chris. &gt;   
    
</post>
<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Its starting to take my blog FOREVER to update. I guess its just getting bigger and bigger. Damn, yo, sometimes I wish I could draw. I have such great ideas and no where to put them. Do you know how fustrating that is? I also wanna do a webcomic. ^^(), sometimes I can be very, very creative. I'm thinking of adding another blog to my account and you know, post stories there and stuff. I wonder if anyone would read it, they'd probably think my junk was terrible! Hehehehehe. Anyway, i'm gonna go set it up and make it pretty, and, um stuff. :D, I found this Lilo and Stitch icon that I wanna post up, but I deleted hello and the image server I use blogger doesn't accept the address. &gt;</post></Blog>