<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
            "A good sermon should be like a woman's skirt: short enough to arouse interest but long enough to cover the essentials."   Ronald Knox .          "He had decided to live forever or die in the attempt."   Joseph Heller .           "Boy, those French: They have a different word for everything!"   Steve Martin .           "Why don't they pass a constitutional amendment prohibiting anybody from learning anything? If it works as well as prohibition did, in five years Americans would be the smartest race of people on Earth."   Will Rogers .           "Always do sober what you said you'd do drunk. That will teach you to keep your mouth shut."   Ernest Hemmingway .           "Smoking kills. If you're killed, you've lost a very important part of your life."   Brooke Shields (during an interview to become spokesperson for a federal anti-smoking campaign) .        Rabindranath Tagore -  ÂAge considers; youth ventures.Â         George Bernard Shaw -  ÂYouth is a wonderful thing. What a crime to waste it on children.Â          "My mother said to me, "If you are a soldier, you will become a general. If you are a monk, you will become the Pope." Instead, I was a painter, and became Picasso."   Pablo Picasso .               Any others? Bueller? Bueller?            People will do anything, no matter how absurd, in order to avoid facing their own soul.   ~Carl Gustav Jung       		 Do you Yahoo!?   urlLink Yahoo! Mail  - Helps protect you from nasty viruses.
     

    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
           So I'm talking to another friend online... Who knows why I decided to stay online tonight? I don't usually chat too much anymore. Well, recently there's been one person I chat to once in a while, but not anyone else.              Well, I've been bored today so I was chatting online and I get a "proposition" from a "friend" (not like someone I don't know or anything - someone I was talking to online) and the conversation goes something like this:              M: Well, you don't miss something until it's gone.       H: Not true.       M: So you say.       H: It isn't true.       M: Actions speak louder than words.         Note: I'm now the Queen of Cliches Evidently        H: I'm thirsty.       M: ....              Point made??              _________              Anyhow, I talked to Kathy today. We sat on the deck for a while just chatting. I was telling her about my furniture and how I decided to just buy the bedroom furniture and accessorize my bedroom since I probably wouldn't have any company to sit in my living room. "Not that I'll have company in my bedroom," I quickly added. DEPRESSING!!              However, this is the rule: I am the sex Nazi. No sex for you, one year!              When men walk into my bedroom they must click their heels, walk without bending their knees and salute me with their penises, but that's as far as it goes! Or comes for that matter.           People will do anything, no matter how absurd, in order to avoid facing their own soul.   ~Carl Gustav Jung       		 Do you Yahoo!?   urlLink New and Improved Yahoo! Mail  - Send 10MB messages!
     

    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      (Notice the timestamps) Asshole (10:07:53 PM): ur missing south park Jess (10:09:18 PM): i'm making a web page for my classroom. Jess (10:09:28 PM): oh. i found a place to rent for 6 months or more. Jess (10:12:27 PM): and pink elephants are traipsing across the lawn at this very moment. Jess (10:13:38 PM): and i created a new blog. i think i'm going to delete the old one  moving on, etc. etc. Jess (10:14:37 PM): and i'm having your quintuplet babies.   they all have an extra leg growing out of their forehead. Jess (10:14:54 PM): i'm going to name them all george, but spell it a different way for each. Asshole (10:16:20 PM): george? Jess (10:16:40 PM): for the man i wish was their dad, you know. my affair.
     

    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
           As I'm in ultra-stress mode with moving and recovery and the new job and all, I will be heard from LOTS! IF I have computer access which is a LONG BORING STORY.              Aside from that, let's talk about the 4th of July: Being the patriotic soul that I am, I MUST CELEBRATE. Considering my condition, I cannot go celebrate at Santee or Fort Jackson as I had hoped, so my other offer is to go with a "friend" who was MORE than a friend a while back here in Charleston.               Well, I guess I COULD go to Columbia, but it wouldn't be a very wise decision. Then again, "Jessica's Book on Wise Decisions" is only about a page long right now.              The whole "going with the friend who used to be more than a friend" thing is the most convenient since it's here and would require nothing too much on my part, but (and it's a very big but and no I'm not talking about my ass) the whole emotional portion of it couldn't be too good. All of you who know the 2-year Asshole history will not have to be filled in for that.              Meanwhile, I tried to drive to the store today and got stranded!               Oh, and lawyers used to give me headaches when I worked for them and I wondered why and now I KNOW... b/c they make everything so hard! ANARCHY FOR EVERYONE!              This has been another ADD and premenstrual raving brought to you by me!           People will do anything, no matter how absurd, in order to avoid facing their own soul.   ~Carl Gustav Jung       		 Do you Yahoo!?   urlLink New and Improved Yahoo! Mail  - Send 10MB messages!
     

    
</post>
<date>02,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Maybe little things amuse me, but I am supposed to be able to UPDATE MY JOURNAL via EMAIL! I used to be journalling on  www.livejournal.com , but if THIS is the case... wow, I just need to change my blog!      I can't figure out how to get my journal there transferred here. Can you say wah? I know you can!        People will do anything, no matter how absurd, in order to avoid facing their own soul.   ~Carl Gustav Jung       		 Do you Yahoo!?   urlLink New and Improved Yahoo! Mail  - 100MB free storage!
     

    
</post>
</Blog>