<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    roseanna is a sailor   
      
</post>
<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        urlLink   
</post>
<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      when i sleep i allow these visions of you to surround me, memories. i like to remember life in your arms, you always feel like home.. no matter how long or how far.. you'll always feel like home to me.. comfort in honesty.. comfort in you and me.. i sleep and i allow myself to remember you here with me.. i know i do, because i wake up and i always remember my dreams, however obscure they may seem. as long as some trace of you is there with me, my dreams stick inside my memories. memories of you feel like home.. you feel like home.. maybe one of these days.. i'll be home.  - a piece of you is here with me..
      
</post>
<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      amanda has me watching futurama..  highly entertained.. but i'm completely tired.. so i am going to go to bed.. i love you all.. not.
      
</post>
<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       i fucked up,  i used the wrong perfume, no matter what i do, it reminds me of all the time i spent with you. can you still smell that perfume on your sheets? if not, do you miss it, do you miss me? well regaurdless i'd miss it being there to comfort you. you know it did, because you know i do.
      
</post>
<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      This is a lie: I Never Have Been Drunk This is a lie: I Never Have Smoked Pot This is a lie: I Never Have Kissed A Member Of The Opposite Sex This is a lie: I Never Have Kissed A Member Of The Same Sex No, I Never Crashed A Friend's Car No, I Never Have Been To Japan This is a lie: I Never Rode In A Taxi No, I Never Had Anal Sex This is a lie:  I Never Have Been In Love No, I Never Have Had Sex In Public This is a lie: I Never Have Been Dumped No, I Never Done Cocaine This is a lie: I Never Shoplifted No,  I Never Have Been Fired This is a lie: I Never Been In A Fist Fight No, I Never Had group intercourse  This is a lie: I Never Snuck Out Of My Parent's House This is a lie: I Never Have Been Tied Up No, I Never Have Been Caught Masturbating  This is a lie: I Never Pissed On Myself No,  I Never Had Sex With A Member Of The Same Sex No, I Never Been Arrested This is a lie: I Never Made Out With A Stranger No, I Never Stole Something From My Job No, I Never Celebrated New Years In Time Square No, I Never Went On A Blind Date This is a lie: I Never Lied To A Friend No, I Never Had A Crush On A Teacher No, I Never Celebrated Mardi-Gras In New Orleans No, I Never Been To Europe This is a lie: I Never Skipped School No, I Never Slept With A Co-Worker No, I Never Cut Myself On Purpose No, I Never Had Sex At The Office No, I Never Have Been Married No, I Never Have Been Divorced No, I Never Had Sex With More Than One Person Within The Same Week No, I Never Had Sex With More Than One Person Within The Same night No, I Never Have Posed Nude This is a lie: I Never Got Someone Drunk Just To Have Sex With Them  No, I Never Have Killed Anyone No, I Never Received Scars From My Sex Partner No, I Have Never Thrown Up In A Bar  This is a lie: I Have Never Purposely Set A Part Of Myself On Fire This is a lie: I Have Never Eaten Sushi No, I Have Never Been Snowboarding This is a lie: I Have Never Had Sex At A Friend's House While They Were Throwing A Party No, I Have Never Had Sex In A Dressing Room No, I Have Never Purchased Pornography  This is a lie: I Have Never Flashed Anyone This is a lie: I Have Never Hooked Up with a Friend's Sibling 
      
</post>
<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       wow. bored. crack. went to class. and i'm FUCKING aggrivated now. yeah that's right, i'm FUCKING cursing because it's so much bullSHIT, oh yeah, i'm getting FUCKING yelled at for stupid SHIT because my stepdad is an ASSHOLE. apparently i curse too much. how about them MOTHER FUCKINGapples.   oh well. my parents are trying to use super stalker skills on my brother, and they want me to like be a FUCKing pawn in it, it's FUCKing ridiculous. b/c he goes to "work" but he is never parked there, and he doesn't ever wear his work clothes and he is never like dirty like a mechanic should be, and if he is getting dressed at work, why doesn't he ever have dirty laundry? whatever i could give two SHITs less about wether or not his stupidASS has a job, he is just being fucking retarded now, and i'm so sick of hearing about it every god DAMN day. and i'm sick of having to call him to basically lie to him, they wanted me to call him and be like, where are you? i need a ride, i'm stranded. so what if he said yes, i wasn't even at the school anymore. so i would be basically selling him out, and thats just FUCKed up. fuck them, just give up on him already, what do they want me to tell them? blah.    i feel very not loved lately, and i better not hear anySHIT from anyone on this, it's just how i feel, i know people love me and all that fun stuff... but whatever, it's not even worth writing down. feelings change. people change too.    i wrote some fun poetry in class today. wanna see? of course you do.     Never Cold. 7/27   i'm almost sure my body's sleeping.  closed off to the world; hibernating.  you try to say i'm cold, but my body's not shaking.  i am not shaken  i am not afraid.  the heat i am keeping penetrated your bones  while you were there sleeping with me in your arms.  that love kept us warm. but this hate boils my blood.  so now that i'm hiding, you think that i'm cold.  little do you know my heart beats so fast that it  boils my blood  i'll never be cold again. - christine.    I Lived (in your arms) 7/27    you thought that you were the one keeping me warm.  all those nights i lived in your arms.  we were always so close but we kept ourselves so far.  you never accepted that i was still living while we were apart.  thought i could never be warm without you there.  what a way to show how much you cared. (that much faith in me?)  leave me here see if i can still feel.  with my heart in your hands, you poked and prodded,  but never breaking it again.  saying how you would never leave me to be cold.    keep my heart warm in your hands, or    please reintroduce it to this hold in my chest.   - christine.     yeah, i wrote the first one out of boredom. and then when i read it i felt like contradicting myself partially. emotionally monogamous with a sentimental overdrive and a habit to hold old grudges just as long asi hold onto everything else. and we all know, i have a big problem with temptation, expectation, and letting go. - i don't know what to sign these things anymore. so i guess i won't.       the one thing that i'll never get is how you turned out like all the rest, but i can take it, i can take it.      
</post>
<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      so today i went to school, went to the doctor, tore apart my house looking for my social security card, found my cell phone, went to the school, got my working papers, went to pathmark, applied for a job, went to roseannas, went in her neighbors pool, ate dinner, came home, got dressed, went to old navy, went to lisas, ate some cake, borrowed some movies, came home, got pissed off b/c my computer was being an asshole, cleaned my room, started my laundry, went downstairs to go thru all of my stuff and throw as much as i could away, filled 2 garbage bags, that both wound up breaking because they were so full, got all of my other shit in boxes and brought it up here, cleaned all the rose petals and stupid shit off the floor of the basement, changed over my laundry, turned the power back on for my computer, sat down, and now im taking a breath before i go fold my laundry, do the dishes, shower, lay down, watch a movie and go to sleep. i'm too tired to even finish doing shit, but i'm too tired to get in trouble so i'm just gonna make myself do it, tomorrow i'm gonna go thru my shit and try and figure out what i'm putting back on my walls and shit, because yeah, i don't even know anymore..  well i need to go, before i pass out, i love you fireflies,  you are my sunshine..over, over again.  -christine.    if only i had one more chance to change my life today then i would never let you go all my friends keep telling me that i should leave you for a while so you must show your love to me and tell me what you feel i thought that even you had feelings for me too i know i was wrong and baby when you care, then i will be there by your side and now i stand here alone in the dark without you there's nothing more that i would like than be with you  i close my eyes but i can't stop thinking of you  and now i stand here alone in the dark without you..   
      
</post>
<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    isn't cindala so perty? lt;3 urlLink    
      
</post>
<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       i think too much for my own good. on any general topic that i think about. today i decided i want to go to puerto rico for 2 months.. more i think about it, next summer isn't the right time.. too much other things to get done... i need to get so much done for Canada       m'aimer por qui je suis.    - love me for who i am.    
      
</post>
<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       I hope that you missed me   I'm glad that you kissed me   I'll see you again when I die  know that I missed you  know that I'll kiss you  Whenever an angel flies by..  Crazy in bathtubs  Those  innocent  backrubs..  I know its confusing,  I know its amusing..  We walk, we find  I dance by your inner mind     I just want to thank you  The pain made me stronger  The artist is what I will stay      Know I'll forgive you  Hope I'll outlive you  I'm glad that you stood in my way   Want to thank you my friend  Want to thank you again  Want to thank you...     stage kiddos. stage.       
      
</post>
<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        a thousand  forevers  undone   one sentence  expands iteself  into this sea of  a thousand or more  forgotten forevers  with transparent eyes  for the shallowest of souls  and pain in the eyes of the  great ones left  when our memories play on repeat  yet negates everything you    (everything you see)   should remember about you and me  a thousand forevers undone   -whomever i choose to be.           
      
</post>
<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    oh jebus! urlLink    
      
</post>
<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
         i cant ever explain this feeling in my gut and why you leaving always leaves me in a rut i get stuck and every fucking time i start to wonder why i even bother to count the days when i think of it you might just be far away marking down the tally till you cant remember these days or even my face if i cant cry the tears because they wont come out does that mean that this body remembers what you are about and it really knows what the deal is this body has been keeping count of these things ive been taking for granted does it count how many tears ive shed how many were wasted it recalls the things you should have said it even remembers what you meant every time that i was gone in the head it could see thru my alcohol blurred vision to the reason why you would only approach me when i was stuck in a drunken daze stuck drunken and stuck the only thing i could need they wouldnt let me leave trying to and succeeding rebuilding this dependency this dependency that was slowly dying with that part of me you always had that way to know when my defenses were down they all always fall down so you could slip yourself back in and so you could always stay around youd never be forgotten in that defenseless mind state i could have never seen you left in the lost and found    I cant ever explain this feeling in my gut  why you leaving, always leaves me in a rut.  I get stuck. (every fucking time. )   I start to wonder why I bother  to count the days when I think of it,  you might just be far away marking down the tally  till you can¡¦t remember these days (my face)   if I cant cry the tears because they wont come out  does that mean that my body remembers what you are about  (really knows what the deal is?)  this body has been keeping count of these things  I¡¦ve been taking for granted (it counts)  how many tears I've shed (how many were wasted.)  it recalls the things you said (even remembers what you meant.)   every time that I was gone in the head,  it could see thru (my alcohol blurred vision)  to the reason why you would only approach me  when I was stuck in a drunken daze (stuck, drunken and stuck)      (--they wouldnt let me leave, it was the only thing i could need--)  (-the only thing I need, never let me leave-)  (the only thing could never need, they wouldn¡¥t let me leave)  trying to (and succeeding) rebuild this dependency  (this dependency) was slowly dying with that part of me   always had that way to know when my defenses were down, (all fall down)  so you could slip yourself back in (so you could always stay around.)  you'd never be forgotten. (left in the lost and found)       one sentence, expands itself into a thousand forgotten forevers. your memory plays on repeat, yet negates everything you should remember about you and me.        -whomever i choose to be.              
      
</post>
<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    
      
</post>
<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        me : i realize you need not my advice just my love. you know you have that. what do i give away now? what do you do when there is nothing left to process package and send away?   lisa : wrap up truth in denial. it leaves something to reveal. rip thru the layers of half-lies because  honesty only means something when it's given as a gift , not as an expectation.  me : a sucker for words, silence means more than expectations. over time you learn that eyes lie. crying doesn't count if you can't look at me while you do it.  deviate the emotion, be somebody else.   lisa : somebody is still something. there will always be something to cry about. the ultimate goal is to be nothing with  nothing left worth the tears.   me : nothing is impossible. impossible is nothing. the  same thing  is the  wrong thing . the wrong thing is nothing. yet it is everything.  lisa : everything turns to nothing. this is the great cliche of living. if silence is golden, give me bronze instead.  i'd rather hear you speak the lies than find them hiding in your eyes .  me : who needs to hear the lies? when you look at me you know they're there. you can feel them when i look away from you. you feel the hidden meaning.  the reason i'm lying . you feel my love for you.  lisa :what i feel is chemical reaction. seratonin. estrogen. testosterone. love is a mating ritual void of meaning. we are not hearing the lies,   we are the lies.  we are not looking for truth.  we are looking for a reason to reproduce.   -- i only let her have the last word because it was the end of the page. that cunt went a fucked up the entire mood.  on purpose  hah.. we are psychos. it took us like 3 weeks to do that. good job us. i like it tho, i bolded the things that stand out most to me. too much fun. 
      
</post>
<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    emo emo emo.. you know you are emo lisa. get over yourself and admit it. join the cult, haha. urlLink    
      
</post>
<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
         and it's just about time for me to get off this roller coaster, there is only so many times that those last couple loops seem to meet your expectations.. after a while there is no surprise in the circling, upside down, going so fast that life seems to fade feeling. the same thing will only get a reaction a certain amount of times.. that last loop before you start all over again.. it's just not intriguing anymore.. it was always worth it.. but it's not good to regurgitate allyour memories because of the loops, whorls and speed that this roller coaster brings.     - - then the person on the loud speaker at the theme park, who has been acting as god the enitre time, stopping and starting the ride whenever they have please has just announced as i perpared to get off:   next stop, stability.           now i just have to fight that temptation to get back on the ride the one last time before i leave the park..        --hope.         life used to be so much easier when..  good-bye only meant till tomorrow  and the fun went on forever..         
      
</post>
<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink     darlink sunshine.. roller coaster accomplice. urlLink      
      
</post>
<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       and that's just it. the grey point. the spot where you got torn right down your fucking middle. the point where you were so  happy  but you wanted  to be hysterical . the point where your logical side tells itself it's being irrational, and that irrational tendancy is  the only thing that feels right.  you want to use some stupid quote to define yourself. and then you look at everything you have saved and realize you have never ever felt like this before. it's good and it's bad. and it's just everything, and nothing at the same time. it's just a figment of your imagination. some big imaginary joke you play on yourself. and then every word you hear out of other peoples mouths makes your mind regurgitate these memories and you want to laugh and you want to cry and you want to forget it all but never let it go at the same time. you want to give everything while fighting yourself to hold back that one comment you have to say. censor yourself while blowing up the world. yeah thats it, thats the point... the spot i'm at.      whew. uhm, sorry to anyone who just read that.. stream of chaos.. it's all good it's all wrong. i have been massively neglecting this journal, and i guess this is why, because i can't write coherent sentences about these boring days without going off on these tangents and it seeming like i am on a one track mind. maybe i am. shut up. i think about things that are outside of my head. just not often. shush. i can tell what you are thinking. stop contradicting me. eh, fuck it.       i miss you sunshine.    i am listening to the nutcracker. i hate the world. no i don't. what the fuck am i thinking out loudfor still?? lisa says she sounds like a manic depressive psycho..i think we both do. i wonder if you can adopt imaginary friends. i need one. oh god. i'm gonna stop now.      -if i told you this was killing me, would you stop?  
      
</post>
<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    there are places and there are opportunities (with shopping carts in mind..) urlLink   
      
</post>
<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      well.. i have not been writing like i should, maybe because then i have to face myself. and analyze how i feel, or because i am completely lazy. probably both. i am bored out of my mind and all i want to do is go to sleep, but my mom is napping in my bed.     ..just because you have ripped off your rearview   it doesn't mean what you've been running   from has dissapeared..    oh well, i guess i am done rambling for now, i will try and update soon,  i promise firefly. i love you. christine. 
      
</post>
<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    look at these batches... thats stella *the spanish midget batch* and megan my favorite skank! stella says to let yall know that sometimes they whore themselves out and her number is... jk.   
      
</post>
<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      wow, waiting is quite boring. i'm such a girl. prissy prissy ipsy pipsy. haha. freak. i'm insanely bored waiting for lisa to come pick my ass up. i've been getting ready for hours now. i do not believe i can do ne thing else. my entire house is clean and if i play with my hair ne more i think it might fall out. oh the crazy shit i do out of boredom.   if i go crazy then will you still call me superman?    oh well i need to stop this.  peace out fireflies.     Christine. 
      
</post>
<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    awe, whos the cutest of them all? lol   
      
</post>
<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    so much crack lol. urlLink   
      
</post>
<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    awe.   
      
</post>
<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    beer pong with eddies dad. urlLink   
      
</post>
<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    this isn't all mine, but it's dedicated   
      
</post>
<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      i do not really know what my problem is or why i am so deeply moved by a quote from a childrens movie. i can't help it i suppose. i miss thinking in clear coherent streams of consciousness. i guess i do not like other peoples points of view today. i think that what that person said, was a negative conclusion on a person they have only met a few times, and have heard many conversations about. i don't think they should have such an opinion, but at the same time i see how they are just trying to look out for me. but it hurt. i think you should not judge that other person yet, because from all that i know about the both of you, you are almost exactly the same. so maybe you see yourself in this person, maybe you don't like the person you see in the mirror.   No. No, you can't...  STOP.  Please don't go away. Please? No one's ever stuck with me for so long before. And if you leave... if you leave... I just, I remember things better with you. I do, look. P. Sherman, forty-two... forty-two... I remember it, I do.  It's there, I know it is, because when I look at you, I can feel it. And-and I look at you, and I... and I'm home.   Please... I don't want that to go away. I don't want to forget.     i understand that your worst is beating the hell out of my best but i can take it, i can take it.  -- forever and always --        Christine... 
      
</post>
<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    i'm so vain.. I   
      
</post>
<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    I   
      
</post>
<date>05,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       every morning that i wake up it still feels like the morning after..  what a roller coaster i play around on.. it's all good, it's all wrong. you can't get through it, you can't get over it. you can't get around. it's like in a dream when you open your mouth to scream and you can't make a sound. you are going down. you are the only one who isn't afraid to keep hugging me when i'm not ready to let go yet. there is nothing like looking at your own history in the faces of your friends. i took that second look, i guess i'm an open book. i didn't intend to hold onto you that long, but i noticed  i wasn't the only one hanging on.  love conquers all. every cloud has a silver lining. faith can move mountains. love will always find a way. everything happens for a reason. where there is life, there is hope. i mean they have to tell you something don't they? i've got all these excuses but i don't have an answer, because your always innocent,  because you're never honest.  it's hard to keep my balance when you look the other way so i'm letting go with every breath I take. so many reasons, i need something more to believe in. the time has come to turn and walk away. through all these changes, mistakes, there was time but now its too late. some things are better stressed when unexpressed, cause silence can be overwhelming. we'll find some way that we can prove you wrong.  i should've known that you were a killer, but now i'm dead.   so what now? - Christine.
      
</post>
<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       urlLink    see, we tried.. haha. asshole. urlLink   
      
</post>
<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Tommy: ... that fucking german bastard..  Me and Kimi: Tommy? you just called spanish german. Tommy: holy shit, that fucking german spanish bastard.  made my night. i love it.  happy 4th of July fireflies..   don't wake me i plan on sleeping in..    goodnight lovely.  i had the picture of sunshine above this but i felt bad.. poor kid and my blackmail potential photography. </post></Blog>