<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       "Like memories of yesterday..."   Outkast, 13th Floor, ATLiens   If my high school had it together and actually was organized with its alumni, or, more importantly, if my high school was old enough to be having reunions, we possibly would have hada 5 year reunion last May. But, our first graduating class was in 1996 so two more years and we'll see if they really know how to keep in touch. Anyways, I have to say that this past week I've managed to talk to everyone in my crew from Edmond Santa Fe High School, which to some people is nothing less than amazing but to me that's the way it is. My philosophy is that if you were really true to your friends and tight with them, you can pick up the phone and yall still will be good 5 years later. But honestly, my crew was tight anyways. =) We're repping Oklahoma in Oakland, Memphis, Nashville, and PG County, but we know how to stay in touch. If you can't say the same for your peeps, sorry for ya!  Another thing about growing old(er) is realizing that in less than two months, I will be 24. Oh, that looks really ugly all typed out, but that's the truth. I'm a 1980 baby. And 24 is only one year away from 25, and that means that when I'm at the club and the DJ goes "For all my grown and sexy people, where you at? 25 and older make some noise!" I'ma be one of those old bamas. It's all good to be 23 cause sometimes the DJ will shout out the 23 and over crew, which is more legitimate to me than being part of the 21 and over crew (you're still fresh and wet behind the ears). Oh boy. But 24. Hmm. I might have to start my own business called 24 Forever and shop there- lots of business, business casual stuff with the occasional short skirt to make me feel young again. lol. OK, I'm not old yet, but give me a month or so....  And with that said SEPTEMBER 14TH PEOPLE GET IT RIGHT IT'S GOING DOWN! I accept personal checks, money orders, prizes, gear, and cash (uh, I've been listening to too much WPGC). So start saving up now! That gives you like 5 pay periods, so be creative. Hmm, I'm feeling better about this getting old(er) thing already... 
    
</post>
<date>03,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I said, um, mirror mirror on the wall Who is the top choice of them all There was a rubble dubble, five minutes it lasted The mirror said you are you conceited bastard ~Slick Rick, La-Di-Da-Di   Whattup people, this is my first posting on the blog (as you can tell) but no worries, I will definitely keep it fresh for you.  Everday there's always a new story to tell or thought to flesh out, and this is just the beginning.  So sit back and relax, I know ya love me and all my stories or else you wouldn't be reading this.  So as I reflect on life and human behavior (I'm sure there will be more than one Metro story to tell- gotta love DC), let it marinate for a while and hit me up w/ur thoughts if you feel so compelled.
    
</post>
</Blog>