<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      So much has happened in the last couple of weeks. Ineed to post more often - I suck.   I've been recovering from the worst vacation EVER! I really thought I was finally going to be able to spend time bonding with Linda without that fucking cell phone. I thought I was going to be able to finally convince her that I am the one she wants to spend her life with! I picked her up at the airport a week ago today. I showed her my Charleston. We had a good day. But that damn cell phone meant doom for us from the start. She just had to call Elaine and tell her she arrived safe and sound. I told her from the beginning to tell Elaine the truth - that she was coming to Charleston to be with me.   It's no secret that there's something between me and Linda. She should have told her... but instead she told her that she was in Florida visiting a friend. Elaine, being no dummy, called work and found out that I was out of town, did a little detective work and realized that Linda was with me. When they spoke, Elaine told Linda that if she wants any part of that relationship that she would be home the following day. So, what does Linda do? She makes love to me in the hotel, has dinner with me, Mom and friends and the following morning she tells me that she has to leave. I am still shocked at the cowardice and pissed that she can't stand up for what she wants. She left me in Charleston. She fucking left me.  My initial reaction was shock. I couldn't even speak when she was telling me that she was leaving. I just could not believe it. Why did she come in the first place? I was so pissed that I shared that part of my life with her. When I left Charleston last October I left many demons and all the bad things that happened to me while living there. Now I will be faced with the ghost of Linda whenever I go back. I showed her my favorite places and I will think of her each time I go there and of how she left me. The only thing I am happy about is that I didn't bring her to Morris Island. I still have that.  After crying back and forth for a couple of hours I took her to the airport and dropped her off. In the hotel I made her say that she has more desire to be with Elaine than with me. She said it verbatim. I also made her say that she wants to try to work things out with Elaine. She said that too. I needed to hear it from her lips... from her mouth. She said it clear as day. I told her that if she walks out that hotel room, that car... it's over. And she did. She walked out of the hotel, out of the car. She actually tried to hug and kiss me. She told me that she loved me. I couldn't even look at her so I stared out the driver window. When she got out of the car I watched her walk into the airport and I cried. My heart was broken. She left me in Charleston.  I went to my Mom's house because I had to wake her up for Traci. Seeing Mom was the last thing I wanted to do. Of course her first words were "Where's Linda?" and I briefly explained that she went back to St. Louis. Mom wanted all of the details, but as always I never tell her any. I took a nap since I was mentally and physically exhausted from the crying. After an hour or so I went back to the hotel - I might as well stay there since I paid for it. I grabbed something to eat since I hadn't eaten but it stayed on the table all night... uneaten. I was nauseated and so tired. I called her a couple of times to see if she was still in  my  city. She told me that she didn't go past security in case I came back to see her. Was she crazy or something? She just left me to go back to her girlfriend and wanted me to come watch her leave me... again. Totally fucked up.  All this happened Friday and we were supposed to drive back to St. Louis on Saturday. In the hotel I told her that as soon as she got back to work I wanted a transfer out of her department because I could not stand to look at her every day. Well, Saturday morning I had a change of heart. Why should I make it easy for her and Elaine? I went to the market and called her from the car and told her that I didn't want to transfer out of her department. I wanted her to be forced to look at me every day and think about what she had done to me. I knew it would be hard on me, but I really wanted her to pay. More importantly, I wanted Elaine to know that I wasn't going anywhere and that I would be in Linda's face every day. I was feeling a little bitchy.  It only took me 11 hours to drive home from Charleston - a new record for me. On the way I thought non-stop about Linda... about the last four months, the last three days... I made little notes while driving about things I wanted to say to her. I was softening up and I knew I was weakening. Will power is not my strength. When I got home one of the first things I did was write a letter to her. I had this fabulous plan. I told Linda that I wanted Monday off to get myself together and to have time to put all of the crap I brought back with me away. In my retarded mind I was actually planning on going to work. I knew that she wouldn't have mentally prepared to see me and she would be caught off guard. I would give her my fabulous letter and torture her with my presence all day. Well... I did surprise her, I think... I gave her my letter and by lunchtime I was jelly. Totally weak. I have this little problem of melting when I see her. My heart beats fast and I lose focus. Her blue eyes pierce right through me. We ended up in the "spank me" room by the end of the day... with just enough time before Elaine picked her up from work (she's on lock-down!)  Sooooooo... yes, I am weak. I love her.  I took yesterday off since Traci was coming through town from Washington State. We picked up Denise and drove over and met Linda for lunch. It was her first time meeting Denise and Traci. Kind of strange with the sequence of the weeks events and now we are all having lunch. It's pretty messed up. While driving to work today I was having Linda withdrawls. I need to be withher soon -It's been a week and I am dying. I was tortured all day at work because when I called her this morning I was talking dirty, which is so unlike me! I don't know why I started doing this... I never used to - it just feels natural with her. I had a bad day today since I could not stop thinking about what happened last week. All I want is validation. I want her to tell Elaine how strongly she feels about me - or at least says she does. I can't believe that they still have not talked about what happened last week. How crazy is that? That is just NOT NORMAL!  So, today I knew that Linda was carpooling again with Elaine (still on lock-down) and I also know that Elaine picks her up between 4:45and 5:00... Well, it really wasn't a coincidence that I left at 5:00, just before Linda left. I must confess. I knew that she'd be out there waiting for Linda. I had not seen Elaine since Jump, Little Children. I saw her before I even walked out the door. She was parked facing the building, facing me. When I walked out the door I didn't look at her right away, but I could feel her eyes throwing daggers. When I crossed the parking lot I looked over at her and we locked eyes - she looked away and pretended to read the paper. I kept looking all the way to my car and she looked again. It felt good for some fucked up reason. I didn't want to be mean, but I wanted her to know that I am still around and I am one fighting bitch and I will not give up! I love Linda and I will notgive up. 
     

        
</post>
<date>04,July,2004</date>
<post>


           
      When I woke up I had no intention of doing anything for the Fourth of July, but as I started thinking more and more about it, I changed my mind.  I called Denise to find out what the plan was for the day and what time they were going to Fair St. Louis.  She told me that she would call me back.  I assumed that she was on the other line.  I went about my business and did laundry, cleaned the house and called her about 3:30.  It was getting late and I wanted to know what was up.  There was no answer so I left a message and then took a shower.  Still no call from Denise.  I was pretty sad about that, considering recent events in our relationship.    At that point, I gave up on the Fourth.  Linda called me and did a one-ringer so that made me even sadder.  I knew that she was out enjoying the day with Elaine and I was sick to my stomach thinking about that.  I try to be positive and not think about them doing things together, but I can't help it - they are ALWAYS together!  I made it a point to forget that it was the Fourth of July.  Traci called and we talked for a while about her new house.  I LOVE moving!  I suppose it comes from the million moves that I did growing up.  It's not the actual packing and manual labor/heavy lifting part that I like...  I just enjoy unpacking and re-discovering my belongings.  I have been in Illinois for 10 months and I have already forgotten what I left in Charleston.  It will be interesing going through all the boxes and finding things I have forgotten.  I also enjoy setting a new house up and making it a "home".  It's funny that I have never felt that way about my current apartment.  I don't really feel that this is a true representation of me.  Most of the stuff in it isn't even mine!  Things will change someday soon I hope.  Becky called a little later and we spoke for a while - Mostly about Linda.  I am still a little weary about my relationship with Linda.  I try to keep positive about it, but I am a realist and can't deny having doubts about her intentions.  I think it's interesting that Both Traci and Becky brought up the point that Linda may have doubts about leaving Elaine and that is why she is taking her time with moving out and moving on.  I cannot even begin to explain how that makes me feel inside.  I feel it in the pit of my stomach.  I have once again given myself completely to someone without them giving themselves completely to me.  You'd think I would have learned my lesson...
     

        
</post>
</Blog>