<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        I love music. In particular, Christian. But if you REALLY want to get particular, I love Third Day. Their brand of music varies from rock to Church hymns. If you've never heard Third Day, you are really missing out on some beautiful lyrics.     One song that I love the most is called Consuming Fire. It calls on the Holy Spirit to rescue this poor being from the pit of darkness and death. When I hear the song, I can just picture this person, arms outstretched, consumed in a burning flame. The body is scorched black. But right in the center is a lightsobrilliant and so intense, that the flames pale in comparison. In all the pain, and flame, and vivid brilliance, that body becomes mine, and I feel the flames of the Holy Spirit upon me, burning, healing, and I feel my body become unblemished, spotless, immaculate.     That's how I picture the Holy Spirit. It consumes you, it permeates your very being; but instead of staying with you, it bursts through you to consume others.     We are merely the embers that catch others aflame.         Until Next Time,    Annalise       
     

    
</post>
<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I write these to no one in particular. Who will see them? Only time and comments will tell. For now, I take pleasure in my anonymity. For when no one knows you write, you can expose your soul.    In exposing my own, I find its colors swirl together like a vast unexplored universe; darkness as well as light. Sometimes the darkness overshadows the light. I pray that it does not happen often. We are all creatures drawn to the darkness of sin at one time or another in our lives. Sometimes it matters not if we pray. Sometimes we pray, but our words are empty, meaningless. Either way, we must have faith in the words which reach the heavens.    Faith. Simple enough in its calling. Such a beautiful word.....the topic of many conversations, tagged to many given names. Yet, just below that simple surface lies a pool of doubt; of fear. For faith itself demands so much from us. It requires that we close our eyes and fall backwards, not really knowing who is behind to catch us. It is the hardest step known to us. But when we finally give in to our doubts, our fears, and close our eyes, and let ourselves fall.....then, my friends, do we see clearly the wonderful, powerful Love that is God.    God is many things to the ones who fall backwards, and nothing to those who don't. God cannot be in your life if you do not let Him in. He is a very courteous God, not stepping in where He is not wanted. God made us to have our own thoughts, our own emotions....if He hadn't, we would all look and sound and feel and react the same. What fun is that? He gives us the wonderful gift of choice. We can choose how our lives will be. We can choose what path we want to take. It is our choice. He gathers up dust, and breathes us into being, and sets us on our way. Being poor dumb animals that we are, we sometimes choose the wrong path and find ourselves where we do not want to be. And still we have a choice. We can be hardheaded and choose to make it on our own, or we can call on the One who loves us beyond our reasoning to put us on the right path again.    God created us in His own image. That means He looks just like me. He looks just like you. He looks just like the person you love the most in the world, and also the one person you hate most in the world. God is in everyone. If we can all just realize that, we would be a lot better off. How can you hate God? How can you kill God? How can you cheat, or ignore, or starve God? We are put on this earth for two things: to love and to serve God and our neighbor. It's that simple. Yet why is it the hardest thing in the world for us to do? Why can't we see the man who is blind and poor and out on the street? Why can't we see the child whose parents abhor? Why can't we see the hungry, the thirsty, the naked, the homeless, the imprisoned, the sick and the dying? "I do see them," we say. Yeah? Then why are they still there?    While God looks like all of us, so, too, do we look like Him. And He is perfect. So that means we have the ability to be perfect, also. Now, I don't know how that affects you, but it scares the hell outta me. How can I possibly be perfect, when my life is so screwed up?!?!?! BY HAVING FAITH THAT GOD CAN STRAIGHTEN ME UP AND SEND ME ON THE RIGHT PATH. So simple, yet so unbelievably hard.    I guess this is too much to post on the debut of my blog, so I will just say for now that I get a little weird when I allow my thoughts to escape onto paper......or space, as it were......    Until next time,  Annalise  
     

    
</post>
</Blog>