<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>06,julio,2004</date>
<post>

     
       After cleaning yesterday, we went to Bed, Bath, and Beyond, where we ended up purchasing a whopping  three hundred seventy eight dollars .  We got some fancy sheet sets and bedspreads for our extra long twin beds.  Hermax called this morning and woke me up.  It's kool though.  But ya it sucks because he's going to Disneyland with his cousins tomorrow...and I'm going with his brother and roselle and my mom and our guests on Friday.  How gay.  We're going to the same place except at  different times .  Oh well.  Every time I talk with Hermie on the phone, it's so  awkward .  When we say goodbye, I want to tell him  I love him  so bad but its so hard for me.  I tried to think of why I'm like that.  I came to the conclusion that I am subliminally terrified of how he would react...  It's funny because I'm so  sure  of my love for him.  I know that I love him and that he loves me.  And I look at other people who  claim  they're in love but it's obvious that they aren't.  I think he has the same problem as I do.  We want to say it but it's so hard.  Every time we hang up, I always say to myself that next time we talk, I'm really going to say "I love you."  And I always  chicken ut  at the last minute.  I mean, it's not like we haven't told each other before.  Oh well.  I just wish I could verbally reassure him of how I feel.  Guess where I'm going tonight?   Drew's  house for choir practice.  Everyone knows what happened between us (the whole cussing me out thing) but he acts as if none of it ever happened.  I don't really give a shit anymore.  And plus, as much as he annoys us, I must admit that I  miss  having him around.  Everyone konws that I'm NOT the kind of person to walk away from a friendship, no matter what went wrong.  Jenny Qin reminded me that friendship is  also  about accepting one another's flaws  .            flooble said that I am
</post>
<date>06,julio,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Vacuuming . Laundry . Dusting . Bed Sheets . et cetera.  Today is a day of  cleaning .  That's basically all I've been doing since I woke up at nine thirty this morning.  My mom used to work with extraordinarily  prominent  women when she lived in the Philippines about sixteen years ago.  These women have kept in touch with her over the years, even with the Pacific Ocean between them ( literally ).  So now that these ladies have retired, and with much money at that, they have decided to come here to  America  for the first time.  Naturally, my mom and I are their primary hosts, as they do not wish to travel all the way to New York to be shown around by their very own relatives.  They are due to arrive at LAX  tomorrow , when we will pick them up.  Over the course of the next two  weeks , we will escort our guests to many well renowned places such as Disneyland, Catalina, and Universal Studios.  Tonight I will be attending a preliminary potluck meeting for my church's annual Children's Beach Camp.  There, we will discuss the following events:   Vintage Car Show/Mini Carnival (beach camp fundraiser) ~  Sunday July 18, after church in the parking lot.   Actual Beach Camp ~  only 2 days...Saturday and Sunday August 7-8 at Mother's Beach.   I have yet to decide what I will be bringing as my potluck dish.  Perhaps some  eggrolls   .  
     
    
</post>
<date>05,julio,2004</date>
<post>

     
      hey everyone.  i got tired of  xanga , and layouts, and stuff, so i'm trying out  blogspot .  i had one before but never did anything with it so i'll start anew.  don't have much to say now, so i'll just leave you be until something interesante comes along.    hasta luego.  
     
    
</post>
</Blog>