<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My teeth are falling out. They come out while eating. Sometimes, I bite down on them. The uppers come out first, which doesn't really bother me, I've been expecting this for years. My bottom gums unhinge. I try to speak but they stick to the roof of my mouth, blood comes spilling forth. I'm confused, I wake up, I don't know what's real. 
     

    
</post>
<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I do, I do it quite often, in fact I did it just now.  I even think that I can burp louder then you.  It's my secret.  I burp as loud as possible.   And to add to that I like shitting too.  Having a good shit in the morning really makes my day.  Pissing is also rather enjoyable.  I'm an old-fashioned type of girl, I like to go in the woods and behind trees.  Some people like to visit waterfalls because they are beautiful, not me, I go cause it feels better to go there.   
     

    
</post>
<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I got mistaken for a high schooler today.  So, although my personality has soured and gone bitter with age, my face hasn't.  I guess all those years hiding from the sun in the basement are starting to pay off.   I laugh at the sun-bathers, with their attractive tans and carefree attitudes.  They will never get mistaken for a mature teenager when they are in their 20's.  And they will probably never read my blogs. 
     

    
</post>
<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      No work today. Must watch Roar. Marathon. Heath ledger before balding. *drools*     
     

    
</post>
<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Why is everyone else a moron?    Then I think  I'm a moron too.   And then I think  I should write this down.      
     

    
</post>
<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The first guy that I told that I loved had been my best friend and more for 5 years. He took my virginity soon thereafter and never spoke to me again.   The second, was his replacement. I had known him for 10 years, he was the dork next door. I rushed into him. The director and the artist, we ignited each other. Men don't like what they can't control. He didn't think I would be anything in life, and I believed in him. How wrong we were. I am glad he has gone bald.   I got the third guy on psych medication. We were together for about a year and for the first 6 months we were inseparable. He took care of me and I him. He suffered frompost traumatic stress following a stint in the airforce. He taught me that it doesn't matter if people like you, only that they respect you. After 6 months he told me that he loved me and I hadto say it back, or elsehesaid he would leave. That was the one and only time I ever used that wordaround him.He got comfortable in the relationship at that point, and he changed.Onone occasion he told me that if he were to kill himself, he would take as many people with him as possible."Including me?" I responded. Only silence followed. He also indicated to me that us breaking up would be bad for his mental health. Former police officers with sociopathic tendencies do not make good bed fellows. I stayed with him until he was able to let go of me.   The fourth man, has thus far been the love of my life. I used to feel my heart beating when I was around him. He liked that he couldn't predict me, but I frustrated him by being uncontrollable. I still wish I was with him, or at least that I knew him. After we broke up I knew that I wouldn't fall in love again for atleast2 and a half years, its been 2 and a quarter.   The fifth and final was my last boyfriend, the cheating cheap whore. I knew after our first date that I couldn't fall in love with him, but that was the point. He pursued me like no one else before. I didn't even know his phone number until we had been together for 3 months. It felt so good, so easy. He was upset one day, commiserating over his worthlessness, and I told him that I loved him (withthe "not in'disclaimer, of course) and I really felt it. I was in recovery the whole time, trying to fix the lingering damage of the third and trying to forget thefourth. He knew that I would neverbe his and instead of leaving, he made sure thathe would never be mine. I found out that he was cheating, because she said she had fallen in love with him, andat aretardedpace I put the piecestogether. She really meant it. I think one day she thought s wallowing his love juicehas been avery meaningful experience. He wanted to get what he had given to me, unrequited adoration, and if that meant banging a fat slut, so be it. She says he broke her heart, he says I broke his, and I say they broke mine.     
     

    
</post>
<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I think about being in love quite often. How I was and I am no longer. The last time IsawErnest was a few months ago. He was standing outside the door of my apartment with a bum knee. I was late for class. We spoke briefly, he was awkward and stuttering which upset me. How could he be nervous?How could he have left if heever truly loved me? I had nothing to say, soI walked away. The first thing I did was call my boyfriend to tell him how much I loved him. He was at a meetingwith my ex-roommate. He had invited me to a movie, but I had so much work to do. I made a point that evening to get my work done early, so I could be with him. He had already made other plans. It was her birthday. It was odd that I was specifically not invited. I put up a bit of a fight. Our relationship was basically over at that point. He kept starting fights with me.Michael said I wasselfish for not respecting his friendship with her (an issue we had argued over since we got together).    I apoligized for overreacting and tried to explain myself. I told him what happened, he never apoligized, he only accused. When I walked away from Ernest I was upset, for the first time I wanted to be with my current boyfriend over Ernest. I thoughtwe had been together for over a year,Michael deserved my affections. So, I let my past go. For the first time in the two years since we had broken up, I felt okay about not being with him. I had finally found something else of meaning. It wasn't passionate, but it was consistent and well-meaning. I thought we improved each other, I thoughtit wassafe. I am a fool.   That was the last time Isaw my ex-boyfriend, and it will probably stay that way.If I had known, what Iknow now, I wouldn'thave let that be the last time. That's it though, it's over, no more dreams of passion, no desire to trust.Michaelruined mylife and changed me future. I think of Ernestoften.Less so, now thatI am single.WhileI was withMichael I always felt pained that Iwas in love with someone else. He always told me that I had changed hislife for the better and I thought that was enough. What I hold most dear in a relationship is fidelity, for him it was devotion. We destroyedthat which issacred in one another.   I got together withMichael to appease the pain. It took many months beforehe started appearing in my dreams. Hewormed his way in and then ate his way out.          
     

    
</post>
<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I think Alexa put it best: Anal food after Mexican, it's just a bad idea.     
     

    
</post>
<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm at a club, talking to some guy that is only interesting because we are already talking. Meeting someone else would require effort, and more alcohol then I can afford. My friends are canoodlingand I'm not drunk enough to find someone to dance with. Frank, I only remember his name because he put it on my cell phone and he's so high, that I've become, in his words "A great conversationalist".    The only thing I like more then picking menupis ignoring them, especially the attractive ones. It's probably not the best mating strategy, but I figure, as awoman I don't need one. My theoryis:their at a club, they know their good-lookingand their assholes. I'm at a club, I'm good-looking, and I'm an asshole too. And as a cocktease we don't really have much to do except turn each other on and help each other's forearms get stronger.      
     

    
</post>
<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I hung with an old friend, of the nearest and dearest variety. He regaled me with stories of his new life, how a phat blunt could unite the world and how coke is okay if beautiful, naked passed-out woman accompany. Then, of course, I ranted about my ex-boyfriend cheating on me and I showed off my new baby, internet revenge. And we laughed over a corn-cob bowl, in a dark backyard on a cul-de-sac that was double parked for parties that I wasn't invited to.       
     

    
</post>
<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yes, I have been thank you very much, and I fucked that up nice and proper.     
     

    
</post>
<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It's sunday. I woke up at 8 am. I went to bed at 6:30. I got home at 5:30. I was getting lost trying to find the GWB between 4 and 4:30. Pizza at 3 andway too many caffinated diet cokes at a Mexican bar.Abonfire around 11, shopping forhappinessbetween 8and10.Losingat aJapanese flashgame at 7,resulting in the loss of theGanguro girl.I learnedhow the London sewer came to be at 6, which is a vital skill to have in case I need to build one. I should not be sitting here with an old deafdog with a mohawk on my lap.      
     

    
</post>
<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I shaved my dogs yesterday in a most successful effort to answer the age old question "Why don't my dogs have mohawks?"  In doing so, I discovered that Princess (I didn't name the little rodents) has a circle in the center of her back.  I believe that all animals should have a bullseye.
     

    
</post>
<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I decided to take a nap at 9 pm last night, which wound up meaning 10 lovely hours of sleep. I was hoping for 11, but these yapping little assholes woke me up. So I think the insomnia might be coming to an end. Maybe outing my ex-boyfriend was cathartic. Sadly, or maybe obviously, no one think less of me for it.   There's this Ani quote that I use to live by,  "I'll walk the plank  I'll jump with a smile  If I'm gonna go down  I'm gonna do it in style"   By the end of my first year at college I had two police reports filed on me and one that I filed, because I was being threatened.   My suggestion to others is don't do like I do (you probably knew that already though).       
     

    
</post>
<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I played with children today and I did not try to make them cry. Although, I cursed more then I would have liked to with the 6 year old. He did not appreciate that I called him kid rather then his name but, as I see it it's a term of endearment that I use with strangers.      
     

    
</post>
<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      "You think your better then me?"    Dedicated to  urlLink Mike   
     

    
</post>
<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I used to date this guy who was supposedly a brilliant playwright. A raging alcoholic, with an ego that was surely overcompensating, for his um deficits(which are so profound that I must mention them in the plural). Nevertheless, I remember hearing how one drunken evening, in a powerful display of brawn, he took a flower pot and bashed it over his head. So his friend (the humble drug-dealer) took him to the hospital where he got 9 stiches, which he removed 15 minutes later. Last time I saw him was at a party at SUNY purchase, from which he has been banned for starting fights with the cops. When the party got broken up he "jumped" out the first floor window, to where the cops were waiting for him outside. I would assume he is either still an alcoholic who waits tables for a living, or he has gone to jail.   My fondest memory of him (cause you know I'm a sentimentalist):  In some kind of drunken stupor, we had the loudest sex imaginable (think porn with power-tools). The best part was that it was a Tuesday during finals week. Just pissing off my roommate that much made it worth it ( her name was Tomoko, rhymes with hot cocoa, a joke she seemed endlessly amused by.)   Sidenote: His penis was so small, that I am only assuming from inference that he had one.   (and I've seen him naked *shutters*)     
     

    
</post>
<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I used to date this guy who believed that cleaning the toilet humbled him. Last I heard he was a heroine addict who was banned from the state of Tennessee.    
     

    
</post>
<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I usually write in a journal at night when I can't sleep, but I am trying to go digital. This way when the government wants to know information about me they will have easy access (illusions of grandiousity, I know). Yes, that I what I want, to be an anonymous open book. That's about as satisfying as drunk dry-humping. No, I want an outlet, which maybe someone will care enough about to read and then give me unsolicited bad advice. It really is a dream come true.   Actually, I'm a collector who owns to much, keeps to much. I write constantly, and then I rarely read what I have written. This, in of itself bothers me. I can't get rid of anything unless I feel like I have exhausted it. So with my writing, the end goal, (from an obsessive stand point) is to gain some sort of self-awareness. I think, and maybe erroneously that a public eye will force me to look at myself more objectively. Because, really as I see it, my problem is that I can't classify myself. I, like most people, see myself through a lens of complexity that is unduly unfocused by undeveloped potential. (oh yeah, I like to use a lot of parenthesis(this is obnoxious(and I'm okay with that)))   Note: that's why I didn't get rid of him, I thought I still had something to learn. I think in the end, he thought I wanted to be with him to control him. He was wrong. (He searches for women(sadly a plural) to give him direction and then fears the control they exert over his life.) If anything, I want to discipline myself, and consistency cannot be forgotten to achieve regularity (yes, I did have fiber this morning). He was a continuity factor that I overrated, a lesson that I thought I had yet to learn, a lifestyle that I wanted to invade. And when his life is said and done, there will be very few who will care enough to remember him. There will be the women that he followed with seemingly complete devotion who have forgotten him like a bad melodrama and there will be his words, that fall onto empty seats as no one pays for the self-indulgence of another.     
     

    
</post>
<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      As I'm falling asleep I see a blurry vision. I am looking down at my body. I am wearing a white dress that flows to the floor.  urlLink My ex-boyfriend  is standing across from me. He stabs me in the chest with a pair of silver sewing scissors. The center, not the heart. That's when I reached for a glass of water, spilling it onto my pillow, my bed.   
     

    
</post>
<date>06,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So this is my first blog. Well now, it's 4 am, I have work in the morning and I am unfortunately awake. I just spilled water on my bed while reaching for a glass of water, so here I am. I have insomnia. Again. Every night that I don't work and don't go out with friends I can't sleep. The easy solution would seem to be to go out with friends, but at the moment I have only two in the area. One I saw last night and the other was working today. Other then that I am an intern and broke, so going out is not a regular thing at the moment. And, of course, I am a consummate loner.   I'm awake...................  I hate it.........................................  I can't stop thinking.......   So that's it, my life in a nutshell.     Why am I awake, you don't ask. Well, very plainly my boyfriend of the last year or so broke up with me back in April. In his oh so miserable tale, I was to be moving in June and leaving him. He just couldn't take being with me knowing I would be in Boston and him in New York. *sniffle* He let everyone now how I had broken his heart. For in his noble rendition of events he had offered to come move there with me, giving up job opportunities, leaving friends, family. He cried to anyone that would listen that he loved me so, he had been a good boyfriend, and I was off to play out some fantasy borne out of reading "On the Road".   Of course, he forgot to mention that for the last 4 months he had been carrying on an affair with my former  urlLink  roommate,  and former friend. Ouch, my ego.   So now I am awake.  Single and awake.    
     

    
</post>
</Blog>