<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Hellooo againnn.....Im soo boredd right now...u have NO idea haha. But today was a good day. My mom  i spent the day together. She took me to the doctors  then she had to take my lil bro into the doctors too. I swear my mom is lik Superwoman. She gets so much done in a day. Especially after she got back from Austria!! Thats crazyy haha. We then went to the grocery store  bought some food. Very Good food. I'm exciteddd to eat it haha. Well i found out that my dad is going to Austria for a week. He's leaving on Friday....I'm gonna miss him SOO muchh. He has to go to my great-grandmas funeral.=(       *ToMoRRoW*~My Aunt is coming in from Nevada...so we have to go pick her up. Shes coming in for my Cousin Monica's baby shower thats on Sunday.We are all going outtodinnerat night i thinkshes staying at our house...but who knos haha!A lot of my family is coming to that actually. I'm going too!! =) It should be a lot of fun actually.       *Sunday*~I gotz church....thennnnnnI have the baby shower...that will be all dayy. I get to see all da fam. I'm actually excited about that....weird?? I THINK SOOO haha. I wanna hang out with Amanda...but i dunno I hope she can.       This is baddd....im liking my best friend nowww this isnt goodd. GRR why mee seriouslyy haha. Why cant i like some1 that im NOT friendz with. Its soo much easier!! Hopefully this wont last longg. I hope it doesnt. We shall seeee =/      ThAtS ALL FoR NoW~       *Love u Alwayz*    *Mel*  
      
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       hello again. Well last night was really awesome. Seeing nirmal again was really cool. I missed that kidd haha.He even gave me a free sub. It was really cool. His mom is soo nice. I walked in  she was like "HI Melissa!!" I luv hismom!! hehe!! I saw Angela last night...which was unexpectedd. We all watched Punch Drunk Love...thats a WEIRD ass moviee dude!! lol I was confusedd. Then Amanda called...i luv that girllll Then i dropped AnGeLa off  we talked in the car. WHAT A TALK haha Then i went back to Nihars  chilled with the guys. They were playing this Basketball game on PS2. It was funny. I really liked it. Then i had to take Darshan home. He was driving...well sort of haha. He took the wheel a few times. Hes a good driver. He gets the Mel Approval haha. Then i went home at like 11:30 when i was supposed to get home at 11 haha. But my mom didnt care, so its all good.Well thats all for now. I just wanted to put this song up. My friend Sammyyy (Sam) wrote it. So i decided to put it in here!! =)       Lately I've been feeling low A remedy is what I'm seeking I take a taste of what's below Come away to something better What I want is what I've not got But what I need is all around me I reach and search and never stop And I'll say...      If you could keep me floating just for a while 'Til I get to the end of this tunnel called... brother If you could keep me floating just for a whileI'll get back to you      Well, sometimes a Jimi Thing Slides my way and keeps me swinging I'd like to show you what's inside Yeah, but I sure don't care if you do or don't like it Brother chaos rules all about Well, sometimes I take a walk there God knows, sometimes I take a taxi Shouldn't care, I shouldn't care Bereaved as I'm feeling      The day is gone, I'm on my back Staring up at the ceiling Well, I take a drink, sit back, and relax Smoke my kind, makes me feel Better for a small time What I want is what I've not got But what I need is all around me I reach and search and never stopAnd I'll say...    Isnt that an awesomeee songg...i thought it was. Thats awesome Sammy!! haha i luv ya bro!!      *Love Alwayz*    *~Mel~*  
      
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Well....this is my first post for this journal. I'm excited to share my thoughts  my plans with every1 lol. yes im a loser haha. But hey...u all know that already haha. Today....I'm going to go pick up Nihar and then go pick upNirmal from his parents store. I havent seen him for 2 months. Its going to be an awesome night. He is like a brother to me. He is also one of my best friends. Then we are all going back to Nihars for a movie night type thing. It should be fun. Friday..I have a doctors appt....not too thrilled about that. But then whenever i come back home. They are all coming over to my house. Even mah girl Angela is coming too I think. I love her soo much. Shes mah lil sis haha!! This weekend should be pretty fun. Saturday I am going to the Renaissance Fair...with my famly...and possibly Amanda. I hope she can come!! Sunday...I have church like always...then I am going to my cuzin Monica's baby shower. Shes soo awesome. I luv her!! Well thats all for now.....if i thnk of something else...ill put it in!! ~Ta Ta for NoW~      *Love Always*    *~Mel~*  
      
</post>
</Blog>