<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The Quest For Food  	I have just received a call from Deksu. She was struggling with our niece, Amal at home. After successfully following my advice to simply ‘cempung’ her and bring her back home to Jitra, Amal sounded happy on the phone. She and her antiques.  	What I wanted to tell was what deksu related to me on the phone. Said she just came back from the petrol kiosk near our house. It seems that the cashier at the counter actually recognized her with “Akak dah mai dah kan semalam ?”… to which Deksu simply replied with a grin and a nod. And since Amal was with her, the cashier commented Amal must be Deksu’s kid. When Deksu denied, she got the shock when the cashier simply asked whether Amal is the daughter to ‘ the akak who drives the Gen-2 that always come in with Deksu’ to the kiosk. She simply had to laugh. This does not show that my car is always in need of refueling. What it shows is that – we are shopping for food too often at the kiosk!  	Since I ended my morning sickness term and enter my second trimester, I have metamorphed into an eating machine. The routine is to grab the keys, holler for my sidekick aka my kidsister and begin the quest for food. Only occasionally do I delegate this to my other family member. Most of the time, it’s me and Deksu.   Early last month it was the sushi. Only then, I was whispering to the handset and Deksu on the other end busy jotting down my selection of sushi. U see, my parents went to pick her up when she finished her term at Aseam. Since the hotel was near to SOGO, I thought perhaps … not, I actually DEMANDED Deksu to bring it back for me. After due consideration however, I told her she can dispensed with my craving then because the journey from KL to Jitra is not that near and by then the sushi loses its appeal.   	I was so ‘terharu’ when they arrived home and I discovered abah actually went to get the sushi just before they departed for Kedah. U know, I never formally tell him I’m pregnant coz I dunno how. I guess he knew kot, and to learn that he did that kinda touch deep down.I may already have a husband and getting into the adult business, but I always want to be his little girl.   	After sushi it was Baskin Robbin. This was easy coz I was due to fly to KL to Sid the next week. I woke up Sunday morning and my first words were “BaskinRobbin’. After having to endure finishing ‘Around the World in 80 Days’ with him and my tummy all grumbling, we went to Tesco. I was already hungry and yet there he was loitering around looking for odds and ends for the house. This is the guy who played Bass for Nirvana’s songs in his Band during our college acoustic concert, the guy who wears his cap backwards well after we finished college, the guy who swears by Smashin’ Pumpkin and Pearl Jam. This guy was trying to find a basket (this has to match with the house)  to put his kitten(dubbed Lanun) n cat(Moncee) so that they can sleep outside and not litter in the house. Sid, my husband. It was then I realized that I was wearing my dress inside out. Lucky it was one of the ‘butterfly’ thing so it was not that obvious.   	In the end, we went to get our lunch (nasi ayam, which I puked out later coz my tummy was too full with air) and finally, Baskin-Robbins. I couldn’t wait so I ate in the car. I have always been a sucker for chocolate. So when I was dipping for the chocolate filling that frosted at the bottom of the cup, by freak chance, the spoon snapped and scooped the load of the ice-cream onto my face and hair. Heeeehehehehe…… I think I last saw Sid looking at me in horror.  	After that the craving became for lesser things. Which got me and Deksu around Jitra, visiting petrol kiosks, supermarkets, wherever there is food. But the kiosk thing is not really my fault. My sister has this fixation of JUSTEA. And she says only  that kiosk sells it. So that was why we had to keep to go there. 
     
    
</post>
<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Counting Sheep – Baaaa………  I know this is going to be a short entry. When I made this entry I’m at my office hitting at they keys because I am way too sleepy to concentrate on any other tasks. Sleeping has been made difficult lately. Last few weeks I sleep like a log. My peepers immediately become heavy once the clock strike 10.30pm onwards.  	Now I’d be lucky to even get away with sleep at half past 2.30am. It’s getting on my nerve. This weekend I’m going to ask Doc Kama for sleeping pills. I can’t go on like this. I used to be the girl who stayed back at the office up till 9pm to finish work. Now, going back at 6pm is an accomplishment. I forget easily, I mix my words.   	    
     
    
</post>
<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      PONTIANAK HARUM SUNDAL MALAM  	Before anyone start complaining about the title in this entry particularly the use of the third word, let it be revealed that first: this is a title from a recently launched malay horror movie (imagine that) and second : SUNDAL malam is the name for a flower (I assume it blossoms at night). Me n Sid brought mama and abah to GSC Gurney Drive, Penang to watch this movie. I was rather impressed with the cinematography but sid as usual has a very high standard but I concur when he commented the fast pace of the plot.   	Anyway, the movie starred Maya Karin. I suppose the make-up artist and the fact that she is not really pregnant helped, but to me she was damn gorgeous in the film, even when she was depicted as a women into her late term of pregnancy. She wore this Kebaya and still managed to look … sensual.  	With this mental picture in my mind, and hanging on to my last thread of vanity (chucklechucklechuckle) one day I braved wearing the maroon kebaya to the office. I felt… beautiful. HaHa. By then I was in my third month and I consider it an accomplishment. Let it be known that this state of mind is as at 10am in the day.  	After having my lunch, I felt kinda stuffy. It does not help either that there were loads to be done at the office. I was handling a phone call standing up and once I was done, putting the receiver down I descend to sit on my swiveling chair. “Plup..plup..plup……” Three of my kebaya dress’ buttons popped open and I stared at them in horror. There goes my Pontianak vanity. And true that people say, action speaks louder than words, the popping out of my buttons marks the end of an era for me. Fashionwise, I am officially PREGNANT or in my term of definition : Fat And Ugly.   
     
    
</post>
<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Like Father Like Baby  When the doc fixed the date for my second appointment, Sid made sure he could attend it. So I made sure each appointment after this is fixed on a Sunday morning.   	When I first came back, my aunt in Baling were opposed to the idea of me being apart from Sid. To those belonging to this school of thought, what’s the point of getting married when you are not there to do the wifely duties like cook, wash, et cetera. But I am lucky to have found my solace in Sid. True, he was rather reluctant but Sid is the kind of guy who would let me do whatever I please, as long as I’m happy with it. Even if he is against any of the ideas that I proposed, the most that would come from him would be ”Tengoklah dulu…” . I suppose his justification for letting me be away is knowing that I did apply for PTD and there ARE chances of me being selected n move to be with him. Godspeed.  	The best part about being apart is working during the weekdays like mad knowing that I’ll be seeing him during the weekend. And I narrow the chances of us getting into fights. I experienced few nasty one during my short stay with him. I don’t want to go through it ever again. Not yet, anyway… hehehehe.  	When the day came for the second appointment we did discuss about the baby. Every parent would say they wouldn’t mind be it a girl or a boy. I guess me too. Mama as hoping for boy. I secretly think Sid wants a girl,since he came from a sibling of boys. Me” I don’t mind. But I do want the baby to have Sid’s eyes. He has the most beautiful eyes. I call ‘em MATA LEMBU coz he has these long lashes and big eyes. Let the baby has his cheekbones and his nose (not mine dear god, please.. coz my nose is like a koala’s) and his sense of practicality (sid calls it his ‘kool’ness). Sid was afraid the baby would have his head. Of all the parts. When I don’t see anything wrong with it, he simply has all against his forehead.  	So the appointment went fine. And as usual Doc Kama scanned my tummy. It was amazing! I saw the baby’s tiny feet and hands (alhamdulillah) and the heart was beating so fast! It was exhilarating. Sid stood there and simply smiled. Frankly, I was near tears. This is our baby. We created it.   	In the middle of my melancholy, Sid broke the silence and exclaimed “Yang… kepala baby ikut macam saya”.. and he sounded amused (panic?). If we were in a movie there would be this romantic song at the background, and with the utterance of the statement from Sid, I can imagine the romantic song’s track getting scratched in the middle of it to be replaced with a track from the horror film PSYCHO.  	Oh gosh. Darling, all babies at this stage have big head. They are developing. I wanted to hug Sid and kiss him there and then simply because he was so adorable at that moment in time. People say when you get married the love weans. I dunno. I find myself falling in love with my own husband over and over again.   	So what if the baby does have his forehead. The more I’m going to love him/her coz part of his/her is an image of the person I love most in my life.  
     
    
</post>
<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The First Visit  	After two weeks I ‘re’start work at Ramli Amar Jit  Tan, my staffs were concerned that I haven’t done my check-up yet. My sister-in-law practically harassed me to go the doc. And being in close acquaintance with doc Kama, K.Ja actually called him up and informed him I’m coming for check-up. K.Ja went to the extent of asking acaq to accompany me… which was absurd so I told her I’d get to it soon. How am I supposed to tell them that I’m still living on the balance of RM400 from my last job I quit. I thought I would wait for Sid to come back to visit first. But one Wednesday I just rang up mama and asked her if she would be kind enough to keep me company. I would have been most comfortable with my kid sist around but Deksu was too busy being a corporate banker at Aseam then.  	So I went for the check-up, without Sid and looking sheepishly around. All the woman I saw there happens to have either a reluctant looking husband beside her and in one couple I thought the hubby look kinda guilty. I didn’t quiet figure out why at first but when I saw about 6 kids trailing in after them I kinda guessed why. I suppose the baby will be the finale to a complete set of a soccer team. Though they may add few for the reserve bench. HAHAHA. Jahatnya i.  	Mama decided to do a check up of her own. My mom has a weak tolerance of pain. My recollection of her from my kid days is this fierce looking mom who rewards defiance with (choose your weapon) hanger, feather duster, cermai branch, etc… . But now that she’s in her vintage years, I can almost associate hospitals and medicine with her. She’s always sick. And somehow, it’s always abah’s fault. Oh well.  	When my name was called I kinda didn’t know what to do so I called for her to follow me. And I was quite sad when she refused and stayed there in the seat waiting for her turn for the doc next door. By then I assume people around think I have this venereal disease or something. Coz u see, the doc I’m seeing is also a Gynaechologist. U can imagine.  	Thank god he was so nice, and very polite. I didn’t expect to get scanned but I did. And I saw this sac inside my tummy… my uterus to be exact. Doc told me I was 7 weeks pregnant, my due date is estimated on 8th January 2004. And that, my friends, confirmed me that I’M GONNA BE A MOTHER!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! First thing I vowed? If ever my daughter’s hubby is away, I’ll always be happy to accompany her for her first visit to the doc.  
     
    
</post>
<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      THE TESTS  	My first pregnancy test was done soon after Sid left for work. They say you have to do it with your first urine for the day. Mine was done after a mug of Nescafe, two cartons of soybean, few packets of MAMEE and few gulps of skyjuice. I took my shower, took the test n remembered the laundry in the washing machine. I ran down, settled everything and went up. By then it must have been more than 10 minutes. When I wanted to pee again that’s when I noticed the thin strip dipped in the cup. My urine test! I totally forgot. And squinting… I ‘think’ I saw a very faint SECOND line !  	Next move? Of course I called Sid. I suppose he was busy and I received kinda a lukewarm response. Because he was nonchalant, I dismissed the idea of pregnant. Suddenly I remembered all the rigorous exercises I been doing. I think if anyone were to touch me then they would have felt stone cold me. I was so afraid that I had to just go n get another test. I decided to buy a different type test.  	The second test proves Negative. I was kinda disappointed. But I guess n Sid was kind to say we can try again and everything. Somehow, my instinct says otherwise… I just knew my baby is here. So Sid agreed to take me to the doc the next day. That night I couldn’t sleep. But Sid snored all the way… heheheh.  	When I went into the doc’s room I was really happy. Yeah I’ve been before a doc before, just that to be before a doc for her to confirm I’m pregnant… geee, it’s kinda weird, and exciting. I didn’t even know what tests do I need to go thorugh. After all, I only have RM40 at the moment.   	I found out that the clinic also conduct a urine test to confirm a pregnancy. Okay, so I went into the toilet, did what I had to do n wait for the result. I was happy, as if I knew the baby’s there.   	‘I’m sorry… it’s negative”. First I didn’t hear her. Then I realized she was talking to me explaining the test turned out negative. I felt something heavy and simply attempt to smile. When I came out from the doc’s room I saw Sid outside the clinic, smoking. I can’t make myself to look at him. I paid the bill, went out and simply relayed the news. He was quiet, me too. Half way to the house I announced.. “the doc is mistaken. I KNOW I’m pregnant.” Sid was still quiet and told me to go to sleep. He went to the office. I thought he didn’t care.  	When Sid came back he simply was there for me. He told me how he related what happened to his friend Joe at the office and was reassured that these things happen. Sid said for me to wait till I’m VERY late for my period. Of course then I was only a week late. I was grateful for the confidence he gave me then.  	That nite, I drank a lotta liquid. Wake up early in the morning and brought my handphone into the toilet. Simply coz my handphone has a countdown timer. My first urine for the day, timed at exactly 3 minutes for the test to work out. Hey Presto – there it was … the two lines glaring at me.  	 	Later in the day I told Sid. I assume he was stunned by the realization and possibility that he was going to be a father. The next week, we decided to go back Kedah, and for me to start work again with The Great Adi Satria aka acaq.    	  
     
    
</post>
<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      SEX AND THE CITY  	Until I got a directive from my Acaq to come back, I was lazing around the house. I suppose Sid did not want me to get bored so he bought me a Five Season set of Sex and the City. I got totally hooked up on it. My fav character shifts interchangeably from Charlotte to Carrie. Sid says Carrie looks like a tramp but personally, I think she’s pretty. Just a bit on the ego side, like a typical male.  	All the while I was hooked on this series, what with me having nothing to do at home in the noon. My routine then was to wake up, prepare Sid’s breakfast if I can haul myself up, send him off (or curl up after mumbling ‘bye’), pile the laundry into the washing machine and quick nap. Oh, I seem to develop this fondness for FOOD. I can barely believe the space I find for food in my tummy.   	Therefore, there the danger lies in my complex relationship between food and Sex n the City. Why ? The gals were so gorgeous so I kinda hate myself when I eat. So there come this point that I decided once and for all I’m gonna look good too. I think I used to look good. Like when I broke off from a silly relationship when I was in college, that got me working sweat. I ended up having only 43kg on me. The best days of my life.  	Coming back to the issue just now… now to start looking good I decided to get a fine piece of skipping rope. Remember in Chapter One when I told I quit my job with only RM400 to survive until the next job? I decided to splurge on digitalized rubber skipping rope. In Jitra it would only cost me RM5 the most. In KL after searching for it at Giant Shah Alam, Tesco, OneUtama  and IOI… I only found it at the last spot. Tu pun selling for the price of RM27.00. Oh well, what the heck. These are investments, aren’t they? 	Sid’s brother have this ab-shaper at their home. So one day, I did 2000 on my rope, bout 200 crunches and 50 push-ups. This went on for about a week. Every day, without fail… these rigorous routine. This is no bulshit… I was s o determined to look like Carrie Bradshaw. I have to say it made me feel gut. But when I called my kid sister at home, my gut got kinda quesy. She says she just finished praying, which means her menstrual cycle for the month ended since about last week.  	I have a close relationship with my sister. So close that our hormones kinda sniff this so each time she starts menstruating I know I’ll start mine exactly a week after. And as I am a very routine person, my bio-clock never miss a beat. I get my pimples/cramp/moodiness a.ka. PMS one week BEFORE my period. Which is the same time my kid sist start her period.   	Until then, there were no sign my period is coming, or any of my PMS either. The next day I went to get a pregnancy test. I didn’t remember Carrie Bradshaw taking any rigorous exercise when she thinks she’s pregnant… ulp!     
     
    
</post>
<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      THE JOURNEY BEGINS….  	During our engagement days, in fact during our courting days, the issue that kept creeping up behind me and Sid was the issue of where we were going to start our lives together. He has always been keen on KL. But I, for one have the allergies for KL. It’s only practical that since I have a good job n family’s near, I opt for Kedah. But we got married after all, thinking that my only option was not to marry Sid. And true enough, getting married makes a bit of difference, you kinda want to be near. So when Meng called up from KL to ask if I’m interested in filling in her vacancy at a firm in Kelana Jaya as she’s leaving for Amanah Raya, it was a prayer answered. Though I left everyone doubting me, particularly my Boss a.k.a big brother and his friends we share the breakfast table with, I went on with the idea.   	I loved the life. I love waking up beside Sid, coming home to prepare dinner for him, simply being there with him. BUT I hate the traffic, I hate my job, I hate my stuckup ex-MCKK Boss, I hate having to drive everywhere to ask the client to sign documents and not getting the claim for traveling, I hate coming back to an empty house when Sid has to stay back at the office till 11pm, I hate having to wake up early to brave the traffic to work when he is still snoring, I hate EVERYTHING except being with him. So seven days into the second month of employment, on a Wednesday morning I gave a 24 hour notice to quit. Life is simple, right?  	My sister-in-law said I’m crazy. Well, sometimes when you are desperate.. you just don’t think. Seven days work earns me RM400. And I was happy staying at home, to the horror of my mom. She was afraid I gave up working. I told her it’s only until I get my second job. And Sid was very understanding although sometimes I think he panicked a bit considering he submitted my resume for the post of an admin exec – nice post but a turn up at the interview reveals gals with short skirt, long hair like pontianak and jobless for year’s end (maybe) competing with me for that post in an architect’s firm. I was blessed with a number of interviews. Only after I made up my mind to come back to Kedah… too bad.                            
     
    
</post>
<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      kakak saya busuk..testing
     
    
</post>
</Blog>