<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I dream often and can usually remember my dreams. I've beenthinking a lot about the meaning of my dreams lately. Here are a couple of myrecurring dreams. Where's Freud when you need him?    Assailant Dream    assailantDreamLately I've had the same dream over and over. No matter if it's a nap or at night, it is the same recurring theme. It is that there is an unknown assailant trying to get into where ever I am. Most of the time it is my parents' house, otherwise my apartment. Each time, I become aware of the assailant and try frantically to secure myself and my family inside. There is always something that hinders my attempts. It might be a garage door that refuses to close or a window latch that won't work properly.    I just woke up from a nap and another assailant dream. This time it was at my parents' house. I was sitting in the sun porch and saw what I thought were two falling stars. A friend of an ex-boyfriend was there and he said they were helicopters. We came to realize there was a massive search going on from the air for some sort of fugitive. I ran to the garage door to call my mom in from outside. She was on the phone with someone and wouldn't listen to me. I screamed at her frantically to get inside. When she finally did, I explained to her what was happening and shortly afterwards, I woke up.    These dreams are driving me nuts. I don't usually have nightmares and when the occasional one comes along, I experience  urlLink lucid dreaming  ( which I love the idea of ) and am able to tell myself that I am dreaming and should wake up. However, each time I have had one of these dreams, I haven't been aware that Iam dreaming until afterwards.     Can't Walk Dream     I often have a dream where my ability to walk is limited. I am usually in a crowded roomand have to walk to the other side for various reasons. The thing that is always the same is that my legs don't want to move properly. It is as if they are stuck in hot tar and I have to sluggishly pull them along. I usually try to make my disability unnoticed. I act nonchalant about it. The feelings of frustration are very strong in this dream. Lots of times I wake up to legs that have fallen asleep.   Slow-mo Fighting Dream   I used to have this dream a lot but haven't had it in awhile now. In these dreams, I am fighting someone but my punches are always in slow-mo and when I strike the person, it doesn't make much of an impact. I am always confident of my ability to kick the other person's ass if only my blows don't gooooo sooooo sssssslowwwwwww. A lot of frustration accompanies these dreams as well.   Wet Dream   Yes, this is what it sounds like. I have within the last couple of years started having "wet dreams". I am able to actually have orgasms in my sleep without ever touching myself, induced solely by my dream. When I first started having these, I was not sure if I was just dreaming the orgasm or if I was actually experiencing one. Through lucid dreaming, I now usually make myself wake up immediately afterwards to determine whether it is real or imagined. I have found they are real! I can wake up while it's happening. Wow!   Flying Dream   I don't ever have flying dreams anymore but as a child Ioften hadvery vivid flying dreams. I remember fearless swooping. I wished with all my might that I could actually fly. Now it scares me. I am TOTALLY afraid of flying in airplanes as well. Weird.  
</post>
<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Captain Chico The Chihuahua urlLink   
     

    
</post>
<date>07,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Kind of a weird topic for my first blog but I just wanted to jot some things down quick about my Xanax feelings.  What I mean is the feeling I get after I take my nightly Xanax.  I took 2 pills tonight instead of one so that I will hopefully sleep.  I feel floaty and light.  Tired and calm.  I quit drinking and replaced that with Xanax I guess.  I am good with it though, only take my daily allotted amount unless an emergency calls for more.  Rambling, rambling.  My typing is taking forever because I keep making typos.  Enough for now then I guess.  Tomorrow I get started on myself and my history.   Night for now...
     

    
</post>
</Blog>