<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      wow...i learned a lot today. It seems like i know more about myself now then i have in a long time. An Amazing guy showed me this Bible Verse today...and it showed the reason for his breaking up with me. It brought back a lot of feelings and I realized that i wasnt over him. And i know i have this wonderful boyfriend right now. and i like him a lot. but i feel like i should maybe try and focus more on God and people that can help me learn to know my Savior more.   Mike~ You never did one thing wronge in our relationship...you showed me how great someone can be to another. You showed me kindness more than i ever thought you would. I know I kept telling you to stay by my side...umm but i think i was really saying to me...but i didnt want to belive that i was the one with the problem. I know even if we arnt together we will meet and it will be amazing...ummm...You need to expirience having a girl that you can hold and touch and see into her eyes. I know that person is out there mike and you will fall in love with her. But i finally got the life i've wanted at home back and i'm soo excited cause i have the trust of my family back and i'm getting all these openings to wonderful opportunities. Everything i gave to you was true...but i couldnt give you the warmth of my heart or the warmth of my own hand. Your an amazing guy, and you will make someone very happy some day. Well you already have made someone happy...me...thanks for all that you did for me...i'm sorry i had to end what we had...and i'm sorry that i cant be there for you. But right now i need to focus on God and the people that can show me how to love him more than i do now. i need to get my life in a path that will show hope in my future. We will be friends forever and i will always be here if u need to talk to me. I'm sorry Mike!!!  Shawn thanks for your help with this..you helped me through a lot in my life! thanks soo much...I'm so glad i talked to u about this.. i know the chose i made was the right one...at least for right now lol thanks soo much!    Grant~you showed me how much God can bring life into me ....Thanks...and i'm glad you said you'd be there for me no matter what! thanks soo much! I'm glad we had that talk...it helped a lot   I'm soo sorry Mike  ~*~Kristin Nicole~*~  Hurt....
     

    
</post>
<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      last night i was on teh phone with mike...and my mom walked in.. i'm not suppose to be on the phone. So i thought i was gunna be in like a whole bunch of trouble .. but i wasnt!!!! : )  anywayz...My mom said that My boyfriend could  call during the day. So i will still be able to talk to him. I was really suprized that i didnt get in trouble or even yelled at... i mean thats a big deal! anywayz...I think they relize how much he means to me! i just hope he knows the same.   Today i went to go see King Aurthur with my dad! it was an awesome movie! i'd tell ppl to go see it...it's a really good movie! anywayz...thats what i did today lol  Mike i'm sorry i just hung up on you... i'm really sorry.. and i love you soo much! never forget that!  My old best friend lindsey, has this bf named chris who is an asshole...and i HATE him soo much... i just wish lindsey could see him in the way i do... well she's made it clear that he's all she needs...so yesterday he told me i was a bad friend to her...so i figured that i would just leave her life with him the way it is.. and just get out of her life. I hate doing that.. but why would i want to ruin the world she loves so dearly??!?!?! Well i hope i didnt give up a friend for something that isnt gunna last.. i'm sorry lindsey... but i dont want to deal with your boyfriend yelling at me and telling me how bad of a person i am.. i dont need anymore of that .. expecially from him. I'm soo sorry. I hope you haev a "wonderful" life with the "man" you think you know.. i'm sorry dont get mad at me for this  Life seems to get harder as you grow up...i just wish i could stay in this stage of life were nothign goes wronge. And i want to be with the one person who gets me the most and in his arms. I know that day will come.. i jsut want it now more than ever...I love you mike! Thanks for being there for me  Shawn your soo sweet to me. thanks for being here for me!!! you made things with me and my love good again in that time when he had doubts.. i'm so glad i have you here to help me. Thanks so much Love ya!  Thanks to all my friends! i love yall soo much!  !*!Krisitn Nicole!*!  R.I.P. lil Mikie D and Great Aunt Mary  I LOVE MIKE!!!!!
     

    
</post>
<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      uuhhh nothing happened today lol anywayz...  I guess i'll jsut say hey to my wonderful friends lol  Lisa! AHH i'm soo glad we talked things out! your soo sweet! so many good times... you cant type! haha that was sooo damn funny.. lol so many good times! i dont know all of them there are so many lol  Lindsey...havnt talked to u this summer much.. but ur an awesome friend and i love you! lol i hate you! your in florida right now lol lol i wish i was with you! lol   Maria! MANFORD! dude he's a pimp he has like 4 wives now! lol PIMP!!! ahh better shut the doors lol anywayz.. your awesomely sweet! and i'm soo glad i have you as a friend  Jamo.. we will chill ! lol your soo sweet thanks for being there for me!   Shawn! Your such a sweetheart! thanks for beign there for me! your my hommie G! lol i'm here for you no matter what!   Mike! baby! i love you soo much!!! your such a blessing! i'm so glad i have a friend like you! your more than i could ever ask for~ Only One... baby thats our song! i will always love you no matter what! even if things are hard to get through.. ill be here for you.. stand by my side please! thanks for everything  Grant...I dont know what happened to us...I thought we were gunna stay friend...but we dont talk as much. your an amazing guy and one of the best boyfriends i've ever had...i did fall in love with you and in a way i still am. your amazing and your gunna be an awesome minister one of these days. i respect you soo much! God Bless You! i'm here if u ever need to talk!   iight i know i missed some ppl but i'm bored and tired i'll type more laters... luv yall thanks for beign there for me  !*!Kristin Nicole!*!  R.I.P. LiL MiKiE D   and my great aunt Mary  God Lives!  </post></Blog>