<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Mommy and I were supposed to hang out. When she got up the power went out, so we showered a the Henderson's house in Powhatan. Then I got a donut, which I had been craving since 3 in the morning. That donut made me feel sick  all day . After my donut we went to the eye doctor. I have a stigmatism in each eye. I had to pick out frames and I'm very picky because I just can't do glasses. Mommy got mad and yelled at me, that basically was the start of a really bad day.  She apologized for yelling at me, but I could tell that she really did mean it when she said I was "plucking her last nerve," so it still hurt. Then we went appraising. I got really bored during house number 1. I just sat there for ever and ever. Then we went to appraise the second house, we couldn't stop before we got there and I really had to use the bathroom. Then we had to take pictures of 4 or 5 other houses. I almost peed myself.  After that mommy took me to Panera bread. Tia called while we were in line and was really angry. Some stuff went on in at the office that I won't get into. It was a lot of drama and I felt bad because it shouldn't have happened. Neither one of us ate.  We went to mommy's interview. I had to stay in the car. I was feeling really bad then, so I put my seat back and tried to sleep. I had Sleeping at Last on, they made me feel a little bit better. I napped on and off for about an hour. Mommy came back and we drove back to the office. It was the longest ride I've ever taken. Mommy's cell phone went off more than normal. Everyone was all upset and I just had to sit back and listen to my mom pour everything out to me. That made me really sad because there was nothing I could do to help her.  We got back to the office, I just got online and pretended I wasn't there. I didn't want to be there. We left for the orthodontist, mommy was on the phone the whole ride there and the wholetime we were in the lobby. I found out that if I don't wear my headgear more I'll end up having surgery. Uh-oh. I missed guitar because of mommy's bad schedualing skills.  We got backto the office and were supposed to leave almost once we got there. Mommy just wanted to change. Well, we were there for an hour.  A very long hour .  Then we went shopping. Nothing really special happened. I got lots of pairs of soffee shorts because they're comfy and mommy said "get as many as you want."  The guy in Arbys recognized me. It was kind of nice to see someone who looked like they hadn't just had the worst day of their life. We got Arbys and came home. I ate really fast because I just wanted to get away from everyone, now I'm pouring everything out onto the dumb internet.  Overall- mommy's cell phone rang a million times more than normal, every hour felt like 6 hours, mommy was upset, Iwas bored, and I just had to sit there and smile. This was supposed to be a fun day. ;(  
      
</post>
<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      My mommy is cool, but she's driving me nuts. I really don't have as much freedom as she saysI do. When it came time for me to pick an instrument after piano I picked drums, she said hell no. When I wanted to play bass she said "No, that's for people who are to dumb to play guitar." Well,did it ever occur to her that maybe I wanted to play bass and I didn't care if people thought I was an idiot.  She's always making me feel bad too becausewhen I need something she always makes abig deal about how busy she is. Then she'll schedual something at a ridiculously bad time, but "it was the only time." I could wait a weekfor my consultation thing, now I don't know if I'm going to make it to guitar because my appointment is 15 minutes before mylesson. Sorry mom, you can't do that in 15 minutes, I'm almost positive.  I don't even want to play guitar anymore. I know that if Itell her this she'll givemelines like "You'regreat at it though, you just don't practice enough"or anything else to make me keep doing it. I've been through this before. She'd rather me do something I don't want to do than letting metry something new. Yet almost all the time I hear "why don'tyou try to add variety to your life?"or "why areyou alwaysdoing thesame things."  I hate being a burden, but that's exactly how she makes mefeel sometimes. I can't talk to her, because we'd be fine for a whole 15 minutes before she started giving me crap. If I could even talk to her for 15 minutes without being disturbed. I can't talk to her in the car at all becauseher damn cell phone keeps going off. I hate that thing. I have to limit my conversations to unimportant things because once that stupid thingrings she forgets everything except her job.  Augh. I hate feeling like this. 
      
</post>
<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just read a thing about Mark David Chapman, the man who shot John Lennon. This statement angered me:   "At his first parole hearing two years ago, Chapman said he did not deserve to go free. He will be up for parole again in 2004. "  What?!? I didn't even know that you could get parole after being found guilty of second-degree murder. His whole life has been very turbulant. He would be fine for a while. He was a born-again Christian in high school, then after 2 attempts at college and a failed engagement he attempted suicide. Since then he's been through serious ups and downs.   He shot John 4 times, with bullets that expand as they hit their target. He couldn't buy the bullets in New York so, he got the bullets from a friend in Georgia who was a cop. He never ran, just waited for the police to come and arrest him.   Since he's been in prison he's had ups and downs, but hasn't had many hard times recently.    “During that hour six came out. [They were] the most fierce and incredible things you ever saw or heard in your life – hissing, gurgling noises and different voices right out of my mouth. … The way I was acting – cursing and things like this – weren’t me, and when they came out I could sense these things coming out of my mouth, hissing and awful gurgling and grinding and I could feel that part of my personality was gone. "    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Edit: Ok, I'm not going to debate comments. I'm lazy haha. I just thought I'd let you guys have fun. Because I know that I'm one of the last people on the planet who supports Bush. ;D  Ok, I'm really sick of people saying that Bush started this war. That's 100% ignorance. Clinton was offered Bin Laden's head on a silver platter and didn't do anything. He was to busy with the women in the White House to solve a problem before it was a problem. So then, on 9/11/01 terrorists hit the World Trade Centers and the Pentagon. How is this Bush's fault?   Weren't you angry on the day of the attacks? Didn't you want justice? Didn't you want to see the men behind this go down? That's what's happening. Those guys are going down. The brave men and women in Iraq are making sure of that. Bush declared war because that's what we needed. If we hadn't gone to war we practically would have been saying "It's ok. Hit us again. We won't do anything."   Now that justice is being served everyone's saying "Bush is an idoit. He shouldn't have started this war." As for the economy- are you living on the streets? How many times a day do you eat? Can you stay warm/cold at night? Do you stay dry when it rains? Exactly, we've still got what we need. Just because your parents can't give you tons of money to buy on stuff you don't need doesn't mean the economy is going down the toilet.   One last statement. Bush isn't an idiot. He has degrees from Harvard and Yale. Get over it. He's a smart guy. Ivy League schools don't just hand out diplomas.   
      
</post>
<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just got up. It's 8:31 at night. I've been asleep all day. My mommy let me stay home from CAP to sleep. That was really nice of her. Then at dinner my daddy started giving me crap about not going to CAP, and how I have a commitment. Dad, I'm effing sick! augh, it bugs me. 
      
</post>
<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I took cold medicine and I still feel like poop. The tea isn't helping either. ;( My throat and chest feel like they're being stabbed with needles every time I breathe. I hugged my mommy goodbye and almost choked because she had hair-spray in. I don't wanna be sick! *pouts* 
      
</post>
<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm annoyed. Michael Jackson owns the rights to almost every Beatles song. Go download some Beatles songs. Ack! Paul and Ringo need to buy them back damnit! I dislike that. I thought it should be posted. 
      
</post>
<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I have 3 blogs. I'm a fcking loser. I think I'm going to use this one for ranting, my xanga for when I just want to blog, and livejournal forconstructive stuff. Yes, that sounds nice. Since I have no traffic here, this is nice for ranting. The fewer people who listen to me the better. So this might be a little anger filled from now on. *I just changed that*  
      
</post>
<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I don't know anyone around blogger. I need some friends up in this joint. So, now that I know no one reads this- what's up? I   Grace and I are insane, haha. Check this out:     sunnysideup611:  COME TO ME MOSQUITO!!! YOU WILL PAY FOR YOUR CRIMES!!!!   dumbfounded490:  *eats mosquito* problem solved!   sunnysideup611:  YAY!!! hahah this thing is killing me   dumbfounded490:  lol   dumbfounded490:  maybe it's just misunderstood   dumbfounded490:  we could make an oprah special "The little Mosquito who could" awwwww *cries*   sunnysideup611:  OH MY!!! I   dumbfounded490:  We could even turn it into a Lifetime original movie!   sunnysideup611:  And the tragic story of how the mosquito was mistreated as a child and how it ran away from the world, only to find Oprah giving her bacon to survive   dumbfounded490:  awwww   dumbfounded490:  then when it was eaten by a big, mean camera   sunnysideup611:  and the camera goes crazy and desides to regurgitate the little bacon filled mosquito up   dumbfounded490:  then it's a bloody disgusting mess   dumbfounded490:  awwww!   sunnysideup611:  so the bacon filled mosquito lives life continually being eaten and then regurgitated and then suddenly, oprah desides to give the mosquito a free bath   dumbfounded490:  With bath salts and bubbly things galore   dumbfounded490:  this is going on my blogger   sunnysideup611:  YAY!!!   sunnysideup611:  says me and the little mosquitoe who is currently on my leg and I'm thinking about smashing it    dumbfounded490:  it shall meet its doom      Grace, we rule.   Hannah gets a gold star for being the first to comment on here.: )  
      
</post>
<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It's freezing in here. I hate being cold, I want a blanket. No one reads this. Hmm, ok. Anyway, I love my music. Ben Folds is a cool guy, so was George Harrison. Paul McCartney is  not  dead. Frank Sinatra and Louis Armstrong have amazing voices. So does Jamie Cullum. Katie gets a gold star for liking Buddy Holly. I really want the Cure's new CD, it's supposed to be a lot like their old stuff. You can't beat their old stuff. I love the Smiths.   
      
</post>
<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      "Here Today" is officially the saddest song in the world. Paul McCartney wrote it for John Lennon after he died. It's definitely one of the most heart-felt songs I've heard. It's beautiful, I cry during it every time.   
      
</post>
<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I have 2 versions of I want you to Want me.  It's an effing amazing song.    Now I have 3 versions.  One makes me want to cry, then throw something.  No Doubt covered I want you to Want me.  I've heard their other stuff, and it isn't bad, but this cover is pretty awful.  I was sad.  Simple Plan also covered a cheap trick song.  Another amazing song that was fcked up.  Damn
      
</post>
<date>08,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hiiii!  I have another blog, woop woop!  I think that Katie has me beat though.  ;D  I'm at the office.  I haven't eaten yet today, eeeep!  I'm going to fall over.  *falls* I'm good.  Did you know that Yesterday was Ringo Starr's Birthday.  I never made him a cake. ;(  I'll do that this weekend.   Happy Birthday Mr. Starr! 
      
</post>
<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Gah, I can't talk to my mom about anything anymore and it's driving me nuts.  I really hate this.  I want to start taking guitar somewhere else.  Scott is cool and he's a good guitar player, but it's been a year and I don't feel like I've made any progress.  I like how I can play whatever I feel like, but the thing is that I can't.  You can't just start someone out hard.  It's getting discouraging.  I can't tell my mom this though because  A. she's never available B. she wouldn't listen to what I was saying anyway and C. she'd forget about it nearly immediately.  Isn't that crazy?  My mom doesn't even have the time for me to talk to her about stuff I want to talk about.  I can talk to her about anythign insignificant, but if it's going to take more than 10 minutes to explain abaondon hope.  She forgets everything too.  I swear she'd forget to come home if she worked alone.  I hate this, I have a lot to say to her but I can't.  Whenever I decide I'm going to something comes up so I can't.  Gah, I wish she had time for me. 
      
</post>
</Blog>