<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
        It's awful.  I'm going for it full time this semester, but that means I'm taking five classes. I have a class on Monday night from 7-10 PM, a class Tuesday morning from 11-1, a class on Wednesday morning from 9-12 and again from 7-10, a class on Thursday from 11-1 and again from 7-10.  I get Friday off, w00t!  But yeah, with the commute and all, this  sucks .  I'm going to be gone all day Tuesday and Wednesay, it doesn't really make sense to try to come home in the middle of the day, I'm not sure that'd even be possible!  I'm going to try to get an internship or a volunteer gig or something for those two afternoons a week that I'm going to be stuck there.  Or else I could just go and do homework during that time.   So I have to figure out my overall schedule for next semester.  Since I'm getting a laptop, I think I still will be able to do some work during that time period, but I don't know....let's see:  On Monday, I guess I'll get up around 6:00 to go running, then I'll come in at 7 and do weights or stretching or Pilates. At 8:00, I'll eat breakfast, shower and get dressed.  Then I'll go upstairs and work until noontime.  At noontime, I'll go out running again or I'll go practice soccer or shoot some hoops or do SOMETHING for an hour and I'll eat lunch, too.  Then, at 1:00, I'll work again until 5, when I leave to school.  I'll get home and go straight to bed.  Tuesay is an easy day.  I'll get up at 6, run, come in at 7, do weights/stretch/pilates.  At 8, I'll get ready for school.  I'll get out of school at 1 PM, come home, go to soccer, eat dinner, do Monday's homework and work until bedtime.  Wednesday is a very long day, I will not shower and I will eat in the car.  Get up at 6, run, and go to school.  Get out of class at noon, eat lunch.  Do homework from Tuesday. Finish homework around 3, do something productive until 7, go to class, come home and go to bed.  Thursday is another long day, I'll get up at 6, run, come in at 7 and do weights, stretches or Pilates.  At 8, I'll go through my routine and leave for school.  After class, it'll be 1:00, so that leaves six hours.  I'll eat lunch, I suppose and then I'll work Wednesday's homework assignments. Finish homework at 3:00, then do something productive until 7:00. Class till 10, come home, go to bed.  On Friday, I'll get up at 6, go through my ususal routine, do Thursday's homework, work until 4 PM, play soccer, eat dinner, and work until bedtime.  Saturday - Sleep in, and all day work.  Play soccer. Go out and have Social Life at nighttime.  Sunday - Sleep in, all day work.  Work on Personal Hygiene such as repainting nails and such.  That's do-able.  That's not so bad!  .  
     
    
</post>
<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      My brother shaved his head last night. He shaved the front of his head completely, but the back of his head still has hair (I guess he couldn't see that well), so he has the weirdest look now. HAHAHA. His head was all cut up and bleeding from the razor, the worst shaving job I've ever seen in my life. He's really sad because he's losing his hair and he's only 22 years old, but what can you do about genetics?     I went swimming this morning. It's so very energizing to dip yourself in freezing cold water first thing in the AM. I'm still wet, though.     Perhaps you're wondering about my blog title. Well, "tyler4president" is my username elsewhere, generally on the Aerosmith message boards. And I really believe strongly that STEVEN TYLER SHOULD BE THE PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED STATES! What a great leader of the free world he'd make! Aerosmith could play the innaguration! = ) For once there'd be decent music, right? He'd give his state-of-the-union address from a scarf-draped microphone. And there'd be no scandal or guessing about his drug-addled past, since it's all so out in the open anyway. I was going to start a campaign to see how many Aerosmith fans I could get to write in Steven Tyler's name on the ballot in 2004 if nobody decent was going to run. I firmly believe that democracy is all about voting for who you REALLY WANT and that it's stupid to vote for the lesser of two evils or to vote for one guy just to shut another out. I started the whole "Tyler4President" thing to show people that our election system is a moronic joke and so I could thumb my nose at "democracy," but then Ralph Nader threw his hat into the ring this year, and I kinda really do want Nader to win, so I'm going to vote for him and you all should too if you like him well enough. DON'T VOTE FOR KERRY JUST TO GET BUSH OUT OF OFFICE, THAT'S NOT WHAT DEMOCRACY IS SUPPOSED TO BE ABOUT.    I have no profound thoughts for you at this time.  Perhaps later, after I've eaten something.      My big plans for TODAY include:  -Returning books to the library.  - Doing some work  - Going and getting an ice cream cone (blueberry?)  - Working on my index so I can release it finally  - Watching the democratic national convention, fun.   
     
    
</post>
<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      http://www.livejournal.com/users/emu_lee/
     
    
</post>
<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I went to the beach all day today. And I have a horrible sunburn, too.  Sex.  I suggest that you read  The Naked Ape  by Desmond Morris to get a basic idea on what I think about sex. I really like that book a lot - although it is dated, and you can tell that he came up with a lot of his ideas in the 1950s, I think it's the only book that takes an objective look at human behavior. Morris tries to help you to step outside of humanity and look at our species as if you were a naturalist or a zoologist observing the behavior of any animal in its habitat. A lot of other attempts to talk about the behavior of human beings get screwed up by all our self-glorification. I love the  Naked Ape  because Morris tried so hard to steer clear of that.  Anyway, read that book. Sex is a completely morally neutral biological function. Like eating or sleeping or going to the bathroom. It is not inherently wonderful, it is not inherently wrong. It's neutral, it just exists, it's a fact of life. Humans have sex in order to perpetuate the species. No, God doesn't think that sex is evil or sinful. This is how most of the more complicated creatures on earth go about the business of reproduction. Sex is a function of the body. That is all.  Humans, however, attatch special meaning and a lot of weight to the sex act because of our niche in the ecosystem and the way that we've evolved. Unlike most primate species, we have a very strong tendency to form pair-bonds. You can't just undo several million years of biological programming because you've decided that monogamy is repressive! In virtually every mainstream culture on earth, pair bonding is the rule. In some societies, you may have multiple wives, but you can't have sex with just anybody. Having indiscriminate, casual sex has been generally frowned upon since the beginning of history! This suggests that there's something deeper than arbitrary social rules at work here. There's a good reason for the human instinct to form pair bonds - humans have a very lengthy period of infancy. A typical chimpanzee reaches full brain development in three years. It takes a human 22 years. A human female is sidelined for  years  caring for her young. You can see why it's so important for the male to be involved in rearing. Do the majority of human females find it at all easy to raise a child without a partner? No, because it's so contrary to our biological programming. Humans have a deeply-rooted biological drive to mate exclusively. This is why we've developed so many emotional feelings about the act of sex.  It's not fair to compare humans to other animals, because other animals occupy different niches, play different roles and have evolved differently depending on what has worked best for them over the ages. Exclusive mating has worked for humans, but it's not for animals like cats who are solitary hunters and whose offspring are grown in a year. Cats don't seem to attatch much feeling or emotion to sex, because they don't need to. Cats attach A TON of importance to the act of hunting and killing, because they have to. Every species has its own thing. The fact that we attatch great importance to sex is an idiosyncracy of our species.  So sex is a morally neutral act. Like eating. But there's a huge difference between eating to ensure your survival and stuffing down a dozen donuts in one sitting. The same applies to sex. Having sex is fine. Having indiscriminate sex with every member of the opposite gender you come across is quite another matter. You don't need to eat a hot-fudge brownie sundae just because it's there. Likewise, you don't need to have sex with the cute guy at the party just because he's there. IT'S ALL ABOUT SELF CONTROL!  I honestly feel that we live in a very sexually repressed society. I think that all this obsession with sex is a compensation for that. Don't forget, this country was settled by Puritans, and I think that the "Puritan" mindest is so deeply entrenched in our whole way of thinking. I think that there's very much a sentiment that sex is "forbidden" and "wrong," and ooh, if you have sex, you're doing something NAUGTY! It's so weird, like porn mags and sex shops, it's always like "Ooh, satisfy your naughty secret pleasures!" What on earth is so "naughty" about sex? If sex were just more out in the open and if people accepted that it was just a biological function, a part of life, like anything else, we'd probably be far less obsessed with it than we are.  I always hear "If you were at ease with your sexuality, you'd be having a lot of sex. People who don't have sex are repressed." But part of being an empowered woman at ease with her sexuality is understanding that sex is a profound act of expression that is special enough that it ought not to be shared with just anyone with a penis. I don't think that abstaining from sex makes neccessarily makes you a loser or is neccessarily a sign of insecurity or fear. It can be, but on the contrary, I think that very often, excessive casual sex is an indicatication of low self esteem...having sex does indeed affirm your sexual attractiveness and lovability, at least for awhile.  I really have no problem with premarital sex as long as you're in an actual relationship. I think that being married first is probably better, because you've got to be pretty darn committed to take that kind of a plunge, but, no, you're not going to HELL if you have sex with your fiance or your serious boyfriend. However, I don't think that empty sex neccessarily adds anything to your life at all.  Having sex to keep a guy is the dumbest thing I've ever heard of.  There's no rules for what makes a relationship work out. Some people have sex on the first date and they stay together for the rest of their lives. Some people date for five years, then they finally have sex on thier wedding night and they're divorced a year later. So "doing the best thing to make a relationship work" shouldn't be the main factor in deciding whether or not to have sex with someone.    "I know some girl who waited two years to have sex with a guy, and then he dumped her right after." Okay, then, so she found out he was a jerk. Good thing she found out, now she's free to find somebody better. That's not a reason to rush into sex early. He still would have been a jerk if she'd slept with him after two weeks. A jerk is a jerk, you can't engineer your sex life to de-program jerks and make them love you.    You can't make anybody like you or love you. Either he loves you or he doesn't. Jumping in to sex too soon or putting it off too long isn't going to change that.   </post></Blog>