<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I will not walk on the water’s edge,  Below the pink mystic sky and the three glowing moons,  Nor will I walk in the water shore sludge,  Surrounded by enchanting dark forests of sadness and gloom.    But straight to the center is the place that I go  In a silver mercury lake of denseness and power,  And on the place I walk is a strong current flow  To send small rippling waves to the edge lining flowers.    In the hazy distance are shining purple mountains,  Planted in the thick water absorbing it’s shiny glaze  And within the glaring purple are many natural fountains  Making beautiful waterfalls in the hidden mysterious caves.    Sand-like glitter drifts from the sky,  Bringing the foreign smell from “the other side.”  
     

    
</post>
<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      My body bleeds,  Blood drips from my hands,  My feet drag,  They limp on the sand.    Every step,  Feels like my last,  I have no strength,  But time continues to pass.    My long hair,  Flies in the wind,  The warm dry breeze,  Caresses my chin.    The glitter in the sand,  Shimmers like light on water,  In this open land,  Stand tall rocks that don’t falter.    My heavy eyes open,  The orange sand rocks I see,  This barren wilderness,  Is never-ending.    The purple sky shouts beauty,  A spirit their must be,  But all I hear is silence,  As the blood drips off of me.    I thought I heard voices,  Somewhere beyond the dunes,  But the whispers were a lie,  I spoke too soon.    Behind me in the distance,  Follows a red trail,  Surely my body can’t go on,  This journey’s bound to fail.    I slowly sit down,  On the soft sand,  My fingers feel sticky,  Dried blood’s on my hand.    Dark red flecks,  Cover my body,  Where’s the blood from?  There’s no wound on me.    My face feels wet,  I don’t remember crying,  I reach and touch a tear,  To only find blood drying.    I close my eyes once more,  Trying to numb the pain,  When I open them,  Reality’s back again.    I look around me,  Hundreds of people I see,  I’m back to every day life,  As I smile lethargically.    I walk in public,  No one really knows me,  But yet they don’t know themselves,  Who are we really?    Would I rather live with the sand,  Is that more of a reality?  Or would I want to live my life,  Where no one knows my true identity?        
     

    
</post>
<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      When I first knew you, I didn’t know you were the one  If God would have told me, I would have been stunned  In high school you were known as Andre the Saint  You were always happy, you never had a complaint.    The differences were crazy between you and I  If I had known we’d be married I probably would’ve cried  “A huge future mistake!” I would have roared  But I had no idea what God had in store.    The irony lives as people find out  The match of June and Andre they most likely doubt  But who is to comment on God’s decision  Our togetherness is not ours but God’s holy vision.    So here were are, a family of three  How things have changed, I would never have dreamed  You are so different, than I thought you were in high school  But those were my bad days, my days as a fool.    Now we are married and a year has passed  We’ve had ups and downs, but we will definitely last  I know in my heart, that you are a wonderful man  I want you to feel loved, well at least that’s my plan.    You deserve so much from your wife  I want to give you your needs for the rest of your life  I often feel like God owes you more than me  But I guess He doesn’t make mistakes so I just have to believe    You have so many qualities that are worthy to admire  It doesn’t seem like there’s much you need to acquire  You are very loving, thoughtful and sweet  Those are usually the traits that husbands don’t meet.    You always tell me that I’m so beautiful  You’ve helped my confidence where my father was pitiful  It’s weird to be loved so much by you  That at times it’s hard to trust it because it’s too good to be true.    Many people long to be loved strongly as you love me  But their awful fate is to remain empty  But for some reason God decided to bless me  With that smiling Andre that I knew in the 90’s.    I hope your birthday hasn’t been disappointing  I didn’t know what to get you, so I just sat and wrote something  This poem is what came out and I hope it has been pleasant  It’s the best I could do for your birthday present.  
     

    
</post>
<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Just so everyone knows, I do not agree with this poem at all anymore. It is no longerwho I am. ---------------------------------------------------------------   Transitional stages change what’s within,  Memories linger, reminiscence of sin.  Clinging on to God, a fantasy of truth,  Asking Him to change me, hoping to be renewed.    Hearing doubts, poking like pins  But I am not the strength, the strength is in Him.  How I long to be different, how I long to be changed,  But old sin and its memories wrap me in chains.    I seek Him, I seek Him, how I feel everyone doubts me,  I know He must love me, but how I feel nothing.  Why can’t I believe the promises He has given?  That He sees me as pure, He sees me as forgiven.    I listen, I listen but silence I hear,  For a strong vivid voice, rumbling low and clear.  “Burdens no more, you don’t have to fear,  Life will not be empty, trust that I care”.    Promises I’ve been taught are never to be trusted,  My passage way for trust is old, brown and rusted.  I must let go, I must let go  I need help from Him, I need to be showed.    He needs to heal me, He needs me to trust Him  But I don’t know how, and where do I begin?  All I know to do is to cry out with desire,  To be different, to be helped, He’ll answer immediately prior.    I pray, I pray  “God show me today,  Your divine righteous reality  How you release the enslaved.  Make Yourself real, make me believe,  Give me faith and set me free”.    Your entire entity exists above comprehension,  How it’s hard for me to trust someone that lives in all dimensions.  Don’t let me go, don’t let me move an inch,  For living my way is worse than a tight clench.      I fear, I fear  Why am I this way?  It keeps me from growing  It makes me delayed.    Sometimes I love You, sometimes I don’t  How humanly love is such a joke.  God make me consistent, God make me strong  You are the ever constant I have always longed.    I’m trusting, I’m trusting  I’m giving You my all,  How I’m walking on nothing  Please don’t let me fall.    I want to be different, exceeding all things  I want to be the person You chose me to be.  Show me what’s wrong that prevents this from being true,  Sculpt me, wash me do what You must do.      I will trust You, I will trust You  I’m going to do as You say  I don’t care how I feel,  I’m doing it Your way.      Written on: December 22, 1998 
     

    
</post>
<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      She poisons his mind, She smirks with evil, His eyes are hypnotized, Her heart's of steel.  He walks past me, I am invisible, He's in a coma My pain is trivial.  She is a witch, She's cast her spell, He's in her control But no one can tell...  But I, I can see, His eyes are in a trance And now he hates me...  Because of you, You bitch, You should die, You took my father And he thinks that I, Am in the wrong When what he hears, Is your siren song.  You better understand, That you will suffer, Your sadism will catch you, Your path will get rougher.  You think you are so righteous, But really your clothed in vomit, Some day you will be in agony, And no one will stop it.  You will sit on your throne Next to satan your friend, You'll think you've won, But then there'll be a dead end,  He'll pat your little head, saying, "Well done my minion," But fear will strike your face, When you realize my vision:  Your destruction is inevitable, You'll both be sent to eternal torture, "And vengence will be mine!" says I, Welcome to your deserved fortune.
     

    
</post>
<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      His toes wiggle in the current The water flows gently over his feet His beautiful face Smiles up at me.  A delicate little giggle Comes from his being He places his hands in the stream Grabbing everything he is seeing.  His eyes shine like topaz His smile beams I love looking into his face How happy he seems.  His skin is like silk Delicate fingers touch me His hugs fill my heart As his little body clings.
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I just read a few testimony's about people who left Christianity. Interesting stuff. I think the only thing that struck me was when someone said, "I've learned that Christians are totally twisting evolution and misunderstand it." I 'd like to know what exactly they're talking about so that I can find out if that's true.  I found that I relate to a lot of what they're talking about, but at the same time I feelthatI see things more clearly than them, although I also do not wish to call myself a Christian. Many of their reasons for leaving Christianity were based on spiritual abuse from other people or misunderstandings of the purpose and interpretations of the Bible (OT mostly). It's quite a struggle is it not? I can't stand people who don't struggle with it. It's not fair that spiritual stuff is so easy for some people and so hard for others. 
      
</post>
<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I find that my mind does more at night when I sleep than I want itto. I often wake up with a powerful hopelessness that makes me think about ending my life. Why do I wake up this way so much? ..I try to analyze. All my thoughts, worries and fears come out in my dreams, almost every night. What do "normal" people dream? I've had bad dreams ever since I was a teenager, but lately I've realized that they say a lotabout me. I think that my dreams do the greiving and crying out that I don't do when I'm awake. When I'm awake I feel the pain in my heart all day long, almost to a point of numbness. Sometimes I think it's gone becauseI'm used to itor because I get distracted from it. But its not gone, its hangs from my neck like a heavy burdening chain. During the day I don't know what to do with the pain. I think over and over again, "What do you do with a lifetime of pain?" "How do you make it better?" "What can I possibly do besides dysfunctional things (drinking, other addictions etc) that actually relieves the pain?" With all the counseling I've been to, no one has even gotten close to helping me find a solution to that problem.  Sometimes I feel like I do not sleep well because my dreams are always bothering me. I wake up desperately wanting to cry, but I can't. What an awful feeling?! Do you ever need to and want to cry, but you physically can't? For some reason I rarely can cry by myself. I wish I could lock myself away and just cry and cry until I felt better, but I can't. The only thing I do is get mad alone.I can the only thing I can do, is dream.  I don't want to hurt anymore, I don't. I want all this to end. I want to find a solution, I want this to be over with... but it follows me everywhere I go. It haunts me in my dreams, it weights itself on my body during the day, it seems as though nothing I do makes it better. I don't want to wallow, I want it gone. It is a dilemma for me. Maybe the dreams will make it better, maybe the dreams can do the greiving that I am unable to do awake, and then someday I will connect with my unconscious and we can grieve together. 
      
</post>
<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Here I am procrastinating from writing my boring paper on the Genesis Flood. How I hate dry research papers that I am required to write. My body and my mind feel so exhausted. I haven't felt the same the past few years. I have never been so sleep deprived in my life. I am a self-declared Navy Seal.  I feel as though I have very little to give anyone. If I do more than lay on my bed, I feel exhausted. Every task feels like it takes 100% of my effort. What a lame way to live. And here I am feeling this way, forcing myself to spend what little mental and physical energy I have, on a boring lifeless research paper.  As I was reading today, I heard my door bell ring. I immediately felt the shooting pain through my arm and heart and a momentary injection of energetic alertness. "Who could it be? No one I want to see for sure. Probably a solicitor." I opened the door and was greeted by a young attractive latina woman dressed in nice clothes. I suddenly felt like a bag woman in my stained white T-shirt and boxers with the fly open. I smelled her pleasant perfume. I instantly thought, "I dont have the mental energy to argue right now," as I gazed down and noticed her carrying a Watchtower magazine. I realized, I'm not arguing anymore for a battle that I don't know what side I'm on. Monica was her name. She did a good job of not showing her irritatedness when I told her I had been told that her Bible was an incorrect translation. I told her everything as though "someone has told me that..." it wasn't "I believe that," or "You Jehovah's Witness are wrong in thinking... blah blah." I didn't want to fight. I didn't want to make her feel attacked or that I thought badly of her. I don't agree with what most "Christians" think or believe so why am I fighting their battle?  When I finished talking to Monica, I told God I was sorry for failing him if I did, but that I can not go on pretending anymore. I feel persecution from others: "You're not spiritually strong June. You need to trust God, blah blah." I feel as though I'm closer to God more now than I ever have been in some ways only because I have at least shown God who the real me is. I have shown myself who the real me is. And I'm still figuring out who that person is spiritually. This is my journey and my battle and I'm not letting anyone scaring me back into pretending to be a Christian again. If I become a Christian it's going to be the way I want to be one, and for me and no one else. It may be on my death bed, but I refuse to play games anymore. 
      
</post>
<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I am cool.  This is my blog.
      
</post>
</Blog>