<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
           Eleanor of Aquitaine:“How, from where we started, did we ever get to this?”  Henry II: “Step by step.” --The Lion in Winter  Buying new clothes can be so much fun because they give you a chance to see yourself in a new way. But sometimes shopping is not such a happy occasion. Like the other day, I had to buy myself a bunch of new pants because I haven’t lost the weight I gained a couple of months ago, and I can’t keep showing up for work in clothes that don’t fit.  I bought all black, of course, but since it was an emergency I had to take whatever black pants I could get. That’s how I wound up with black linen trousers embroidered with a summer-themed pattern: sun glasses, bathing suits, beach chairs. I call them my clown pants. I wore them yesterday, and all I needed was a big red ball to put on my nose.   I pray that this is the last time I have to buy emergency pants.       
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          Is going to Dunkin’ Donuts for coffee like reading  Playboy  for the articles? Well, whether it is or not, that’s what I did the other day—and may I add, I asked for skim milk, not regular, in my decaf.    On my way out, two surprising things happened: 1) I spotted a handsome man through the glass door, on his way in. A truly handsome man is an unusual find (let’s face it, there’s a reason women are called the fairer sex), yet there he was. 2) Then he held the door open for me!    It wasn’t his good manners that shocked me, but that he even  saw  me. Because fat women are virtually invisible to men.    I know, several times over, what it’s like to respond to an online personal ad with a photo, then never hear from the guy again. So for a handsome man, especially, not only to notice me but to be considerate too…! What is he, a circus act? Does he also catch bullets between his teeth?    Maybe, amid the sideshow fairway, he struck up a relationship with the Fat Lady that really left an impression. Maybe he has super-human vision that lets him see the invisible. Or maybe size just doesn’t matter to him. All I know is, I’m still scratching my head.      
</post>
<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
           I’m getting the fear.   Fear of failure. Fear of a lifetime of fat. Fear of further disappointing myself. Fear of never living up to my potential.    I’m losing resolve. I’m caving in. I’m feeling old. I’m looking fat.    And what exactly replaces food, when that is practically the only thing to look forward to? Salad, steamed vegetables, grilled chicken—they’re a penance. The reparation for years of bad choices leaves me gagging.    I can’t live like that and I can’t live like this. I can’t accept the way I am and I can’t change the way I am.    Just another day in the life of an addict.      
</post>
<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      If chocolate were crack, I’d be a $2 whore. So you can understand why I identify closely with drug addicts and alcoholics. (Workaholics? Not so much.)  I got a call recently regarding my blood test results. The general practitioner’s office manager began with: “The doctor wants you to make an appointment with the nutritionist.”  Why? She quoted my ridiculously high cholesterol, “bad” cholesterol and triglyceride levels.  “Dr. O wrote ‘Horrible!’ in your chart,” said the office manager.  I don’t need to see a nutritionist. I know what I’m doing wrong. I know I’m killing myself with food.  My mother literally dropped dead of a massive coronary when she was 63. Her mother died of a stroke at 60, followed two years later by her father—also of a stroke.   Everybody’s heard a story like my former neighbor’s, who continued to smoke even as she was suffocating with emphysema. I identify with such people. I always knew when the time came for me, I wouldn’t be able to help myself either, despite my family health history.  “Why don’t you just stop eating?” an acquaintance once asked me. Hey—thanks for the fresh insight! I never would’ve thought of that! Obviously, if it were that simple for me, I would’ve done it a long time ago.  My acquaintance wouldn’t understand the Apostle Paul when he wrote in the Book of Romans,    “I do not understand what I do…. I have the desire to do what is good, but I cannot carry it out. For what I do is not the good I want to do; no, the evil I do not want to do—this I keep on doing.”  I used to think that in Heaven I’d eat as much chocolate as I wanted without impunity. But not to have chocolate at all, and never even miss it— that  would be Heaven.     What I et today: Lightly sweetened iced tea, a croissant, 2 cups of fruit, half a mozzarella sandwich with pesto, and a baked potato with genuine old-timey butter. 
    
</post>
<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night I did a half-hour exercise tape. While that’s not much time, it’s a comfort to know that I actually burn more calories than a thin person doing the same workout because it’s extra work to tote all that lard around.  I used to love exercise. I got into it about 10 years and 60 pounds ago. I didn’t get thin, but my fat-to-muscle ratio changed significantly. I had a lot of endurance and strength, and actually got to the point where my body felt good even when I wasn’t exercising. (I never would’ve believed it if I hadn’t experienced it first-hand.)  Now I’m starting at square one and overcoming inertia is the primary challenge. Sometimes just watching an exercise program can intimidate me: I think I’ll never regain the level of fitness I had before because I’m so big and old, so I end up doing nothing.  My range of motion is incredibly limited now—was it so 11 years ago? Well, 11 years ago I didn’t have a bum back. I can barely bend to mid-shin now. 	 It makes me sad to remember when I could lie on the floor and bring my legs straight over my torso and touch my toes to the floor over my head. Maybe I had more elastin in my system at the time because I was an adolescent. I sure ain’t no adolescent now.    What I et today: Fruit, an oatmeal square and coffee with skim milk for breakfast; Salisbury steak, a scoop of mashed potatoes and peas with gravy and baked Lays for lunch; two handsful of mini pretzels, 2 oz of graham crakers and a cup of coffee w/whole milk. 
    
</post>
<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      God help me. My 20W pants barely fit any more. Six years ago, I was down to a 14 and, even though that is now classified as a plus-size in some venues, I felt very good about myself. At my thinnest (i.e., 20 years ago) I was an 8—roughly Catherine Zeta Jones’ size now—and couldn’t believe it. Even then, I knew it wouldn’t last.   But I never thought I’d get this big. When I saw myself in a new suit last week, I expected to look OK since it was a dark monochrome. But I looked like a double-wide trailer. Yes, I am critical of myself, but even in my mind’s eye, I don’t picture myself  that  big. The reality is actually worse than my perception. Now  that  is a nightmare.  I think about food, weight loss and fitness about 80 percent of the time. That means only 20 percent of my waking hours is devoted to everything else: God, family, friends, pets, culture, politics, ecology, the presidential election, movies, TV, books, music etc. Plus there are overlaps such as, “Why am I not as thin as actress I see on TV right now?” and “God, will you help me lose weight/exercise?” So, really, I think about food etc. more than 80 percent of the time.  OK, here’s a theoretically achievable but somewhat ambitious goal: To weigh less than 200 in six months. Is that too much to ask?     What I et today: 2 muffins, a serving of soft pretzel sticks with butter, a medium strawberry/pineapple smoothie, a few mini pretzels, most of a Taco Bell double-decker taco and an apple empenada. 
    
</post>
<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>
</post>
</Blog>