<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Can anybody tell me how to get the links on the side of the page? so I can put links for my sisters site and a few more. I feel so bored Yester day I went to "K" days ("k"= klondike) I went with Stephanie, my best friend, she is a very daring person, and I'm a very smart person, she goes on all the "puke-your-guts-out" rides, and I being smart, don't. Well its not like I didn't go on any scary rides, I just didn't go on "the drop of fear" or the "G" force".( both sickening) but I led a troupe of people through the pitch black caves of the terror trench, kind of like a haunted house, except you cant see any thing and there are sticky webs hanging from the roof, and rubber hands on the floor. I walked calmly through, pulling a chain of people, who were to scared to go in by them-selves, behind me, while Steffie was whimpering " lets get out of here" sorry Steff, but you were. my bravery lies in different places, those places being the more sensible ones. I can lead people through any obstacle ( except for riding a motorcycle over a flaming pit filled with crocodiles) I can lead a team very well, I can deal with being scared, I just can't deal with throwing up! thought I'd leave you a quote by me  "oversleeping doesn't make dreams come true, it just makes them last longer." :) "all that glitter ain't gold, its glitter glue" " it may not be made of gold but it sure is lined with silver!" " lord give me the courage to do what I ask you to allow me to do, instead of just asking and not following through." okay that last one was lame, but who really cares? if you did care you'd comment more often. No really I love you because you are reading my blog, I'd just love you more if you commented on to.   Synthea   
      
</post>
<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       hey hereI am, blogging from the Valentine residence .   it is quiet now almost too quiet, but wait thats because three of the five that are here right now   are sleeping, and the others are playing playstation 2 sonic  something or other  game .   for now here's the setting. "The rooms are quiet, the doors are al open, the windows are   covered, the air conditioners are on, their gentle hum drowned out by the sound of sonic   commenting on how he will beat the certain boss. The thumbs moving quickly over the hard   black controller. And the gentle hum of my computer as I click away at the key board, nothing   beats silence."    aren't I ridiculously dramatic?     i just helped abram( 6 almost 7 years old) install his grade two, math game, yes grade two .    his family goes like this   Brian Valentine Dad'   Linda Valentine mom   Jesse1 1 grade 9/8 male   Nathan 9 grade 8 male   Aleashea 8 grade 5 female   Abram 6grade 2 male   Andrew 5 grade 2 male   Shanna-lynn 3 preschool female   Jedidiah 2 preschool male   Daveena (spelling) 14  months    female         and i am baby sitting all of them except Aleashea and Andrew for two weeks.   what a work load, ontop of teahing swimming lessons.      love ya all, though i don't know who you are,       your in christ    S  ynthea  
</post>
<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      on;y one more day of work, today! yeah. except i have to baby sit for two weeks over night. gotto go bye i'll write later 
      
</post>
<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       WOW NOT TEN minutes from my last blog and i am now in a great mood ,  though i doubt it will last long i'm so tired.   i got a sub for thursday, so now i can go to Klodike days!      woo Hooo! i feal great, its kind of strange though i could't get a sub when i was    sick, but i can get one so i can have fun, strange the way God works i'll never understand it untill i reach heaven.   check out this site its my favorite    urlLink  http://www.lordoftherings.net/     
      
</post>
<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      i am sooo mad i just finnished writing a whole lot , and then i go to save it. it's not were i saved it it's gone! grrr!wow that blew off fast i'm not angry anymore i think it's becausi don't really have the energy to be that angry :) here are some new ( they might not be new to you) emmoticon-like things i found.  &gt;</post></Blog>