<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   It's strange. I'm a procrastinator, for the most part.  However, once I begin something, I can't turn away from working on it until it's done.  It's like I'm drawn to the task like I'm metal and it is a magnet.  Well, I think I have figured it out: how to add pictures on to my weblog.  However, because I didn't put these pictures up while I was in Oxford, I am now backtracking myself to add pictures to the blog. 

						
</post>
<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    I rest in my room under the hue of the light. I think to myself. I am sure I haven't forgotten. I haven't.   Property of D. Hall   

						
</post>
<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Maybe I can give them the evil eye.  Property of D. Hall  

						
</post>
<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Yummy going into Pizza hut?  Property of D. Hall  

						
</post>
<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    What are you lookin at?   Property of D. Hall  

						
</post>
<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Interesting, very, very interesting.  Hey what's the secret guys.  Hmmm...how can I become more creative.  Property of D. Hall  

						
</post>
<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   This evening my family and I went on a number of errands.  First, I had to get my windshield wipers re-placed (it rained). This took nearly an hour.  Second, I had to take my mother to several stores.  Realizing that I hate going to the store and shopping, I opted to go to another store to look around.  But wait, before you tell me that I was stupid because I went into another store,  I must tell you that it was not the average store.  It was Blick Art.  I love art stores.  They remind me of high school and how I sat and drew for hours.  I remember the peace I received from shading each gradation and finishing a piece to present to the class.    Tonight, I think I discovered what I've been missing.  It's true, I've been missing sleep a lot.  I've been missing friends. I've been missing reading.  I've been missing relaxing.  I've been missing intellectually stimulating conversations.  I've been missing exercise. And much more...Despite missing these things, the one thing I have forgot that I missed is my creativity.    It's horrible trying to get a blog suitable to my liking.  Either the colors are not right or there are no comments.  Whatever the case I've been struggling to make it mine.  It's not enough that the words are mine.  I want more.  I want the design too.   I remember last Friday night I went out with my family for steak dinner.  The one thing I realized was that as a work-aholic and perfectionist, I never found time to sit down and chill.  I never thought about what I wanted for me.  At that moment I decided to quit my second job.  However, it did not work that easily.  I tried and I was offered a compromise with my hours at the store.    In the Blick art store that thought re-manifested itself in my mind.  Why aren't I creative anymore?  What on earth do I do with my time?  Where did my dreams go?  Where's my creative spark?  I think that this is what I've been missing.  Now, I have to find it again, but slowly.    I have to dig down deep and enjoy more sunsets.  In fact I've got a sunset watching planned for Sunday evening. I have to spend time in solitude.  I have to gather myself before making another sporadic solution.  I have to re-learn to create. 

						
</post>
<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    An evening to remember, polticians ready for the election.  Property of D. Hall  

						
</post>
<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I can't bare to stay awake any longer. I'm finally going to sleep.  Tommorrow shall be a beautiful day.  Obviously, I figured it out. 

						
</post>
<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    This is me at Shakespeare's home.  Actually, I'm in a store.  I just thought that holding a feather would look cool.  Property of D. Hall  

						
</post>
<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink     Anger. I never know what to do. Right now, I'm angry at myself. I'm angry that I didn't expect so much responsibilty headed my way. At least not this soon.    I had been planning a trip to Los Angeles for the next three day weekend, when all of a sudden the bills came in. Knowing that this situation was headed my way, I made a plan of attack. I decided to pay my bills before they got to me. Guess what happens next? No. I am not victorious over the bill collectors. Instead, I struggle in the grasp of the evil one. Yeah, I said it! Bills are evil.    As I speak to the man who probably lives in Anywhere, Wisconsin, my facial expression changesas he tells me the banks policy. He cannot reverse the early feecharges. "How can I be charged for money I don't have! I set my bills to go out on the 15th not before," I said.    "Sorry, mam. We cannot reverse those charges," he said.    I sat in my chair at the front desk at work, furious at a system with no forgiveness...    Later this day, I chatted online with a home girl avoiding another inevitable bill. Time for student loans to get paid, I knew it. Instead of dealing with the statement, I decided to go to sleep. I had been depriving myself of many needed hours of sleep for the last two days. (This weblog's to blame. Wait, I am to  urlLink blame!@#$% ) Inapped for two hours.    Upon waking up, I decided to open the piece of mail that I knew wasa bill. I opened it, and of course it was an inevitable bill. They want TOO MUCH MONEY!!!    Now, I sit in my room angry. Angry that I lived as if I didn't expect this coming. And, angry that I now have to deal with this on top of family responsibilities. I barely have a grace period, ah... all of one month, and I have credit debt too.   After all of this, enrolling in law school looked great today! Between the government takingtwo of the eleven days of work for taxes, and an expensive investment in education, I don't know where to surrender. Pain is temporary, but victory is forever. There's a price to pay for everything.      

						
</post>
<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I can't believe that my work day is over. It has been hected. Today, I was asked about why I was wearing a wool jacket at least three times by the boss. I guess that's a hint that I can start to relax with my clothing. OF COURSE I still want to look conservative. I would much rather have it cooler inside though. Tonight, I'll watch a couple of episodes of the West Wing the first season. I have never loved a show so much. I sure hate I did not watch it when it was debuting. Instead, I'll catch it on DVD. I'll be several seasons behind. I just love Rob Lowe's character. The character makes me want to write for the president!   

						
</post>
<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Lord Henry said in  The Picture of Dorian Gray :   "It is sad thing to think of, but there is no doubt that Genius lasts longer than Beauty. That accounts for the fact that we all take such pains to overeducate ourselves. In the wild struggle for existence, we want to have something that endures, and so we fill our minds with rubbish and facts, in the silly hopes of keeping our place."   I must say that this is all too true. I am a person who thinks about my beauty lastly. I go to the store in ugly jeans and a T-shirt and with all sorts of writing on it. I prance around town make-upless. However, I have something else holding me up, and that is my degree and my mind. Genius is something I think one should aspire to be, not because one wants to, but because one needs to. I know that the little beauty I have will only last for a second, but the knowledge and understanding about this world is timeless.   

						
</post>
<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   This account is an example of how I usually deal with things ,which occur that I do not like. I like to respond by first getting it off my chest, and then I analyze it to understand why it happened. Here it goes.    Have you ever been to a fast food place that's too concerned with giving you what you want? I have. Just today I specifically told Arby's that I did not want any extra sauces. After parking on the side (because my order wasn't ready), the worker came out and brought my food. She quickly left to resume the lunch-time rush. When I looked into my bag lo and behold there was not one extra pack of Arby's sauce but several, along with horse-raddish. It still makes me shiver. ( I hate extra sauce) Also inside were several napkins. I can't make that bigof a mess. Where does it end? I guess Arby's has big overhead costs. I personally, do not want to add toitscostand neither does the environment. Can I speak for the envionment? I'm sure theyoung woman who prepared the bag was not concerned with the fact that I didn't want the sauces. In fact she may not have gotten the message from the person who took my order. However, all this is circumstancial and it only proves that when working fastone canforgettodo the thingsothers askedher to do.Anyhow, the point I am trying to make is, if you can save it, do it. I'm understanding, but I'll still complain.      

						
</post>
<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Josh and I in the Prime Rib Loft.  My sister Ro first introduced me to the Prime Loft. Josh is one of the hard workers there.   urlLink     urlLink    

						
</post>
<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Rhonda and Crystal outside of the movie I Robot urlLink     urlLink    

						
</post>
<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Girls night out urlLink     urlLink    

						
</post>
<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Arby's sauces  Property of D. Hall  

						
</post>
<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    It is not enough to get things done; they must be done right....     Arthur Twining Hadley (1856-1930)       One of myfavorite things to do is tostart over. I try to start everyday afresh, focusing on whatcan be done, rather than, what cannotbe done. Occasionally, the day starts off horribly andit makes everything elseseem togo wrong also.    For example, yesterday was one of the worst days of my life because it was so stressful. It seemed like everything I did went wrong at work. The copies were not getting made; the letters weren't written correctly; and, Ischeduled two peoplefor one time slot. In the end, the day ended on a positive note. I had to re-focus and think, "this happens to everyone; everyone has an off day.    Sometimes one forgets that it's not the end ofthe world ifshe has a day where everything is out of control. The next dayshe can make adjustmentsas needed. Key word, needed.    I can't control the world. I can't control time. I can only control what I do in the time I have. Hopefully, I can do the things I need to do. Even though sometimesthings go wrong, the next day is one more chance to do them, as well as a chance to start again.         

						
</post>
<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Greetings!  Property of D. Hall  

						
</post>
<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    My niece and I are using the cash register at the museum.  Property of D. Hall  

						
</post>
<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    This cutie is going to be a heart breaker!  Property of D. Hall  

						
</post>
<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Isn't she one of the cutest things in the world!  Property of D. Hall  

						
</post>
<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						     "There are two difficult things in the world. One is to make a name for oneself and the other is to keep it."           Walter Schuman      Indeed, creating a name for oneself is difficult. A signature personalty, a signature style and a manner of doing things, are just a few issues one must think about when making a name for oneself.   Recently, I have began to think about who I want to be. I first started by changing my hair, then my style and now I have began implementing a vocabularly which is conscious of how I want others to percieve me (using big words is what some call it). Nevertheless, it is me I am designing,a whole new attitude on life for myself and no one else.   I am responsible for myself. I must answer to myself. That is why I must take the first step as Schumann said, which is to make a name for myself. I suppose for the rest, only time will tell. Look at Martha Stewart. However, I am aiming at a name that endures like Oprah's!   
</post>
<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Me on a serious morning.  Property of D. Hall  

						
</post>
<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   Every once in a while, I receive a reality check.  It doesn't matter who it's regarding or what, but nevertheless it's a check that teaches me.  For instance, the other day someone I worked with was fired.  As a response I am trying to do the best work of my life.  Secondly, now someone else is coming in her place.  I am nervous because I think that I may have to work harder to edge out the competition.   Oh yes! that lovely phrase called competition.  It worries me.  It helps me, and it scares me.  Why you may ask?  Well, for starters I am trying to survive here and so I go into flight or fight syndrome.  I never usually fly, but fighting is hard and streneuous.  Of course, I tell  myself it is only temporary, but  do I hate it.  The reason why is that it begins all over again.  It never ends.   On a good note, I believe that I can fight!  It will be a challenge, but I will do more than survive.  I will conquer.  Speaking of conquering, I plan to go to the gym and run at least one minute.  ONE MINUTE!!!  I have to build up to more minutes, especially if I plan to run a 5-K.   

						
</post>
<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   I have turned over a new leaf.  I am 24 years old.  I can't believe it.  My birthday began kind of sappy, but is ended great.  I went to Joe's Crabshack.  It's my new favorite restuarant.  Photos of the glorious day below.  By the way this was over two weeks ago.   

						
</post>
<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Me, oh me!  Property of D.F. Hall  

						
</post>
<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Who's that girl???  Property of D.F. Hall  

						
</post>
<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Ro...  Property of D.F. Hall  

						
</post>
<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Good food  Property of D.F. Hall  

						
</post>
<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    More searching...  Property of D.F. Hall  

						
</post>
<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    A nigerian bill  Property of D.F. Hall  

						
</post>
<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Mom and sister picking out something to eat  Property of D.F. Hall  

						
</post>
<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    An old freezer at Joe's  Property of D.F. Hall  

						
</post>
<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    Joe's Crabshack door  Property of D.F. Hall  

						
</post>
<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    No, I don't I'm broke!  Property of D.F. Hall  

						
</post>
<date>13,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink    My sister blocking the sun at Joe's  Property of D.F. Hall  

						
</post>
</Blog>