<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Jay and I went out to Kreckle’s and ended up going out to the broken bridge! He didn’t seem like he liked it at first, but the most we walked around, the more fascinated he seemed. He took lots of fun pictures. We didn’t stay back there all that long cuz the bugs were eating me alive.   urlLink      urlLink      urlLink     After that, we came back and donked around at my house so I could show him pictures of my week with Doug and such and so we could get caught up since it’d be over two weeks since we’d seen one another. Later, we headed over to his house so I could drop him off. I really wanted to see Gretchen and Marty. They weren’t there when I got there, but by 8:30 they had both gotten home from work. I was so glad to see them. And they were glad to see me. I had originally only meant to go over there for a few minutes and it ended up being over an hour and a half. Oops!   =) Lydia
      
</post>
<date>29,June,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, here I am. I’ve been working on the massive “summary” of our week on and off all day. It’s been pretty quiet all day here. Miranda left for horse camp first thing this morning. I picked her up at 3:15 and took her and her friend Abby over to dance. Kyle had his friend over. He was pretty darned annoying… but not really a bad kid. He didn’t want to help pick up Life after we played and kept like throwing little rubber balls at me and such. He didn’t really do much that could hurt me badly or anything… it was just way obnoxious. Kyle kept standing up for me, though. And that was way cute.   I went to Lincoln yesterday with Leese. Then she came over to “mah crib” and we had a spaghetti picnic and went down to the broken bridge! We took some cute pictures… but I look like a boy cuz I had a big tee on and my hair back in a braid. So we have plans to get somewhat cuter and go back down there tomorrow and get more fun pictures.     urlLink     urlLink       urlLink     urlLink      Jay just called a few minutes ago to see if I’m up for a Kreckle’s run. Yum yum! Of course I’m up for Kreckle’s! How could I not be? And I WAY ready to see jay. It’s been over two weeks since I saw him last. Darn that  urlLink Spoke Folk  stealing him and Gretchen way.   Well, I’ll be wrapping it up so I can continue writing my entry over the week with Doug!   =) Lyd
      
</post>
<date>14,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      matt reminded me that blogger is supported by google. and google is amazing. but all my friends are on livejournal. *sigh.*
      
</post>
<date>12,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       When I get older losing my hair  Many years from now  Will you still be sending me a valentine,  Birthday greetings, bottle of wine   If I'd been out till quarter to three  Would you lock the door  Will you still need me, will you still feed me  When I'm sixty-four   You'll be older too  And if you say the word  I could stay with you       I could be handy, mending a fuse  When your lights have gone  You can knit a sweater by the fireside  Sunday mornings go for a ride  Doing the garden, digging the weeds  Who could ask for more  Will you still need me, will you still feed me  When I'm sixty-four   Every summer we can rent a cottage  In the Isle of Wight, if it's not too dear  We shall scrimp and save  Grandchildren on your knee  Vera Chuck  Dave   Send me a postcard, drop me a line  Stating point of view  Indicate precisely what you mean to say  Yours sincerely, wasting away  Give me your answer, fill in a form  Mine for evermore  Will you still need me, will you still feed me  When I'm sixty-four
      
</post>
<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      i fell in love with The Perks of Being a Wallflower all over again. i picked up so much more this time, too. so many more details. i rushed it last time. i read it for the basic plotline. and missed so many things. it was so much better this time.   "And in that moment, I swear we were infinite"
      
</post>
<date>11,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      we had an awesome storm a few hours ago. only bummer is, i was supposed to be going over to amber's for a cookout/swimming! but it was gorgeous. like you'd hear on a cd. and then it made the power go out for two hours. so when i wanted to go out, i had to manually open the garage door!   it's weird when the power finally kicks back on. the majority of the electrical items just pick up right where they left off. lights turn back on, the dish washer and washing machine kick back on, the tv, everything. they don't even act like there was ever a problem. it was weird to walk downstairs when my parents werent home. i thought they were. the computer light was on at mom's desk. and the stove top light. and the family room lights and TV. and everything. it's odd. it really is.
      
</post>
<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      yeah. shopping yesterday. sucked. a lot. really. and now, my legs hurt. a lot. *nod* we walked around  that  much. i suppose you could argue that maybe i'm out of shape, and that even a small amount of walking could make my muscles hurt. ...and with that, i would have to agree.   i'm finally straightening my hair. and realizing just how much karen really chopped off on friday. i'd been wearing it curly since then so i wouldn't have to find out. well, it's not good. at this rate, i'll never get anywhere near donating for locks of love. and gosh, i've only been trying since i was 13. i'm now 17. do the math. in addition, i decided way back when, that i wanted to wait to chop it all off until i went away to college. well, now things are looking like i won't be actually "going away" to college until i'm 19. not 18, as planned. my parents are a bit hesitant to send me out of state to college, but i won't have it any other way. so, it seems we're making a bit of an unofficial compromise. i go to Lincoln Land Community College (where my dad teaches part time, therefore, i get free classes) for a year, and get my free classes, and probably get some of my gen. ed. classes out of the way, and maybe continue with a couple... or three... of my languages. that seems to be the unspoken deal. hopefully it works out. wow. that was tangenting at its best. and didn't deserve to be one large paragraph. but ive never been good at the whole paragraph thing anyway. i really should learn not to post right after i wake up. yes, yes, oh, yay.   my computer is making a really odd, annoying, buzzing, weird, crap noise. doug and i tried to figure out what was causing it and i lost a chunk of my finger. mmm.
      
</post>
<date>10,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      cancel that about my day sucking! courtney is amazing!
      
</post>
<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      today sucked. a whole bunch.
      
</post>
<date>09,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      now would be a good time to go on about some wonderful news in my life!   I thought it was just luck that i could now fit into a B Cup as i've been wearing A since forever, but no! I'm now spilling out of all the A's! wooooha!   </post></Blog>