<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Hello from Thunder Bay! Land of fresh air! So long smog!      Ali and I arrived in TB Wednesday morning. Mummy was waiting forus at the airport, and bid us a rather treacly greeting. Just kidding.       All has gone well. I'd like to paint the living room + kitchen...but I fear it'll be a bigger job than I'm prepared to commit to. Mum wants green for the living room.Anything is better thanpink.      Well, I'm off to enjoy crisp breathing. Will talk later.  
      
</post>
<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Last night I saw  The Door in the Floor .Jeff Bridges was great, as usual. And"Jon Foster"...this was my first experiencewith him, and I thought he was great.As for Kim Basinger, I wasn't sure what to think of her. At first I thought her acting was a little overdramatic, but then I recalled that she won an Oscar, so I figuredher performance was purposeful. The jury is still out. NOW definitely liked her "aimless dismay". I like this take on her:    "This is Basinger's best film and performance since L.A. Confidential, in part because Williams, like Curtis Hanson, recognizes the essential fragility behind Basinger's beauty."    She definitely has fragility behind her beauty. Those eyes...    Anyway, ineffectual is the word of the day. Thisstrong coffee I'm drinking is anything but ineffectual. Now I'm wired and ready to conquer.    
      
</post>
<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
                 AVOCADOS RULE!      
      
</post>
<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
          Today's word of the day is salient. I'll try to use it in a sentence...        "Salient meansnoticeable or prominent."        In other news, I read in theMetrothat Peterborough is flooded! My Granny lived in Bobcaygeon, and we went to Peterborough often, so this hits close to home. There've been no injuries, but the old people had to be moved out of their nursing home into a hockey arena. Unbelievable. And then this quote:        "At one point early this morning, you'd be taking your life in your hands if you ventured onto some of those streets. You would not have been able to stand up; the currnet was moving that fast."        Isn't that wild? For more info hit this:        urlLink   urlLink http://www.ctv.ca/servlet/ArticleNews/story/CTVNews/1089895413637_5/?hub=CTVNewsAt11      Well, I suppose duty now calls. Talk later.     
      
</post>
<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        The word of the day according to dictionary.com is  ACUITY  (Acuteness of perception or vision; sharpness.)    The word of the day according to me is  LABRADOODLE  (Cosmo says it's a cross between a labrador and a poodle.)      
      
</post>
<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        I'm happy to report that it's almost home time. It's been one ofthose days where your hair is  driving you nuts  andyou just wanna put it up, but you don't want to get a ponytail dent. The wind is not helping the situation.        My horoscope today was confusing: "Do some personal pampering. Refuse to put your feet up." A little contradictory, but maybe it's symbolic of the Pisces fish swimming inopposite directions?        Well, no use dwelling on it.        'Til later,        La Boot      
      
</post>
<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
        Hello. Here I sit at work. I love keeping a journal, but lately I can't pick up a pen. So I'm taking the electronic route. That's the story.   Today is a grey day. Cool and damp. I woke up a little after 8, and I feel quite refreshed because I was in bed by midnight last night.   I don't have much else to say, unless you want to hear about what I have to do today at work. What do I have to do today? Well I'm working on a spreadsheet that will act as a directory for contacts. Also, I'll have to make a deposit and pay a few bills.   This weekend I really need to focus on finding a place to live in September. I also need to buy a cat carrier for Ali, and a bike.   Well, time to work. I'm sure I'll be back later today...   The Boot      
      
</post>
</Blog>