<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My best friend is getting married next year to a man I've never met. I've never even seen a picture of him! She's asking if I'll come to the wedding. Of course I said yes, but gawrsh, I wanna see a picture of him already. I've asked politely several times in the past year. Now I am resorting to email harrassment. I'm emailing her song lyrics, all with the word "picture" in them. So far I've emailed her "Pictures of You" by The Cure and "Turning Japanese" by the Vapors. Today I am considering sending "Photograph"...that's Def Leppard, I think. Ihope she gets the frickin' hint and emails me a pic soon. I'm not sure how many more songs I can think of without doing some actual research. 
     
    
</post>
<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My grandmother just called me from California. She and I are both haunted by the generation in between. 
     
    
</post>
<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Large homemade Starbucks iced coffee...bliss. The boyin SpongeBob pajamas is talking nonstop next to me on my bed. He is offering me 15 kisses, but quickly retracts the offer. Hereconsiders and gives me 34 instead.   Ah, he went to bother Daddy now. Perhaps I can think clearly for a few minutes.   In my 35 years of life (almost 36) I have spent over 10 years in therapy. I'm not currently in therapy right now, but I probably should be. My childhood is rushing back in a wave of dizzying and paralyzing fear. I'm trying to come to grips with the soap opera which was my life...and in some respect still is my life. I have a journey ahead of me. I am afraid to begin it, but I must journey to retain anything which resembles sanity. I must face my demons and vanquish them handily, lest I become a mirror image of my mother who has been admitted to a mental health facility 3 times in the last month.   Since the wave began over a year ago I have insulated myself so that nothing could hurt me. Yet I still hurt. I must reclaim my psyche and rise as the Phoenix from the ashes.   Or perhaps I can just debate here which of my parents did the most damage, that would be fun!  I need to write. What other reason does one need to blog than that one? 
     
    
</post>
</Blog>