<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It is currently July 15, 2004, and don't we all know what that means? Well for those of you who aren't 17 and about to enter into your senior year at GACS, I'll tell you. It means that college choices and applications and school schedules and standardized tests and working and college visiting are all tunneling down on you at a rather rapid pace. (Forgive the grammar, I'm reading Faulkner, and on that note I should have finished the book by now, but it got caught in my mother's car, and we tried to move the seat back and it got demolished, and instead of picking up just another copy, I reverted to my OCD behavior and had to find a Modern College Library Edition, which I just did, at my local goodwill. Thanks for sticking with me thusfar.)   Well, if you are not in this situation, let me enlighten you, it's pretty crazy. Not crazy in the sense of  oh I forgot I have a vocab quiz tomorrow  or  wait, was I supposed to turn that homework in last Tuesday  or even  do you expect me to believe that the AP exam is tomorrow and I'm supposed to plan prom tonight?  No, its a different sort of crazy. Its kind of the crazy decisions that will dictate the rest of one's life. (I choose now to use the correct pronoun use.) Its the sort of thing that makes one realize that even without a Jr./Sr. Banquet to plan, one still has AP classes galore, Cheerleading, Academic Team, and college applications. Let me also point out that the applications aren't even that bad, its the decision of which one to go to that's going to kill me.   Another clarification I should make is that I'm not meaning to complain. Honestly, I am not. I wouldn't know how to live if it weren't in this hectic mess. In fact, apart from feeling buried alive in all the stress, I find energy and purpose out of it. Its a sort of doppelganger mission of sorts. Call me Ismael. Well actually, don't call me Ishmael. I just wrote that because I couldn't think of a literary hero with a weird purpose. Ok, here's one, call me Howard Roark, Dagny Taggert ( think "my work was all I had..."). And although I know Ayn Rand doesn't apply to my life, and that I don't espouse all of her views, her characters are accurate here. What I'm trying to say is I want love, just a different kind. Also, not really what I wanted to say.     At this point I'm sure all of my *cough readers cough* will be thinking, how can this seemingly intelligent girl jump around like this? Well I'm sitting here telling you, or rather typing to you. I am broadcasting over the seas that there is a method to my madness. My happiness is not at stake here, my parents are not pressuring me, I don't desperately need scholarship money, I don't need to put all these crazy expectations on myself. BUT, here it is, the dies irae,  and what does the trumpet sound? I am freely walking into all sorts of classrooms and hallowed halls, with freshly lined paper and an extra fine point pen. And ladies and gentlemen, if you have stuck with me this far, I am pleased to tell you that I am happy. I think.    
     

    
</post>
<date>15,July,2004</date>
<post>
</post>
</Blog>