<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Why is it that every time I see her/him, I long to see you… Every time I feel her/him  I want to feel you…?  Why do I seek fro you when I have her/him?  I have him/her… but… I want you  This is driving me mad. You are driving me mad. Pushing me to the brink of insanity…  because of what you do to me. Even if you don’t know it, even if I don’t know it.  Because I feel it. But… I love her/him  Do I ?  Am I lying to myself ? was I only drawn to her/him because I can’t have you? Because I know you can never be mine?  Or… because I thought I didn’t love you anymore? But why is it that I prove to myself wrong when you’re so close to me? So close yet… so far away. Because I know this is not meant to be  So… why did I turn to her/him?  … I didn’t want to be alone anymore. Even for just a brief moment  And I realized I’d rather be alone. I’d rather be alone than live this lie  I’m a fool for daring to confuse myself… for blindly trusting a complete stranger… and for tolerating false feelings. And knowing all along… but refusing to turn back  I didn’t want to hurt her/him  But I’m hurting her/him more by doing this  And I know it. I know that I’m lying to her/him… I’m lying to myself. Why can’t I love her?  Because I’m still in love with you.  Then why can’t I stop?  Because I don’t want to  I’m lost within this void of complexity… caught within conflicting emotions  Especially when I’m with her/him. Why does she/he love me?  I want her /him to hate me… hate me for not loving her/him… hate me for loving you  I want her/him to hate for wishing that she/he was you…  Falling… hah! Such a vague word to say. But just recently, I can’t help but use the term again for something I felt inside. Sometimes I think. Why you? Why does it have to be you, of all the people to fall in with? And up to now I’m still wondering why    When I think about the things that ignited this untouched emotions I can’t help but laugh  I dismissed the thought as something unimportant and ridiculous but… no  I felt as I’m so weak to fall that fast. the first time I look in your deep, brown orbs, the time we grew quite close to each other because of the nights we shared stories and laughs over the phone.. all were still deeply etched in my mind. Sometimes I’m moved to the verge of crying because of what we’ve become now, so cold and distant to each other.  My sanity’s driving me mad, what shall I do? There’s only one way… for you to know the truth. The truth that I have hold a clandestine love towards a person I knew I should not love. But… I can’t. I can’t because of my fear towards rejection, pain and love not given back. The half of my mind says I should but the other says otherwise.  Now I’m more confused of the things occurring. What will I suppose to do? Will I just keep this seemingly unending emotion to my lone self or should I shout to the world what I really feel?    Well… I have no choice but to choose the latter. I’m going to tell you. I know, this note wouldn’t even change the way you look at me, the way you show that beaming smile every time I meet you along the road, or even the way you regard me as your friend. But even though this feeling I have for you won’t have a chance to even reach that heart of yours, I’ll be all right.   
    
</post>
</Blog>