<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         I just ate a burned microwavable frozen  chicken pot pie  that was drowning in  tabasco  brand red pepper sauce. Life is good.      But anyway...      I recieved another  collegeboard.com  letter with specific information on how I did on my  June 5th  SAT exam. You know, stuff like which problems I missed, which problems I skipped, the problem difficultly level... And while I was skimming through this SAT  mumbo jumbo , it suddenly hit me that collegeboard.com is very, very mean. Ibelieve it enjoys  watching the profoundtears of  innocent  teenagers and listening to their distressed anddesperate cry for mercy.    I mean, really, how many lives are they destroying with this one exam, anyway? How many  dreams  are being squashed? How many times has the SAT exam kicked dirt onto the faces of dedicated students?     Who am I  ranting  for? I am rantingfor thestudents who had their goals set on furthering their education, but was never accepted to their dream schoolbecause of the stupid test they call SAT. I'm defending the parents of students who spenthundreds and thousandsof dollars on worthless,  excruciating  hours of private tutoring. I am defending schools who are ranked in accordance to how well their students do on a test that includes problems that will NEVER be applied to real life. Goddamn, it's enough to tick the most composed person off.    And you know what I hate about  optimistics ? ...This one, insanely redundant excuse:    "SAT does  not  measure a person's intelligence! Colleges look more into community servce and good grades and GPA--"    --and BULLSHIT!    Yes. Bullshit. That's what it all comes down to, ladies and gentlemen:  Bullshit .        
     
    
</post>
<date>16,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          This was a short essay, and my first stream of consciousness piece,that I wrote several months back. I really don't know what else to write about.             Three-quarters of a year ago, it was my seventeenth birthday. I was at Olive Garden and the nice waitress gave me a free slice of cake of my choice. I believe I chose the lemon cake—its official name I do not recall—but I know I chose lemon because I have a huge thing for citrus-flavored foods. Someone told me that Olive Garden is the McDonald’s of all the Americanized Italian restaurants—but that isn’t of importance.      What’s important is that I was sitting there with my family and newly found adult friends (please do not ask why these new “friends” of mine are adults, as I do not want this piece of writing to get very long), and that slice of cake was staring up at me. The candle had flickered like a miniature, pocket-sized firework, and as tradition goes, I was told to make a wish and blow out those fireworks.      I didn’t make a wish. I was more eager for the cake than I was for any tradition.        Yet I suppose that while I was eating the cake—the cake was good, though it could have been better with coffee—I knew that deep down inside, I wanted nothing more than happiness. That is, after all, what wishes all come down to, right? Nobody makes a wish for their own misfortune or grief. That would be stupid and very much ridiculous.      Well three-quarters of a year later, I am sitting on top of my grandmother’s bed with an extremely slow laptop on my lap, wondering if, in the past three-quarters of a year, my wish had come true. Am I truly happy?       School is over and I graduated my junior year, passing my Language Arts class with an 89.5. I hate decimals. And I hate 89s. I also hate classes that teach you writing. Writing, to me, is a form of expression, not a form of rules and regulations.      And it has almost been a full year since my parents’ divorce and my adjusting to the huge changes in my life. I moved to a different state, leaving behind the small Texas hometown that I grew up in, as well as the people that I grew up with. I lost my best friend. I haven’t seen my dad in months. In my new, rented house, I share a room with my grandmother, who snores the way a person passes bad gas. I don’t have a driver’s license yet, and I’m too scared of my new neighborhood to ride the bus all by myself. …I don’t think girls should ride public buses by themselves. I know a girl who did. The story wasn’t pretty.       And yet with all these concerns and with all the impediments that seem to block my path to happiness, I suppose I cannot complain. There were still the times when I smiled and appreciated the good term called life. In that perspective, I am happy. Whether I am or not, however, I still think back to three-quarters of a year ago and recall that that lemon cake tasted good—very good, actually.    It just needed the coffee.         
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       So it was my first week as a senior and it's getting better and better as the days go by (mainly due to the fact that I recently changed my schedule). It's packed with all the good stuff: Six periods of art and seven periods of AP courses throughout the year. It'll be fun. Being nerdy is my thing after all.          Schedule for Year 2004-2005     1)  Photo Design    2)  AP Psychology    3)  Economics    4)  Drawing  Painting    5)  AP 2-D Design Portfolio    6)  AP Literature       1)  Photo Design    2)  AP Psychology    3)  AP American Government    4)  Photo Design    5)  AP 2-D Design Portfolio    6)  AP Literature       Um, wheee. Thrilling, yes? Ah, and for you dumb ones, the first set of periods are for my first semester and the second set is for the second semester. And yes, I am taking Photo Design three times this year, which means I will graduate with four semesters of Photo Design, as well as three semesters of Drawing  Painting.            My Goal:    Graduate out of high school with enough skills to make Da Vinci roll in his grave.            Besides all the art I'll be messing around with and the studying I will have to do in order to raise my embarassing GPA, I will spend a good portion of this year enjoying the last year of my youth.           Birthday:  Not celebrating        Homecoming:  Not going        Pep Rallies:  Don't care        Part-time Job:  Can't drive        Prom:  Not going        Senioritis:  Won't have it        Graduation Celebration:  Won't have that either         The last year of my youth will be exciting. Why? Because by the end of the year, no matter how much I study or how often I exclude myself from the joys of the last year of high school, and whether I pass or fail, become smart or stupid, get into Harvard or a special eds school, I will still be able to lift my head and walk as an adult with the prospect of growing up and initiating my life.    ...Actually, that sounds a little corny.   Forget I typed any of that. I'm gonna go study Psych now.    
     
    
</post>
<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Yes, when I have little Johnny Depps and Johnny Depp grandchildren, I will prop them on my knee and say to them, "You see this hand here? Well sonny, back in my day when I was a beautiful and a fabulous girl of seventeen, I shook hands with Congresswoman  Denise Majette ."       "Oooooo... Aaaahhh... Really , grandma Stefanie Depp?"        That's right, sweetie.      I was down at  Albany, Georgia  again with The Godfather and my mother yesterday for our final panal meeting for a bid on this huge project for my mom's company. Well, conveniently,  Denise Majette , who is currently running for a senatorial position, was there. She's a wonderful woman. Smart and a brilliant speaker (though I suppose anyone brave enough to become the  first  female, African-American  Senator  of Georgia has got to be a brilliant speaker).      Granted, during her wonderful speech, I was particularly busy swatting gnats, squishing ants, and fanning myself from the cruel southwest Georgian  humidity , and probably missed half of what she was saying in the process. Either way, from what I managed to pay attention to, I'm quick to decide that she is a very awesome person. After all, anyone who was an undergrad of  Yale  and graduated out of  Duke 's School of Law, then becoming a famous judge  has  to be worth the recognition. Plus, she's female and a minority.       Two thumbs way, way up! :)    If you're an American citizen, a Georgian, and at least the age of eighteen, then  vote  for her. I probably will when September 17 rolls along.      Oh. For anyone who's curious but too lazy to  Google , that's her :          
</post>
</Blog>