<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I got back Sunday afternoon.  It was a fun wk for me at least.  Not too sure if my brother and sister had as much fun as I do, but they normally don't like hanging out with the family up north.   Monday I put my two wks in at Wendy's.  Yup-next wk is my last wk of being employed.  Two days after I came back home Ashley decides to be stupid-runs off again.  Of course the consequences get worse.  Now she has one of those tracking devices that are worn on the ankle. Her life is on a downward spiral.  But last night we found her and my mom dropped her off at the police station and they had court today(that's when she got the anklet thingy).    Today was a pretty good day for me.  Nothing too extraordinary.  Woke up at 8:00(which is a suprise, especially with no alarm), took my sweet time to get ready for the day, then went up to my old alma marter(sp?).  I saw some of my old band buddies-it was nice.  Then Kelly and I went to La Fiesta to eat.  After all that I went to Biloxi.    The doctors scared the crap out of me.  They made me think that I was going to have to get two or three shots. HA ha.  Tomorrow night my mom and me are going out shopping for dorm stuff. Yee haw.
    
</post>
<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I got back Sunday afternoon.  It was a fun wk for me at least.  Not too sure if my brother and sister had as much fun as I do, but they normally don't like hanging out with the family up north.   Monday I put my two wks in at Wendy's.  Yup-next wk is my last wk of being employed.  Two days after I came back home Ashley decides to be stupid-runs off again.  Of course the consequences get worse.  Now she has one of those tracking devices that are worn on the ankle. Her life is on a downward spiral.  But last night we found her and my mom dropped her off at the police station and they had court today(that's when she got the anklet thingy).    Today was a pretty good day for me.  Nothing too extraordinary.  Woke up at 8:00(which is a suprise, especially with no alarm), took my sweet time to get ready for the day, then went up to my old alma marter(sp?).  I saw some of my old band buddies-it was nice.  Then Kelly and I went to La Fiesta to eat.  After all that I went to Biloxi.    The doctors scared the crap out of me.  They made me think that I was going to have to get two or three shots. HA ha.  Tomorrow night my mom and me are going out shopping for dorm stuff. Yee haw.
    
</post>
<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Serendipity means a fortunate mistake or accident...Today while in New York City we went by there(inspired by watching the movie "Serendipity").It's an ice cream shop/restaurant. Although we didn't get to eat there b/c the wait was too long. So I tooka picture of the sign. But let me tell you the beginning of the story...ha WE GOT LOST ON THE SUBWAY..thanks to my lovely sister. So we were there we were going the total opposite direction in which we were suppose to be going for about an hour and a half. Once we got off it was raining-ack. Rain, Umbrellas, alot of people, and New York City do NOT MIX WELL. So after this whole experience you can imagine how cranky and irritated I was.      Yesterday we went to Six Flags Great Adventure. It was fun- I rode most of the roller coasters and convinced my sister to do so as well. So now she loves them too. Tomorrow is the reunion. I'm not sure how I feel about it. Hopefully it won't rain. All I know is that there are a few people coming from Ireland, France, and Austrailia so I'm excited about meeting them. Not much left to say...ciao  
    
</post>
<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Yesterday we left Penntucky and went to my Nana's house. My little cousin Sean was there-I felt like a little kid again...I played with bubbles(tried to eat one or two), put together a spider man puzzle, and made little figures out of playdough. Later on that night we went out to the boardwalk. Sean and I went on this upside down ride-which was great! Then he and I went rock climbing. It was fun. The houses that I saw though were gorgeous. Yea-and they only run for a million or more dollars. I love it up here-I've always loved the north. Today we planned on going to the beach, but instead we'll be going out to the lake. That's fine with me I guess.  byee 
    
</post>
<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      It was nice to be able to get to sleep in today(got up about 11:30). A couple hours later we left to go out to eat at Fuddpuckers-then to the park for Christopher. But all of us "grown-ups" played as well. Man I miss being a kid. Even though I still kinda am. Then we went to downtown Bethlehem, PA. I liked the environment of everything. After all of that I was ready for nap. Then my cousin Katie came over to Beth's for dinner. Yummy-it was baked Ziti(spelling?). Very cheesy. Right now I'm listening to the Gin Blossoms, I was actually suppose to go to their concert, but my sister waited like an idiot to get the tickets and then they were sold out.   Tomorrow, we're suppose to be heading out to my Nana's-back in New Jersey. audios 
    
</post>
<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This morning my brother woke me up, singing. Yea at like 9 in the morning, I wasn't too happy. Last night, I caught fire flies for the first time ever. It was cool, I've never really seen them up close. One lit up in my hand-i love the little things.Later we met up in this little diner with my Aunt Kathy, Conor, and Ryan. Then we went bowling. The first time we played I won with a 98! Then my sister got a little competitive and then she won by one point. I had a score of 102(hey I guess I should mention we had the little gutter liners :) ) ha ha.    Later on this week we plan on going into the city, Six Flags, The boardwalk, and then of course the reason why we came- the family reunion...i wonder if anybody will be able to guess who I am. I'm at Beth's house right now, earlier Uncle Tom, Darren and Clare, and Uncle John were here. This is going to be short-  Au revoir.   
    
</post>
<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I didn't get to sleep until about 3:00 in the morning and then woke up at 7:30. Miki worried me because I thought we were going to be late for our flight. But of course, we got there way before time. There was a mixup with the tickets Miki and Christopher had, so their luggage was "temporarily" lost. Hahaha. After we got picked up by Uncle Tom and Aunt Kathy we went on over to my Aunt Ann Marie's.It was nice-I saw my Uncle Frank and Aunt Eileen as well. Then we had this nice little barbecue...tasty, I think I can officially say, I like shrimp! Tomorrow we'll be going over to my cousin Beth's house and stay there for a day or two. I think we're also going to the boardwalk. That's all I have to say for now, I feel like I'm ignoring my hostsssss.   Goodnight YouS Guys. 
    
</post>
<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Hmm...I already have a journal type thing online already on xanga. But I feel like this one is going to be different in a way. Tomorrow I'll be leaving for New York and Jersey. I love it up there-the feeling is amazing. So different from the coast...well at least to me that is. Not so sure I could live in a big city like that though.  It's 11:07 right now and Christopher, my nephew, is on the couch asleep-and here I am typing for myself, sipping fruit juice, and listening to Journey's faithfully. Music-I love it. All varieties, whatever catches my ear, whatever catches my emotions...country, alternative, soft rock, latin, jazz, the genres go on and on. Ha-it's 11:11 right now...reminds me of Puja in class. She never missed making a wish on that thing. Occasionally I would wish, just for the fun of it too. It's exciting about going off to college, but I still have longing for the past. I kinda want to go back one more year-not possible I know.  It's a mystery. But they still try to see  Why something good could hurt so bad... One love feeds the fire. one heart burns desire. Wonder whose crying now? ----Journey.  Night. 
    
</post>
<date>03,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        You build me up You knock me down Provoke a smile And make me frown You are the queen of runaround You know it's true You chew me up And spit me out Enjoy the taste I leave in your mouth You look at me I look at you Neither of us know what to do There may not Be another way to your heart So I guess I'd better find a new way in I shiver when I hear your name Think about you but it's not the same I won't be satisfied 'til I'm under your skin Immobilized by the thought of you Paralyzed by the sight of you Hypnotized by the words you say. Not true but I believe them anyway                                                                                     
</post>
</Blog>