<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I came home today at around… 9:30 pm. We had a group project. We interviewed an entrepreneur. I tried a construction worker’s hat afterwards. When I took it off, my friends started laughing because my forehead suddenly became dusty! Haha =p It was fun. We rode a Ford Ranger(courtesy of beat). As one of the leaders of the group, I did a lot of things. It was laborious. I learned that even though there are factors that hinder you from attaining your goals… you should never give up… life is about taking risks… and I will take em’… anytime… anywhere... I don’t want to have regrets. I don’t care if I commit mistakes because you will indisputably increase your knowledge from it. It is where you will be able to learn by yourself. Toil and endure is what it takes. You have to persist until you succeed.
     

    
</post>
<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I attended my prosec class last Saturday… no gimmicks for me except for a party :)… I talked to the daughter of my teacher. Her name was Meg and she’s in first grade. I noticed that she was an intelligent conversationalist, a fluent English-speaker and a friendly kid. So I told myself… “this kid must be a product of MC”… and I guessed it right… She’s a knoller! I told her that I was also a knoller before. I asked the name of her section and she said, “1-Adelfa”… I was like… hey that was my section before!!! Anyway, I went to Alexis’ party afterwards and I came home past 11pm. The party was fun!!! Benjo taught me how to play the piano. I’m getting fat. I want to take up fencing lessons but the problem is, it’ll make your arms bigger! After my prosec lessons, I plan to take drum lessons and taekwondo lessons. I hope those plans will push through or else, I don’t know what’s in store for me… There’s something good that happened this week but I wasn’t able to write it here in my blog.. I was so lazy that I didn’t study anything but I still qualified in our science quizbee(top 1 out of  5 others who qualified). It’s my second time so wish me luck… =p
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My mom said that if my grades aren’t that good, I’m gonna have a gimmick cut-off. If that’s gonna take place, I can only go on gimmicks about twice a month. That sucks!!! I have some things to go against. First, I noticed that most of my friends that are in love are preoccupied or in a world of their own. I hate that… Next, some people take my escapades gravely. I love kidding around but I don’t intend to piss people off. Finally, my friendly attitude is being misunderstood. I don’t want to elaborate. I had a great time in yellow cab with my friends, Beat and Trixx. The pizza was luscious!!!  I’m have a mediocre of sleepyness and being wide awake... now that's weird.  Here’s a quote that I wanted to send to a friend of mine but I don’t have load!!! Haha =p I’ll just share it with you guys.(swerte niyo!!! Joke…)  I really want to be close with you Close enough that in time,  I’ll just hold your hand and without saying anything, You know I’m saying something like this: “Dito ka lang hindi ko kayang mawala ka.” 
     

    
</post>
<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I asked my seatmate and laboratory partner… “How do I look?” … “wasted!” hahaha… School was so laborious, arduous, painstaking, backbreaking, grueling, exhausting or simply nakakapagod!!!… I ate at mcdo… I feel like writing in tagalog… so… puyatan na toh!!! My eyebags will be back to life once again… hahaha kiddin’!!! seriously, I have to do a lot of things right now. I don’t know what to do first. I want candy corner!!! This is so non-sense. I better end this blog before it gets tedious. =p 
     

    
</post>
<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      like my blog title says… I'm a gimikera. i'm still a member of barkada twenty!!! it's the best barkada. I came from linden suites. I also came from 17:28 concert. Me and Trixx went to Starbucks afterwards. Instead of ordering the tried and tested, all time favorite Mocca frap, I tried something new… strawberries and cream. It’s yummy!!! The mall was crowded. I couldn’t take it. A friend once said, “ang sarap magbasket pag umuulan.” And so I said, “sige try ko.” I waited for the rain to come just to try the basketball thing out. It rained a while ago. I took my bro’s basketball in the car and played basketball in the rain. It was fun!!!  
     

    
</post>
<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I can still smell smoke right now. That is for the reason that our student-directed laboratory experiment in biology took place hours ago. We preserved a milkfish. Smoking was the most amusing kind of preservation. I insisted on holding the fish on the stick. The whiff of the smolder was excruciating. The fish ended up squashy. Me and my groupmates smelled awful afterwards. When we got inside the classroom, I sprayed Victoria’s Secret’s 77 magnetism perfume. It was a mixture of the whiff of smoke and a heavenly scent.
     

    
</post>
<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I attended my speed reading lessons today. I read a book entitled, “Jonathan Livingston Seagull.” I read it for 6 minutes. Here’s a book review…   As a learner, have you felt that you are spaced out from “the flock”? Well, this story is essentially about a seagull, struggling to be distinctive, innovating new flying skills and setting his mind to a goal without limits. That seagull is Jonathan. He wants to improve his skills in flying. The story’s imagery is inspirational. It conveys a message to the readers to dig deeper, climb higher, and apply yourself with more vigor for a reason not quite explicable, even by you. Don’t limit yourself. Bach’s wizardry with metaphors is ingenious. Jonathan's determination and all-consuming passion to fly higher and faster and more safely parallels with my own desire to be better in all aspects. I found myself realizing the broader underpinnings of what it truly means to be a learner, a teacher, and an evolving spirit all-in-one. This book is truly a must-read, something to savour and to retain in memory for the learnings that it taught me can never be acquired in the traditional school lessons. 
     

    
</post>
</Blog>