<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         So, I went to diving yesteday, did one 2 1/2 and made it all the way around, then i did another and landed smack on my face, a day later, I STILL HAVE A HEADACHE!!!     I was at Candace's last night. First time in like forever! Haha but anyway, we went out to the Oaks for some midnight swim, but it got rained out. We went to Chili's and ate instead then went to blockbuster to get some movies. We got "You Got Served" and "The Perfect Score" since those are the only 2 movies her mom would let us get. Haha, yeah, sucks! But anyway I might be going to Christy's later tonight.. HAHAHAHA! JJ is scared shitless of her, it's so funny..    Candace told Pat today that he used to much tounge, it pissed me off! But that is like all that I have to say now.. so I'll chat ya up later!   
     

    
</post>
<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         So, I was at Utica Square last night, like every Thursday night, and it was mucho fun! Like at first things went kinda slow, but then everyone split from each other, I went somewhere with Patrick, and then Candace, Jackie, and Callie went somewhere else, later on I find out they were trying to find us.. but anyway, back to Patrick. We went into a lot of different stores, held hands, you know.. that kinda stuff. Then we walked to someplace.. I don't even know where, andwe kissed, then we walked back to everyone else. I met, er.. Katy? Patrick's like old lover or something, I dunno what she was, but I met her. She said she just wanted to meet Patrick's girlfriend, and I have no idea when I became that, I don't remember these simple words, "Wanna go out with me?" Never, never do I remember hearing, or reading them. But if I'm his girlfriend then like, what happened between me and Jake, and Candace and Jake, and Madison and Jake is kinda.. BLEH!          Hahaha, only funny thing at Utica Square though was that, a couple of us had to kiss another girl &gt;.    Anyway, I had Jackie over to spend the night, we swam and I figured out how long I can hold my breath. 1 minute, 30 seconds.. Yeah, that's right, I can hold my breath for that long. Haha, but that's really all that I have to tell.. I'll chat ya up later!   
     

    
</post>
<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         So, I have been at Madison's for the past 2 days. I haven't been able to sign on because her computer is PISS slow! Haha, anyway, here is what has been going on.     At Madison's house I learned to skateboard, and so did she. She got a new fan for her room so its actually cool and not burning hott! I came home today, got a new swim suit, a new shirt, and some new school shoes. I also when to the farmers market with my mom and got some fruites and veggies. I came home and Candace and Jake came over, we skateboarded and waited for Madison and stuff. Then we went swimming, this is were the fun started. Hahaha. We swam and stuff, and then it started getting darker, and out of the blue Madison brings up how everyone should make out with Jake, well, funny thing is, we all did. Heh, Candass was first, then me, then Madison. I didn't mind it, it's just.. well I kinda have Patrick S. I mean, me and him aren't going out, but we kissed and he likes me, I like him.. I think we are kinda something, but I'm not sure! Anyway, after that Madison, Candace, and I got pizza, ate it all.. we were way beyond hungry.     So to break this down, sweet and short, I had a kick ass couple of days. I'll chat ya up later!     
     

    
</post>
<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Sotoday went by pretty slow for me. Woke up at around 9:00 to do my hair, makeup, clothes, then I went to church to acolyte. Haha, I learned a new trick: "How to sleep with my eyes open." I did that while the guy was giving a sermon. Btw, his sermon was completely pointless, like, I didn't know where he was going with it. Anyway, after that I came home and sat on the couch and like passed out. I was soooo way beyond tired. Madison and I tried to go to sleep at like 12:30, but then we wanted popsicles, so we got those, and then we were wired. Like it just came out of nowhere. We threw beeny-babies at my door to try to get it shut, and the next morning my mom walked upstairs and was like, "What the hell? Why are here beeny-babies in the hall?" Haha, it was so funny. And then Madison wrestled with me because she wanted me to go get more popsicles right after I had just come back from downstairs because I got a cup of water. She kept tickling and pinching me with her feet until either:     A.) Shut the door    B.) Got popsicles    C.) Shut the door and got popsicles    it was a very eventful night because we kept laughing and stuff, but anyway.. what to post.      Oh! I had Otter (Michael) and Candace over today to swim with me and Mads. Much fun. Otter leaves for camp tomorrow, so sad. Almost all of Mads' other best friends are leaving for camp, while mine are staying in town!! Haha, in her face! But yeah.. We tried to get Otter to play spoons, its sooo funny how we play. I'll be sitting behind Otter, he will hit Candace on the head with a spoon, and then candace will be like, "1... 2... 3...[bam!]" And I would be the one to hit him on the head with a spoon so it would hurt. We alsogot into a water fight with the hose at first, and water balloons, and then we all jumped in the pool. It was so much fun. And then Madison had this horrible craving for corndogs, so my mom was going to the store to get some stuff and she got her corndogs. There was originally 24, there is now like 10.. all because of her.      So anyway, that was pretty much my day. Who knows, there might be more tonight. Madison is staying the night again for the 13th time in a row, and Candace might be staying the night too, but who knows. This is gonna be some party :P I'll chat ya up later!    
     

    
</post>
<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        So, I just got home from a movie.. and well, I'm excited. Papi S. and I held hands, cuddled, and shit. And at the very end we kissed, before we were about to leave. Made me happy since it was only my second real kiss.  Anyways, I have yet to break the news with Candace, I'm sooooo way excited I can't wait to tell her!! I think I'm going to call her right now.     Anyways, I think I'm going to go so I can call her. Otherwise I get mucho confused and I can't multi-task. Just doesn't work for somebody like me. So yeah. Chat ya up later.  
     

    
</post>
<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         So, I don't know what exactly I'm doing here, but my friend JJ got me interested in this whole site thingy. Anyways, I'm Caitlin, also known as Landian, Fishy, or Minow. Er, I'm a 14 year old girl who currently lives in Oklahoma, at least the last time I checked I did. I have 2 older brothers, Matt (20 years of age) and John (17 years of age), and most of the time I can't stand either of them! Well, I'm thinkin I'm going to post a picture on my next post because this computer won't let me, since it's stupid and a piece of crap!!! ANYWAYS! There is absolutely nothing to post in this thing right now. Nothing important has happened to me lately. Well actually, come to think of it, something has.               Ok, so like, one of my good 'ol friends Jake R. was at Utica Square when I went with Mads, and I hadn't seen him in FOREVER! No joke, almost 6 years, and I saw Murray, or.. yeah, something like that. I don't remember his name or how to spell it. Utica Square is officially the place to be on Thursdaynights. I'm going everytime now, at least when I can make it! It's so much fun, haha I got home andI had dirt in my hair from when Jaketackled me, and me and JJ were laying in thegrass. OOO! And I saw Papi, Pat, Patrick S.whatever you want to call him, there! But I didn't get to talk to him because, well... I don'tknow? And one more thing, I think all the Carver/Booker T. Washington people are warming up to me. They used to think I was a bitch because at Kelsey's party I was way WAY tired, like I could barely stand up, and I felt sick, and i was FREEZING! And at the Carver Prom, my stomach was killing me because of cramps, so I didn't want to dance or do anything, and when Eric kept forcing me to dance I got pissy. So to all the Carver/Booker T. Washington people, you know I'm not usually like that, I swear. You guys just caught me on bad nights.       Ok, so maybe I didn have alot to say. I'm just one of those unpredictable girls most of the time that will suddenly think of something to say, and say it! Muahahaha! &gt;=D Yes, I am evil.. evil fairy princess. Lolz, anyways... I'll chat ya up later!         
     

    
</post>
</Blog>