<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         var password; var pass1="YOURPWD";  password=prompt('PWDQUEST.,' '); if (password==pass1) alert('ANSWER); else { window.location="URL"; } //--&gt;  I got this code from Mad-html.com 
    
</post>
<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink     AINT SHE DA CUTEST TING YA EVER SAW?!?!?!!!!?!?!?!?!???  
    
</post>
<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    keep clicking on him he falls over! LOL  
    
</post>
<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink      Because you won't be able to play with them when their stiff! LOL   Also People you do wanna click on them! LOL  
    
</post>
<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Here's My Puppy I wanted to adopt one of each! LOL   urlLink    
    
</post>
<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink       Like my kitty?. Anyways! this girl Whitney has been giving me a hard time like......calling me swear words! and then wants to be friends again!  I think she just doesn't like HomeSchoolers or whatever!. What I don't get isthat so many people don't like HomeSchoolers? why!?! I mean it was the environment your raisedin not where you were tought ofhow you act?.   One HomeSchooler messes up and we all mess up I guess..........     It just bugz me!:'(      Anywayz.......  "If you don't wanna accept me for who I am! then don't I've got actual friends......if you think I'm a snot it's your opinion don't mess around with me if you don't like me sorry but that's it. It's not worth being someone's friend if their going to push you around!"      sorry! just having mood swings!        
    
</post>
<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      *A Christmas Wish*  Ellie Jo woke up at 7:00 A.M. She got dressed went to get her stationary and started writing to her pen-pal Mary Lynn. She writes:        Dear Mary Lynn;  How are you? It's a little too *hot* here!. Thank you for the birthday card you sent a few months ago! Sorry for not writing to you faster. You go to school right? I've told you that I'm home-schooled right? I really like home-schooling, but I wanna see what school's like, is it fun?. Oh, I can see Mr. Kerris coming. God Bless you and your family!    After she got in Mr. Kerris' car and they went on their way to his shop where she gives out a flyer with every cup of lemonade. She's right in front of his shop, so he gets more customers and so does she. "So, Mr. Kerris I thought that if I staple some flyers around with some BIG-BOLD! colors we could get more customers. It could say... every fifty dollars you spend you will receive a free cup of lemonade at Ellie Jo's lemonade stand 'where lemons are happy to serve you'!" How about that?" Mr. Kerris laughed and said, "I'll certainly think about it Ellie!". After they opened the shopthey started looking around his shop for some bright paper and markers. She had only turned ten a couple months ago so she couldn't make anything big and fancy, because she didn't have a computer at her library, and on top of that should wouldn't evenknow how to work one. So, she bought markers and coloredpaperand began to writeout a flyer with some pictures. Shemade a few different ones since she had about ten pieces of paper.She used the copy machine with color ink to print them out.Mr.Kerris was a very generous person so he always let her use it for free!.    At 12:00P.M. he put a, "Be back in an hour sign." that Ellie Jo made andgot ready to take her back home.Ellie Jo sat down tocount her money because shehad about double the customers thatday becauseit was aSaturday.She picked up her jar that she kept hid under a loose floor board on thedeck in front of the store so she could count all of it and saw she hadenough for thatblue dress in the store that she had wanted for church.She also had enough money to get both her and herDad ahot dog. It was herlucky day!She went to the clothes shop and boughtthe dress, then asked Mr. Kerris if she couldget two of his hot dogs.He got them for her and then they went on their way home.    She read the last few pagesof, Out of the Dust. It was about her fifth time reading it because she loved sad stories. She especially like this one for some reason?. Mr. Kerris dropped Ellie Jo off at home. She fed the horses, cleaned the chicken coop, fed the pigs,milked the cows,washed thethree dogs then went inside the creaky screen door. "Ellie Jo,is that you?"    "Yep! It's me Papa!" Then she ran and hugged him.    "Doall ur'e chores?"    "Yep!"    "Sell any lemonade?"    "Sold double than usual! and I don't mean double-double for a Saturday!!!"    "That's great! Buy anything?"    "Yep a hot dog for you, a hot dog for me! Aand a new church dress!"    "Good the other one was above ur'e knee, it's about time you gotta new one. Now did you spend all urge money or just todays?"    "Todays!"    "Good because you'll need it to save up fer them wanna lessons"    "Yep! Wait what?!? REALLY!!!! NEXT YEAR I CAN!!!! YAY!!!!"    "Even better this October so you can practice on Christmas songs"    "REALLY!! THANK YOU!!! but I don't think I have enough money for it" then she sighed.    "Well I'm gonna give you a months worth of wages because I got double what I spected. I got promoted, so you get half of my months wages that'll be enough for a year"    "Yes! I'm gonna go write to Mary Lynn."    "But you already-"    "Yes, yes I already wrote to her. I have to tellher though". So she curled up on her bed and wroteto her.Later she played with Dizzy her cat with the new toy Mary Lynn bought him. Then Ellie Jo changed out of her old dirty overallsand changed into her PJ's. Finally, before she went to bed she looked at her pictures she kept all the pictures they owned in her room. She looked through them then saw a picture of her mother the night before she died. As her eyes filled with tearsshe saw a picture of Billy Jr. when he was first born. Then one of her and her Dad with him, then she saw Billy's grave stone and she started to cry so she prayed beside her bed and went to sleep.      October 30th        Ellie Jo just finished practicing, Joy To The World, then she got a call from her Dad and he sounded rather excited! He said "I have someone very special for you to meet!" She'd never really get a call like that before?. Later that night he came home with a rather attractive women she had never seen before?. "Ellie Jo this is Alison. Alison this is Ellie Jo," her father said with a big grin.    "Nice to meet you! Your father hastold me so much about you!"    "Oh, he has?" Ellie Jo said, and then whispered to her father, "Papa, who is this women?" Then he chuckled and said "Why this is my very good friend! I've known her for a few months, but Iwanted it to be a big surprise to tell ya tonight and bring her over forsupper!"    "Why didn't you tell me?" then she ran upto her roomhe thought she was mad and he went to go in the room but it was locked .    "Ellie what's wrong?"    "Papa go away please!" she saidpolitely.    "Iwant you to tell me what'swrong now!"    "Go downstairs please!"    "Hve it your way. I'll just eat your piece of peach cobbler!" and he went down the steps and put down three bowls with mashed potatoes,corn,andchicken fried steak!    "Ohhh Bill, you didn't need to make this all for me!" she said thankfully.    "I didn't" he murmured.    "What?!? you mean Ella Jomade all of this!?"    "Ellie Jo"hesaid while doing a fake cough "Well it's the thought that counts I guess?". Then he heard Ellie Jo's door creek open then she came down the stairs with her hair tied in a white ribbon to match her white lace at the bottom of her light blue church dress.    "So that's whatcha was doin all that time makin ure-selfperty fer Miss Alison!"    "Miss Alison Papa?"    "Yes, I'm not married" she said.    "Oh".    They ate dinner while Alison and her father talked and complimented her cooking.Miss Alison couldn't believe such a girl ofher age could make such a wonderful meal.The months went by till Christmas and Alison kept coming more and more after and Ellie Jo finally started to like her!. "Ellie Jo!" Christmas is over in five minutes! Playus one more song please!"    "Sure,Miss Alison! What song?"Ellie Jo said.    "I want you to start calling me Alison okay! and ask your father I think he should pick this time!" Alison said.    Her Father picked to sing we wish you a Marry Christmas because her father had a surprise that was worth more than any kind of gift the best gift of all forAlison right beforeto be exact oneminute before Christmas he said "Alison you have one minute to answer my question and this is one that would change our lives forever, Will You Marry me?" then he showed ared velvet little box that looked like an ornament withher birthstone, a beautiful redruby!    "YES I WILL!" "So that's why you've been taking over time so muchsince summer---" then cutherself off and said so exited.    "OH MY GOSH SHE SAID YES! I'm gonna have a Mommy again!!!". They got marriedinJuly and in September Alison got pregnantand in June exactly at midnightit just turned to the 16th they had a baby boy and named it Billy Jr.    The End 
    
</post>
<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Mary Jane went to the movies with her best friend Halla to see The Lord of the Rings, Return of the King. This movie was based on her favorite book. They went early Monday morning because it was a snow day at their school. "That was better than any of the other Lord of the Rings movies" said Halla.  "Yeah" agreed Mary Jane, "So who's your favorite character?" Halla replied that her favorite character was Sam, to which Mary Jane replied, "My favorites are Merry and Pippin." Then the pair went to Pizza Palace where Halla ordered two pieces of pepperoni pizza, and Mary Jane ordered a glass of water and salad with some oil and vinegar dressing.  After lunch, they went to Halla's house because she had to be home before her big brother's graduation party started. Mary Jane left to go home and watch videos of the trip she took to Paris with her parents (this is her parent's favorite place in the world) for about an hour. After the videos, she ate leftovers and started to writeon her web journal. She typed in "Dear Diary, I just came back from Halla's house and a great movie, Lord of the Rings!" She continued writing about her desire for the warmth of Spring weather and her upcoming birthday, then signed off, "Mary Jane Williams". She finished her day by shopping online for some new clothes, but there wasn't anything she felt would give her the look of the famous movie star she desired. It was now time to wind down and she got into her favorite pink nightgown trimmed in yellow (these are her favorite colors). She removed the ring her great grandmother gave her and happily went to bed.  Seven years later, Mary Jane was finishing moving in her bookshelf, "FINALLY!" she said relieved that she was done moving in everything. Then the phone rang and it was Halla saying, "Emergency meeting at my place". "K?" she replied and they hung up. She rushed over to Halla's apartment building and asked, "Halla, what's the emergency?". She said, "Come inside" she said. They went inside and sat down, "I HAVE GREAT NEWS!" Halla said. "What? Tell me!" she begged, "Okay, here go's... I got a job!" "What?" "Yeah, I got a job with an animal rescue team!" "OH MY GOSH!!! you mean you finally found one here? That's gr--" "That's the problem" Halla interrupted "it's not here". "What? So how far away is it?" "Another problem is it's in Africa". "AFRICA?""Mhmm" she replied, "it doesn't mean it'll break our friendship will it?" Halla asked. "No, no never!" she answered. "So you're okay with this? Cause if you're not I can say no". "No, I'm okay with it" she said untruthfully "you sure?" She said "Yeah, I'm totally okay with this really!" "Okay?" Halla said suspiciously.  Mary Jane helped Halla pack because she had to be packed within three days, which was Mary Jane's Birthday. Mary Jane went home, turned on her computer, and started typing in her web journal, "DIARY! a horrible thing happened and I mean the worst thing in the world! Halla's moving away and I mean AWAY! to Africa and on the worst day EVER! I mean on Christmas..... I mean.... I would have been bummed, but not as bummed as on my Birthday! I felt so bad that I said that I was okay with it, OKAY WITH IT! Well.. I'm gonna shop online for a while, it usually helps." Then she signed off as she always does, "Mary Jane Williams". Halla moved away, but Mary Jane found two stylish friendship bracelets and the first charms she bought for them was a plane (because she's moving), a lion (for the lions in Africa), and finally a house, so she won't forget her home.  Two years went by and Halla got married to the guy that owned the animal shelter. He was eight years older than her which means Halla was 20 years old and he was 28 years old. Halla is having her first child at age 22. Mary Jane went to see Halla because Halla said she was pregnant. Mary Jane went over to Africa carrying two new charms for Halla. One charm was a bride and a groom to symbolize her marriage, and one charm was a baby for her first child. Mary Jane lived a long life. She had 15 kids and a huge mansion.  Halla stayed in Africa and helped conserve wildlife with her husband and had 3 kids and lived out her years in the African jungle, whileMary Jane devoted her life to caring for her own children, foster children and adopted children.  The End.    
    
</post>
<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
                                 Hey ya'll! CHECK OUT THIS PERFECT FOR ME RIGHT!?.             I AMTHE LOTR FREAK!                                                                         NO ONE WILL EVER LOVE LORD OF THE RINGS AS MUCH AS ME!!!!!!!                   
</post>
<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      * *   Okay Siblings are off the computer butthe little brother is threatningthat he'lldelete their game!!!!:-O.                                     FINALLY!!! THEY'VE LEFT:-D       K bye!      
    
</post>
<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
            I am on thephone with Sam and her little brother(5 years old) is going crazy on the computer like......p        asdsaodasofashfasfoasifoaisjfijsjfoaisfasijfo Brandoxxxx onadoiasoShannonasasdoasdiasBRANDON    RASFOASDIANRnbon        so I that's why I called her so she's trying to get him off! LOL. I'm hoping he'll get bored. Shannon (her lil' sis) is now IMing me. Well gotto go I guess, Britt         
    
</post>
<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Before I found my goggles yesterday I had to gotto swimming lessons without them! so my eyes kept watering! the other day at volleyball camp they were watering and this girl was like "what's wrong?!?" (she probably thought I was crying over my BF or something! (Like I'd have a boyfriend at my age! "PAH!") LOL) so I was like "Oh! I go swimming so they water all the time!" then I couldn't even underrstant what her friends were saying they were babbling so much and so fast! LOL. Also another girl asked me yesterday all that I can say is that it "musta felt stupid!."                
    
</post>
</Blog>