<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       As the days approch..Thinking about high school gets scarier.VERY freaky.What classes will i go to? Will i find my way around? What if i cant turn the dial thing on my locker? =P I dont know but im going to have to find out sooner or later.At least my next door neighbores go to the same high school as me so they can help me (Ones 1 year older then me and the other is 2) I hope im going to be in my friends classes.I will DIE without being in one class without at least one friend... And maybe a cute guy too =) Hehehe jk.I know i cant be stuffed in a locker because the teachers said we dont fit =P (We took a tour around the whole school before elementary school ended) But the lockers are big enough for all our school stuff.oOo And the main thing im wondering about... Does our school supply list and info come in the mail or what? Agth, at Elementary school they didnt give us too much information about this.. they think the kids can predict the furture or something.Walking past my elem. school to go to my high school will seem very very odd for me.Concidering my elem. school and high school are right next to eachother.. Infact, seperated only by 1 gate! =) Check out the gym for the high school.. P.E Will be fun.Same with drawma.My drawma teacher looks like Albert Instien or whatever =P White poofy hair.. freaky.The cafateria food is good.We tasted some when we took the tour.The schools big so i know im going to have trouble getting around =P In fact, the washrooms are clean too XD Very nice.The problem is the ppl... they all look freaky too me.VERY freaky.No one my size except one kid thats prob 2 cm smaller then me so called smurf.Anyways, im off now.Ill leave my thoughts like this...  
     
    
</post>
<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        If you didnt know, i have another life outside of my home =) That would be my school "life". Why life? Because my school and home are 2 diffrent lives for me.Too make it better - Im going to high school so i can be expecting tons of diffrent things to happen and... &gt;=)  ...Get this - My sister wont be going to high school for another 2 years so even better for me too have a diffrent life at school.  What I'll be writting on my school blog is -  Things that happen ONLY in school and have to do ONLY with school and what i think will happen to me IN school.You get the point - In school only.So, on my other blog ill write about home, friends, family, and just things that are OUTSIDE of school (Hehehe, sorry witht the caps lock there) So go to my other blog to see my school life?  To get to my blog that tells about my home life , go to my profile, go to the very bottem, and you will see a list of blogs.There will be two, one named school life and another blog named Life Starts Here.Click on life starts here.    
     
    
</post>
<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       YES! 3 More days till i get to sleep in my own bed and see Nicole,Rebecca and my mom Maria.Im really happy (My matress on my bed is very bouncy and comfy thank you very much) Im going to miss these last days.I have about $4 left so today and tomorrow im getting a slupree..And i think im going to get cookies today too.Hehehe =D I might go alone concidering that Denise probably wont come.What about Cristine? Ah, she would make me buy her something in order to come.Of course im going to miss being yelled at, but that'll happen at home to so everythings cool.We havent been to a chinese restaurant in a while so my mom promised well go when we get home =) Like a coming home present thing i guess.In my other blog i already wrote what im going to miss but im going to be SO happy when i see Rebecca and my mom.And OF COURSE my baby sis Nicole =D (Nicki) She can almost walk now and i miss her a ton.She likes soft popcorn, which is odd since i just found out.I cant forget about my friends either.I cant wait to see them and hang out with them! For 1 month not seeing them is long for me =D oOo And the water park right beside my house.ITS SO HOT! I cant wait to cool down.Well time to go for me.My times up on the PC. See ya! =)  
     

    
</post>
<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       I am i getting headachesbeacuse of how im trying not to be yelled at every day or is it normal? Well im thinking more then usual and trying things ive never done so i can say that im not sure about these headaches.What should i keep my mind focused on? Trying to be a goody goody and not get in trouble or trying to get home (Still at my cousins) and have some fun with my other friends? Im SO comfussed and i have no clue how to solve it.Since im having days were im friends with my cousins and days when we hate eachother, today is a friend day.Yesterday wasnt.. and probably tomorrow wont be =P I would concider it a pattern.But right now, i cant focus on that.I have to focus on thinking about what to focus on &gt;.  
     

    
</post>
<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I find it really odd that people go write about someone.Not just anyone someone, but me.This "person" goes on blogger, writes about me, and yet knows that i read her blogs.Does she seriosly TRY to hurt me that bad? Well if she writes about me why cant i write about her? Lets see: shes always yelling at me for no reason, when i try to do something nice she tells me not to do it,and she treats me like crap comepare to other people.YES, it does hurt me inside and she may or not know it, but it does.Cant she think about my postition for one time? I mean, right now i can be with my best friend playing for crying out loud, having the best time of my life. =( I did shed some tears today and i probobly will shed more, but why should i? she doesnt care anyway... 
     

    
</post>
<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       So get this, were all MELTING of heat as we are outside TRYING to play badmonton.Denise (My cousin that likes me one day and hates me the next =P) runs and gets the hose and wets me ALL down!!! =D It was halarious! My butt was all wet and same with my top.She wet cristine then i ran to the house and wet denise soooo bad =D We then stood in the sun for like 2 mins and we were dried off (Kind od weird since we were SO wet) We went back inside and we are just cooling off right now with the fan on.Wow, today has been a sure drag untill now! Its weird! Its like one day its icy cold and the next its boiling! (Im talking about my connection withmy cousin) Its odd but its getting better.Were going to draw after this (We are drawing fans! And we dont suck either =D) But ya, just wanted to inform you on the crazy water fight =D   
     

    
</post>
<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       My best friends are people that i talk to everyday and hang out with.Dont concider me a best friend if i hung out with you once ok? =S My best friends are and always will be:   Joanna   Regylin   Sherylin   Amy      YES, if your name isnt here your not my BEST friend but you still are my friend =P My second "fav" friends (VERY close to best, hehe) are:   Courtney   Sheri   Kassie   Lilia    If you are on that list, you ARE special =P Hehe.Well, whenever i mention my best friends, it will ALWAYS mean Joanna, Regylin, Sherylin and Amy.  
     

    
</post>
<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       1. Dont talk behind my back.If you have something to say about me, say it to my face instead    2. Dont tell me that i eat to much because i already know that (Even though im skinny)    3. Invite me places with you and ill like you &gt;=)    4. Dont act like your my friend 1 min then the next your ticked at me for no reason    5. Dont talk to me about how you go out with your "best friends" when i wasnt even invited    6. Im snobby when im grumpy =P Dont catch me at a bad mood (The mornings)    7. If im mad at you, dont act all nice to me to gain my friendship again (Hehe, my sister)    8. I hate bossy people so dont boss me around (Acceptence of my mom)    9. At school, dont follow me around because most likley ill be with my best friends    10. Dont tell me my underwear is showing because i dont care! =D    11. ONLY my friends can tell me when im having a bad hair day &gt;:)    12. If im doing homework, dont bug me    13. LAST BUT NOT LEAST (Applys to everyone): Do not EVER start yelling in my face.EVER unless your my mom! And 100% chance my mom isnt looking at this so dont EVER yell in my face        
     

    
</post>
<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Im at my cousins house and guess what, i was invited to my best friends birthday party -.- Great aint it? Im still at my cousins and i REALLY want to go... =(If iwas i was at home with Lilia or something cause i can still go to my friends houses.. Nothings wrong wiuth going.. well the only thing wrong is if Addas mom/dad will let me.I can ask my mom for money for the presents and i can take the bus! Wow.. Im so mad and sad right now.Denny is still as grumpy as she is with me even though i didnt do anything and shes anoyying me more then i anoy her.Yep.. things are just going great...    EDITED-  Me and Denny are STARTING to get along =P  
     

    
</post>
<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Ive been at my cousins house for now 2-3 weeks. (Ive even lost count of days) Ya, and i miss my mom =( Lucky her...In new york having fun with my sister nicole,my dad and my other sister Becky. (My OTHER sister is with me cristine) oOo How bad i want to be innew york =D My cousin Denny got me inspired to draw so i drew like 9 pics already.Its fun here but i miss my other friends! Its to far from here to go to their houses so i cant see them, only call them.At least i got msn here! In fact, my cousins have 3 computers, all have msn =) But im only aloud to use 2 of them WITH permission and they all are pass protected so eh, they dont like me on.Hehehe =D My cousins im staying with is Denise,Adreana,Radu and their parents.Im staying around another week so im hoping were going to have fun for the last few days! we played poker at 1:00 am last night and IT WAS SO COOL! We played with chips.Hehehe i hope we play tonight!  
     

    
</post>
<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Today was a good day so id say it went smooth. (OK not PERFECT) Anyways, i need a slurpie or im going to die &gt;. .  
     

    
</post>
<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Heehehe.Red faced freak XD Thats me.I went swimming AGAIN today and i got a surprise today.A burning red face.Heh, reder and reder it will get very soon.WILL THE BURNING EVER END! As one my friends quoted.I responded no.Today, one i got to the pool we had pushing fights and pushed eachother into the water.Luckly, the life guard didnt see half the times we did push one another =P  (You can get kicked out for pushing other people) After pushing and swimming, we had the first break.Me and 2 other friends went to get chips,cookies, and gum from superstore which is located 2 mins away from the pool.I got the best gum EVER. (Im a gum freak person.I can chew one pack of gum a day.I love gum.Love.Gum.You get it.) So when we came back it was swimming time again.This time we were trying to splash old people by jumping off the edge and landing right beside them in the water.We had fun trying to get the oldest lady in the world wet.She was a hard one man.She didnt wanna get her precious "Sunglasses" wet.After we got ppl wet, we bugged the life guards by asking them how much they get payed an hour. =) A few actually responded.It was break time again and we ATE.We were starving.After it was swimming time AGAIN.We had races and splashed and everything else you would do in the water.After we all decided it was time to go home.We were very tired from swimming so long.I walked home in a happy mood knowing that this is how my summer is suposed to be.Once again, the only bad thing was the tan &gt;.     Sunscreen. 
     

    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      SOOO sorry if my blog fonts are all mental.For some reason, they do that.Yes, it ticks me off.But how am i suposed to fix it? o.O Ill probably start a new blog if this keeps messing up.If i start a new blog ill write the adress on here and ill copy all my blogs from here to my new one XD Comfuzzling.Anyways.Ya.Dumb Blog. 
     

    
</post>
<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       WOW! Yesterday i went swimming and had the best day with Alana,Marya,Molly,Alana F,Megan,Danny,Lilia, and more. (Sorry if i forgot you!) So anyways, we had chicken fights and we jumped and splashed and i must say it was the BEST day ever! I met new people and had tons of fun.I got flipped over like 5 million times by people and it was SOO cool.The only bad thing was getting a tan on my face =P It got a little red but the redness is going away...its funny.I scrunch up my nose and i get a little tingly feeling in my eyebrow cause of the tan! Hehehe.As long as mt face doesnt peel  o_O  Very scary.I wanna get my back tanned.Im scared ill fall asleep in the sun XD My sister did.. Hahaha.Red back.Cute.Hey... how come some ppls backs and fronts go a nice golden tan but so go red =P For example, my moms front and back is so red that it can blind you.But my back and front goes tanned. (Except my face.My face needs sunscreen.) Well.I cant wait to go swimming tomorrow with my friends.I know its gonna be another fun day.Today i didnt get to go though cause of my mom.. (Wanted me to stay home for no reason) But im pretty sure she'll let me go tomorrow.If i dont, ill be very mad &gt;.</post></Blog>