<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink   
     

    
</post>
<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Well, I stitched all day on it, between the laundry and the children of course, and I got the little bugger done! I don't like how the cat turned out, though. He looks like he is one armed, but he's not. You just can hardly see the outline of his arm. I should have used a darker thread for the back stitching. But oh well. I still like it.    
     

    
</post>
<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    progress on the 2nd bib as of 7/20/04 urlLink   
     

    
</post>
<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Howdy Ho there Friends, Yes, I know I'm a little corney.But hey...some one has to be. I stitched the night away yesterday and now have a pic of my progress on the second bib. It's coming along great.   
</post>
<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Well, I finally got a pic posted to this blog, thanks to Amy...I don't know why I can't figure these things out myself. I'm puting in a pic of my 2nd one which is 1/3rd done. These are stitching up really fast for me, so long as I actually put in the time. My scanner doesn't seem to want to scan for some reason, so I'll have to take a pic of my progress and post it later. It's a really cute one though. I don't know yet which one I'll stitch for the last...but I'm anxious to get it started too. Well, happy stitching everyone....    
     

    
</post>
<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    My first finish for my Hancock class.  Let's do Lunch. urlLink   
     

    
</post>
<date>17,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       This is my first post...And I really don't know what to say....Ummmm.....I love to cross stitch. I have been doing it since I was around 18ish. I'm posting several pictures of my works. Today I finished a bib that I am making as a demo for a cross stitching class I am going to be teaching at Hancock Fabric which begin on September 4th. I started the 2nd one and I hope to finish it by tomorrow. After I finish the 3rd bib I will start on the three bookmarks needed for my 2nd class. So it's stitch stitch stitch for me. I have a stitch a long I want to get to, but it will have to wait until after I get the bookmarks done, at least. I'm very excited about this class. It is my first chance at teaching and I hope it goes well.    
     

    
</post>
<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well here are the pics of the finished bibs, towels and bookmarks.  I'm happy to have them done.  Now I have to start on the waste canvas projects and the bread cloths.  The waste canvas is going to be on bags...they'll be cute.  I've never done waste canvas...so wish me luck! 
     

    
</post>
</Blog>