<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      A while back a young friend on a message board was asking us older wiser heads for advice about his love life. I admit I got a bit carried away, but perhaps someday I'll write a book and this can be a chapter:   Hey Matt….    Honestly, I WOKE UP at 7:30 am thinking about your story. This is WAY longer than I intended it to be.   I was thinking that I really can’t understand how YOU feel, in part because I am a woman, and in part because I never had experienced the apparent intensity that you feel toward this girl. THEN I realized I had felt like that once, but didn’t have the guts to tell that person how I felt.  What I can share is a woman’s point of view.  What we have here, to boil it down, is a young man, infatuated with a slightly older woman who prefers to think of him as just a friend, but he wants more than that; what you want to know is can you do anything to change that.    Probably not much. At least there is nothing you can do to change her feelings overnight. One of the problems with the guys I dated who professed their “love” to me is that, when I said I felt only friendship for them, they weren’t interested enough to stick around and see if they could change that – except for two guys,Dave (not his real name)and Tim. I married Tim.  Dave and I were good friends in high school and after. Then one day I received a letter from him in which he hinted around that maybe his feelings were becoming stronger than that. When he came back from his tour (he was part of a touring acting company), he professed his love and actually said he wanted to marry me. (we were in our twenties, but the basic idea still applies.) I explained that I loved him, but my feelings were of the “brotherly” love type. I said that if he wanted to try and change that, we could do stuff together and see what developed. All successful romantic relationships have a strong element of friendship, so that was a good sign.  For two years we “dated”, andDave was great. He never made me feel pressured and we had a good time together. He even lost weight to be more physically attractive. There wasn’t anything he could have done differently or better.   At the end of two years, he was preparing to go off to a university that was a long ways away. He took me out to a very nice restaurant. When we got back to my apartment, I gave him a big hug and said, “Dave, I love you, but I don’t think my feelings are ever going to become the marrying kind. You have to know this before you go off to Wisconsin, so you can feel free to find someone there.” He was sad.  Two months later, he was engaged to someone he met at college. Now they are married and have four kids!    AfterDave I dated a few guys who pushed for the physical aspect of the relationship before I had a chance to get to know them. When I wasn’t ready to “make out” on the second or third date, they took it as rejection and “dumped” me.    Then Tim came along. We dated and when he brought me home, he gave me a little peck on the cheek and said good night and that was  it  every Saturday night for the first two months! He gave our relationship time to develop and solidify. By the time he was ready to give me those longer, slower type kisses, I didn’t feel as if I were kissing a stranger. Every date was like another piece of the puzzle that we fit carefully into place to see what the picture would be. He built our relationship slowly, patiently, and, over time, I grew to trust him and realize that this was the kind of man to whom I could entrust my future happiness and my future children.  About a year later, we married, and now we have been married for over eighteen years and - it is good! Our love, which started as a tender plant that blossomed and bore fruit, has turned into an oak tree with deep roots and strong limbs that shelter our children and don’t shake with every blast of wind that comes along.  But, I wax poetic. Teaching literature makes you subject to sappy metaphors. (get it? sappy? a tree? haha.)    Here Matt interjects, “Hey Piper, will you knock off the crap and get on with the lecture?”    Certainly.     To win ABC, follow steps A,B, and C.    Step A: Accept that you and she are friends and be content with that relationship for now. Don’t put any pressure on her; just be your charming self. If it is meant to be, it will happen without you forcing it. Actually, it’s a good thing that she is reacting to your admission of love like she does. If she was ready to rush into a girlfriend/boyfriend relationship with someone she knows only superficially, I would suspect she’s one of those needy girls looking for a man to lean on. They can be clingy and whiney and that gets old real fast! Her independence and clear-thinking indicates a person who is emotionally healthy, and that’s probably one of the things that you find attractive about her.    Step B: Don’t YOU be the needy/clingy/demanding one. Be someone who is attractive because you are relaxing and fun to be with. Girls like intelligence, self-confidence, and tender, protective strength. Build the relationship slowly and patiently. Show that you think of her and are considerate of her feelings and respectful of her opinions.    Step C: If you want a Queen, you have to make yourself into a King. Visualize the person you want to become. Have some clear-eyed, long-range goals for your future and be working towards them. Keep in mind that as you make choices now, you are building a foundation upon which the future structure of your life’s happiness will rest. (more visual metaphors)  How do you do this?   1. Choose a talent and commit to developing it. Whether you have ability in art, playing an   instrument, singing, playing tennis, martial arts, acting, or maybe just involve yourself in   community service, becoming good at it will   a. make you stand out from the crowd and get respect.   b. give you something with which to feel good about yourself, building self-   confidence.   c. make a nice tool with which to woo your beloved.   Most people have talents, but don’t develop them because it takes a long time and they   just don’t have the gumption to stick to it. That’s why people who are really good at   something stand out.   2. Be a class act.   a. Choose to do the right thing. This will not only ultimately create a sense of self   satisfaction, but will result in you having a good reputation, which will ultimately   make you more attractive to the right kind of woman.   b. Dress neatly. You can’t control the fact that you inherited grandpa’s big nose, or   your mom’s bad eyesight, but you can control looking like a lazy slouch or an   immature kid who thinks he has to look like a  gansta  to be cool, or dying your hair   bright orange, which only makes people think you are desperate to be noticed.   All that kind of stuff does is make you fit in with other questionable characters who   are doing the same thing. (How do you get attention? Refer back to 1.) How a   person dresses is only a surface appearance, but it is an indicator of what is going   on inside. First impressions are important.   c. Watch your language. I don’t wish to offend or be critical of others who use   profanity, so I’m not going to say any more about it here, but if you’re looking to   appear classy, it works against you.   d. Educate yourself. Read a lot. Go to college if possible, but it’s not necessary. Be   a well-rounded person who has opinions and can back them up with intelligent   reasoning. This requires a foundation of information.   e. Develop healthy habits. Avoid McDonald’s French fries. They make you break   out. Get exercise. You don’t have to look buff, but you don’t want to look like a   couch potato either. (On the other hand, buff is big points in the attracting girls   department.)    f. And I hardly need to say this; avoid drugs and alcohol. I have seen nothing but   pain and trouble from using this stuff to dull your senses.    3. Dump the baggage. Yeah, so your childhood wasn’t perfect. Deal with it.   Some people have great sob stories that they love to share with everyone. They use   a difficult childhood to excuse their own failings and bad habits. Initially, this   whining gains them sympathy and attention. But ultimately, others tire of being a   listening ear and a leaning post. These people end up sabotaging their   relationships and are seen as a potential risk. Or they will be picked up by a   person who sees them as a sure thing – as someone who will put up with anything   because they seem to need someone else so badly.   If you truly have serious problems, get help. Some people have their hands so   full of the baggage, they have no hands left to pick up and hold on to the happiness   right there in front of them.    Step D. I just thought of this. Somebody once told me that a good sign when looking at potential mates was to observe how a man treats his mother. They explained that, when a guy wants to marry you, you are their goal, and guys are very goal oriented. Even if they treat you like a queen during the dating phase of the relationship, you still don’t know how they will treat you after you – the goal - have been obtained, and they have moved on to their next goal. To get an indication of this, you observe the guy’s attitude toward the other woman with whom he has a close relationship – his mother, and whereas you don’t want the relationship to be abnormally close, you do want to see him treat her with respect and consideration, because that’s how he will be treating you, more or less, after you’ve been married a few years. (This is a generalization, of course. A friend of mine married a guy who disliked his mother, but there were extenuating circumstances. The marriage is 20 years old and good.) When I saw that Tim had a great relationship with his mom, that was a very good sign.   I said all that to say this: Work on your relationship with your mom. Your attitude toward woman in general is heavily influenced by the kind of feelings you have for your mother. Scary? You bet. But you actually have more power here than you think.   Teens tend to let their parents do all the work involved in having and maintaining a healthy parent/child relationship, and then resent it when things are less than perfect. Some parents don’t know how to do this. They haven’t had good role models in this area, so they are either too controlling, or too critical, or too hey, whatever. An adversarial tone builds up, and life with mom and/or dad becomes a series of battles and one-upmanship. Teens can work to diffuse this.   1. Always tell the truth so you build trust. It may take them a while to realize they can trust   you, but if you don’t betray that trust, you can point out to them that you have shown   reliability and honesty and have earned their confidence. My daughter used this on me and   it worked.   2. Be affectionate. Tell them you love them. Parents need your reassurance as much as you   need theirs.   3. Share when you have problems. And if they start giving you the big lecture, gently explain   that what you really need right now is someone to listen; you’ll let them know when you   want advice. Then make sure you actually ask them for advice once in a while. Even if   you don’t really want to hear it. There might be something in there you can agree with.  Learning to develop and maintain a healthy relationship will be a big advantage later on. Some people spend their whole lives trying to find happiness; some people create it.      Now, if you’ve actually read all this, you must be serious. Most of this stuff is long-term, and you want results tomorrow. Sorry. That’s life. But life can be GOOD!  Good luck, God bless, and I hope you find happiness.  
     

    
</post>
<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I have to take Sam to the doctor's today.  My ear canal is infected again.  I want to post photos, but can't figure out how to do it. I know it can be done....  "&gt; There. Let's see if this works.  
     

    
</post>
<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink Charlie's deer on Flickr - Photo Sharing!  Gotta try this button out. 
     

    
</post>
<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
      When I woke up this morning, the first thing I thought of was "This is the last day of my diet. Get through the day and tomorrow at this time, you can EAT!!!"  Tim and the kids and I are all on the fat burning soup diet. It's a seven day fierce effort to lose some weight before vacation, at which time I will gain it all back again.  The first three days involve a lot of fruits and vegetables and THE FAT BURNING SOUP. this is a concoction made of celery, green onions, green peppers, tomatoes, cabbage, and carrots in a Lipton chicken bullion base.  The soup is eaten everyday. According to the instructions, it takes more energy to pass this stuff through your body than you get from the calories it contains, so in essence, the more you eat, the more weight you lose. This would be great, except it tends to turn on you after two days. Or as Sam put it this morning: I'd rather eat my own vomit.  Anyway, it's now 8:30 pm and I think I'm going to make it. I have lost 7 or 8 pounds.  Was it worth it? Yeah. Also, according to the plan, the diet also does a detox of caffeine and sugar addiction from your system. If that were so, why is it the first thing I plan on eating tomorrow morning is the sweetest cereal I can find?   
     

    
</post>
<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       I have just about had it with Freewebs. I think they've gone on vacation and let their host website business disintegrate. So now I'm shopping for a new, more reliable web host. I don't know if this will work. A Blogging site isn't what I had in mind, but none of the other sites seem to fit my purposes like freewebs did, so I guess I just start in.    urlLink http://flickr.com/photos/88303_48600090482@N01_m.jpg  
     

    
</post>
<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Tim and his dad discussing Tim's new toy. 
     

    
</post>
<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Lucy on morning canine patrol.
     

    
</post>
<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    I thought I could send two photos at once, but I guess not.  Here's the August photo as previously mentioned. 
     

    
</post>
<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    I had seen (and photographed) what I think was the same tiger swallowtail butterfly in May.  And here he was again, looking somewhat the worse for wear, in August.  
     

    
</post>
<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    This summer has been an oasis of joy.  The cool temperatures have, I'm sure, been a part of that feeling of contentment, but mostly it's because I have been aware of how happy I am.   My husband and children, my home, the wonderful people in my life, my faith, the beauty of the countryside - I have never felt so completely content.  A feeling of joy makes my heart overflow with grateful appreciation to God for all the love that surrounds me.   I've been through some hard times in my life.  I guess that's why I recognise and appreciate the good times when they come.   
     

    
</post>
<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    I visited a local flea market the other day.  Mostly flea markets are full of just junk, but the fun is that among the trash, you find little treasures.  I found a turquoise colored glass bud vase that looks like a jewel in my kitchen window.  I found a litttle brass nome.  And I found bunnies.  But I had to be content with taking them home in a photo. 
     

    
</post>
<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
         urlLink          urlLink lovedog06      Originally uploaded by  urlLink tamaki .  
</post>
<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      To Emily and Samuel from your Mother  The Introduction to My Journal for You April 9, 1990       When I was eight-years-old, my mother died of cancer.      The rest of my life I kept looking for a message from her.  I thought that maybe, on some milestone day of my life, someone would come to me and say, "When your mother realized she was going to die, and wouldn't be here to see this occasion, she wrote a letter to be given to you when the time came."  Then they would hand me a letter that would contain a precious message from the mother I missed so deeply, whom I barely knew and to whom I never said good-bye.      Every birthday I wondered about it - At my high school graduation, at my college graduation, on my wedding day...  Finally I confided my dream to my older sister, Jan.       She told me our mother didn't leave any letters.  She said Mother was so intent on having a positive attitude and "beating this thing", she never admitted to herself she was dying until she was too sick and in too much pain to think of such a thing and act on it.      Now I wonder what it would have been like to know my mother as an adult.  I have asked people who knew her to share their memories.  I have pictures, but don't remember the sound of her voice.  Sometimes your Aunt Jan tells me I just did something or said something just like mother would have said it.  It makes me happy and sad at the same time because then I feel the void her going left in my life.      So anyway, I'm saying all of this to explain why I'm writing this book, letter style, to you, my children.  It will contain family stories, advice, and explanations of why we did things certain ways. This book will allow me to communicate to you all I want to tell you someday just in case something happens to me before you are old enough to understand and remember.  AND if I don't die, well... great!  I will write down some things that I might forget or just never get around to telling you.  It will give me a chance to let you know me.      It's hard to imagine "years from now".  Emily, you are only two; affectionate, rebellious, a lover of music and dancing, artistic with your crayons, and full of energy.  Even now you are trying to turn the page while I am trying to write.  You are squealing, making faces, and waiting impatiently for Daddy to take the oatmeal cookies out of the oven.      Samuel, you are only two months old, but you smile and  talk  when anyone pays attention to you.  Emily is so exuberant in her affection to her "Baby Bother", she makes you nervous.  You look worried when she is right in your face, leaning on your stomach and kissing all over you.  Right now you are in your swing and waking up from your nap.  No doubt you are making plans to keep mother up late tonight.  Or maybe you are wondering when mother is coming with the chow.  Well, she's coming right now! 
     

    
</post>
<date>08,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    We camped (or perhaps I should say trailered) in the Porcupine Mountains in the UP this summer.  This is Overlooked Falls, a small but beautiful little waterfall.  I love to visit waterfalls, but the kids find them boring.  
     

    
</post>
<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Lake Superior is my favorite of the great lakes, although Lake Michigan is a close second.  It is cold and crystal clear, big, strong, dramatic, and sparkling turquoise BLUE.  It was there I learned to enjoy snorkling in order to be able to get a good look at the beautiful rounded rocks beneathe it's surface.  Swimming in July and August is cold, but not impossible. 
     

    
</post>
<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Cally only feigns sleep.  Let that dog get six inches closer...  closer...  just a little closer....   Ka POW!
     

    
</post>
<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Cally loves surveying her domain from the safe felling of the trailer. 
     

    
</post>
<date>05,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      We're back from vacation.  Tim and I both have a sense of time passing and things changing.   Next summer will be our last with both children "ungraduated".   They still argue and fight and play together and insult each other, but it's less irritating when you imagine yourself a few years into the future traveling in a quiet car, just you and your husband, your children somewhere else.   We figure vacations are going to get a lot more expensive because we're going to have to come up with really great trips to make them want to come with us when they don't have to.  We went to Cozumel in January and it was great!  If we could dig up the money to do that again, they would definitely want to come.  But we will also be trying to pay for Emily's college education.  Expensive vacations might be out of the question.  We are thinking about Arizona - Grand Canyon - Tim's Aunt and Uncle live out that way and would like us to visit.   Then there's a fishing resort an older couple told us about north of Thunder Bay (top side of Lake Superior) on Whitefish Lake.  They said the fishing's great there.  This would be a draw for Sam, but I don't know if Emily would come.  Meanwhile, time passes.  
     

    
</post>
</Blog>