<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        I'm back!! Yes, I love it here lol. I want to say thanks to everyone at Fanbolt for welcoming me! Britney, Chloe, Joy, Malfoy, Kristen, Rob, Caroline, Alexa, Tamara and Anji! Thanks, guys!!          I really didn't say a ton about me before, but that's because I'm not too complicated. Nothing like ogres or onions(sorry for the Shrek reference)!! I'm like a little kid deep down and I'm immature when I want to be. My fave movie is really serious but I also live for Pirates of the Caribbean, Anchorman, Shrek and The Lion King. My youngest sib is a baby, after all.          Great blogging again...          Today, I've slept until 9 a.m., watched my tape of the ULTIMATE Disney Channel movie  Pixel Perfect  and then I did some aerobics before getting online. I love just hanging out during the summer. I'll be a junior next year... which'll stink. Senior year I think you do less work... that's what my friend Autumn said, anyway.           Don't you think that's a pretty name? Autumn. I wish I was named something that cool. Summer, Winter, Autumn... not spring. That's an oddname (no offense if that's your first name!!!) It's a nice last name, though. Melanie Spring... that could work. Nope, I'm waiting for Melanie Brody, Melanie Ullman, Melanie McCartney... ooh, that last one is nice! I'd be Jesse's wife, not Paul's. LOL.          Thanks for listening!! Today I'm buying my Maria Mena CD!! WHOO HOO!!   
     

    
</post>
<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Hey everyone, I just created my very own blog!! Well, I guess the best way to start is by saying something about me... my name is Melanie, and I will be 16 in 2 1/2weeks. I live inNew Hampshire with my mom, stepdad, 2 sisters, my kittenMiraand 1 half-brother. My dad lives in New York and we don't visit him unless it's Hanukkah. My favorite singer is Maria Mena, who sings "You're the Only One". I also like Michelle Branch.Maria's CD comes out Tuesday, so I'm psyched. My favorite movie is  Where the Heart Is . My favorite actress is Amber Tamblyn, and my favorite show is  Joan of Arcadia . Myfavorite place in the world is my room, where I writesong lyrics andplay my guitar.I can't wait toblog some more, but I have to go.           
     

    
</post>
</Blog>