<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well I've been thinking for the past couple of dayz of things that I could write about. You know, those things that are important and I couldn't think of a thing...until tonight. My friend "Billy Bob" ( I love using that name.) and I were talkin' and stopped talking for a couple of dayz. Anywayz after I found out the reason I felt totally stupid. Then I realized that I am so asorbed in myself that I should be the center of everybody's universe. OK so I didn't think that but I did that I was one of the most important people in my family and friends lives and that if something happened to me than everyone should come running. Anywayz that idea is dead. Even though the idea is dead I'm still gonna talk about me quite a lot because like my friend Lacy always says, " If you don't talk about yourself then nobody else will."  My church had VBS this week (July 26-30). I taught 3-4 year olds, 5-6 years olds, and finally 5-6 grade. I loved teachin' the younger ones because I was teachin' them something that they didn't already know. Little kids are so innocent and full of love that everytime I stop to really watch them, they amaze me. So throughout this week I have written two poems. One is extremely personal so I won't share that but the second I think everybody should hear. So here it goes:  Reality
</post>
<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well I've been thinking of a post that would mean something and after recent events in my life which well remain personal, I have chosen the topic of men and women. Now I'm not talking about physical differences because I'm not a perv., I'm talking about all the other stuff.  So I'm gonna start with the easiest sex, which would be the male (men). First off men are simple. They want their food and their sports. Now I understand that many guys don't like sports but yet they love something else. Take my friend Derek, he likes the sax. So Derek wants he's food and he's sax. Now in the relationship part of their lives guys are one of two things, pathological liars or a sweetheart. The liars are out numbering the sweetheart 4-1 and also if they are a sweetheart the first thing you do is  make sure they aren't gay!!  Now I have no problem with gay guys, I have many gay friends but they sure can't be a "special" guy for ya. The liars are the guys that say they will do something and they never do. ex. call, e-mail, talk, and the big one is commit. Which brings me to my next point, guys are afraid of commitment. This is the truth the facts come straight from my personal experience.  Now on to the ladies!! What can I say about the ladies?? I could say that all women are perfect but that would be a lie. Where guys want two things, women just want one...unconditional love. Now is that so much to ask for?? I think not. Now there are some women that are pathological liars but not many, and if they are then the only reason is because men have hurt them sooo badly that they have harden their hearts. And another thing is that women aren't afraid of commitment!!!  Well I do believe that I have finished my second post, so enjoy!!! 
      
</post>
<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well this blog so gonna have tons of mistakes. Well not mistakes but things that when I'm older and look back on will embarrass me. I'm on the verge of something new in my life. I'm about to embark on a new life...it's called college. I'm ready for it, I've been waiting my whole life to get out where nobody knows me and I can start over. The only thing I will miss will be my neice Sheila Jo. She is the light of my life and can't imagine not being around her. She is with me every day and now I will be four whole hours away from her. :( But I understand that I must get away if I want to move on to the next step of life.   Well this blog is titled "simply me" so I guess I must tell a little about myself. I'm the youngest of three girls. My life has been simple. I live in a small town, probably the smallest town in Arkansas. I go to school with people who's main purpose inlife is to judge people. My greatest and most cherished friend moved away leaving me all alone. She moved all the way to Georgia. I guess my greatestwant out of life is to be in love. The problem with that is that when I'm finally in love I "push" that person away. I know I do it whenever I do it but I can't stop. My greatest insecurity in life is that I won't live up to what people expect me to be.I'm going to college to be a doctor but I would like to join the Peace Corps and after doing that for a couple of years settle down and be a housewife. Family is more important to me than all the money in the world. Well I'll end this post and do it again tomorrow. 
      
</post>
</Blog>