<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Ok, I weigh a lot. I had lost 50 some pounds a year ago with Weight Watchers, I was very pleased with my experience. I don't know what happened, but I've gained it all back. I need to get over this and move along. I need to stop feeling sorry for myself. I just need to bet back on that WW horse and say, " Getty up!"   Ok, I have issues. I don't think a person gets to 310 without some. I tell you, I was shocked when I got on my home scale and it went past 300. I thought maybe 290, or 285, NOT 310!!! I'm right back at square one. No wait a minute, I have learned something, and it was a shock. Maybe that was my "a ha" moment I keep reading about.   One thing I do know, it seems it takes more than being sick of being fat. For I am sick sick sick of it.   I've been embarrassed, too. That hasn't motivated me, in fact that just makes me want to eat all the more !!     Well, I'm going to keep on keeping on for now    amie    
     

    
</post>
<date>18,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Well, hello out there, all you bloggers.     I'm very new to this, a little nervous, but here I go.     I'm 42, married with two teen sons. I am an RN, I work at a geriatric psych acute care facility, I'm the day charge nurse, meaning, I just happened to be the bossiest when the job opened.     The focus of this blog is to document my journey to fitness. I've struggled all my life with low self esteem and a high weight. I've been up and down the scale, motivated, unmotivated, frustrated, left out, made fun of, heart broke, and penniless. Well, not penniless, I got carried away.    I will post my weight every week.    I will post my thoughts here, for allto see.    I will faithfullygo to my Weight Watcher meetings every Sat AM.     I will walk at least 5 times a week.     I willwrite down everything I put in my mouth, maybe not here.     I will do my best to support you, my blog friends.     Today, my weight is 310. I walked 2 miles. I stayed on program.     Yours truly, Rikgril            
     

    
</post>
</Blog>