<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I cruised down the New England roads trying to light up the road through my purple rimmed plastic eye glasses. Surely I need a new prescription? It's dark out and what I can see through the headlights are trees arching over the winding road. When cars whip around the curves from the other direction (those damn locals), I feel blinded and impotent, positive I'm going to drive right into the next goat, but miraculously my tires and I stick to the black top and make our way into the happening part of town.   I cruise right by that part of town outinto some roads. These roads are less wild country and more tame suburb, so I feelmore comfortable snaking along trying to follow my map. Eventually the street signemerges and then there's a small road on a barely visible corner. That was the trick Teddy had told me about to find their house. The other useful tip was that the address and the number on the mailbox outside the house were distinct. I turned my car off andlookedwarily at the 4 inch Gucci pumps I'd brought along to wear. I pushed them aside, donned flat black flip flops and was just finishingreapplying my lipstick when I saw Teddy ambling down the front walk.   "Hi!" I said, immediatelyglad I'd opted for flip flops.Teddywas wearing ablue polo shirt and khaki shorts (the same blue polo shirt he'd been wearing the last two times I'd seen him? Hmm.I wonder.) Teddy and I hugged.   "Hey, good to see you. Did you see any cabs? We thought we saw two pairs ofhead lights." I immediately felt self-conscious for taking time to exit my car, and followed him toward the house.   "Oh, Teddy friend!" A young man walked out of the house and exclaimed when catching sight of me.   "Lizzy, this is Conan." The man did have a bit of a resemblance to the talk show host, but finer featured and not as convincing of a caricature.   "This is going to be overwhelming, so don't worry if you don't remember people's names -- I don't even know them all." Teddy and I climbed a flight of stairs into a kitchen. There was a disconnect between the lovingly fashioned country oceanside decor and the group of rowdy adults drinking beer from plastic red and blue cups.   "Do you need a drink?" I merely nodded. Another nameless man handed us three clean cups and Teddy commandeered a third to take a shot of jagermeister.   We threw back our liquor and then scrambled as the crowd descended down the stairs and into the first massive van cab. The second cab rolled up alongside and I climbed in. Teddy came and sat beside me. I was pretty sure I smelled puke, but kept that thought to myself.   We were waiting in line to enter into the bar. It was Nantucket and it was a typical island dive bar, but on the fourth of July, it might as well have been members only access. I felt small, and couldn't stop standing on my tip toes. Regardless, I was not really clearing Teddy's shoulder.   We went into the bar toward the back and Teddy bought us drinks. He said that's where the crowd usually went to gather. Because no one came back there, we rejoined them toward the front of the bar. We had jello shots. They were very tasty. Everyone picked red.   We were all standing around. Teddy had given me over to Mark to entertain while he used the restroom.  "So, how manysingle guys are there? There's me." I pricked up my ear attentively, but didn't register whether Teddy meant his girlfriend wasn't around or whether she was no longer his girlfriend. While they determined the ratio of couples and single folks, I unzipped my terry cloth hooded sweatshirt and tied it around my waist.  Teddy turned back toward me and we started talking about the halcyon days of undergrad. And in the midst of school talk, we discussed how we first met.  I knew a guy, Dan, who was interested in me. He called me and would ask what I was doing. Dan had a job at one of the local bars. It was a very vanilla bar in every sense of the word, and because it catered mostly to jocks and doe-eyed vapid chick sophomores, I usually steered clear. However, via Dan, I had free drinks and reserved status at the bar. Toward the end of senior year, all I wanted to do was be at a bar, so even if Dan's bar wasn't my first choice, I'd show up.  One evening two of Dan's frat brothers showed up. This guy, Stu Smith and a good-looking blond guy I'd noticed, but never met. Teddy.            
     
    
</post>
<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       This weekend I met up with a few friends at this very hip bar in the southern part of the city for some drinks for a birthday. I called my friend Evan earlier that day to ask him to join in the festivities. He called me back around 9:30 or so, already sloshed and starting to slur.  "Sure Lizzy, is it ok if I bring some people?" He sounded super suspicious, so I queried whether he'd be bringing ten people. he assured me that wasn't the case, but by his tone I could tell something was up.  I'd been at the bar drinking citrus sours, a specialty, when Evan walked in, disheveled, unshaven and sporting some new extra pounds and accompanied by Eric, also unshaven and uber casual. Their apparel was out of sync with their surroundings, but no one was pounding down the doors of this trendy establishment. Hot summer weather and no big lines out the back. Eric came over and kissed me and I felt his gritty cheek.  "You look really good, Lizzy."   "Watch out, Eric has your cell phone number now." Evan grinned his cheshire cat smile and smirked in a really sleazy way.  "But you have a girlfriend." I said definitively to Eric.  "Not anymore. Maybe you and I can go on a date." Eric grinned and leered all at once.  "No girlfriend, huh? It's a whole new ballgame." I said, unsure of whether I'd wanted him to say he's single again.   
     
    
</post>
</Blog>