<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       This is going to be my last post before I leave for vacation!  Kentucky, here I come! ^^  I've spent almost all day today packing and cleaning up the house XD  I got my shorts, t-shirts, tanktops, shorts, underwear/bra's, and socks packed.  I need to still pack pants and the remainder of the clothes I need, and the stuff to keep me entertained on the 2 day car ride there ^_^  I've got 4 books (Dude, Where's My Country? ~Micheal Moore~, Stupid White Men ~Micheal Moore~, Uncle Tom's Cabin ~Harriet Beech Stow~, and Oliver Twist ~Charles Dickens~), Gameboy Advance, Notebook (I plan to write almost constantly!! I love to write and going on a long trip is perfect for it ^_^),  Camera (taking tons and tons of photos!!)  But, I know this was a short post, but when I get back from Kentucky, the posts are gonna be looooong!!!  XD   
     

    
</post>
<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        No words can express my utter exaughstion. All day yesterday, we scrubbed the house from wall to wall, head to toe, one end to the other. The appraiser  came today, so all yesterday was stressful. We scrubbed the walls, the floors, vacuumed all the carpets and furniture, bleached litterboxes and the ferret cage, dusted everything, washed like 2-3 loads of dishes, 7-8 loads of laundry, cleaned all the bedrooms, and a whole lot more. I slept like a freakin' rock. It was so exaughsting. Then today the apprasier came (FINALLY). It took him like...2 mins to appraise the house -.- AND THEN we found out that we can go to Kentucky! YAAAY!!! I can't wait! I think the funnest part of the entire trip is the way down there ^_^ I love driving through all the states looking at my surroundings and scribbling interesting things in my journal (Yes, I'm a writing sorta person). I can't wait!! Eeeee! lol ^_^ Gotta run!   
     

    
</post>
<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I am so happy!!!! I told my mother I was Bisexual ^_^ I did it casually XD Like I was saying previously, my best friend Katie doesn't like gays or lesbians or bi's, so I brought that up first, and I said, "I don't see why Katie doesn't like lesbians or gays! I would date a chick, so I guess I'm Bi or something, and what if I moved in with Katie when I turn 18, and brought home my girlfriend!? What would she do then?!"And my mom was like, "Yeah, I don't see why she'd be so upset!" I feel sooo much better now that she knows! It's like a huge weight off my shoulders! Now I have to tell 3 people. My father (gonna have to tell him sloooowly, cause I don't know how he'd react), my best friend Katie, and my elder sister, Sam ^_^ I know Sam would support me in any decision I make, cause she wuvs me!! XD So does my father, so if I tell him slow and don't just tell him at breakfast, "Hey Dad! I'm Bi!" then he'll get used to the idea. Katie is the one I'm worried about. I love her like a sister, and I'm afraid that she's gonna lose it, but I guess I don't have a choice. I'd rather tell her now, right before I go to Kentucky, so she has 2 weeks to think about it while I'm gone, and then when I get back, maybe her mind will have changed about it. I guess if I'm patient and wait, good things will come ^_^ But then again, there's always the chance that nothing will have changed and she'll still not like gays/lesbians/bi's. But I know if she's truly my friend, then she'll accept me sooner or later, and if not, then I move on and find friends who  can  accept me for who I am. I would just rather her adapt, cause I want her to be my friend :P Ah well, alas, if life deals you a crappy hand, throw the cards away and get a beer! XD   
     

    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I've had a stressful day &gt;. still  angry about it. I know it sounds horrible vain and stupid, but I can't help it. I hate that girl so much and then to find out my best friend hangs out with her? I was like, O.O I guess it does sound selfish and stuff, but I don't want my best friend hanging out with her! I guess I'm afraid that if she spends too much time around her, then she'll change to be more like my enemy -.- I guess that's an irrational fear, but it's true. I guess I should just let it go, but I can't &gt;.      
     

    
</post>
<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I'm debating on a huge decision, and it's tearing me apart. I think I might be Bisexual and I don't know if I should tell my parents. They love me and would probably be comfortable with it, but I can never be sure. I don't want to upset them, butI don't want to hide it forever. I hate hiding it, like it's some horrible secret, when really, it's not! It's a wonderful thing and I embrace it fully, but being only 13, I assume my parents would just say, "You're too young to know what you are!". I love them and they love me but I still don't know how to break it to them. I don't know if they'd be happy, disappointed, or be like, "Oh...ok! Whatever makes you happy!" I think they would probably say whatever makes me happy, but there's always that slim chance that they'll be disappointed in me. I love them sooo much and I don't want to hurt them. All my friends know, and they don't care, but with my parents, it's different...&gt;. .  
     

    
</post>
<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I'm watching the Sci-Fi documentary, "The Buried Secret of M.Night Shamylan." It started out as a "normal documentary" and ended up being more like the Blair Witch or rather one of M. Night's movies!They've got a specific set of approved questions to ask, certain places to be, things to say, and they CANNOT AT ANY TIME make eye contact with M. Night.Everything was so strict, you'd think the Sci-Fi crew was interviewing the president! Then, later on, M. Night and the crew go out and eat some dinner, go to a bar, etc. and all of a sudden M.Night is this happy, perky, social butterfly talking and letting people take his photos. He went from sheltered recluse, to Mr. Popular. It was like he was a different person! Even Johnny Depp (oooo teeheehee *-drooling-*) was involved. He wanted to play a part in the movie, "Signs", but they were going to make him sign a contract saying that he couldn't say a word of anything that went on there. That was a little freaky, but THEN he had all these quotes and stuff, and it all got really weird, so he said Forget it, and Mel Gibson (hahahahaha he's a dope XD) took the part instead. I was like, "Woah, even Johnny Depp got involved with this!" But I was glad he didn't take the "Signs" part cause I thought that movie sorta sucked....it was ok though, not the greatest. Supposedly, M.Night "died" from drowning. A deer fell through the ice in a river, and M. Night walked out to save it, fell through the ice, and "drowned". His mother then cradled him in her arms and walked into the river, drowning herself as well, as Sci-Fi put it, "Bringing him to his maker in person". So supposedly, M. Night isn't even alive! I think that's a crock, but I don't deny he might have "connections" with spirits or ghosts as some people describe them. I  do  believe in spirits and such, and it  is  possible he might have some connections with them. I guess you never know! ^_^        
     

    
</post>
<date>19,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        This is my first blog post, so bear with me. I thought it would be a neat idea to start a blog, cause I'm always losing my journals!  I figured it wasn't exactly easy to lose a website :P Anyways, I'll probably be posting in this one a lot.      Just yesterday, my family and I decided to storm chase (yeah, I know, we're crazy). But we always enjoy it. This one was a bit more..."intense". We started driving along behind the squall line to stay outta the real thick stuff. Well, we pulled over to watch the storm going on, and all of a sudden, we start seeing tornado tails dropping from the clouds!!! We started driving again (yeah, like I said, we're crazy, but we wanted to see more of the storm). So we continued driving along, and all of a sudden, the rain started real thick, and we couldn't see anything so we pulled over. That's when things got REEEALLY bad. We saw the wind change direction and then we felt the wind slam against the car. WE GOT CAUGHT INPART OF A TORNADO!!! It was amazing! Everything seemed to go in slow motion. My heart was beating fast, but felt slow.Everything was white because the hail (ranging fromgolfball size, to baseball size, to 3 baseballs stuck together size), and andrain was so thick. My sister reached over and grabbed my arm and said, "Risa...are we still on the ground?" I leaned up and nodded saying, "I can still see the road." Then Dad sped down the road away from the tornado and we started driving down a different road. Then I looked out my window and pointed, saying, "Mom...mom..MOM!"cause she wasn't listening. She said, "what?!" I was like, "LOOK!" and we saw another tornado coming down. Mom shouted, "DRIVE!" We drove and drove through the pounding rain and hail until we reached Thompson, where my grandmother lives. We took shelter there until we were sure it was safe to return to home. It was sooo surreal that moment we were caught at the edge of the tornado. It was like something from a movie that you'd never think could happen in real life. It was AWESOME! ^_^  
     

    
</post>
<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I've returned from Kentucky and I'm so happy to be home!!  I love Kentucky, and love  being  in Kentucky, but I missed all my cats and my dog and snake and ferrets!  If I could bring them with me to Kentucky, it'd be PERFECT but I don't think they'd like a two day car ride!  I barely survived it (had my younger sister in the car....she can be rather pest-like sometimes).  I'm not going to attempt to tell everything that went on in Kentucky in here yet, but as soon as I find my Kentucky Journal, I'll put it on here ^_^  
     

    
</post>
</Blog>