<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
              What I've been fightingfor since December 2002 is suddenly gone. What my life was revolving around for the last year and a half is no longer there. The question that invades my mind half of my waking hours and most of my dreams is:     Where do I go from here?      What do I do now? How do I continue my life? On minute I think I'm starting to move on. Then next thing I know I wake up from a dream that was all about him and it leaves me depressed once again. AmI going nuts?  Idle hours definitely have been doing me no good. Butit's not possible to be busy 24/7. I think a lot about what he's doing. Who he's hanging outwith. Does he think about me.  I'm so pathetic :(  But where do I go from here? 
     
    
</post>
<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I wrote him a letter today. Said all the things I didn't say, told him I was going to be fine, told him to take care of himself, thanked him, apologized, and said a final goodbye.   I needed it for closure. Somehow when we broke up it was so abrupt. I was crying so I didn't say all the things I wanted to. It was too cold an end to such a warm relationship. I'm glad I did it. I feel better now. Now I know the meaning of 'when you love someone you have to set them free.' - Cheesy but true.    Attachment and Detachment,    Hello and Good-bye,    the cycle of my life.    Tell me... How often must I die?     - Virginia Lichauco De Leon     Time to move on.    
     
    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Me and Sweet Pia. Happy Birthday Girl. I love you. urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      DAY 1 was the LET IT ALL OUT stage.  DAY 2 was the I'M FINE, I CAN ACTUALLY DO THIS stage (or maybe aka denial stage)   Now it's day 3, and I'm at the QUESTIONING stage. Starting to question everything about him, about our relationship, and what the whole thing meant.   How serious was he anyway?Was he ever?  If I couldn't travel there as often as I did, would he have taken charge? Would we have lasted this long?  How long ago did he know it wasn't going to work?  Is he relieved now?  Is he sad.  Does he know how muchhe meant to me?  Does he know how much I gave up.  Should I have fought for it harder?  Should I have ended it sooner.   So many questions which might go forever unanswered. One minute I'm regretting the situation. The next minute I'm sighing with relief. One minute I'm questioning if he ever really took me seriously. The next minute I'm reminiscing all the ways he showed me his love.   I worry about him. Until now. (eeww, how sickeningly sweet and martyr-ish, I know)  But I do. Even though he's probably being a typical guy and is out partying every night and celebrating his bachelorhood. I still worry. So sue me. I worry that deep down inside he may not be as happy as he looks. I worry that he's lonely. I worry that he might drink and drive. I worry that he might meet a girl who won't treat him well.   I worry that he might meet a girl who  will  treat him well.   One minute selfless, the next minute selfish.   It's a phase.   I am again thankful for my friends who keep me strong and preoccupied and optimistic. You guys rock. My family knows as well now, although I act more casual about it to them. I guess if I allow myself to break down in front of them, I know they'll worry too much, and I know I'll be more emotional, and I know they'll be too affected. Anyway, I know they're there for me.   It's his sister's birthday tomorrow. Pia. She's the sweetest thing since strawberry jam. She's turning 14. "I'm a teenager"...she says. And "I love Anna."   She always tells me, "Anna's soooo special. And sooooo sweet."   I'm going to see her again. I know it. Whatever the circumstance.   Happy Birthday Sweet Pia. Take care of your Kuya. Take care of your family.   I can't even take care of a hamster. Friedrich's dead.  
     
    
</post>
<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I think he's dying. He hasn't been eating, he sleeps all day and all night. When I pick him up he doesn't even try to run. I think he may have broken a leg during his great escape because he isn't walking straight.    So today Friedrich and I stayed in my room all day, in bed for the most part. It's been a really long day, and all we seem to want to do is curl up in a corner. It would be nice to think that Friedrich was just feeling my pain and empathizing. That’s what pets should do for their masters right?    Unfortunately, in this case…I think he’s simply in pain himself. At least the two of us are finally sticking together. 
     
    
</post>
<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      So that's the way the cookie crumbles. One day you think you think you've found him. The next day, he tells you you haven't.    A year and a half. Not time wasted, but somehow time lost.    I don't regret going into this relationship back in December of 2002. I learned a lot about myself:    I learned that I am capable of loving far beyond what I expected.   I learned how it feels to be that much loved back.  I learned I can be strong when the need arises.  I learned that life will always throw something at me to test my strength.  I learned that life will also give me a helping hand when I am weak.  I learned to love the people he loved.  I learned that the people I loved, came to love him.  I learned how to cook.  I learned that just because I 'felt' he was the One, and 'just knew' he was the One... it doesn't mean he is.  I learned that I am able to accept what I cannot control.    I learned that distance is a great force to be reckoned with, and so is age. And that sometimes, they win.   I want to thank all my good friends who have supported me through this, and continue to support me - throughout all the drama and somber conversations. You guys have been awesome. You guys know how much I loved the guy. You know what I did to try and make it work. And I know that for you all to see where it has ended up doesn't make you very happy either. You have all showed your concern... and even through this first day, I should say I have been doing better than I expected- because of you guys.    Jessica,  Thanks for calling. I needed to cry to someone. And I'm glad it was you.   Ate Kat,  I know it's hardposition for you to be in. But thanks fortalking with me. Ithelps me a lot.   Cheps,  I know you have your own problems, but thanks for being so concerned about mine.   Betsy ,thanks for allowing me to dump on you too. I know i'm a lot to handle.   Mela,  you inspire me with your optimism. Thank you.   Monina,  I know you're not as updated as you should be, but I know you're there for me. I'll talk to you soon.   Thanks everyone.    For your sakes and mine, I promise totry and turn my frown into a smile... and turnmy drab entries intochirpy comedies. This is so much drama even  I  feel like hitting myself in the head.   In other words, batok.  Anyway, this is my blog now. I need to start anew. I'm trying to keep the list small for now, just while entries are still a bit personal. I'm also still trying to get a hang of this new site, so hopefully soon it will look more like me. (btw, for those of you who don't wanna have to create a username/pword just tocomment for the current or any future posts, you can click on 'post anonymously' and write your name nalang at the end of the comment so i know it's you)  Til the nextentry, when hopefullymy eyes aren't all puffy and I can actually see what I'm writing.  I love you guys.Thanks again.  
     
    
</post>
</Blog>