<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>29,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       It's time. Time for a generation of Christians to rise up and spread the Word. Time for the Christian bubble to pop, the Christian subculture to be abandoned, the Christian cliches to fall by the wayside. Time for a generation of artists to take the media by storm. Musicians, poets, writers, this is our calling. Not to create a soundtrack for the Christian life, but to connect with a fallen, hurting world. Let's write, sing, talk about pain --without treating it asan end in itself. Let's express love poetically,romantically, with full hearts or broken hearts without dragging the it through the filth of sin and impurity. Let's realize that we are not  of  this world but we  are in  it. I'msorry, but how many nonChristians want to listen to MWS or SCC? Now, I respect these men and their ministries, but honestly, I don't see them having a huge impact outside the Christian circle. I wish Christians could be Christians  and  artists without having to be "Christian artists." Let it start with Jenna. Let it start with Jeff. Let it start with Caroline. Let it start with Michael.  And    let it start with me.    
    
</post>
<date>24,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       . . . so much for my happy ending. I'm so sick of inane, cookie-cutter pop songs. Yet I've become so accustomed to listening to inane, cookie-cutter pop radio in my desperate attempt to conform to the world around me. No more. I'm over it. I'm over not being able to think for myself. I'm tired of pretending. I have my own ideas, opinions, and beliefs, and Irefuse to let others dictate what those ought to be. I'm tired ofnot thinking for myself. Yes, I still shop at American Eagle. But you know what? I  like AE. Their clothes fit well. I'll wear my AE clothes and sit in a coffeeshop and drink tea while reading novels by Chaim Potok and Madeline L'Engle because that's what  I  like. If you want to wear AE and drink coffee in a coffeshop (even though you don't like coffee)and discussthe latest gossipwith friends (even though it isn't true), fine. But I'mready to think for myself.   
    
</post>
<date>23,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I had more people ask me today where I was going to college. For the record, I have another year of high school left (joy), and I DO NOT KNOW where I am going next year. I know where I  want  to go, but I haven't determined if it's feasible yet. So please, either back off or give me the courtesy of thinking of something unique to ask me about instead of pestering me about the future. C'mon, I know you have it in you.   
    
</post>
<date>22,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       If you remain in me and my words remain in you, ask whatever you wish, and it will be given you.   Ask whatever you wish. What's meant by that? As far as I know, this passage is meant to be taken quite literally. But is there some larger context that I'm missing? Can I simply ask for and receive $25,000+ for college tuition? Or is that a selfish request? Whatever you wish. I suppose if that's what it says,that's what I'll ask for.   I don't claim to be a greatscholar ortheologian by any means. However, I can read. I'm simply going to trust my God.     
    
</post>
<date>20,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       It's been 11 months and 9 days since I last saw you. Only now am I aware that I don't know you, not really. How could I? You have been glorified and idealized in my mind, as I've filled in all the details I didn't know about you with what I would choose if I could. You're my ideal, and I live every day with the tinyspark of hope that someday, perhaps not today, and perhaps not tomorrow, but someday, I'll see you again. But that's not possible, because you'renot  real . You don't exist. You're a figment of my runaway imagination. Yes, you're somewhere out there, but you're not who I think you are. Were I tofind you, I think I'd beterribly disillusioned, and I don't wish that for either myself or you. So thank you for making me want to write. Thank you for being my inspiration. Thank you for giving me a love of piano, Chicago, poetry, and music. Thank you for teaching me how to hope. Thank you for changing my lifewithinthe four days that we spoke. Thank you, and good-bye. I need to be able to look at the stars without wondering if you're doing the same. I need towant to move to Chicago because I love the city, not becauseyou live there.I need to write about  my  life, as it is, not as I wish it would be. I need to stop feeling sorry for myself. I need to experience life without wishingI was sharing it with you. I need to be able to listen to music, to read poetry, to sing, to laugh, to  live  without thinking of you.         . . . what you are to me, I do not need.       
    
</post>
<date>20,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Or, perhaps, merely a continuation of an unending attempt to find the proper place to translate the promptings of my soul into proper words. I haven't decided whether or not I'll let anyone find me here. On one hand, I need a place where I can freely spill my thoughts. On the other hand (in addition to different fingers), I have an intense desire for someone to understand me, to know what I'm thinking, to see all that is flawed and imperfect about me . . . and accept me anyway.        I have found acceptance in countless places. My church. My youth group. My school. My friends. CMC. However, last Sunday I returned to my old church after a four year absence -- the only place where I have ever been utterly and completely rejected -- and realized thatI no longer had any desire to win acceptance there. I wonder why it is thatI desire acceptance so deeply, yet whenI don't receive it (and even when I do) I simply move on the the next source of it. I suppose the reason for my search is simply that I am a relational being (though my introverted personality struggles toadmit it), and I was designed to crave acceptance. However, I have yet to find it unconditionally. . .        That's not what I intended to say . . . but I suppose that'salright.         
    
</post>
<date>20,juillet,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       So, you were here last week.  Here, in the midst of my world.  Talking to  my  friends.  Most likely drinking coffee at  my  Caribou.  Perhaps sitting in  my  church.  But I never heard from you.  I never saw you.  It kills me that you didn't call, didn't show up, didn't search me out.      And thank God you didn't.      Let me hide in my reveries of a chance meeting on a Chicago sidewalk.  Let me cling to my dreams of an overheard voice in a crowded Starbucks (up north, of course).  Let me find you in the illusion of snowy streets in the Windy City, but let me never find you here.  This is  my  world.  Soon I'll start a new life in Chicago, and if you're a part of that, I'll be living in a dream come true.  But soon is not now.  Now, my world needs me.  It needs me to live in the present, not in the past, nor in the future.  You visit like a flash of lightening, brilliant and passionate, yet leaving destruction in your wake.  I need my life to be whole right now.      It kills me that you didn't call.      It would have killed me if you did.  
    
</post>
</Blog>