<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      21 June 2004   Has anyone noticed Linda Rondstat lately? Does she look like that creepy overweight Asian lady from  Mad TV  or what? I'm concerned. When are these opinionated singers going to learn to tolerate differing opinions? Personally, I support her right to dedicate a song or two to Michael Moore, but I will just as staunchly defend the right of her audience to be irritated by it. It's such a tiring subject, and you'd think that she would want to save herself the outrage and just lay low for a while. If I looked like that I would!   
     

    
</post>
<date>20,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      20 June 2004    Today we learned that Sandy Berger, former National Security advisor to President Clinton, is facing criminal charges for allegedly stuffing classified documents related to the 9-11 Commission down his pants, taking them home, and then "accidentally" losing some. Supposedly this investigation is months old, and Democrats are crying foul over the leak, saying that the revelation was politically motivated and timed to deflect attention from the findings of the 9-11 Commission, which are due out later this week. Both the  New York Times  and the  Washington Post  buried the story, nestling the news safely off the front page, where virtually no one would see it. Thankfully, however, we have Drudge, and even the Today show led its first hour with some banter about it. (Nevermind that they had David Gergen, a McCain-esque "Republican" to complain about the political ramifications....we have totake what we get from Katie Couric!) Amazingly, however, I'm not as outraged by the media slant as I usually am. This time, the old Clinton rage came back. What is it with these people? To me, the answer to this questionis sadly easily answerable. When I heard explanations from Berger's lawyers that he knew what he was doing was wrong by the Archives' standards but not technically illegal, I knew we were back in 1998, arguing over the meaning of the word "is,"all over again. The moral unclarity of Clinton and his staff never ceases to amaze me. It is wrong to go to the Archives in Washington and stuff documents in your pants. It is wrong to take them home. And, I believe, it is wrong to "lose"highly classfieddocumentswhen the 9-11 Commission would surely be interested in them. Now, I also realize Berger is innocent until proven guilty. But the fact that Berger took documents that related to Al Queda terrorists entering the country before 9-11 (under Clinton's watch), that were essential to the investigatory actions of the 9-11 Commissions, and that may have been useful politically (to Bush opponents, for example), all tell me that this isn't a simple misunderstanding. Oh, that and the fact that Berger himself admits to the "sloppy" actions. Berger has been an unpaid advisor to the Kerry team. I worry that he has passed on some of these documents to them, and that his behavior will work to further divide the country. (Did you know that the documents he took were drafts penned by Richard Clarke?) Regardless to whether or not this proves to be a front page story, we Americans deserve to know just where those "missing" papers ended up.    
     

    
</post>
</Blog>