<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I got back from my Durham/Chapel Hill, North Carolina trip yesterday. It was fun. I spent the night on Thursday atmy Uncle Bobby'shouse. My brother, 2 of mycousins, and I watched a couple of movies that's about it. We were gonna go four wheeling but it started to storm. Friday, I went to Erwin for about an hour to go get my Grandma from my aunt's house. When I got back to Durham, Will and the same two cousin's hadgone tomy aunt's grave. So I decided toplayThomas, my 5 year old cousin, at his pond. Then I went back to Chapel Hill and stayed at the condo.Saturday morning,my dad left to go to Uncle Bobby's house. My mom, my sister, and I have to wait til' 12:00 to leave because we had to wait for the cable guy to give us internet access. When we finally got to Uncle Bobby's house, we hopped into one of his golf carts, rode down to the helicopter hanger (it's like a warehouse where he used to store his helicopter). When we got there, we had to clean EVERYTHING in it. There were about ten 4-wheelers, 5 dirtbikes, 2 or 3 regular bikes, the golf carts. Then we swept. We couldn't sweep in little small sweeps, it was one continuous sweep. He didn't want dust to get on his old cars. After that my dad and I went with Uncle Bobby to feed his horses. Sounds easy, but he's got 40 horses. All in all though, I didn't mind helping him out. It wasn't that bad. Then after was fed the horses, we went back up the hill to his house, said goodbye, and came back home. I enjoyed my trip up there. Saturday was the only day we had to work. It wasn't bad at all. Well that's all I can think of so I'm gonna go. 
     
    
</post>
<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Hey,    Today was probably my first realization that summer's ending. The major event *also the only one* was registration was today. I got Mrs. Brinson. So far Jennifer is the only one I know of who is also in her homeroom. A lot of people seem to be in Mr. Herman's homeroom. I hope more people are in Mrs. Brinson's. That's about all I want to talk about on that topic. Tonight I'm going to a BBQ at the Gurley's. That's about all I can think of at the moment. I'm leaving for Durham/Chapel Hill, North Carolina tomorrow so I may not have time to write a new entry. If I find time I'll add one though.       -Charlotte 
</post>
</Blog>