<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I asked my daughter today what her inner voice defines about her these days.   I wanted to hear her  very deep  inner voice- not the stuff like, "a great vocalist," or "good test-taker." The deep inner voice that  defines her  is what I sought.   Mine is, right or wrong, "special and different."   It wasn't always that way. It used to be "slutty and irresponsible." Then it changed to "overwhelmed martyr/screw-up-at-life." Then, I turned 30 or so and it evolved to "trying very hard." In later years, it changed to "successful at work but not quite there as a Mom." And so on. I'm sure it will keep changin' as I go.   My daughter's inner voice, right now,is "the Good Kid."   I got to thinking about that. I asked her if she knew what happens to Good Kids. She replied, "They die early?" I said, "Well, sure. They get mauled by tigers." (See, we share a morbid, sick sense of humor, we Wheatleys.)   "Seriously, though," I said. "'Good Kids nearly always have something in common: They have fantasies of being bad, and since they're good, they're really bad at being bad."   I went on to describe it- we all have those friends who are just  not  good at cussing. They're also terrible and weepy when drunk. They "get caught" more than everyone else.   My goal as a parent is to try like hell to encourage them to figure out what they're thinking, feeling and living, such that they can be comfortable in happiness before they're parents themselves.   Yeah, I realize that things like hormones, lack of maturity, and lack of education prohibit some self-actualization, but I still GRANDLY envision my kids being simply and utterly as happy as is possible at this moment and every moment in the future.   And of course, true happiness is often borne through tribulation and mistake-making. So don't get me wrong and think I'm Alice in Wonderland-ish. 'Cause I'm more like the cynical Susan Sarandon in whatever that movie was where they flew off a cliff in a car.   But could it be that a person's label of Good Kid could hamper their ability to be bad, and therefore redeemed, and therefore, happy?   I dunno- it's just what I've been thinking about while reading  The Ragamuffin Gospel--  Manning's description of the Catholic definition(s) of sin- mortal and venial--While he draws a hilarious picture of his experience in confessingadolescent masturbationwith his priest, the shame he also endured was palpably recognizable to me.   He's making it painstakingly clear that Christ apparently preferred sinners toGood Kids. He said he came for the sinners. He let the Good Kids do their thing. (When I say Kids, note I don't mean the little children who He obviously loved dearly.) The Good Kids were apparently "Pharisees" back then.   I donna wanna mi' daughter to be a Pharisee. Yuck.   So anyway, if it's true that he loved the sinners, then the question I have is whether to encourage my daugther to just  be . Not be the Good Kid. To just be.   And perhaps screw up every once in a while so she can learn how freakin' awesome it is to be unconditionally forgiven simply because Jesus loves her. Nothing she can do can make that bigger, better or different. It simply is what it is.   Hmm.      
     

    
</post>
<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I just fell in love with Brennan Manning, author of  The Ragamuffin Gospel  and  Ruthless Trust . His followers were mine as a younger "christian," Michael W. Smith as a teen, and more importantly, Rich Mullins as an adult.   Rich came to San Antonio frequently when I was doing the Baptist thing. I'll never forget one night when he played and my mom and I were there. It had to be at least ten years ago, and I honestly have no idea why only Mom and I ended up at this event.   It was her birthday.   I watched and somehow decided that in heaven, I'd be married to someone like Rich, because he GOT it. He understood the way that Christ was about. And he'd be a good husband. I literally coveted Rich Mullins' existence. (though I was married with three kids at the time and didn't have his existence.)   Ok, so of course, there's some weirdness about that. But I really lusted after Rich in the most spiritual of ways. I just wanted him to be my husband and then everything would be okay. (Mom, at that time, wanted me to marry Carmen, but that's another blog.)   So later, Iused my "Christian connections" and got us into the Christian bookstore "afterparty" and he came in and as he was exiting after a ten minute acoustic thing, and we passed him on the stairs. I screamed to him like I was a groupie and he was a Beatle, "RICH!! IT'S MY MOM'S BIRTHDAY!"   He stopped and looked at me. I grinned charmingly and said, "Pretty please, could you sing her Happy Birthday???"   He looked at me (and with whatI hopewas wishfulness that I was his wife,) sang it. Sweetly and with authenticity.   And my mother was as thrilled as all get-out. And I always loved him more for that.   When I learned he died in a car accident, I just ached. I even committed the mortal sin and actually "prayed" to Rich on a regular basis when I was confused or lonely.   So fast-forward to today: I'm at  Barnes and Noble  picking up Brennan Manning's  Ruthless Trust  and was inadvertently directed by the store clerk to  The Ragamuffin Gospel .   And lo and behold, there was a message in the forward by Rich,   And lo and behold, DUH, this is why he's called his band  The Ragamuffin Band .   Good lord. Could it be I'm finding what I was looking for? Even if it's  not  being married to Rich?   I'm overwhelmed. Because guess what? Today is July 26. My Mom's birthday.   No joke.   
     

    
</post>
<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Going to a new church is hard. Especially when it's not a "church."   When it's more of a gathering, where there's a lot of encouragement for people to be honest and affectionate, it's almost like you're on a date. Or you're in junior high. You feel like everything you do could be keenly analyzed.   You wonder if you're dressed right. You're being inundated with new faces and names. You wonder if your butt looks big in those jeans.  You wonder if the guy next to you is simply being kind to your kids, or if he's a freak. You want to know the story about that couple in front of you who have four kids that don't look like them. Did they adopt? How cool is that?   You want to know what makes those people who sit on the front row who they are. Are they special friends of the pastor? You especially want to know this, since in your non-"church," the "pastor" isn't a pastor. He's just the leader of this unruly bunch.  Who's that woman in the back, the one bustling about and apparently holding things together? Does she get paid to work so hard? Or is she independently wealthy and has alot of time on her hands? Her shoes are fabulous. Wonder where she got them? You can't ask, 'cause you're just here to observe. And everyone seems so busy except for you.  Wouldn't it be a hilarious, cosmic joke if everyone around you is pretty much thinking the same thing?   Wouldn't it be sweet if everyone started asking those questions aloud?   
     

    
</post>
<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Alone  is a weird concept. What does it really mean?       "I hope you don't grow up and be  alone ."      "Please. Just leave me the hell  alone! "      "Finally, the kids left and I was  alone ."      If you start to actually look at the word, I promise, you'll feel like you're on acid. It's a strange word.  Alone .       Good? Bad?       I say good. Though before I always saw it as bad.        Alone  is not alone at all.    Alone  is simply quiet.Purity isperceived as alone, 'cause it has no makeup. No one notices the girl without makeup. Except God.       Alone  is not lonely, despite its lingual derivatives. We all yearn to "be alone." To escape the talk, to be by ourselves. To experience nothing, yet every single thing that we've put off forever.        Alone  is when we lay on the bed and no one is around, and the comforter is on our cheek and we don't have anything, not even a mother, there to silence our juvenile commentary. At that place, we're just baby grown-ups.       And that's when the conversation with God occurs. That's when we bargain like there's no tomorrow. That's when the  real  comes in and we know that  He's  the One who is actually real, and by God, we'd better get this shit figured out.       It's often called panic. It's often called epiphany.             
     

    
</post>
<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Go this moment and rent  The Human Stain .       Watch it, please.       Come back.      Now go buy the book, which is simply phenomenal.      Come back.      Finished?      Y'all. The layers of humanity are thrown in front of us, begging to be examined. I want to talk about irony. I want you to  get  it.       There's really nothing but desperation for love sitting before us. And there's nothing but love sitting before us.       Just watch it. I have a feeling you kept reading this before you obeyed me, dammit.      :-)  
     

    
</post>
<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Contemplative Me.  Not at all what I generally look like.   urlLink   
     

    
</post>
<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Be still and know that I am God    Psalm 46:10       But those who wait on the Lord shall renew their strength    Isaiah 40:31      Here's a Rule of the Universe: If you're a redhead and nicknamed "Missi," you're likely to be told to "sit still" or "hush up" or "slow down" for most of your life. People who sire children should be aware of this and think twice-- If I'd been named "Siobahn," perhaps I would have developed a colt-ish figure and been more inclined towards serenity. Alas, this was not the case.      I struggle frequently with that missive,  be still , in every area of my life. Whether it's shutting my mouth, or resting my brain, or driving on Bee Caves Road, I am constantly going-going-going.       Today, I had to stop working on something to let the cleaning people do their thing in and around my office. I decided to leave the phone inside and slip out to the pool for a while. It was, decidely, torture.       I was floating around and wondering if anyone had called. Then I decided I was so hungry that perhaps I was starving myself. Maybe I needed to go back inside and fix a small snack? No, the cleaners were busy in the kitchen.       Wonder what the kids were up to?       Could my neighbors see how fat I look on this float?      How come I'm a slob and can't keep the pool area swept?      Those plants are gonna die because we never water them.      God, I'm so hungry.      Is it late enough in the day to have a cocktail? I mean, it's  Friday .            Be still and know that I'm God .      But I don't know what the hell that means.        Yes, you do .      No, I DON'T.       Look UP, idiot .      And would you believe that the color of the sky in Austin, Texas today is the very definition of "sky blue" in a Crayola package, juxtaposed against "grass green" in the trees? And it smells kind of froggy in my backyard. And there are these cicada-sounding things going off everywhere. And the sun feels good on my skin. And floating is right up there with skydiving.      It's all there. We just have to be still for a second. In my case, I was back inside within 45 minutes, and I feel like I slept for twelve hours.              
     

    
</post>
<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       When's the last time you woke up on a Sunday and really, truly, thought: "I am SO excited to go to church!" ?   C'mon, admit it- church sucks.   For me, at least, church is something my parents instilled by forcing me to go.   But I've stilltried nearly all of them:   1) I've tried the  traditional  ones that have large, inspirational architecture and intellectually interesting rituals.   And wow. All of that inspired me. I had the most amazing experience in St. Patrick's cathedral once with my best friend. I remember leaving and feeling that it was almost like a (really good) sexual encounter. The vastness of the building, combined with the hushed reverence that it commanded, caused this wonderful discussion of Mary Magdelene's role as a female disciple, and I felt awe and power while we quietly worked through a few personal issues.   But I know I wouldn't awaken each Sunday and feel compelled to visit St. Patrick's. Quite the contrary; I want to reserve it for a few special times. It's too freakin' awesome to become that familiar to me.   2) I grew up in the beautiful, homey,  community  churches. They're everywhere, and their allure is never really denominational, truth be told.   Instead, the claim to fame in these churches is that they love kids. They nurture families and provided a place for us back when we were kids, and now, as we have become parents, they have a neat Sunday School program which prepares the kids for school and also re-instills our generational values.   The great thing about community churches is that you can raise several generations of children with the same old folks, thus creating a sense of family. Unfortunately, in every "family," Grandpa thinks his way is right, and that it transcends ANY modernity. So, Mom and Dad listen to Grandpa. And kids rebel against that, and come back into the fold after law school or having children themselves. It's inbreeding at its worst, but it serves to educate uson all that modern politics isabout, eh?   Oh, and "church splits" in community churches are the bloodiest.   And many peoplejust eventually wake up one Sunday morning and decide that  Meet the Press  and the  New York Times  are more interesting and less painful for both themselvesand their kids.   3) I love the  fun  churches. These are the ones with charismatic pastors who garner a national television audience. The music rocks, the building is usually donated by a local millionaire (who controls the church council, incidentally) and their Easter and Christmas Eve candlelight services are standing-room-only. I'm telling you that this exists in every city in the U.S.; Austin isn't unique-- it's common in progressive churches and in fundamentalist ones.   I love being entertained at these churches. You can also differ in major theological viewpoints with the pastor, but because you're sitting 10,000 feet away from him, and he's so nice and funny, you don't even try to "chalk it up." You just show up occasionally and brag to your friends about the rock concert you get to attend each week.   And one day, you just wake up after a hard night of life on Saturday night, and decide to sleep in and watch your pastor on his next televised viewing.   4) The  emotional  churches are often branded as fundamentalist, but my take is that they're the most compelling, because they actually deal with reality, or at least part of it. They focus on human frailty, which is what we all lay awake praying about at 4:30 in the morning when it's still dark and we realize we're screw ups.   "If we could only speak in tongues, God could hear us."   "If we're sick and have a little faith, God can heal us."   "If we're having an affair, God can send us a Christianto save us."   There's a certain truth to this, methinks. And there's a certain condemnation that makes us depressed and inferior.   And we wake up one morning and decide to go to Gruene Hall instead, 'cause we're sluts/bad people anyway.   -------------------------------------------------------   Ironically, in the end, I'd like to get up one day a week and gather with people who respect a portion of all the above descriptions. I'd  like  some tradition. I'd  like  people to care about my kids. I'd  love  some coolness. I'd  like  for people to call me out when I'm messing up as a person.   In my view, it would be neat to have a  Breakfast Club  church, where you have the geek, the athlete, the princess, the outcast, and the reprobate all hanging out together and learning something.   Because after all, aren't we  all  the geek, the athlete, the princess, the outcast, and the reprobate?       
     

    
</post>
<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Deny thySelf, yet love thy neighbor as thySelf .   Huh?   What did Christ mean when He talked about our relationships with our Selves? Much church doctrine is centered on "Self sacrifice." It's hard to comprehend sacrificing someone/thing called mySelf when I don't know her very well. If my spiritual pursuits have been, up to now, focused on denying mySelf, then how can I love someone else like I love mySelf?   Here's amom; here's an analogy: I constantly struggle with smoking. I deny mySelf (sometimes), but feel SO deprived. Because I see not being able to occasionally smoke as deprivation,I then treat mySelf as a deprived person.   So then, I have these kids. When they ask to go to the movies, my automatic answer is nearly always no. So I love my neighbor as I love mySelf. My deprived Self. While this isn't a justification for smoking, since I'm changing my views on it these days, I spent years where that has literally been part of my existence.   SO...   Of all places, I think I figured something out while going to the bathroom this morning. My teens were pouncing around outside the door trying to get me to agree to yet another endless solution to summer boredom. My instinct was to yell, "SHUT. UP. NOW. JEEZ!"   For some reason, the adage, "Do unto others as you would have them do unto you" popped into my head. Suddenly, it wasn't about the fact I was powdering MY nose. I was hurled to the outside of the bathroom door. And my face turned red, because I remembered earlier this morning when my son was in the bathroom downstairs and I was knocking incessantly to tell him to hurry so we could make his doctor's appointment. Yep. Them apples fall very near my tree.   I got to thinking about it, and how I'd felt when, during the earlier bathroom incident, my son had yelled, "GOD! MOM! I'M! COMING! JEEZ!" And I guess I do believe in being "filled with the Spirit" after all- because as I remembered that, something came out of my mouth that was other-than-Melinda: (calm) "Guys, I'm in the bathroom. I'll come out there and love on ya' in just a second." Yeah, I know. Pretty cool. They'd already moved on to bigger and better things by then, but it still had an impact.   Ok, so back to mySelf. I felt really good about mySelf when I did that. I was like, "Damn. You're the bomb." And I still recognized God was involved because a) I was thinking about Christ's teachings when it happened, and b) I responded like He probably would've.   So there was this little lightbulb that went off: What if sacrificing one's Self is about sacrificing the crap that makes us feel like losers (like yelling at people)...the stuff that makes us loathe ourselves and panic that we're going to Hell?   Could it be that it's all one sweet, vicious cycle? I love you, you love me, we're a happy family? If I love you, I love me. If I love you, my sense of Self becomes heightened. I want to treat mySelf with the same love I give to you. If I love you, I expect- no, desperately desire- you to love me back. I'm as weird as they come, but my tiny little brain has to wrap itself around these concepts in order to fully invest mySelf in pursuing Jesus' way of living.      
     

    
</post>
<date>21,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      The anticipation of school reconvening loomed large in this household. The feeling was mutual, punctuated by doors slamming, complaints of the crapola food they had to eat here, and my whining about the plethora of computer viruses accidentally downloaded on my computer by "no one."  I liken the environment to pre-Christmas, where shopping and baking makes for one bitchy Mommy. But the grand day of its arrival creates a psychological block that prevents the memories of the previous days to intrude. Come to think of it, childbearing also produces the same effect.  So, I stumble out of bed at the ungodly hour of 7:50 a.m. to transport the teens to their respective campuses. I'll add here that it is sheer bliss when children come of the age to not only dress and feed themselves, but to shun your advances to assist. God's so good in that regard, ain't He?  Turning left from my neighborhood street onto Bee Caves Drive during the school year is tantamount to proceeding left on 5th Avenue in Manhattan during peak hours. One needs a cabbie or public transport. Given that we have neither, and the kids have informed me that the school bus is wacked, uncool, too early, and above all, downright  dangerous , I am relegated to driving them for a few days out of guilt. This, too, shall pass. It always does for me.  Ten minutes after approaching the intersection, a kind gentleman lets me in and we're off to the races. I drop Amanda, the sophomore-with-a-sassy-haircut, at the high school. As she crosses the street, I see two Abercrombie OC-type boys checking her out. For some reason, this pissed me off, but I veered away from them right before I got too close.  As we approached Troy's junior high, it was obvious that every parent had fallen hook, line and sinker for the ol' "the bus is wacked, uncool, too early, and above all, downright  dangerous " speech. And apparently, they weren't too happy about it. There was no friendliness. There were no smiley waves like we do at football games. Instead, we sat in a line, brows furrowed-- determined to hold our place in line and  not. let. anyone. cut .  As we finally approached the school entrance, I had practiced deep breathing and turned to ruffle my baby's hair before he exited the car. "I lov..." The door slammed. He waved behind his back without looking at the car. Sigh. I'm a chauffeur, that's all.  40 minutes later, I arrive home from the three-mile roundtrip trek to the schools. I breathe deeply again and proceed to do the following:  1. Take a long, hot bath. (Boring. Took 5 minutes.)  2. Drank coffee and checked email. (10 minutes.)  3. Listened to talk radio. (Sigh. 3 minutes.)  4. Checked email again. (Why don't I have any friends? 1 minute.)  5. Blow dried hair. (4 minutes. )  6. Tried to take a morning nap. (10 minutes.)  7. And so on.  By mid-afternoon:  1. Decide I should volunteer at each of the kids' schools one day a week.  2. Read their schools' websites to acclimate myself to their upcoming events.  3. Wonder if Amanda knows that there's an audition after school this afternoon?  4. Call Amanda's school to leave message about audition after school this afternoon.  5. Wonder what time Troy's football practice is over?  6. Call Troy's school to inquire.  7. Decide to take Troy and friend to McDonald's to celebrate their first day of school.  8. Call friend's Mom to let her know and learn she's picking them up. Already arranged by Troy.  9. Try to take a nap.  10. Write in this blog.  Life's so sweet when the kids are back in school. I give it three days and they'll be calling me to ask that I deliver some of my "crapola food" for lunch.  Ciao for now.     
     

    
</post>
</Blog>