<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
            FRIENDS NOW AND FOREVER              CINDY’S FIRST BOYFRIEND           “ Oh!! My God I am so excited today’s Alisha’s birthday? I can’t believe she’s inviting boys. I hate boys and….” was all that I kept saying as the evening kept coming closer and closer. Today is Alisha’s 11 th  birthday and I am beginning to feel very anxious. But the worst thing is she’s inviting boys. Yuck!! I am Cindy Smith and I am 11 years. Alisha Graham is not my best friend but we pretty much hang around together. We live in Canley heights,        Australia    . It’s a really cool place and we go to     Canley       Heights       Public School    . Kylie Rodriguez is my best friend and we love hanging around, shopping and of course we do a bit of studying together. I do have other friends like Petronella curk and Amelia Billick and I can tell you that even though we are 11 and supposed to be acting like “young ladies” as our parents say, we are tom boys(except one of us) and we enjoy being just the way we are.                 Alisha however doesn’t behave like us any more. Its fun being around her but suddenly she acts weird. I’ve spoken to my mum about it but she tells me that Alisha is going through a phase and that she’s growing up. She plays around with us but all of a sudden when Julian, Ian and Harry come around she acts peculiar. Last year she could stand up to them when they bullied us around and now she finds them good-looking. Yuck!!                Today Alisha is having her birthday party and she asked me to help her put up her decorations. So I said I’ll do it. I have to arrive an hour earlier so that means I have to start going in for my shower. I already chose my clothes a pair of jeans and a red top that said GIRLS RULE! Alisha helped me pick out that top; she said it matched perfectly with my brown complexion. I have brown skin and jet black hair, tall and chubby. I have no brothers or sisters and sometimes it gets lonely. Petronella and Kylie have somewhat the same features except that they’re a bit thinner. Petronella hasn’t got a brother and a dad. Kylie has a sister who’s two years younger than her. Alisha wants to become a model when she’s older so she’s cut out all the chocolates and fatty stuff from her diet. She’s really skinny and tall but I must admit that she is prettier than the rest of us. Amelia is quiet but that doesn’t mean I bully her around, she voices her opinion whenever she wants to. Kylie and Petronella are just like me we’re bold and stand up for ourselves. But Amelia is good looking too. The five of us have been friends since kindergarten and FRIENDS NOW AND FOREVER is the motto of our little group. To tell you the truth I came up with it (I’m not boasting).                Alisha used to be like us but she’s changing, and changing rapidly. I got ready to go and my mum said she’d drive me over. It was a ten minute drive but I heard a ten-minute lecture as well, with things like “Cindy, behave like a young girl, act decently and give us a call when the party’s over so that I can pick you up.” “Alright mum, I know, I know”. Mum can be annoying sometimes that she makes me want to scream.                I arrived at Alisha’s place and I rang the door bell. It was about two seconds later till I heard Stephanie’s voice saying “I’ll get it, you carry on”   “hello steff what’s up?” nothing much how bout you?” “Nothing”         “Alisha’s in her room, I’ve gotta run, cya later?”        “Cya”                 Stephanie is Alisha’s older sister. She’s 14 and when she went out with a boy for the first time, all of us whispered to each other with words like “gross”, “yuck”, and “is she crazy”        And Alisha said the same thing but now it seems like she’s desperate to get a boyfriend. Alisha also has an older brother and he’s 17. His name is Nathan but I don’t speak to him that much because he seems to be leading a very busy life. Alisha’s sister and brother go to high school.                I went up to Alisha’s room which took me about 2mins as her house is quite big comparing to any of us. I knocked on her bedroom door which said “ALISHA’S ROOM” and below it said “PLEASE KNOCK BEFORE ENTERING”. Immediately a voice replied “who is it” and I answered back saying “it’s me Cindy can I come in?”        “Yeah sure”.                So I went in and I stood there dumbstruck with my mouth opened. I couldn’t say anything, but at last when I could speak I said “What on earth has got into you?”   “Hello Cindy, do you like my new hairdo?”Alisha had on a lovely blue dress with a red motive. But that wasn’t the point, she had make-up on (a bit too much) and her lovely brown hair was now blonde. I always loved her hair but look what’s she’s done to it.                “What did you do to yourself?” I asked.                “Oh! Cindy you won’t understand, steff helped me do it and I love it”                “I don’t know what’s wrong with you but if you’re comfy with it then that’s good”. Deep down inside I wished that she would come back and be normal like us.                I plonked myself on the bed and looked around and to my horror found that her bedroom was re-arranged. I was so busy looking at the birthday girl that I hadn’t noticed her room. All the posters of Barbie and Winne the pooh had been pulled down and new posters of some freaky guys were up. I didn’t like it at all.                “Happy birthday to me” she started singing and it was only then that I realised that I’d forgotten to wish her for her birthday.                “Alisha, I’m sorry I forgot”. Handing her a parcel wrapped up in gift wrapping paper I apologetically said “happy 11 th  birthday”.                 “That’s alright, I was just kidding” she said as she received it.                  She came over and I gave her a hug.” Really” I asked                “And to get your present”                With that we cracked up with laughter and later she said” The decorations are done but I was hoping that maybe, you could help me take the food down to the rumpus room?”                “ Happy to help”   I answered and with that we went down and laid   out the table with all kinds of sandwiches, chips, punch, biscuits, and some fruit for the birthday girl. When that was done, she checked her c.d player and all her cd’s.                 “Alisha, are you going to have dancing?” I asked hoping she’d say no.                “Of course Cindy, everyone from our class are going to be there and everyone loves dancing so I decided I’ll have dancing after all”.                I didn’t know how to dance but I curiously asked again        “Is it going to be like a boy-girl dancing party”?                “Maybe, but I hope Ian is there, I want to dance with him” she said as if she was in the seventh heaven.                I just carried on and I couldn’t wait for Petronella, Kylie and Amelia to arrive.                One, by one everyone started coming in and then Kylie came in. I was so happy to see her. She was also dressed in her normal, casual clothes. Amelia and petronella also arrived soon and the party began. Alisha went over and started to chat with Ian as if he was a movie star or something. I couldn’t wait for the games to begin. I’ve always loved that part of the party the best since I was small.                Alisha played some music and said “everyone lets dance”. It was a slow number and it had to be a waltz. Everyone somehow found partners including my friends. “What are you guys doing?” I asked Kylie and Petronella as they got up to dance with James and Daniel. But they just shrugged and went off. Amelia sat close to me, and I thought at least one person agrees with me but soon Mike came over and asked her if he could have a dance and she went all pink all over her face but in the end said yes.                I was so mad with my friends; some of the kids were just watching so I just stood there with a sandwich in my hand and waited till the song was over. Later everyone resumed to their places and started chatting but I totally went mad and asked Kylie” Do you know what you’ve done now”. And she said” oh!! Come on Cindy it was fun, I liked it, and James and I got to know each other better and we’re going out to the movies next weekend”.                I just stood there and said nothing, what could I do? All my friends are acting indifferent and I even wondered if they were the same people I met years ago. Then Alisha said “I’m dying to know what you’ll bought me so can you gather around to open up my presents? Everyone got into a circle and she opened up Simon’s gift, it was a notebook with stars all over it. Then Petronella gave her a pen, Kylie bought her a brooch, Amelia got her an alarm clock which was in the shape of an A. Alisha got tons of gifts like   necklaces, bracelets, earrings, autograph books, photo albums, story books and she kept saying” its lovely, I love it, its beautiful, very sentimental”. Obviously mine was the last one to be opened as I was the first to arrive and I was waiting for her to look at mine and say “I love it”.                I bought her a t-shirt with Barbie on it and I thought it would be perfect. But after seeing her bedroom after a long time I wasn’t so sure. She tore open the paper and said “ its nice” in a very sarcastic way but I knew now that she didn’t welcome it but I just pretended I didn’t care   but deep down I was hurt and wanted to cry.                 We had a little more dancing and then she said in a bold voice “everybody we’re going to have a game”        “A game, don’t you think that’s a bit childish” Pamela blurted out but I was happy until Alisha said “Not any game, its spin the bottle”. With that everyone got into a circle without being told except me. I just stood there, and Alisha came over to me and said “Don’t make a scene, or ruin my party, just play”. For the first time ever I just agreed and played along but I felt miserable.                Each time anyone kissed anyone I murmured to myself saying” yuck”. Even Amelia and Kylie had a turn. It was my turn next and I hate boys, now I had to kiss one “go on Cindy” Alisha said with a look in her eyes that meant don’t be daft just have a go. I spun the bottle and it landed on Calvin, one of the boys in my class. Its not that I hated Calvin, I liked him but only as a friend.                Actually I was the one who had to make the first move but surprisingly he did and I went mad, so mad that I stood up and said “I hate this stupid party, I can’t believe I came, I hate it, have a nice time Alisha” and I stormed out of the room expecting someone to come behind me but no one really did. I went up to the living room and saw mrs.Graham there. “What’s wrong love?” but all I could say was” would it be okay if I used your telephone?”                 I reckon she must have guessed that something was bothering me and I didn’t actually want to mention it so she said “Alright love, it’s over there” and pointed to my right. I replied in my politest voice saying “Thank you” and went over and dialled mum’s mobile number and asked her if she could pick me up now? She said she’ll be there in another 15 minutes so I sat down on the couch and watched the hands of the clock turn slowly. 15 minutes seemed like forever.                 Mum arrived and I thanked mrs.Graham and got into the car. The first question was “How was the party, Cindy”.        “Good” I replied.                “Is there something that you would like to tell me” she asked. At that moment I felt my face turning red and hot tears swell up and before I knew it those tears came trickling down my face. I couldn’t stop crying and I knew mum was getting worried so as soon as I went home I asked her if I can be excused from dinner and I went straight to my room, got into my pj’s ready to go to bed when mum knocked on my bedroom door.                Mum always comes to speak to me when she knows I’m worried and sometimes it helps but right now I really didn’t think it would. “Come in” I answered. She came right in and said “Cindy, are you alright? Your eyes are puffed up.”                “I’m fine mum”                “You know sweetie, if you don’t want to talk that’s alright”                At that moment I felt that I could speak to mum and I told her all that had happened. Mum always understands how I feel and gives me good advice.                She listened without interrupting me and at last she spoke saying” I know that this is a very hard time for you Cindy but this is a time when things change. May-be your friends are just growing up and realising things before you, that doesn’t mean anything’s wrong with you but eventually you will be just like them soon”                “I don’t want things to change, I still want to play with dolls and teddy bears, I don’t want to talk about boys and make up, and it feels as if I’m loosing my friends”                “I know Cindy, but trust me, it will be different soon.”                “Do you reckon what I done was wrong” I asked                “Well yes, I guess, but if you call Alisha tomorrow and explain everything to her, she may understand it”                “I guess so too, I feel guilty now, but I feel much better after having this little chat with you, thanks mum”                 She came over and gave me a hug. I really felt better and I went to bed. The next morning I got up, although I felt guilty and I wanted to speak to Alisha I didn’t feel like I wanted but I knew I had to.                        I had a wash and went downstairs with the intention to call Alisha but a surprise awaited me there. “Surprise”         And I really felt relieved for some reason to see my friends. Mum also was there and I certainly didn’t want to apologise in front of mum so I said “can we go up to our room”. “Wait a sec” Kylie replied and lifted up a big brown paper bag.                When we went upstairs, everyone was silent, then I broke the silence by saying “Alisha, I’m sorry I spoilt your bir- thday party, I was….” But before I could finish Kylie opened the brown paper back and brought out chips and a few sandwiches “these are the remains from yesterday, I thought maybe we could have a little chat.         “Where’s petronella?” I asked        “She has a dentist’s appointment” Alisha answered.                For the first time today Amelia said” I’m sorry Cindy, we should have been with you, instead we went off dancing and playing. “ Look you guys, I know that I still act like a little kid but that doesn’t mean you have to be like me, I know someday soon I’ll be like you’ll and I’m waiting for that day but I still want to be a little girl and I want us to remain friends forever” I replied.                The room went silent again and then Alisha came over   and put her arm around me and said “ Cindy its alright even though we realise certain things before you we’ll still be your friends” .                “Really”        “Yeah of course”.                We started talking about what programs would be on TV and Kylie all of a sudden started grinning which brought suspicion upon all of us.        “Spit it out Kylie” I said                “Cindy, I’m not sure if you’re going to like this but…”        “What, hurry up”                “Yesterday when you spun the bottle, you were supposed to go forward to kiss Calvin but he came forward instead.”                “So” I asked                “Later he told me that he wants to go out with you because he liked you”                I started to blush and I felt like I was on the top of the world. “Yes”                Alisha then said “so we answered for you, saying yes”                 “I’m going out with Ian on Saturday and so are Kylie and James and Petronella and Daniel and Amelia and Mike. So we decided that we like to all go out together”.        “It will be fun Cindy” Amelia said                Again I felt happy and I said “I have to ask mum, just a sec”. I darted down and saw mum sewing.”Mum will it be okay if I go out with my friends and another friend this weekend to the movies?”                “Who’s this other friend?”                “Calvin, he asked me out so I want to go out”?                “Sweetie, are you doing this just so you can keep your friends?”                “No mum, I feel different now, can I go?”                “If you feel comfy with it”.                I was so happy and Alisha couldn’t believe her eyes. We started talking about what we would wear and Alisha persuaded me that she’d do my makeup.                 Saturday finally came and mum picked out a blue top with silver hearts all over it. It looked really pretty. Mum said she’d drop me off. When I saw my friends there I was relieved. I said bye to mum and gave her a quick kiss and went. I saw everyone there and then I saw Calvin, my heart skipped a beat. He looked gorgeous in his jeans and t-shirt. He held a red rose in his hand and kept smiling at me.                “This is for you” he said, handing me the rose “and you look pretty”                “Thank you and I like your pair of jeans” I replied.                Immediately Alisha whispered in my ear “yuck!! Look who’s going out with a boy and telling him he looks good too”.                “Stop it Alisha” I replied but I could feel myself blushing.                “Let’s get going, the movie’s starting in about 5 minutes and I’ve bought the tickets” Alisha said.                “Where are Petronella and Daniel?” I asked                “They are in already”. Amelia replied.                We went in and found our seats easily, off course I was seated next o Calvin.                The lights went out and the movie started but instead of watching Calvin and I were chatting, till someone from behind shouted” will you two down there shut up”.                So I suggested that we go and have something to eat. “Alisha, we’re going out down to the café, meet us up there” and we went up to the café. On the way Calvin and I were speaking about lots of stuff and then in the course of conversation he asked” What happened yesterday? Was it because you have never kissed anyone before or anything else?”        “Yes I’ve never kissed anyone before and I guess I was not ready”. I didn’t want to tell him the actual reason, what if he thought if I was weird or anything?”.                “Can I tell you something” he said        “What’s that, Calvin?”                “I really like you, Cindy and its okay if you haven’t had your first kiss because I’ve never had one too”.                I was surprised but I just said as calm as I could “Calvin, you seem like a pretty cool guy and I like you too”.                He smiled and before I could say anything else he leant over and kissed me. I felt as if I could scream. I just smiled and suddenly we saw everyone else come into the café.                “Is the movie over already, Petronella?” I asked                “No but we’re bored”.                The evening went of perfectly; mum said she’d pick me up at 8.00. The others had their parents to pick them up too and one by one everyone else left except Calvin and myself. He said he’ll wait till my mum comes. Mum finally arrived and before I could go he said “Cindy, I had fun, and can we go out some other time?”                “I had fun too and I hope we go out again, bye”. I quickly gave him a kiss on the cheek and ran to the car.                As soon I was strapped mum asked me “how was your evening”?                 “Excellent mum, I loved it”.        “That’s good, sweetheart, was that Calvin standing there with you?”        “Yeah mum, he said he’ll wait with me till you come”                “That’s nice of him, ask him to come home sometime and have dinner”.                Mum kept on talking but I was wondering why I had spoken about boys so badly, some of them are really nice.                The next day Alisha, Kylie, Petronella and Amelia came over to my place and we just kept chatting about yesterday. “you guys I’m sorry, I didn’t understand that it can be fun to hang around boys, but I’m happy cos I had a nice time yesterday, my first date, my first kiss and ………”.                “Wait a minute, you didn’t tell us anything about your first kiss” Petronella said                “Didn’t I, I thought I did” I replied as casually as I could but I couldn’t help blushing.                They wanted to know exactly every little detail so I told them and when we were finished, Alisha said” I told you, you will be like us soon and soon has come”                “I know I said, and it feels great to have such good friends like you’ll to chat to. Thanks “                Kylie said “friends forever”                Yeah we all replied “friends forever”.                So it was fun and I wouldn’t change my friends a bit cos I really liked them. It was great to be friends again and to tell you the truth it does feel great to hang around boys especially boys like Calvin.                THE END                                                            Its Alisha’s 11 th  birthday and our five friends are having a disagreement, while Cindy thinks boys are yuck, the others seem to say its fun to hang around boys. Things are changing rapidly for the five of them. What will happen next?               
      
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
             HIGH SCHOOL AT LAST                                        “That’s it I had it young lady, no more talking about this” dad said almost shouting. “But dad…” I said “That’s not fair”.                 “Jessica, could you pass me the peanut butter” dad spoke completely ignoring my statement.                   With that I had to rest my case but I still think that it’s unfair. There is the mega problem that has just exploded in my house partly because of me, well the whole problem is because of me (I can’t help it).                I guess you’re still confused with all this stuff. Let me explain this more clearly. I’m Kylie Rodriguez and I live in      Canley Heights       Australia    . It’s a wonderful place in fact it seems like the best place on earth and I go to Canley Heights Primary School which is the best school on earth but it won’t be too long before I have to leave this amazing school. It’s like this we (my friends and I) went to this school since Kindergarten and we love it but they get to go to     Canley       Heights       High School     (all four of them) and I have to go to     Canterbury       High School     which is about an hour’s drive from here. And I don’t want to go.                My friends are Amelia, Alisha, Petronella and Cindy along with my boyfriend James. We are all 13 (at least most of us). Cindy is best friend and has been my best friend since forever and she’s really the best, best friend any one can have, she has black hair with brown complexion and jet black hair, she’s a bit chubby and tall. She has no dad or brothers or sisters and lives with her mum. Excepting the fact that that she gets really angry very easily she’s pretty cool. Then my next friend is Alisha she used to get really snobbish at first but I think Petronella rubbed her edges of her and now she’s just okay. She loves to sing and dance and when she grows up she wants to become a model, gosh she will be perfect for that job because she’s really skinny and a very fair complexion.   Alisha has an elder sister and an elder brother.                Petronella has a brother; well he’s not her real brother but her step brother-Mark. She used to live with her mum alone but then her mum started dating and now that guy (Nathan) has moved in with them and they are deciding their wedding which will be in a couple of weeks.   They first decided a date and then they postponed the date. Petronella has lime complexion with brownish- blackish hair and is very studious and she loves reading just like me.                 The next friend of mine is Amelia, who’s the quietest person in our group. She has a step brother and she lives with her adopted parents. Amelia also has lime complexion and light brown hair. She loves reading but she doesn’t read stuff like me she reads books on animals. When she grows up she wants to become a Vet (a doctor for animals).                         “Kylie, look who’s here” Jessica called out. Well I almost forgot I have a sister and I live with both my parents. Jessica’s 9 and she goes to the same Primary school as me. We get along together most of the time except that she’s always the genius of the family and off course the baby of the family. She always gets most of the attention and I don’t.   I’m usually not the jealous type except when it comes to her.                 “Who is it?” I shouted back.        “Come down and see” she called back.                She can be   very tantalising at times and it annoys me. I ran down as fast as I could and there I could see my mum and dad speaking to a girl whose back was turned towards me and I couldn’t help but scream “Angela”. Angela has always been my favourite cousin and she helps me sort out my problems just by talking to me. She has black long hair and brown complexion.   It had been a long time since I’ve seen her because she lives in     Melbourne     and she rarely visits but we have lots of fun when she comes even though she is about ten years older to me.                   “Kylie” she greeted me “how are you”. “I’m good” I replied and I ran over to her and hugged and kissed her.                 “How are you?” I asked “when did you arrive? How long are you …” I began when Jessica interrupted me “Don’t you think she needs time to relax Kylie after her long flight”.                “Brat” I muttered under my breath. But just as I looked up my dad’s eyes were on me so I just smiled and spoke “Um… actually yes I think you do Angela, I’m sorry”.                 “That’s okay” she replied “I’m staying over for the next week or two because I’m changing jobs and I thought I’ll have a break before starting over at my new job”.                 “Awesome” I replied “We can have tons of fun together this time”.                “Well I don’t think Angela will want to spend lots of time with you this time because Ken has come with her” mum said.                “Ken!! Who’s Ken?” I asked.                “Ken is my boy friend and he’s come down from     Melbourne     and he’s staying at one of his friends place” Angela said.                “Okay” I said. I think my voice must have sounded exactly how I felt-disappointed because immediately Angela said in a rather kind voice “We can still do some of the stuff together, but not as much as we used to”.                “Great” I replied trying to sound cheerful and trying to smile but I knew that Angela would’ve known that I was still a bit disappointed. Everything settled down and the evening came, James my boy friend called up. We’ve been going out for eight months.                “Kylie” he asked.                “James” I replied                “How are you?” he asked.                “I’m good thank you, how are you?”                 “Oh I’m okay, listen I was wondering if you want to go out for a drink of coke or something at McDonald’s” he asked.                “Sure” I replied “Meet you at the end of the street in ten minutes”.                “See you then” he said and hung up.                I took out my jumper because it was a bit windy and I didn’t want to catch a cold. It was about five in the evening and it was already turning a bit dark.                “Mum, dad” I called out “I’m going down to McDonald’s with James now”.                “What time will you return?” I could hear mum ask..        “In an hour or so” I replied.                Immediately Jessica came down to me and asked “Can you bring me a cheese burger and some chips?”                “Jessica” I replied “I’m going out with a boy and he’s paying; what do you want me to ask? ‘Can you buy my little sister a burger?’ I don’t think so”.                “Here’s the money Kylie” Angela said appearing on the scene “You needn’t ask him for the money, you can get a burger for your sister yourself”.                “But…” I tried to speak but I couldn’t think of anything to say.                “But what? She asked.                “Okay” I replied and taking the money from her “Spoilt brat” I muttered under my breath.                “I heard that” Jessica said “Angela, did you hear that?”                 “Yes, I did” Angela replied “And I’m a bit worried about Kylie’s behaviour”.                “My behaviour” I asked “I don’t think there’s anything wrong with my behaviour or even if there is, it wouldn’t be happening if this little brat wants everything she sees”.                “Kylie stop that nonsense” Angela said in a tone that really she meant what she said “She’s your sister and what’s wrong with her asking for something?”                “Everything” I replied “I can’t go out with some of my friends and there she is asking for something or worrying to come”.                “Your so annoying Jess” I said with a change in my tonality.                “Get going will you” Angela said looking at me and then turning to Jessica she said “Jess, let’s play monopoly now, can we?”                “She’s such a looser” I mutter to myself.         “Stop that now, Kylie, will you?” Angela said.                I just walked out of the house and kept thinking all the way how Angela spoke to me and I realised that I felt really hurt and I started crying but as I came close to McDonald’s I wiped my tears away and when I saw James I tried my best to smile but he knew at once that something was wrong and gave me a hug as soon as I came. I went closer to him then he kissed me.                “What’s wrong?” he asked.                “Nothing” I replied “nothing at all”.                “Really?” he asked “Then why is   your face tearstained   and your eyes all red”.                “I just had a little fight” I replied trying not to start crying.                “With whom?” he asked.                “Can we not talk about this?” I asked.                “Fine” he replied “That’s okay”.                Just then I noticed how hurt he felt and I didn’t want to fight with every one today. “Jamie, I’m sorry” I started “I didn’t mean to hurt you or anything and actually I do   need someone to talk to right now”.                “That’s okay Kylie” he replied “You can talk to me anytime you want okay” and taking my hand we went inside.                 we got our stuff and we sat down.                “What’s wrong” he started.                “My cousin Angela has come down from     Melbourne     and she has a boy friend” I said.                “What’s wrong with that?” James asked.                “Nothing’s wrong with that but now we had a fight and guess whose side she took” I asked.                “Jess’s” he asked.                “Yes, can’t believe she above all people, we used to be best friends and now it seems so different” I said trying to eat the burger that I had in my hand.                “Why, what did you do?” James asked as he was sipping on his coke.                 “It’s a silly thing, um… Jess wanted me to get her a burger and I said that I was going out and I can’t but as soon as I said I can’t Angela came on the scene and handing over the money to me she said that I had to and then when I called Jess a brat she … she..” I couldn’t say anything more because I was choked.                Slowly James took my hand and spoke slowly “Oh!! Don’t worry Kylie, it’s such a small thing Angela will probably forget about it by the time your home.                “She probably will” I said but I wished I could really believe that. We finished our snack and I got Jessica a burger with some French fries and I started on my way home.                 When I arrived Jessica came running to me “So you did get it, thanks” she said and snatched the stuff out of my hand.                 “How was your date?” Angela asked as she came into the living room.                “Not too bad” I replied “At least I had some peace of mind which I don’t seem to be getting here”.                “You know, even I get peace of mind when I’m out with Ken, it feels great doesn’t it?” she asked as if nothing had happened. But I was hurt, terribly hurt and I wasn’t just going to let this drift by.                 “Yeah, whatever” I replied and started walking out of the living room.                “What’s her problem?”   I heard Jessica’s voice.                “Probably a bad date” Angela replied and both of them giggled. I felt my cheeks go red and I started crying. I can’t believe Angela’s changed so much.                 This Ken guy must have done something to her because this is not the Angela I know. That night after dinner I went up to my room and took out a magazine to read, it was a Girlfriend magazine. As I was reading someone knocked on my door “Who is it?” I asked.   “Kylie, it’s me Angela”.                “Come in” I replied.        Angela came into the room and plonked herself on my bed “So” she began “Was there any problem?”                “Problem?” I asked feeling a bit edgy.                 “Yes” she said “With your date with James”.                “One, it was not a date, two, there was no problem, the only problem I have is having a younger sister” I replied.                “Kylie, c’mon your sister is not all that bad, you should be proud of her she’s such a talented girl, did she tell you about that math...” Angela started.                But I cut her short “Angela, I know my sister’s a genius and I know that I’m a… what do you say … a dummy but you don’t have to keep telling me that”.                “Who said you’re dumb, I just…” she began again but once again I cut her short “Well, how come you have time for me any ways, shouldn’t you be spending time with Jessica?”                “Kylie, you are acting like nothing but a spoilt little brat which you’re normally not but at the end of the day it’s left up to you” she said “I just came here to tell you that I’m going back on Monday and I’ll be back here next week”.                “But we haven’t spent any time together” I started but she was already walking out of my room “Sorry, but I guess it’s your fault”.                My fault, how can it be my fault, it cannot be my fault, what did I do. All these problems started only because of Jessica.                “Jessica” I shouted as I stormed into her bedroom only to find Angela sitting there and talking to her so as usual I stopped.                “Yes” Kylie said in a sarcastic tone because Angela was there.                “I was wondering if you saw my pen” I said in a nervous tone.                “No” I didn’t she replied.                “Kylie, do you want to play monopoly with us” Angela asked.                Something told me that I had to play; besides monopoly was one of my favourite games. “Yeah!! Okay” I said at last.                Angela smiled at me and then she looked at Jess and said “Jess, you said you had some studying to do for that great math quiz, I think you should study now, I want to spend some time with Kylie”.                I immediately knew that Angela wanted to talk to me in private. “Kylie, do you mind if I use your room for a while” Jessica asked.                “Go ahead, so long as you don’t steal anything” I replied sarcastically.                Jessica left and I was just looking around her room. Her room is always neat and tidy and certificates stuck all over the walls. “Look at all this” I said looking at Angela “She’s so smart”.                “Come sit over here” Angela said motioning me to Jessica’s bed “Everyone’s smart”.                I let out a sarcastic laugh and said “I wish I were like her, getting so many things and having mum and dad say such good things about me” then I stopped “I can’t believe I’m saying all of this, now I can be officially called not only a dummy but a jealous sister”.                “Kylie” Angela started “Every one gets jealous at some time, and everyone is good at something”.                “How come I’m not good at anything” I asked.                “You are good at something, it takes time for some people to learn what their talents are” Angela said “Even Jessica’s a bit jealous of you”.                “Of me?” I asked “But she’s the clever one, what do I have for her to get jealous of me?”                “Well, look you may not be extremely studious or anything but look at how many friends you have, look how social you are?” Angela said “Because she’s so good at everything it’s so hard on her when examinations are close, like, if she fails then your parents would be disappointed but if you do they are always there encouraging you to do better and besides your parents know your capability so don’t worry”.                Angela does give such good advice and it’s hard not to believe it. Then the moment she mentioned friends I became sad, I think she knew that so again she said “You’re thinking about your friends aren’t you?”                “Yes” I replied “I’m going to miss them so much and I’m going to miss James”.                “I know how it feels” she said “I felt the same way when I left year-12, it was so hard but after a while I went to college and I met new friends, then when I had to leave college again I had to leave those friends and I made new friends at work and now I left those friends and I’m going to make new friends at my new work spot”.                “But aren’t you scared you’ll loose your friends?” I asked, the thought of my friends leaving me flashing before me.                “If it’s true friendship, trust me it’ll be there forever” she said “I know it’s hard but life is always like that, meeting friends then leaving them and then making new friends it’s like a…. a….. Cycle”.                “True” I said thinking hard about that “What about James? You know he’ll be in a different high school and I won’t know what’s going on, if he’s meeting any other girls and... What if he gets a new girlfriend?”                “Kylie, you’re still in primary school and you’re only thirteen, if he finds a new girlfriend, well then…. May be you’ll find someone else later, after all there are many fish in the sea”.                I was asking her about boys not fish, can’t she speak so that I can understand “What fish?” I asked.                “Well it’s a grammatical phrase that there are so many there boys out there and you got so many years to go, or if you want this relationship to work out, then you got to trust him and he’s got to trust you” she replied.                Then it seemed clearer to me. “I hope it does work out” I said.                “May be it will, in the mean time don’t give your parents such a hard time just go to your new school and give it a shot” she said.                “Yeah!! I will” I said “And Angela sorry about the time I was um… rude to”.                “That’s okay” she said kindly “And do you think you should apologise to Jessica?”                “Should I” I asked thinking carefully.                “It’s up to you” she said “Oh and another thing, did you have a fight with James because I can make out that you had cried before”.                How can she make out, I didn’t want to tell her that her words hurt me, or should I tell her?                 “No, there was no problem at all” I said slightly stammering “I was just um… hurt a bit when you were taking Jess’s side”.                I looked at her in the eye and she said “Well when you’re in the right I’ll be on your side and when you’re in the wrong I’ll tell you straight away”.                Angela was always like that, she’ll tell you how she feels straight away “Yeah, okay” I replied and went out of the room and into my room.                “Hey Jess, how’s the math going?” I asked.                “Great, I just love maths, it’s so much fun” she replied.                Math fun, I hate math so much its sickens me to death and I’ll be lucky if I get a C.                “Great” I said going closer to her “Listen, about the burger thing, I’m really…”                But she cut me short “That’s okay, can you help me out here with this problem, I can’t seem to figure it out, I keep getting 26.2 instead of 24.2” she said pointing to a sum on her book which looked like Greek to me”.                But just then I looked at the problem a bit more in detail and read and re-read and I figured that I could figure it out “Look, I said you made a mistake you forgot to subtract 2 here” I said.                “Oh yes” she replied “How silly of me, anyways thanks a lot now I’ve got to go through chapter seven” and she went out of my room.                Now I had a perfect idea since it was Saturday tomorrow I thought that may be I could ask Angela to come with me to get my formal outfit. I immediately ran out of my room to Jess’s room “Angela” I said “Can you come with me tomorrow to get my formal outfit” I asked.                “Um…. I” she began and I knew it would be a no “I was thinking of taking Ken out for lunch”.                “Okay fine” I said a bit disappointed.                “I’ll tell you after I call Ken” she said.                “You don’t have to not go because of me” I said although I wished she could not go.                “I’ll tell you in a while” she said.                After a while she came into my room and said “I can’t break off my date with Ken”. That’s it I thought I’m never going to spend time with her.                “But” she said, I hate when people say but and they don’t come to the actual thing that I want to know “You and Jess can come along”.                “Cool!!” I said “Thank you” and I gave her a hug.                 The next day we went shopping and I had a tough decision on what to buy, I think it aggravated Ken a lot because he told us to keep shopping and he’ll meet us in the food court when we’re finished. First Angela thought that a red dress with silver roses would fit me nicely but then Jessica said that I should go with a pink dress, finally I settled down with a neon blue velvet dress which was plain. Both Angela and Jessica said it was too plain but I liked it so I got that dress. Then later we went down to the food court and had fish and chips. It was a lovely day on the whole and I was glad.                That week went off perfectly and it was really sad that Angela had to leave but she said she’ll try to come later. School also was going on perfectly. One day at school James, and all of my other friends were having lunch together “Kylie did you get your formal dress as yet?”   Alisha asked as she was eating her sandwich.                “Yes” I replied “I got Angela to help me out”.                “Can I come over and see it?” Cindy asked.                “Sure” I replied “In fact I have an idea”.                “What” everyone asked.                “Well” I replied “I don’t think we can include the boys on this plan”.                Immediately the boy’s faces went down because they always seemed to like what stuff we do (not that they are girly or anything).                “Who cares?” Alisha said.                “Hey” Ian her boyfriend said “We do”.                “Sorry guys” I said “But I was wondering, if we girls could all meet up at my place and dress up and look at ourselves”.                “Great” Petronella said.                “I…” Amelia started in a quavery voice.                “What’s wrong” Cindy asked.                “I… won’t be able to come” she blurted out and then looked at Mike’s (her boyfriend) face and he had a puzzled look on his face.                “Why” Mike asked still trying to figure out what was wrong.                “Because I” she began “It’s David’s first birthday and I’ve been saving up since forever and if I buy my dress I won’t be able to get him a little bed of his own”.                “Well” Alisha said “We can always put our cash in together can’t we?” she said looking at us.                “Sure” all of us chorused including all the boys.                “Thanks” she said “But I don’t think I can let you’ll”.                Just then Alison one of the girls in our class who always likes to pick on us came close to us and said “Well, look who doesn’t have money to get her own dress” she said.                “Well at least she’s got good friends to help her Alison” Alisha retorted, Alisha and Alison never got along with each other since kindergarten. Alison just let out a haughty sigh and left.                 “Amelia, we’re going to get you a dress no matter what” Cindy said and looked at us gesturing us to say something supportive so I began “Amelia, you have to get a new dress, this formal comes once in a life time and you just have to get a new dress”.                “Are you sure?” she asked us.                “Course we are” Petronella put in.                We kept chatting for a while “You know something I’ve always wanted to go to high school, I thought it’ll be cool but now I know I’m going to miss this school a lot” I said thinking hard about it.                “Yeah me too” Alisha said “And Stephanie said that the teachers in high school are not as easy going as they are in primary”.                “But” I said “They can’t be that bad, I’m going to miss all of you’ll so much though”.                Immediately Amelia who’s always the most sensitive in our group began to cry. “Please Amelia” Cindy said “you’re going to make us all cry now” and she couldn’t speak any more because she was choked.                “Not you too” Alisha said “now I’m going to…” and she too was wiping her eyes, one by one all of us started crying (excepting the boys).                “Look on the bright side” Ian started “We’re all going to be together…” then he stopped because obviously he forgot that I wasn’t going with them “Sorry Kylie” he said feeling a bit guilty.                “That’s okay” I replied and then I thought about me going into high school alone without knowing anyone and the more I thought about it the more I felt sad and depressed.                “Stop acting all mushy now” I said wiping away a tear “We’ll still be friends and we’ll still get to meet each other”.                “I only hope you’ll don’t forget me” I said again” and this time I meant it for all my friends but especially James. He must have figured that I meant it for him because he said “We won’t and if we do…” then he   paused “No; we won’t”.                Just then   the bell rang and we had to get to class, during the English period our teacher Mr. McKenzie said “I don’t think we’ll be having our normal lessons”. Immediately everyone started booing because normally when he says stuff like that it means that we’re having a test.                “Hold on a sec” he started again “We’re not having a test” then the class quietened down “I’m just going to talk to you’ll about leaving primary school, I know it’s going to be hard to leave primary school and high school may be a little bit different from primary school, like now you’ll have to stay in one class but in high school you have to move around from one class to another each period”.                That’s all that I heard because I was sad   and miserable and worst off all I was scared. James was sitting across the room and flashed me a smile (a sympathetic smile) and I managed a weak smile. Finally class was over and I walked to the front gate because mum said that she’ll pick up Jessica and myself after school.                 “Hey Kylie” Jessica said.                “Hey” I replied.                “Kylie, you know the math quiz I was preparing for” she began and I kept telling myself not to get jealous because I knew that she would have got a high mark.                “Yeah, what about it?” I asked.                “I got a 100%” she replied.                “That’s great” I said “Guess all that studying paid off”.                “Are you okay?” she asked.                “Yeah, course I am”                “Your sad aren’t you” she enquired even more eagerly.                “Sad? Me? No way” I replied.                “It’ll be okay” she said “You’re only going there because it may be more fun there”.                “Thanks” I said “Mum’s here” and both of us ran towards the car and mum did enquire about my day but I just said “It was okay”. The rest of the drive was all about Jess but I didn’t worry because my thoughts were only revolving around my friends and James.                The next day my friends were coming over and I tidied my room and bought heaps of snacks; usually I’d go to Jessica and tell her in a loud voice not to come near my room but this time I went over to her room and knocked on her door “come in” she said.                “Hi Jessica” I said.                “Jessica I um... came over to ask you if you could give my friends and us some privacy because..” she cut me short “Don’t worry I won’t” she said.                Just then I remembered what Angela had said about Jessica getting jealous of me having so many friends “Jess you know what? Actually I do want you to come and join us”.                “Really” she asked with a brightened expression on her face “You don’t mind”.                “Yes, come but can you come after a while not right now?”                “Thank you” she exclaimed and came over and gave me a hug, Jessica and I don’t hug that much and it rarely happens.                After a while my friends arrived and we were   talking and chatting and I informed my friends that Jessica would be coming and they were actually cool with it (much to my surprise). Jessica came in and she was having a lovely time with my friends and we tried on our dresses and it was simply splendid.                The week drifted by very quickly and the last day of school was really sad, most of the kids were crying and I couldn’t stop myself from crying all day. James kept on saying stuff like “It’ll be alright” and “I’ll still be your best friend” and it made me sadder when he hugged me.                 I made it a point to speak to all my teachers (even the ones I disliked). Most of the teachers gave me good advice and told me that they’ll never forget me (As if they wouldn’t?)                The evening of our formal came. I was busy getting ready with Jessica helping me out. I brushed my black hair and tossed it across my shoulders then I put on some jewellery and last of all the make up but I think I overdone the   make up part because when I arrived at the school gym James kept staring at me in awe. He looked really cute in his tuxedo. “What’s wrong?” I asked.                “Nothing” he replied still staring at me “You… um… look”.                “Scary” I helped him out.                “Yes” he said “Can you go and chip some of it off”.                “Okay” I said and took out a tissue and looking at a mirror in the hall way I took off everything.                “Is that better?” I asked standing in front of James.                “Much better angel” he replied.                 Angel, he called me an angel I could’ve fainted right there but I knew I mustn’t be giddy headed and I must act mature so I just said thank you. As soon as I went inside I spotted Cindy and Alisha standing in a corner and perving over some of the guys (who were not their boy friends).                 “Alisha, Cindy” I squealed and went over to them they looked so beautiful in their outfits “You’ll look so beautiful” I told them. “Look at you” Cindy said. “You look great yourself” Alisha put in. Alisha had this beautiful green dress which was strapless and Cindy had on a black dress which was short sleeved dress with sequence all over it and she had her hair left loose which she kept tossing over her shoulders all the time. My neon blue outfit looked a bit plain comparing to theirs because my outfit was plain and it was a long dress but I liked it.   The best thing was that we looked even better then than we had the other night.                “Is Amelia and Petronella here as yet?” I asked.                “There they are” Alisha said pointing; when I turned around I could see Petronella and Amelia walking towards us chatting and giggling on their way. Petronella had her brownish black hair tied up a bun and a huge clip keeping it up and her peach coloured dress threw out perfectly on her. Amelia looked good too except that she was the only one who wasn’t wearing make up (She hates make up) but her lime coloured tight fitting dress suited her nicely (we managed to get her a dress at last).                 “You’ll look fantastic” I said as they came closer. “Thanks” both of them said “But I think we spoilt the surprise by rehearsing it beforehand” Amelia said. “I think so too” Petronella said.                “Thanks you guys” I said sarcastically “After all it was my idea”.                “Stop it” Alisha said “We’re only playing around. Amelia suddenly looked a bit sad “What’s wrong Amelia?” Cindy asked. “I was just wondering if we’d be friends forever or will this end when we go to high school”. “Off course it won’t” I said “We’re friends from little and we can’t just forget about each other or can we?”                 “I’m going to miss you” Cindy said looking at me “We’ve always been in the same class Kylie and now we won’t”. She looked so gloomy and very soon I knew that she’ll start bawling her eyes out “Come on you guys” I said “We’re going to be friends forever and ever, now we have this last party…” and I couldn’t continue because I was choked then I tried my best not to cry and thank god I succeeded “Let’s not cry now” I said “Amelia, stop crying and you too Cindy, Petronella not you too, Alisha please, come on don’t you’ll want me to enjoy my last party?”                At last all of them stopped crying, the music started Mr. Tinter our school principal started speaking “Good evening everyone” he began “It’s nice to see all your bright and happy faces and I must tell you that Canley is going to miss all those happy faces” he kept speaking and James came over from across the room and stood next to me with his arm around me and we began listening to Mr. Tinter speak “You’ll have been excellent students even though a bit naughty at times, and I won’t keep you’ll long from enjoying yourselves but I just like to get one message across, I hope that you’ll have had a lovely time Canley, and I hope you’ll learnt something from this school and I hope you’ll carry on this good reputation with you’ll wherever you’ll go, thank you”. Then he stepped down and every one applauded (one reason may be because he gave a short speech).                 The music began again and it was a fast number so all of my friends along with the boys got into a circle and began dancing. The dancing was CRAZY, after a while everyone began leaving the dance floor to get some rest; we left the dance floor to get some drinks. After some rest the D.J stopped the music, “Kylie Rodriguez, this song is dedicated for you from Alisha, Petronella, Cindy, Amelia, Ian, Calvin, Mike and your best friend of all- James, its called ‘Friends Forever’”. It was a slow number and James came closer to me and whispered in my ear “Wanna dance?”                “Sure” I replied still wonder struck, then I turned around towards my friends and they were all smiling at me suddenly I couldn’t see them anymore because my eyes were probably gleaming with tears both mixed with happiness and sadness. The song was simply beautiful; the chorus went some what like this         As we go on, we’ll remember all good times we had together        And as our lives change, come whatever        We will still be Friends Forever.                   “I’m going to miss you” James said looking me in the eye “You’ll probably find really some good looking guy”.                “James, stop that” I retorted “You know I won’t do that, and besides don’t you trust me?”                “I don’t want you to go” he replied “I know we’re young and as the adults say it’s just puppy love but I don’t think it’s just puppy love, it’s real love and I can feel it perfectly well” he paused for a moment and then went on “I love you Kylie”. I couldn’t resist crying I couldn’t believe this was happening to me.                 Finally when the party ended mum drove me back home, most of the way it was silent then I decided to break the silence “Mum” I began “Isn’t there any way I could go to the same school as my friends?”                “I know it’s hard Kylie but eventually you will have to leave your friends and trust me in no time you’ll make new friends” she replied.                “But I’m going to miss them, I just can’t it’s too difficult” I replied.                “I know doll” mum replied “But don’t worry, it will be better”.        “Why exactly am I going to this school mum?”                 “Because it’s a school that’s perfect for you”                We arrived home and ha dinner, with that I went to bed. That’s it I thought as I was lying in bed; no more Canley Heights Primary School, and I still didn’t know why I was being sent to Canterbury High.   The Holidays went by rather quickly, it was the last weekend.                The next morning was a Saturday and I slept in, I only woke up with the sun shinning directly in my face. I had a wash and went to have breakfast, just as I began the phone rang “I’ll get it” Jessica said and made her move towards the phone. “Let it go on the answering machine Jess” Dad said. Dad doesn’t like us to do stuff when it comes to meal time. “Okay” she replied and sat down again. The phone rang a couple of times more and the answering machine started “Hello, no one is available to take your call, please leave your message after the beep” Beep!! The phone went and then a familiar voice started “Hey Kylie, Alisha here, I guess your still sleeping anyways give me a call when you wake up, catch ya later bye”.   During that little message I looked at dad wondering if he’ll allow me to answer it then, he just glared at me and went back to his meal.                After our breakfast, Jessica and I done the dishes and I got to the phone, I dialled Alisha’s number and Stephanie (Alisha’s elder sister) answered “Hello” she said.                “Um... Steph?   I asked.                “Yeah, Kylie” she said immediately recognising my voice “Hold on a sec, I’ll get Alisha for you” then she kept the receiver down but I could still hear her shout out “Alisha, phone call for you”.                After a while Alisha answered “Hello Kylie” she began “got my message?”                “Yes I did” I replied “what’s wrong?”                “Oh!! Nothing” she replied “I was just wondering how you’re feeling”.                “Thanks, but I think I’m okay” I replied.                “Okay” she replied “I was wondering if you’d be able to come over to my place tonight”.                “Tonight” I asked “What’s happening?”                “Oh!! I’m just having a sleepover, just us girls” she answered.                “Sleep over” I said “Cool, but I have to ask mum”.                We chatted for a few more minutes and then I went over to mum and asked her, she said okay, then as I was getting ready Jessica came to my room “Kylie, where are you off to?” she asked. “Just for a sleepover at Alisha’s house” I replied. “Oh!!” she said “great, have fun”.                “Jess” I said “I really wish I could take you but…”                “That’s okay” she said “I have my books and I have the tele.”.                “Listen” I began “Can we do something fun next weekend, you know after going to a dumb school it will be fun”.                “Sure” she said brightening up a bit “It will be fun, but I wish I had friends though, and then it would be fun”.                “Come here Jess” I said and gave   her a little squeeze “I   know how it feels not to have friends because I’m going to miss all of them when I leave but just try to talk more act friendlier and most of all loose that frown of yours and show off that beautiful smile you have”.                “Do you really think someone will want to be my friend?” she asked looking so pitiable.                “Sure they will” I answered “Just be yourself, it’ll work out”.                “Thanks, Kylie” she replied “I’m glad you’re my friend” and then she went out of my room looking a bit better.                That evening mum drove me over to Alisha’s place, I was dressed in my pyjamas which had teddy bears all over it, I rang the door bell and Alisha answered it “Hello, come on in” she said opening the door wider. “Thanks” I said admiring her pyjama suit; it had little red hearts all over it         It looked beautiful; when I went inside I saw everyone else there “Hey you guys” I said.                “Hello” everyone chorused and I knew that something was going on “What’s going on?” I asked.                “Nothing” Amelia said, “Nothing really” Petronella backed her up. “Okay, if you guys say so” I said.                “Let’s go up to my room” Alisha said “we can pick out the videos to watch tonight”. The others and I went upstairs with our sleeping bags slung across our shoulders. Then as soon as I entered Alisha’s room “Ta da” all for of them shouted out together, when I looked around Alisha’s room it was filled with stickers and posters which said “Kylie, you’re the best and we’re still your friends and you rock”. “Thanks you guys” I said “You’ll do have to do all this I mean...”. “Yeah, whatever” Cindy said. “As if you don’t appreciate it” Petronella said. “Don’t make a big fuss over this” Amelia put in. “Look what I have” Alisha said holding a video camera in her hand “Say hello everyone” she continued “I’m taping this out”. “Alisha” I shouted “How can we possibly be ourselves when we’re being taped out the whole time”.                 “Why not?” she asked “I’m just going to keep this down   here and let’s party, that way we’ll have our last primary school party on tape”.                “Okay” I gave in “But can you just put that thing down and come and join us”.                “Memories dear child” Alisha said in a sarcastic tone “We’ll have lots of memories”. We cracked up at this joke and began our party, there was tons of food to eat and we played lots of games but I think we chatted a lot most of all and I had lots of fun. “I’m really going to miss you’ll” I said. “C’mon Kylie, it’s going to be just the same, the only difference is that you won’t be in the same school” Cindy said. “Yeah, it’s not like we’re going to discard you or anything” Amelia said. “Yes, remember we’re going to be friends for ever and ever” Petronella said. “Okay, now stop getting mushy all of you” Alisha said knowing that we were on the verge of crying “Ten years from now we’re going look at his video and laugh at ourselves”. “I forgot we’re on video” I said. Petronella looked directly into the camera and said “If anyone besides the five of us sees this video ten years later may be our kids or something, this is what we were when we were leaving primary school”   the rest of us just giggled.                 After a while we settled down to watch a movie- The Titanic the most romantic movie I’ve seen. Then we watched Cheaper By The Dozen a comedy movie, which was fun. It was around four in the morning that we were sleepy and went to bed after a pillow fight. We woke up at    twelve noon    and we were still sleepy, we heard footsteps and then Mrs.Graham knocked on the door “Girls time to wake up” she said in her rather shrill voice. “Not now mum” Alisha called back “it’s our last day to sleep in”. “Okay girls just another half hour, because Kylie and Petronella your folks will be here soon to pick you’ll up and Cindy, Kylie’s mum will be picking you up, so hurry up”. After that we couldn’t go back to sleep, we were just rolling around “Girls” I said in a rather lethargic tone “Thanks a lot for all this”.                “That’s no problem” Alisha said, “Yeah no problem at all” Cindy said, “I hope we do this more often” Petronella said. “Not always at Alisha’s place, it’s not fair that way” Amelia put in “We should have sleepovers at each other’s places as well”. “Sure we should” I responded “I’ll just love to have you guys over because you’ll are just great”.                We had our brunch (which was breakfast and lunch together), at the table Alisha said “So, Kylie are you ready for school tomorrow?” “Yes, I guess so” I replied “I may be ready with all the stuff like books, but not ready to face the kids and the new school there”. “Are you scared?” Stephanie asked as she entered the room. It may look as if Stephanie is a bit nosey but we like her to join in sometimes in conversations. “A little bit” I replied then I thought for a moment “Okay a lot” I admitted. “Oh!! Poor thing” she said sympathizing “It must be hard for you”. “Well it’s like we’re starting kindergarten again” Alisha said “We’re going to be the youngest again”. “Yes, I know it’s hard, but look on the bright side there will be more hot guys to perve on, high school guys are hot!!” Stephanie said “Wait a minute not just hot they are cute and…” “Yes Steph but we already have boyfriends” Petronella said. “Oh!! Yeah, but trust me you’ll will find tons of other guys when you’ll go to high school”.                 That made me think of James again “What about these guys, we’ve been going out since forever” I put in “Surely we’re not going to just dump them”. “Look, I don’t mean that, that will definitely happen, I’m saying that sort of thing mostly happens” she replied. “Well, if that sort of thing happens” I started “I don’t think it will”. “All the best though” Steph said as she was walking out “And remember just be yourselves when you’ll go to High School”. “Thanks” all of said.                Later mum came over and picked up Cindy and myself. I went home and started getting ready for school next day. I kept praying that the day should go by slowly but it didn’t, it just glided by quickly.                 The next morning I got up, had my shower and since I didn’t get the uniform as yet, I took out my black long sleeved turtle neck top and a pair of jeans, then I combed my hair back and held it up with a clip, I put on a little bit of blush, a tint of lip gloss and I was all ready.                 Since it was my first day mum said she’ll come along with me. “Have fun Kylie” Jessica called as I was getting ready to leave. “Thanks, you too” I replied hurrying up. I can’t believe the holidays went by so quickly, but thank God it all ended up with a party at Alisha’s place. I was all ready to leave and so was mum, we got in to the car and it was a 45 minute drive. When we arrived there, mum jumped out and we went to the front office. Let me describe the school first, the walls were all covered in blue and yellow paint (it didn’t look very welcoming). There were kids all over the place, at one end I saw a girl and a boy making out, wait a minute I can’t   call these people kids, they’re people. “Hello” mum said when we reached the office; the walls there were covered with year photos. A plump lady was there and smiled at us as mum was speaking “Hello” she replied “What can I do to help you?” “Um… this is my daughter Kylie and she’s new to this school, all the form details were already filled up the other day” my mum replied. “Kylie, Kylie” the woman replied as she was going through a few papers “Here we go, Kylie Rodriguez, You’re here to join Year 7” then she looked at me and smiled. “Yes” I replied in a very small voice. “Here you go love” she said handing me a piece of green paper “This is your timetable; I hope you find your way around here, the classes are all labelled so I don’t think you’ll get lost”.   “Thanks” I replied. “If you’re going to join in today, there’s no use in family waiting with you” she said. “No, I just came to drop her off” mum replied “I’ll be heading off to work hon.”                   Mum gave me a kiss goodbye “Don’t worry doll, you’ll be alright, I’ll come and pick you up at three okay” she said and gave me a hug.   After mum left I felt like crying I was nervous, I felt as if I was starting kindergarten again. The place looked so big and frightful.                 The bell rang and I looked at my time table it said 7M3 (Maths) A9. A9!! I didn’t even know which block I was in, how am I supposed to find my class, just then I saw a teacher and I went up to her “Excuse me” I started “I can’t seem to find my class, can you please help me?”   “Sure” she said then looking at my time table she told me to go straight and then upstairs and that I would find my class upstairs. I thanked her and thanked   God that I’d   found my class. I entered my class room and I looked around, there was not a familiar face to be seen, every one was sitting with someone. There was a spare seat right up the front and I had no other go but to sit there.                   I could not concentrate on anything in class and during lunch I had to sit all alone, it was like hell. When mum came to pick me up I tried my best to act as if school was so great but on the whole speak I was so angry with her for not letting me choose the school I wanted. I couldn’t wait to come back home and as soon as I arrived home I went straight to my room and lay down and cried and cried, till I could cry no more. I stopped crying when someone knocked on my door “Who is it?” I asked wiping my face. “Kylie, it’s me” Jessica said “There’s a phone call for you”. “Come in” I answered, after she handed me our cordless phone I thanked her and answered the phone “Hello” I said “Kylie” Cindy squeaked “How are you?” she asked. “I’m good” I said trying to sound as cheerful as possible. “That’s good” she said “We had the best day at high school; we had problems finding our classes, but guess what?” “What?” I asked still feeling so sad and miserable. “We have to move around every period but we’re all in the same class, isn’t that great?” she said. “That’s really cool” I replied and at that moment I started crying. “Kylie?”   Cindy asked “Are you okay?” “I’m fine” I replied still crying, then I felt something a feeling, is Cindy doing this just to make me jealous, how could she? “Cindy” I almost shouted “I know you had a great day and everything, but you don’t have to make me jealous”. “Kylie, I thought you’d be happy for me” Cindy said “I didn’t mean to ma…”. “Yeah!! Whatever” I cut her short and I slammed the phone down. At that very moment I wished I never even said that, after all I should’ve been happy for my friends, not jealous. Since it was the first day we didn’t get any home work.                 While we were having dinner, dad and mum kept asking me stuff about school and I tried my best to tell them that I had the perfect first day. After dinner I went to bed. The next day I got up with the intention of making new friends and to try and be more social.                “Hello” I said to a girl who was sitting next to me during my math class. She looked really pretty with her dark eyes and brown hair “Hi!!” she said. This is it I thought, the beginning of a new friendship, a little while later another girl came and looked at me, looked right into my eyes which made me scared, this girl was skinny and tall with blue eyes “Excuse me” she started “ But I think you’re sitting in my place”. “Well, I didn’t….” and I stopped because she started speaking again “I don’t want to know what the explanation is, just get your butt off the seat and move” she said in a really unkind tone. I looked at the girl who was beside me and she looked back and mouthed “Move”. I was surprised, what was wrong with these people here. I just gave both of them a weird look and moved to the front row and sat down there.                 The whole day I tried to make more friends, I tried to talk more but some how I couldn’t find any one to be my friend. That week past by rather quickly, at the end of the week as Alisha and everyone else planned went out together. We went down to a new fast food place near my house. Of course the boys were there too. James greeted me with a tight hug “Hello” he said as soon as I arrived “Sorry about not calling you before, I was um… um…” “Busy” I helped him out, I was a bit mad at him though for not calling me. “I’m really sorry Kylie” he said. “That’s cool” I replied “After all we’re in high school now”. “I missed you a lot Kylie, how was high school for you?” he said. I just let out a sarcastic laugh “School, was just perfect, except the fact that I hadn’t made any friends at all in school and I miss you’ll like crazy”   I replied. “Sorry to hear that” he said with a sympathetic look in his eyes “I didn’t mean to make you feel sorry”. “I know” I said “I can’t believe that I miss you’ll so much”.                “Did you find yourself a new girlfriend?” I asked sarcastically. “Yeah heaps of them” he replied “How about you? Did you find a nice new boyfriend for yourself?” “Not really” I replied.                 That day went off perfectly, I apologised to my pals and they gave me the confidence that they’ll always be there for me and I’m glad. The only thing left for me to do was make more friends. The sleep over went off brilliantly too.                 It was Monday morning and I got dressed for school and I caught the bus. As soon as I entered I saw one of my class mates there, seeing that there was a chance for me to make a conversation I went close to her and asked cautiously “Is this seat taken?” “No not really” she said looking at me directly and a smile appeared when I sat down next to her “Thanks” I replied. “That’s okay” she said.                 We travelled for a while and then she asked me “Who do you hang around with at school?” “Um…” I began wondering what reply to give her, should I tell her that I have not yet made friends, how can I tell her the truth then after a few seconds I replied “No one really, I have no friends at school because I’m new”. “Oh” she said with a funny look in her eyes, she hesitated to say something then she finally spoke clearly “You can hang around with my friends and myself at school”.                I felt so much better that someone had asked me to join their group. “Thanks” I said “Are you sure you’re friends won’t mind?” I asked again. “I’m not a 100% sure, but I can always ask” she replied casually. “Cool” I said and we kept chatting about all sort of stuff, I told her how I hated to leave my friends and join this new school and she told me how she had a brother and a baby sister. It felt so nice to have someone to talk to and I was glad.                School went on as usual and I met all the other girls, there was Kimberly who seemed to be the boss of the group and there was Helen, Amanda, Lena and there were a few guys around, one of them looked so elegant and smart and so charming but very quickly I corrected myself and told my self that James was there. To be precise school went on perfectly that week and when I told my parents and Jessica about how I’m enjoying school they were so happy. Jessica and I hung around more often together. We spent so much time together, we went to the movies, to the mall and this time I actually enjoyed myself.                 At school, I made lots of other friends and it was just perfect.                “Hello you” I heard a familiar voice when I picked up the phone. It was after school and I rushed home as soon as I could because I wanted to go on the internet fast so I could chat to my friends online but as soon as I came I heard the phone ring. “James?” I asked. He laughed a little “want to come down to my place to watch a video because I’m babysitting Emily and since this is the first time I’m babysitting, a little help would be greatly appreciated”. “Right now?” I asked hoping he’d say no. “Yeah” he said “But if you...” he started off again. “I’ll come” I said “It’ll give us some time to chat”.         “Great, thanks Kylie”        “That’s k, I’ll be right over”.                I had a quick shower, wrote a not to mum         MUM, JUST GOING OUT TO JAMES’S, WILL BE BACK IN AN HOUR OR SO        KYLIE.                Then I told Jessica that I’ll be out and I headed off to James’s. “Hi” he greeted me. “Hi” I replied. It really seemed like he was having a tough time with his little sister, he was carrying her and he looked completely tired. “Looks like your having a really tough time now” I said. “Yeah” he replied, just then Emily started crying. “May I?” I asked James stretching out my hands out to carry Emily. “With Pleasure” he said.                 I actually got on very well with Emily, but I didn’t t do anything extraordinary, I just did normal stuff (Baby stuff).   After a while Emily was napping and James and I were having a banana split that was readymade. “Kylie” James began and he had a serious expression on his face “You know… how you and I are… going out and stuff, I think…we have to, you know…” I could see that he was trying hard to bring out the right words. “Break up?” I helped him out.                 “Yeah” he said “it’s so hard like not to notice other girls at school” he said.   I tried to manufacture a smile but I guess I didn’t succeed. “Kylie, you’re a really good friend and you are really the best girlfriend ever, but that’s why I don’t want to hurt your feelings” James said.                 “I know” I said “I face the same problem when I’m at school”.         “Really”?                   “Yeah” I replied “But we still can be good friends, can’t we?”                “Of course” he said “So?”                “So that’s it then” I replied “My first break up with my first boyfriend”. After that I felt Goosebumps on my skin and my eyes become heavy with tears and before I could stop myself I started crying and the best thing was I didn’t know why.                 “I’m sorry Kylie, I didn’t mean to hurt you” James said.                 “Its okay” I replied wiping my eyes and trying to stop myself from crying “I didn’t think I’ll take it so badly”.                 He leaned over and gave me a hug, I looked up at him and he managed a small smile   “I better get going” I said “It’s getting late”.                 “Okay” he said “I’m sorry about that…. Its just that I don’t want to cause you to get hurt”.                “I understand” I replied “sorry if I made such a great deal out of it”.                “Thanks for helping me out with Emily” James said.                 “That’s okay”.                I put on my jumper and went out doors. It was a bit chill out side or may be it was only me feeling chill. “Kylie” I heard a voice, I turned around it was James “Yeah” I said.                 “Friends Forever?” he asked.                “No” I replied “Friends now and forever”.                He smiled and I smiled back.                         I went back to my house and into my bed room. I took up a book and started reading. Someone knocked on my door.         “Come in”                “Hai Kylie” Jessica said coming in.                “Hi, how was school?” I asked.                “Good and you? She asked.                 “Excellent” I replied.                “Really?” she asked “Because you look really sad”.                “Do I?” I asked “There’s nothing really wrong”.                “If you don’t want to tell me that’s fine, Kylie” She said.                “Okay I’ll tell you after all you’re my sister” I said “I just broke up with James”.                “Aw! I’m sorry” Jessica said “How come?”                “It’s because now that we’re in high school things become so different, there are plenty of other girls and boys that we’d prefer someone else” I said.                “But aren’t you sad?” Jessica asked.                “A bit, yes” I replied “but every thing happens for a reason”.                “Kylie?” Jessica asked “You know the time we spent together?”                “Yeah”                “I had the best time of my life” she said .                “I’m glad to hear that Jess” I said “That’s really good, and we can do more stuff together later “.                She came over and gave me a hug, I hardly ever hug my sister and this was something unusual. Jessica probably did have the best time of her life.         “Kylie, there’s a phone call for you” I could hear mum call. “Commin” I shouted back. I ran down as fast as I could.                 “Hey Kylie”         I immediately recognised that voice; it was Angela’s “Angela!!”   I said.                “Hey Kylie, I got your e-mail just today” Angela said “Look I’m sorry if your school isn’t the best now”.                “No Angela” I said “It’s just perfect now, I’ve made a few friends and it’s really great I love it”.                “Oh, that’s great then” Angela said “I’m glad to hear that and I hope you make more friends”.                 “Angela, how’s Ken?”                 “He’s alright, how’s James?”                “James and I um… are not going out anymore, we broke up” I said.                “I’m sorry” Angela said.                “Well, don’t be” I said.                “Well aren’t you feeling sad?” Angela asked.                “At first I was, but he finds it difficult not to notice other girls and I guess that’s a good enough reason, so that means we don’t trust each other so much and trust is one of the basic necessities in a relationship and we don’t have it so… well I guess that’s it” I said and then took a breath after speaking such a lot.                “You speak as if you’re a grown up Kylie” Angela said and she laughed.                I didn’t know whether to laugh or not so I just said okay. I chatted to her for a while more and then I went up to bed.                I lay down and I looked up at the ceiling and thought to myself, “life is so funny at times and when you have a problem it feels as if it’s the end of the world but when life goes on just fine just the way you want it you feel as if you’re on the TOP OF THE WORLD” and that was just the way I was feeling at that moment- ON THE TOP OF THE WORLD.                The End                                                                                         High School is something that the girls always looked forward to but it isn’t what Kylie actually wanted. It’s time to move on and get into high school and Kylie’s parents want her to go to a different school from her friends.   She absolutely hates the very thought of it. She tries to explain to her parents that she cannot leave her friends or her boyfriend-James. She tries to explain things to her cousin-Angela but right now she feels that everyone is against her and everyone hates her but above all she gets jealous of Jessica- her sister. Jessica has always been so brilliant and clever and is good at ever so many things. Kylie’s world is turning upside down but when is everything going to come back to normal or will it ever come back to normal?   Will everything change when our five friends go to High School or will they still remain Friends Forever And Ever?                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                             
    
    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
               Once there was a little girl named Claire, she had everything she wanted in life, good home, good friends, and good education. But she always seemed to be discontented with herself. She was a girl of 13 with straight jet black hair, black eyes, lovely features but she always seemed to be complaining about her looks. Her parents and elders kept telling her that she looked fine but she never seemed happy like for instance just because she saw someone on TV with blonde hair, she wanted blonde hair.             One day as she was passing by a shop on her way home, from school, she was having a conversation with her friend Elizabeth " How I wish I had blue eyes instead of black eyes, at least then I would be beautiful” just then a busker (a person who entertains people on the street) who was playing a violin spoke out in a firm yet kind voice " At least you have eyes to see the world, never mind the colour ". When she turned towards this man she saw he was blind. Till today she is discontented with herself but at least now she tries to be contented with herself and every time she thinks of putting herself down or criticizing her self a picture of that poor man flashes in front of her.      
     

    
</post>
</Blog>