<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>22,March,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~  My Commandment  ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~    You'll keep your distance   Holding back tears   Inside you're dying   Murdered by fear  Though I have left you   Alone in the dust   Battered and broken   Unable to trust  ~    You'll keep your distance   Drowning in tears   I'll give my commandment:   Thou shall not heal  ~    The day burns down on you   Your eyes are red   You can't sleep at night   My scent fills your bed  Although you insist   On saving face   You're lonely and longing   Lost, out of place  ~    But you'll keep your distance   Drowning in your tears   I'll give my commandment:   Thou shall not heal  ~    You don't want to want me   You don't want to lie   Keep faking you smiles   Every time she walks by  You can't decide again   Between fallacy and truth   I know it hurts now   That I'm fine without you  ~    But maintain your resistance   Drowning in blood and tears   I've given my commandment:   Thou shall not heal~  Maintain futile resistance   Drowned in your blood and tears   I've given my commandment:   Thou shall not heal~     You'll never heal         ~fin~  
    
</post>
<date>16,March,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       ~~~~~~~~~  Number 45  ~~~~~~~~~    So you'll push me away   I'll wait behind the line   So you don't swing that way   Good luck living your lie   I wish you all the best of luck   With your new life, new friends, new guy   I can be happy now   Now you've told me why   But how dare you sayI'll soon forget   How dare you speak with such regret   I'm sorry I wasn't there enough   Sorry I can't be your best friend   I'm sorry that now you think   Our friendship has to end   I know that you warned me   But you have to know   It may take me a while   To learn to let go   If and when you want friendship   I'll be waiting for you here   Teaching myself how to let go   Learning not to feel tears   Only one more thing to say   With meaningful words and cheap, pointless rhymes   Forget about our romance   But remember our good times   Remember the fountain   And dancing in the rain   Remember the kisses   All the pleasure, the pain   Remember us burning   That book in the snow   Give me back your friendship   And I'll let you go.      ~fin~      
    
</post>
<date>17,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       ~~~~~~~~~~~  Reminiscence  ~~~~~~~~~~~    I miss you more than I want to   I miss you more than I should   I miss the way you held me   Until the morning came   I miss the way I used to hear   "I love you" everyday   I miss the way we used to act,   The people we made mad   I miss the way we used to talk   About the times we've had   I miss the way we used to kiss   The tender, playful bite   Imiss the way we said goodbye   The same way every night   There's nothing like being in your arms   The love, the comfortable security   And yet I know that in your heart   There's nothing left for me   So I turn on my blacklight   Wishing it were Christmas blue   And cry listening to the songs   Most reminiscent of you   But where I used to taste the love   The comfort for my fears   Lying here in bed alone   All I taste are tears.      ~fin~  
    
</post>
<date>14,September,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~   Mon Vampire Charmant   ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~      Sharp pain   Dull ache   Stainless steel and flesh   Brought together by an addiction   An ardeur that must be fed   A bloodlust that pushes   To the brink of insanity   And far beyond   Feel it flow   Feel my life   Flow from my veins   To your lips   Savor each drop you can manage   For it will soon be gone   You must not let them see   You must hide your weakness   For it is not brought by pain   Or damaging words   It continues now   Simply because   It always has been   And always will be   It fills the void   That emptiness inside   Left alone,   It will consume you from within   Dissolve your mind   Your heart, your soul   Until all that remains   Is your beautiful shell   And your bloodlust   It is all that drives you   And as your lips press softly   To my scarred and bleeding wrists   My soul is healed   And I have the love   Of mon vampire charmant   Once again, and always.      ~fin~  
    
</post>
<date>25,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       *Anniversary*    all She wanted  all She’d never known  She saw first from You  held her captive  love and hate  trapped, still waiting for You    kept her close  but freed her spirit  still captive, yet still free  keep her hate,  surrender love  it now belongs to Me    and on this day  that no one knows  today She thinks of You  hears my voice  returns to Me  gives herself to the Truth    but alas your Ring  yet still remains  my hope will not run thin  soon your ring  is replaced by mine  holding Her love within     ~fin~     ~~for My Baby Girl~~  
    
</post>
<date>11,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       ~~~~~~   Unclean    ~~~~~~   One night of lust  One night of sin  Don’t make me hate you  Give up, give in  Knew it meant nothing  The one night I gave you  Finally chased by delivering day  Never my lover  Always my friend  Never allowed  To touch me again  Won’t you stop staring?  Keep your hands off me  Get out of my head, bitch  Let go, make me free  You know I don’t love you  You know it won’t last.  I let you touch me  I think I need a bath.      ~fin~  
    
</post>
<date>06,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       ~~~~~   Whore   ~~~~~    It’s begun already, too late to turn back,  Whatever you do, don’t let go.  Need someone to touch me, let me feel,  Whatever you do, don’t leave me alone.    Felt your skin and saw his eyes,  Whatever you do, don’t stop.  Knew my heart died and wished it was him,  Whatever you do, don’t let me fall.    Saw you breathing again, salt on your skin,  Whatever you do, don’t speak.  Felt you relax, wishing for love,  Whatever you do, don’t look at me.    Your eyes finally closed, dreaming of me,  Whatever you do, don’t ask me to stay.  Stand beneath the hot water, trying to make myself clean,  Whatever you do, just go away.      ~fin~  
    
</post>
<date>06,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       ~~~~~~~~   Blue Eyes   ~~~~~~~~      Crawl deep inside yourself  covered with your perfect hair  perfect Body  perfect life  and watch yourself fall to ruin  before your very Eyes.  everything that haunts you  you’ve brought with you here.  now your only Refuge  has become your greatest fear.  watch as your Shell crumbles  following the setting sun.  now the once safe Night  threatens to speak of what you’ve done.  don’t let your Eyes grow tired.  don’t let your smile grow thin.  know that you can always  Retreat farther within.  hold on to them for all you’re worth  try to save what’s left of your Lies  and keep trying to hide behind  your sad, vacant Blue Eyes.      ~fin~  
    
</post>
<date>06,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       ~~~~~~   Tonight   ~~~~~~      Cutting wind brings you nearer to me  Conscience pushes you away  I’ll hold you close and keep you safe  But you know I won’t stay  Affection will not come easily  Lust eternally does  So I’ll keep you at a distance  You don’t know the meaning of love  Sting of salt pressed to raw flesh  Bite of blades and flame  Transform you in the blackened night  Morning finds you just the same  Keep your calming, soothing tone  Replaced by cries and screams  Within this beast, your fragile soul  Nothing’s ever quite what it seems  Let you find me of your own free will  Then kept you tied to me tight  Sweet lips make you mine for all time  I’ll let you have me for tonight.      ~fin~  
    
</post>
<date>06,October,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       ~~~~~~~   Request   ~~~~~~~      I gave you what you wanted  Let you give in to your lust  Revealed your dark side by candle light  As you fell to emotions you shouldn’t trust.    Opened your eyes in a darkened room  You melted into my sweet embrace  Felt your eyes try to open me  Myself reflected in your face.    Took the last of your innocence  Made you mine for one night  Let myself fall into the darkness  Abandoned truth and right    Tasting sweet, seductive sin  Knowing it was wrong  Words whispered in the hot, flickering light  Should be forgotten by the dawn.    My tongue felt your sweet crimson life  My fingers felt your heat  Fed my ardeur from deep within  Conscience lay dying in defeat    Never kept against your will  Not becoming a slave in my bed  My heart is mine, and mine alone.  You can have my body instead.      ~fin~      A/N: Request, Tonight, Unclean, and Whore all refer to a friend I slept with who just happened to be my ex-boyfriend's sister. Oops. We're still good friends. All three of us. I have no idea why I wrote so much about one rather meaningless night...  
    
</post>
<date>22,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      ~~~~~  Roses  ~~~~~    Roses for Ari of purest snow white  sealed with a kiss from blood-tainted lips.  Dipped in the sin of a hidden past  coated in honey from bees that don't sting.  Left for her there to wither and die.  but preserved by the hope of unspoken lies.  Yet all that she sees and all that she will  are roses for Ari of soft snow white silk.  ~fin~ 
    
</post>
<date>15,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       ~~~~~  Tears  ~~~~~      Feel the drops fall   slowly running down her skin   Your kisses making   her pain disappear   With each drop   that you take into yourself,   soften your heart   and let her in.   Realize that "she"   is you.   The skin    is yours.   And the tears you   so lovingly kissed away   are blood.      ~fin~  
    
</post>
<date>15,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       ~~~~~~~~~  *Promises*  ~~~~~~~~~    so enticing  the nicotine mixing with  the sweet scent of the Chocolate  it shares a home with  knowing i should not want it  knowing i should resist  but the aroma’s so inviting  asking me to strike a Flame  pleading with me to inhale  but i promised You i wouldn’t  so yet again, my beautiful baby  as nature over culture  water over Flame  Love wins over temptation  and Promises over Desire   ~fin~    
    
</post>
<date>15,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       ~~~~~~~   Covered   ~~~~~~~      Touching me  Loving me  Needing me  But remember I am a rose  Delicate  blood-red  covered in thorns  ~  I want you here with me  forever and for always  but you must survive  the thorns  and dragons  left on the path  by other’s wrath  and my pain  ~  The road inside is painted  with my blood  a beautiful wet crimson  shimmers in the moonlight  of my world  ~  Keep your hands on me  but love me for my heart  my core, non-existent  but slowly growing still  ~  Keep me close  Drive me all night  make me shake  Wrap yourself around me  Pour yourself into me  ~  Hold me like you’ll never let me go  Love me forever.  But remember I am a rose  Delicate and blood-red  ~  and covered in thorns.  ~      ~fin~  
    
</post>
<date>15,December,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       ~~~~~~~    The Rose    ~~~~~~~     A gift for you    A gift ~    of me.    your rose.  Delicate and painted  blood-red with malicious  protective thorns  slowly dying,  murdered by your sweet kiss  by the beautiful touch of  your skin  that leaves me unprotected.    Without prick or flame or claw.  Open and raw,  laid out before you,  vulnerable and yours.    Naked before you,  you’re holding your knife.    Make me bleed  for you  I will like it  but please don’t hurt me    I need you too much  Claim me, babe,  and make me yours.    I’ll love you forever  and I’ll love you for  always  if you’ll promise you’ll  always  be mine.        ~fin~     
    
</post>
<date>31,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        ~~~~~~  Apathy  ~~~~~~      Walk through life in a daze.  Trying to pry myself  out.  Out of a bloody existence.  I’m living in my past.  In hers.  Can’t let go.  Why can’t you just leave me alone?  Just get out.  You linger longer than asked.  Your presence hangs about me.  A no longer sweet aroma.  Spoiled.  Insipid.  You’re no longer welcome.  Tore me up.  Ripped.  Walked away.  But refuse to leave.  You cannot.  You will not.  Played your games and  lost.  Lost more than I thought  I possessed to lose.  Get away.  Stay away.  You’re filthy.  Hands tainted with  My own blood  reach out to caress me.  I run but you follow.  Why are you still running after me  you’ve asked before.  Still puzzled.  Still chasing.  Scratching and clawing.  Reopening my wounds.  My back, my throat.  Most vulnerable.  Torn like a whipping boy.  But now there’s someone  to lick my wounds for me.  Don’t want me healed?  Then you shouldn’t have left.  Keep your regrets to yourself.  I’ve got my own past to burn.  My own secrets to keep.  My own interests to protect,  to protect me.  So just stay away.  Don’t call.  Don’t write.  Speak every now and then.  Let me know you’re alive.  But don’t tell me how you’re feeling.  Don’t tell me how you’ve been.  Don’t tell me you miss me.  Don’t talk about our past.  If you refuse,  Then don’t talk to me at all.  It’s not that I really hate you.  It’s just that I don’t care.      ~fin~  
    
</post>
<date>04,January,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       ~~~~~~  No title  ~~~~~~    Bastards.  You fucking bastards.  ~  Watch and ignore  see the signs  don’t want to know  Watch him steal  her from me  The wolf with  my beautiful lamb  My baby girl  ~  Could’ve stopped him  Should’ve seen  Searched for help  Bruised, Bloodied  Broken and left  empty handed  ~  My lovely one and only  Stripped of what is  hers.  Childhood.  Safety.  Innocence.  ~  Hard eyes filled with tears  ~  You could’ve stopped it.  ~  Daughters  Girlfriends  Lovers  Wives  Mothers  ~  Congratulations  ~  The world’s a little  dirtier now  because of what  you did not stop.  
    
</post>
<date>03,February,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       ~~~~  Angel  ~~~~    Come with me, love  Follow me to my blood soaked paradise  Hold my hand and you’ll soon see  How deep my bloodlust runs  Your eyes will burn at the sight  Of my Elysian Fields.  Your Angel isn’t  I fell long ago  My music turned to ash  My wings to razors painted crimson  with my love  my pain  my obsession  I’ll tear you up  drink your tears  your blood  your obsession  ~  Mine  ~  Come with me, love  Give in to me  You’re drawn to me  Held to me  Can’t let go  Try, my love  my barbed wire will cut you  deeper  Deeper  Deeper  your life to my lips  my saving grace  my ugly beauty  my addiction  ~  Mine  ~  I’ll draw you out  Make you mine  Forever  Eternity isn’t that long, love  Your Angel is here with you  Hold my hand  I’ll keep you safe  Bound to me  Your sanctuary and refuge  I’ll give you luxurious pain  Take yours away  Give yourself to me, love  Give yourself to me.     ~fin~    
    
</post>
<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       ~~~~~  Open  ~~~~~      Not enough.   I tried so hard.   Lesson is, never try.   Go.   Sate yourself.   Fulfill your fantasies.   Taste him.   Taste her.   But not me.   You'll never have me   the way you once did.   I'll stay here alone.   Because I'm not enough.   Not good enough.   Not strong enough.   Not weak enough.   Not childish enough.   Not jaded enough.   Not enough for you.   Keep your fucking roses.   Nail me to a wall.   Pale flesh washed white   from blood loss and tears.   Stupid.   Give your life to me.   Watch me learn to hate you.   As if I didn't enough already.   Despicable, you are.   Weak.   Childish.   Beautifully Jaded.   Bleed.   Kneel.   Beg.   No.   I won't.   I can't.   I shouldn't.   I will.   I always will.   Unhappy for you again.   Here for you so you   can be okay.   You called me your Angel.   Said I was born to fly.   But all you do is tie me down.      ~fin~    
    
</post>
<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       ~~~~~~~~~~~~~  Adrenaline Eyes  ~~~~~~~~~~~~~      Watching you  Dying  Pleading with me  to help you  to save you  to take you.    I’ll watch you  Bleed as  you scream as  you cry as  you call as  you Die.    Call for her  but she ignores.  Hearing you and  answering only my call.    Dependably unreliable to you.    You’re beautiful  as you lay  stained  as you beg  broken  as you cry  scarred.    Pale flesh encased in  darkness  disguises  Pain and  Lust and  Fear and  You    Hide from yourself  Run Forever  Forgot to live but  Now you’ll  Die.    Stand and watch  as you pale as  you beg as  you need.    I’ll call her to me.    We will share  in your Death  as we shared  in your Life.    Drink your life and  your Death and  you’re Pain.    Bleed out as  your tear falls  on the pavement  As you stare into  my Adrenaline Eyes  as I call your Death  to me with my laugh,  my Kiss,  my Love.    Stare into my Adrenaline Eyes  and watch my soul evaporate.      ~fin~  
    
</post>
<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        ~~~~~~~  and You  ~~~~~~~    Turning to the sky    Laughing.    Knelt in the street for    all to see    But no one watches.    Fallen on     raw knees, raw    hands, raw    faith.    Beg to be seen    Beg for pity    Beg for me.    Pale flesh and blue eyes    Stained and    Streaked and    Scarred    By your inadequacy.    ~    Feel the sun, the    warmth, the    life, and    Feel it leave     You.    Single tear,     releases    pain turns to    flood    Staining     You're beautiful    and raining on    the pavement.    ~    want and    need and    Beg for release.    Please end it.    You can't and    won't and could never.    Can't    Stand can't    move.    Bleed out as    the warmth clouds    over You.    Rain falls as    Your tears as    You're pale as    ~    you Fall.    Can't stand.    ~    Can't move.    ~    Dying.    ~    I'll save you.    You can have    my life and    my blood and    my soul     andYou'll.~    ~    ~    Live.    ~fin~   
    
</post>
<date>03,June,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~  Calling Contradiction  ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~    Get out.   Get out of my head   Get out of my heart   Get out of my life.   But Don't stop calling.   Don't talk.   Don't talk about her   Don't talk about me   Don't talk about us.   But Don't stop confiding.   Don't preach.   Don't preach about love   Don't preach about trust   Don't preach about honesty.   But Don't stop believing.   Don't tell me.   Don't tell me you loved me   Don't tell me you tried   Don't tell me you're sorry.   But Don't stop remembering.   Don't speak.   Don't speak of hope   Don't speak of opportunity   Don't speak of life.   But Don't stop dreaming.   Get out.   Get out of my head   Get out of my heart   Get out of my life.   But Don't stop calling.   Please don't stop calling.   You of all people know   I am nothing but   A walking contradiction.      ~fin~  
    
</post>
<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       In   love Not with you not with her. With a memory. With an image. With an evening. Touch me remind me design me. Mold me into anything. Whatever will make you happy, honey. Call me sweetheart. Hold me through the night I’ll stare into the Blue lights and pray for eternity. In love Not with you not with her. With a kiss. With a touch. With a scream. Too quiet. Too out. Too much to handle. I’m sorry, baby You’ll say. I just don’t need you anymore. You’re body, it just don’t work for me no more. A kiss. One last kiss. A ring returned by a reluctant friend. Tears on pavement. Can’t live without you. Don’t leave me. A call. A truth. A lie. I’m sorry, baby You’ll say. I’m sorry. I’ll beg. ~ In love Not with you not with her. With the rain With the pain With the complication. Only happy when it rains, it’s not you I want. I’m simply in love  with being in love. With a kiss With a touch but mostly,  with a memory.      ~fin~  
    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      This is completely random, but I accidentally deleted Court's comment. Now I'm sad. I liked that comment. IT made me feel good. Now my feel good is gone. Damn curiousity. ::sniffle:: 
    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       ~~~~~~~~~~~~  The Fallen Angel  ~~~~~~~~~~~~    Outcast by the divine.  No longer wanted.  You’ll soon see.  Left to fend for yourself  When you were promised help  shelter  comfort.  Alone and Cold  in the dark  Drunk with fear and  pain and  hopelessness.  No one will come for you.  No one will hear you scream.  No one  ~  but me.  ~  All you’ve got.  I have everything you need  and all you have  is what I choose to give you.  Laid down  stripped down  tied down.  Feel  you’re powerless.  Laid open by  kisses and  caresses and  blades.  Relax, my love,  I mean you no harm.  All I want is  ~  everything  ~  I’ll be your Angel  I’ll be your vampyre  I’ll be your hell.  and You will love me for it.  ~  You are Mine.  ~  As you’ve bled me dry,  so I’ll bleed you.  ~  My kiss tastes of you.  Your skin  Your lips  Your blood  Your life.  ~  I will drink you down  and then  you will truly  never survive without me.  ~  Mine for eternity and always.  ~  I promise, I’ll take care of you.  ~  Come to my Elysian Fields,  my blood-soaked paradise  and you will want for nothing, my love.  ~  All I ask in return  ~  is you.  ~~~~    ~fin~    A/N: open to interpretation.  
    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~    While You Were Sleeping    ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~        2:17 AM.  Lonely and cold.  Drawn inward by inexplicable sadness.  Exhausted.  physically, mentally, emotionally  Dead.  You’ve chosen me.  Your Angel.  Your victim.  Your always.  You’ve brought me down,  stripped me down,  tied me down.  You laid me bare.  Made me open  Made me trust  Made me vulnerable.  You kissed me gently.  You whispered softly.  You touched me slowly.  And then you bled me dry.  Kissed me and consumed me.  Loved me and emptied me.  Filled me and spent me.  2:28 and I remember.  Bloody pages and scarred wrists  from the last time I was bare  the last time I was opened  the last time I trusted.  Tear-stained and blade-weary  My hands,  my pages,  my mind  can take no more.  No more love  No more lust  No more pain.  Blood and chocolate and endless cell phone calls.  I can’t get to you.  Can’t make you see.  Can’t make you understand.  Can’t  understand.  Please don’t leave me  I can’t live without  the luxurious pain you bring  I’m only happy when it rains  Blood, sweat, and tears  my eternal nourishment.  my only nourishment.  2:35 AM.  Lonely and cold.  Dead in the dark  with only the cat to trail  small, bloody footprints  up the stairs,  down the hall  to the room where we kissed  where we loved  where we slept,  where she’ll curl up next to you.  You’ll wake in the night  to her small, frightened body  curled in your arms  and my blood on your hands  at 2:43.    
    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        “Only Human”    I am a fifteen year old boy. My name is Shaun. I know you can’t really generalize anything, but I’m going to try anyway.  ~~  You develop a certain intimacy, being someone’s friend. When someone trusts you enough to tell you everything, you develop a certain love. Consider, for a moment, being told a deep dark secret that of course everyone has at least one of, and knowing that you are the only one told. Makes you feel all warm and fuzzy, does it not? What if your “best friend” happens to be of the opposite sex? How many times do the two friends end up “falling in love” with one another? Or is it really love? Sure, they love each other, but are they in love? What’s the difference? Suppose, though, that they end up dating. Will anyone question them if they kiss in the halls? Will anyone notice their stolen caresses in the darkened passages? What if they are of the same gender? Is it then no longer okay for them to be together?  ~~  So I feel for her, is that so terrible? She loved me, I loved her. It never really disappears, for the emotion remains. But while I know I loved her, was I in love with her? Maybe love isn’t meant to be understood or interpreted. Maybe a girlfriend is just a friend that you kiss. No objection, right?  ~~  So what if I told you that everything said is true. I did love her, and still do. She was my best friend. Assume, even, that a girlfriend really is just a friend that you can kiss. But I am not a fifteen year old boy. Fifteen, perhaps, but a girl. Has your opinion of me changed? Of course. You’re only human, right? What do you know about love?    ~fin~    A/N: A vignette I wrote for Sophomore English.   
    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       ~~~~~~~~~~~~~  The Truth Within  ~~~~~~~~~~~~~      You cry that you can't handle it   That you can't handle me   But you can't go on without it   You're more than people see   You know we are all liars   You know we all deceive   But what you think each one conspires   Depends solely on what you believe   If you open your doors   And let one lover in   What then when she pours   Her own life from within?   Will we both remain?   Will we both be lost?   Is it worth the risk for the gain   No matter the cost?   You know we'd both give anything   To know you belong to each   And yet the choices of your heart are remaining   Too distant, far out of reach   I was not the one pleading   I never wanted you to choose   But now I lie here bleeding   Your love, my life, I'll lose   Inside you know you like the hurt   Knowing that our souls will burn   And as we three play our charade,   Our time runs thin with each passing day      ~fin~      A/N: also written long, long ago. kind of seems ridiculous, all that emotion, now. I guess it's always a little different when you look back on it. Thanks to Ruoxi, who put up with me *through* all of it. I LOVE YOU! Not that you'll ever read this...  
    
</post>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       ~~~~~~~~~~~~~  My Broken Glass  ~~~~~~~~~~~~~    You say you want me   You say you need me   You say you love me   You lie   You love her and we all know   You tried to make me believe   "I will not fall back into her world"   But I will not be drawn back   Onto that broken glass   From the bottle I threw myself   I have repeated this cycle   This fallacy   Too many times   I have made myself lose   Too much life   Too many tears   Too much blood   I will not stand for this   You say you feel nothing   You say you love her   So be it   I will live, I have before   But ifyou ever hurt her   It will be you   Lying on my broken glass.      ~fin~      A/N: written long long ago about an ex-girlfriend who started dating another ex-girlfriend. I'm now very good friends with one of them, and barely on speaking terms with the other. I never could figure out who this one was really talking to.  
    
</post>
<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      So I got my new schedule. 1 - Physics - Wahl 2 - AP Us History - Babb 3 - English III - Osteen 4 - Wellness - Hubbard 5 - I.S. - Hubbard 6 - Pacesetter - Lanigan 7 - PreCal/Trig - Kalis  Whee.  Feel my excitement.  hehe.  that sounded dirty.  sorry....lack of sleep.  Anyway, I have to go read a book and write 3750 words.  Before tomorrow.  Much love, Angel. 
    
</post>
</Blog>