<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>22,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   This is my first Blog. I'm guessing you are suppoosed to treat this as a Diary. I know that people treat their diaries very differently, but mine is just a log of my thoughts. So if you find something insulting, I ask that you please forgive me. I live in Minneapolis MN, I'm 15 years old, and I currently am going into 10th grade. I am Dating a Senior in Highschool who I care for very much. I nicknamed him roo, quite teh oposite of him because he's 6' 3" a foot taller them me. But I'm tigger and Tigger and Roo are best friends, so I figured it would work :)...  I want to show you guys some of the things that I write, so that you can get an idea of what goes through my head...Then I won't feel bad if people think I'm crazy for my writing, because At least I will have given them fair warning.  this is a story that I am in the middle of writing. It is going to be a long short story, but that is fine, just as long as it comes out properly         Within the Next Three       It’s interesting when you’re at the end of something and someone asks you to tell the story of how you got there. Do you start at the beginning and tell the story as it progressed? Generally that is how you would proceed...but when the beginning doesn’t make sense until you know the end, and the end is too vague and complicated without the beginning and the middle. Then, you must start in the middle.   Starting in the middle of the tale, with “a day like any other day” does nothing any justice. I personally have never experienced a day that has been the same as any other. It’s like trying to say identical twins are the exact same replicas of each other. If anyone has passed a day that is the same as “the other day” I would love to meet them and tell them what a boring and horrible life they live, for if you have the privilege to be free, then you should take it. However, there is a period in the year that time ceases to exist, and it is when my ailment started. During that season...summer.   In the summer, as a teen on vacation, time lacks any type of its natural flow. Everything becomes a blur of which day, what month. Day becomes the time where you sleep so you can go and play at night. And when you play at night, what you do doesn’t matter. There are no rules, no boxes that the rest of the world has to live with. Some of us hunt, others drink, and there are many of us who search for substances that only make the mess of their minds worse. In truth, none if these things pertained to me. I was freed like all of the others, cut loose from the chains that bound all of us. We were liberated from the schedule that made us mechanical. But I stayed on the schedule, I just made it so that I lacked the responsibilities I should have had. So I guess, it was no different for me that summer, not until I had the first dream.   Every one of us has had what most call a nightmare. It is a distortion of realities in out minds, where everything is twisted and unusual, and nothing makes sense. There are the times when everything you’ve learned as right is wrong, and everything you’ve known as wrong only gets worse. Or there are the kinds where you are running from something, or where everything changes and everything you’ve worked hard on goes to hell. But there is another kind of nightmare. Those are the ones that come true. Good dreams are wonderful things to have come true, but nightmares are irreversible disasters that fate places before us.   We’ve all had a day where everything seems to have gone to hell. You forget your work at home and found out later your rabbit decided he would have a wonderful meal out of your project. And the one person you’ve ever liked asked out your best friend, who accordingly accepts and treats you like the ground she walks on. At lunch, your favorite shirt got pasta sauce spilled all over it, and your little brother had infested your closet with bees as a present to you. And he only did it because you caught him snuffing crack and you told your parents. Finally at the end of the day, you feel like it should all just be done and you throw your backpack on the ground and rush to your room. Just so you can bawl your eyes out, knowing that you are in the one safe place that will never be taken away from you... Home, but what if that suddenly gets taken away?   It doesn’t matter, it won’t happen. We all think that, and I don’t blame you, I thought that too. It’s the kind of thing that only happens in someone’s worst dreams, but then again, they come true all too often. Now I know, now I realize that dreams are the catalysts to everything, every beginning. Reality is just the solidification to everyone’s eyes, it is the beginning of the end.     I had a hangover from the overabundance of noise that I had just been exposed to the previous night. My alarm had gone off at 5 in the morning, and I had only slept for two or so hours. I hadn’t gotten home from the dance until 2am anyways. The song that my Clock was playing was a balled by Sting “...Please take me dancing tonight, I’ve been all on my own...” The words rang in my head like a sounding gong throughout a Buddhist temple. I guess I cannot complain because I love to dance, and parties are an essential part of my life. Like air. I stumbled to the bathroom and stubbed my toe on the base of the bath. I looked like I had been in a train wreck. My face was swollen and purple and the bags under my eyes made me look like I had been snuffing something. But I wouldn’t have been, because I won’t touch that shit. My eyes hurt and my forehead was sweating. In the mirror I could see my pupils adjusting to the sunlight through the bathroom window. My parents were both gone at work, my mom was on a business trip for a magnet fair for the hospital, and Wayne was out scouting good places to climb “gone for the weekend”. I love them both, but my dad was going to pick me up later so I was a little more then mad at them.    I started the shower, the hot water was a relief on my skin, and I could feel the knots in my back muscles begin to fade away. It felt like a steam iron rolling out the wrinkles of a shirt that had been discarded on the floor in a heap. The bathroom light kept flickering. I didn’t need it so I turned it off, my hand reaching out of the shower like a person reaching for a dead person’s soul in one of those ghost stories. The alarm went off in my parent’s room, loud and forgotten. I dropped the soap bottle onto the tile and ended up slipping on it because it had spilled over, its cap broken off. The alarm clock kept getting louder, buzzing in my head, screaming at me…like it wanted help, wanted me to make it stop. I tried to get up, but I slipped again and hit my head on the garnet counter, the sharp edge cut into my skin and I fell into a sleep. (Boyfriend, this is the beginning, she sees this, but happens 3 years later. Something I have to do with that number…)   ~Come here, now you brat!   ~I don’t want to. I’m not going ANYWHERE NEAR YOU!!!  The little girl stomped her foot on the tile so hard the glass vase fell off the table and broke. The man screamed at the little girl and flung a shattered piece of glass at her. It cut her temple and she fell on the floor scooting away like a broken dog getting away from its abusive owner. The man’s eyes burned into the skin of the child. One hand grabbed her neck while the other tore the summer dress the child’s mother had given her. Her screams remained unanswered by the walls of the house, nothing came to help.   I woke up, my face was caked in my blood and my head spun. The cut had been deeper then I had expected, much deeper. The clock screeched at me, begging me to make its task finished. Growling, I crawled out of the bathroom, my knees scraped against the floor making bloody streaks because I had bled a small puddle, and the soap and water had mingled with it to make a little mess from hell.  I rolled out of the bathroom and shuffled into my Mother’s bedroom. The soft colors were only exaggerated by the small amount of light the shades let through. The room was perfect, it was like a home within a home. It was cleaner than the bleached dessert sand, but it wasn’t anal because there were these little trinkets and memories on the shelves of the dresser and books. A faint scent of the perfume my mom wore on special occasions caught my attention. It drew me in and I almost got lost in thought, but the alarms allure was far greater.  It read 6:38 meaning I had been unconscious for the good part of an hour. I rolled my eyes into the back of my head running over the mental checklist of the things I needed to do. The mental checklist that never gets done, the one you ignore. 
</post>
</Blog>