<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Good friends are the greatest treasures of the earth. A person without a good friend is someone who walks constantly alone in the dark. Without my friends (especially Haley) I dont know where I'd be. You have to be careful with friends though. They are hard to come by, and should be hard to lose, but that's sometimes not the case. With Haley it is. Haley stands by me with whatever decision I make. She's like my foothold for every single day. She keeps me steady and calm when at any moment I could completely crumble to nothing. She has no idea what she means to me and she never will. Not even if she read this. Haley's the kind of girl who has no idea that the smallest thing, the smallest compliment she makes, can completely turn around my whole day. She makes me smile with the drop of a hat. Haley is the kind of friend that every person needs at least one of. You know those people who you are almost exactly like? Well, Hayes is mine. I am the enabler and she is the enablee'. :-) But in all reality, we both enable each other ( to be lazy that is). We call ourselves the lazy perfectionists. There is a whole lot oftruth in that statement. We are almost too alike it's scary. But its great. She knows everything I think and feel just by looking at me. And I can do the same for her. Anyways, Haley has no idea how much she means to me, so maybe this will give her a clue... Love you Hayes... Hose  
     

    
</post>
<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Hey! This is another poem Haley wrote about me.... you can also visit her website at   urlLink http://www.haleymargaret.blogspot.com              the tiny hands    wringing    out of confusion, guilt, frustration    the smooth eyelids    fluttering    out of contempt, anger, hatred    the weak muscles    contracting    out of mistrust, disbelief, shock    the loving heart    breaking    out of longing, desire, love    my eyes watch    as i try to dry thetears    all i can do    whisper    "i love you and everything will be alright"    but my voice cracks    with the uncertainty    that is certain        -haley        thanks for being there hayes... thanks for everything     
     

    
</post>
<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Okay, so it's 2:05 in the morning and here I am crying.... I have this best friend, Haley, she's so great. She knows how to make me laugh when I'm the most heartbroken girl in the world. Haley's been one of the best things that has happened to me this past year. Haley's been there for me more than anyone else in the world. She listens to me ramble about nonsense and things that matter and things that dont mean anything. Anyways, Haley writes poetry all the time. She's written two poems for me, one I just found out about tonight.... thats why I'm crying. You see, my cousin committed suicide April 20, 2004. Haley wrote this poem....      It's selfish   and it'  s stupid   and everything between   and to the left   and to the right   of every word you didn't mean   it hurts   and it aches   and I bet you didn't know   and I'm mad   and I'm sad   but only because I loved you so   it makes and it breaks   everything I ever knew   it's hazy   but it's clear   there's just one thing left to do   I aim   and I shoot   and now it's all gone down the drain   it's over   and it's starting   there is no end to the pain      **R.I.P. Matt**      thanks Hayes.... love always, hose...    
     

    
</post>
<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Hey guys. Let me give you a word of advice. In case you don't know this, never call a girl fat. It's just not right. This is a prime example of what will happen to you if you do. ok, so I was online the other night over at my girl, Kristina's, house. My friend Carlos gets online with his friend Scott. Scott was drunk needless to say. Anyways, they got to callin me and Kristina fat. Not cool. So we were like stop and they kept on going... once again, not cool. So, he says he's sorry right? But by this time, I'm completely pissed off. As of today, I'm kinda talkin to him. I tried talkin alittle, but now its like he doesnt want to talk to me so whatever. If you ever feel the need to call someone fat, simple advice.... dont do it. Good job! Anyways, I'm out for the night. Bye yall!    
     

    
</post>
<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
              ok... so I used to have one of these things back when I was in middle school.... oh the drama of middle school. ya know? The boys and the "heartbreaks". Everything was dramatic because that's what you wanted it to be, not because it actually was. Everything was exaggerated and totally blown way out of proportion. But then again, what's changed?? NOTHING. High school is just as gay now as middle school was then. All the drama... who needs it? Who REALLY needs more drama in their life??Not me. I'm sixteen and have way too much as it is. Coming up next... my life story.... it's really quite interesting... like a soap opera almost....              
</post>
</Blog>