<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       did not update anything for this few days    coz its full of crapz   didn't wanna write it down =)   we have camp fire today (31/7)   quite nice some part but...   boring for most of ta time   ....hahhax   i throw a can and hit markus hard in ta face   o.OxXx .... he got a big baluku there   feeling very guilty after throwin him...   hahha.... scolded zul coz he kep playing with my hair   so irritatin...hate him!   but sometime i think he's helpful and friendly   other time he is nothing more than shyt!   am i very bad?...hahah    think i am....haiz...   my darling ps me today...   nv wait for me then go sleep... so funny   i watch 'i robot' today with darren and liling...   i'm the light bulb* again...so sian   reach home at 1.30 am....hahah   sleepy now....ZzzZzz   nitez*  
    
</post>
<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        WhaT tHe...!!!  toDaY daMn swAy niA!  waKe uP laTe... 6.15 thEn waKE uP,  taKE taXi tO scHoOl  reaCh scHoOl at abT 6.45  firSt tiMe reaCh scHooL so EarLY  then the lAst twO peRioD of tHe dAY is ThaT idIotIC tEacHer leSson  i hAte chiNeSe!!!  lIang laO si is lEavinG uS foR fuRthEr stUdy!  i miSs heR! and i thInk mY whOle clAsS wiLl miSs hEr toO!  shE's thE bEsT chinEse teAchEr wE evEr haD!  thAt bloOdy cHao lAo si(neW tEachEr) frOm chIna dE...  dOn leT me go hOme aftEr schOol niA...  aSk mE to StAy baCk do The tEsT! haiZ...  sTupiD de... sO anGrY wiTh tHAt teachEr  wE plAnnin tO seND hEr baCk to chIna... LOL!  miSs my daTe wiTH somEonE coZ of ThE tESt!!!  so sAd... foRgeT it...  its a  BloOdy  daY!        
    
</post>
<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       erM... i have a doggiE noW,   anD her nAme is NUINUI...   souNd so DisguStiN! buT vErY cuTe nIa   toDaY iS as sUX aS otHeR suNdaY...   i dOn lIkE sUndAy... dOn nOe wHy    maYbe tHe thOught thaT thE neXt daY is MoNdaY baH...   bOriNg... i hAve hOmeWorK buT dOn fEeL lIkE dOiNg thEm.   aqIf juSt tOlD sOmetHinG tHat i Nv wAnnA heAR ... so IrriTatIn   i Noe hOw tO scAn lIAo! hahahX... qUiTe sTupiD laR...   nTh muSt abouT tOdaY, thE onLi thIng iS i haVE to taKe cAre oF thE toOpID doG noW   mY dArlIng laTeR goIng ouT... miSs hiM niA...&gt;.   yAwN... caNnoT sLeEp sOmeMorE... haVE tO taKe cArE of NuI sqUarE!   =)  
    
</post>
<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          aRgH!~ tHiS mOrnIng wAke uP aT 7 aND gO baCk to sLeeP tIll 7.45!!! hahha... latE fOR brEaKfAst wIth ShuFeN theY aLl aND i wAs lAtE foR haLf aN hoUr! &gt;.</post></Blog>