<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I don't know whether to be happy or cry. Sometimes weekends are just too hard to go through. It's nothing but one big fight with myself to stay on my HEP (healthy eating plan). I won't call it a diet. That word just brings up too many bad memories.  Like being on WW in High School and having to sit in the basement eating my bowl of tuna with carrots and canned mushrooms, no Mayo or anything. I tried eating some tuna the other day without Mayo. It made me sick. Reminded me of those dark days of isolation. It was like a punishment for me. "You're to fat to eat with the rest of the family." Geez! No wonder I have a problem with food.    Let's try another color, shall we?      A blue mood today. Not sad, not gay, just a little blue.        No, more like purple. Does purple mean power? I feel more powerful this week after being OP the entire time. WooHoo! I also feel powerful because I need to do some home improvement projects this weekend. One I've never tackled before. Kind of scary, but powerful.        Green, kinda green today. Filling up on veggies and fruit. Had a great supper last night with steamed fresh broccoli and summer squash. Going to have tuna sandwich tonight with fresh tomatoes.         Brown on Monday, cause I'll probably be bruised after this work I'm planning to do. LOL       But it's a good feeling. I like being able to take care of myself and not have to call someone or pay someone to fix things. Plus the home improvement store can be a GREAT place to meet guys!!!!        
      
</post>
<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I was looking at the grocery ad last night and noticed something that really ticked me. The only thing on sale that was point-friendly was grapes. Yup, that's it. The rest of the sale items were junk food. Pizza, candy bars, ice cream, snack crackers.   All these huge pictures of all the foods I'd love to eat by the bucket full and that's what's on sale. And I probably have coupons for most of them too.   It takes a huge amount of my will power to walk into that store and ignore all the junk that's on sale and oh, so much easier to eat than something from scratch. Am I missing something? Maybe I just don't know how to put a meal together. Am I lazy or ignorant? You tell me.   Last night I tried making a veggie chili. I cooked my 1/4 c. of brown rice with seasonings and zucchini and summer squash. Then I added 1/2 c. of chili beans. It was really BAD!!!! I could hardly stand to eat it, but I ate it. I don't know why. I guess since I went to that much trouble and couldn't think of anything else to fix. I would have been better off making the beans and rice and had the veggies on the side. Am I trying too hard?   I need some good cookbooks. Anyone got any out on eBay?????   
      
</post>
<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I do a lot of thinking sitting on the toilet. Don't laugh. I don't know why. I don't spend that much time on the darn thing, I just think really fast.   So this morning I'm sitting there stressing about staying OP today and how my weight isn't coming off fast enough. I thought about all the time and energy I spend "thinking" about the whole issue of loosing weight and why I want to loose weight and why I can't loose weight and what's wrong with me and how will I stay OP this weekend and how I want to eat junk food and how I don't want to eat junk food, I want to get this weight off and it was like,"what am I doing?"   Just get on with life and do it. Just do it. Get it done. Quit stressing over it and just do it. Quit whining and do it. Geez, if you'd just stick with it, it would be over, the weight would be off and by that time I'd learn to eat right and love to exercise (ya right!), and this whole thing would be over.   All righty then...............I'M DOING IT.   
      
</post>
<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, I was on plan yesterday. Finally! I swear that first day getting back OP is the worst. And I almost blew it over a bowl of cereal last night. I was hungry. It was a legitimate snack, I just didn't need two serving sizes. So I opted for oatmeal instead. Not quite as good, but, hey I ate it.   I did haveanother revelation of something. I was reading an article from  urlLink http://www.frolicanddetour.com/losingthecow/ and she said something that really struck a cord in me. She said that she realized that one reason she was having such a hard time with loosing weight was because " Your using it for something."  Meaning her weight. Wow, that really said something to me. Was I using my weight for something. I could feel the fear rising inside me at the thought of actually getting all this weight off. What was that????   Why am I afraid of loosing all this excess weight?    I'm afraid I still won't get a date, even if I'm thin.  I use my weight as an excuse to not do anything, travel, go places by myself.   I won't know what to do with myself.  I won't know who I am.  Dirty old men will look at me, YUCK.  I'm so used to being fat, I ......   So what do I do with these fears?   I don't care about "getting a guy". If no one want to date me, it's HIS loss.  Even if I loose the weight, it doesn't mean I HAVE to do anything that I'm uncomfortable with doing. It doesn't mean I have to do something incredible with my life. God is still in control. He will tell me what to do next.  I'll rely on God to tell me that.  O.K. I'm still the same person. My appearance will change, but not WHO I am.  So what?  Yes, that's true. But I can also get used to being thinner as I go along. It's not going to happen over night anyway. I'll adjust as I go.   THERE IS NOTHING TO BE AFRAID OF.   LET GO OF THE OTHER STUPID SIDE OF THE ROPE!!!!!!  I need to quit fighting myself. I need to quit being afraid to see the number on the scale go down. I mean, it really does scare me. But not anymore.  Oh, and I put note cards up all over my house with notes to myself about eating healthy and exercising and doing it every day, one day at a time, to get to my goal. I think I'll make some more for the exercise room.      
      
</post>
<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      O.K. So summer is almost over, but Hey! It's never too late to start! I might not be in that bikini this year, but next? Who knows!!!   So on this summer challenge you need to list the following, so I'm going to do it here for all the world to see.   1.  Make a list of the three things you like most about your body.    A. My eyes are very pretty, hazel, and I really like them.   B. My hair is naturally curly and I like the cut I have right now.   C. This is getting harder. Hmm....It used to be my waist but I don't have one anymore. I'm still kind of curvy. I'm not really boxy, so I'll say my overall shape. Even though it's 6 sizes too big, it's still a nice shape.   2.  Make a list of the three things you least like about your body.    ONLY 3????   a. My stomach has gotten really huge   b. My boobs are really saggy now   c. Cellulite. I have a lot of it.....everywhere. Enough Said.   3.  Make a list of three things that you are denying yourself by not being fitter and having a body you can be happy in.    a. I don't like buying new clothes while I'm at this size. I guess I feel like I don't deserve them or I shouldn't be in them for very long.   b. I don't go places by myself and do things I enjoy doing. I'm too self-conscious as this size.   c. I don't even think about dating.   4.  Make a list of three things you could do right now that would make a difference.   a. Stop binging.   b. Stop sitting around all weekend and do something.   c. Stop eating sugary junk.   O.K. That's over!!!!!!!!!!   Now I sign a contract with myself that: I, Jennifer, will commit fully to this program by being willingto look honestly at my behavior and feelings, nomatter what they are, and to record them accurately in my journal. (That's this thing. ) So I guess you'll know if I don't. Email me if you don't see me doing it!!!!  Well, you heard me. I'll get this weight off.   Today's weight: 211.5       
      
</post>
<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well, I actually thought I had a revelation on Friday night. After I went to bed, stuffed from eating too much junk, I kept asking myself why I was doing this? Why???? Was it just emotional needs or what?   In a way it was but then I thought that maybe the emotional need wasn't what I thought. Maybe it was not loneliness or fear or sadness, maybe it was rebellion. I had been told what to eat my whole life. I was put on diets from 5th grade on. I wasn't allowed candy or desserts and if I got caught with candy, I was punished. I remember telling myself, every single day, that when I got out of there, "NO one would ever tell me what to eat again." and "When I get out of here, I'll eat whatever I want."   Those inner vows are the voices I hear whenever I try to eat healthy. It's like I won't even listen to myself tell myself that I need to eat healthy foods. Is that insane or what? Yet, I feel that I've hit on something. When you think that I said those things to myself every day for 8 -10 years, then what is it that's at the core of my unconscious mind? Wanting to eat whatever I want. So how do I stop those voices or inner vows? I have to re-program what I tell myself. I have to get up and say, "I want to eat healthy today. It's the best thing for me. I want to lose weight and be healthy. I want to exercise and eat the right foods today." And do that every day.   I vow to make note cards and put them on my mirror and fridge and cupboard doors so that I read them every time I go to eat something. I have to get past these inner vows or I will never get anywhere in loosing weight. Willpower alone won't do it.   So now that I say all this, I must confess that I continued to eat all day Saturday and Sunday. Obviously the note cards are not up yet. But they will be tonight.   
      
</post>
<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      July 23, 2004   Starting again, after another lost weekend. Lost because I wasted my time eating junk food. Why do I do this to myself. Is it just out of self-pity or boredom? If I could find the answer to that question, I supposed I could write a book and become the next "Dr. Phil". But I have to find the answer within myself, for myself, or I'll never get to the other side of this journey.   How important is being able to eat mass quantities of junk food? How much is that food worth to me? Why is it so valuable that the thought of going without it is overwhelming? Even terrifying? Is it because I don't know of any other way to cope with being alone? Does it make being alone "better" in some way. As if I'm thinking, "Hey, if I'm alone, at least I can eat." I know I've thought that. My new thoughts should be, "Hey, a nice relaxing weekend. I can get a lot done around the house, relax and really stick to my eating plan." Sure! If it were only that easy.   I fight with myself all week long, trying to decide if I'm going to be good this weekend or not. The description of good being that I'll not over eat. As if the act of eating wisely or not, determines my worth as a human being. AHHH Where did that even come from? My mother? My piers?     This, people, is going to be hard!!!   If you want to know more about me, personally, pictures and more info that just this journal, go to my other website at:  urlLink http://pages.ivillage.com/jenu12b/   
      
</post>
<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      O.K. it seems really stupid to think that I am controlled by a candy bar or a donut. I mean, isn't it ridiculous to think that because that item of food is in sight, that I HAVE to eat it.  I think about food more when I am trying to avoid it. I put food in categories as to how bad or good it is. I "run" away from the bad foods and make myself eat the good foods, even if I don't like them.  Seriously, does a normally thin person eat like this? My daughter is very thin and she doesn't eat like this. I want to eat like a normally thin person. To eat healthy but still be able to eat foods that I like. Isn't that normal?  I guess I'm just so sick and tired of this whole thing. I'm tired of being "afraid" of food. I'm not going to be afraid anymore.  
      
</post>
<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Why does it seem that time just flies by but when I'm sitting at home trying not to eat an entire Pizza Hut pizza, time stands still. Or when I keep hopping on the scale morning after morning, and nothing happens, the days speed by. But when I think of how long it will take to get to goal, the days stretch out forever?  Does time really go faster and slower? It sure seems like it.  I am really at a point where I don't know if I want to do this any longer. But I know that if I give up, I will only keep gaining. I guess some point of success is knowing that at least you've maintained. Only I haven't. I've gained 22 pounds since August of 2003. That's not maintaining. And I haven't been able to get it back off and keep it off. The closest I got was 196 for Vickie's wedding in June. Then I ate to stop thinking about the fact she was married and gone and I was alone.  I tell myself that if I'm never going to meet a man, then at least I can eat. How crazy is that? I pacify myself with food. I don't want to give it up. When it comes right down to it, I don't want to give it up. I want to eat candy and donuts and cake and ice cream and chips and pizza and hamburgers and French fries and I want to eat as much of it as I want to.  How do you get past that? It isn't just emotions. I WANT to eat this stuff and I don't want anyone to tell me that I can't.  HELP! 
      
</post>
<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Wow, it's August already. And I'm still the same size. This is so depressing.  I finally got through one weekend without binging. I can't even believe it. I ate over my calories but it was not a binge. I worked hard this weekend, inside and out, on stuff around the house. So I figure that I would rather eat a few more calories than try not to eat and end up binging.  I almost went to McDonald's last night. I put a pork cutlet in the oven with squash, tomato, spices. I didn't know if it would taste good or not and I had convinced myself that if it tasted like crap, I was going out. Thank heavens, it was pretty darn good. The cutless was flawless and the squash wasn't too bad. And I can say that it was better than a cheeseburger and better for me than fries. So, HURRAY for me!   
      
</post>
</Blog>