<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
        I'm worried. I watched "Bowling for Columbine" tonight and have seen "Fahrenheit 9/11" twice. I'm worried because Michael Moore has somehow become attractive to me.This really does worry me. I even noticed that hewears a wedding ring...         A friend of minerecently wentlooking for love and thought he had found it via the internet, some 2,000 miles from here. So he bought love a round-trip tickettothe Silicon Valley.They had spent hours on the phone together. Theywere soulmate's - he was sure of it. She's exactly what he's been searching for. She is a transgender.I admit I can be a bit naive, so I askedwhat that meant, exactly, not wanting to leave it to my imagination. And stalling for time while my brain processed that this also meant that my straight friend, who I had once had a quick oral-sex-fantasy about, (he has a tongue that rivals the lead singer for Kiss...)was not straight.      
</post>
<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       My cell phone was disconnected this week.I was a member of a family plan, but I'm thinking that I've just been disowned. My ex was paying for it, and even though he's not very good at paying things on time, I expected it to be on the next day or sooner until I called and found out that the outstanding bill is$853...      I'm sure I've developed a brain tumor. He'll have to turn the phone back on since I'll be in and out of the hospital from here on. Right? Well, I don't really want it back - I'm sure that I was bound to crash into some poor soul because I haven't mastered the hands-free theory just yet.      Now, I admit I may have had a tiny bit to do with the size of the bill. I have a friend in Washington, who I haven't heard from in a while. In fact, I wanted him to be just a tiny bit more than a friend... So when the conversation heated up, well, we talked for two hours... He did most of the talking. I managed to figure out the hands-free thing that night.      
     

    
</post>
<date>07,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      I've lost eight pounds in nine days. I've given up a twenty-plus-year-old addiction to regular Pepsi and switched to diet. This, of course, was no ordinary addiction. This was a replacement for food - I was truly a Pepsi-fueled human. I woke up with one and went to bed with one. And had quite a few in between. Now, I'm eating - food - and learning how to chew again. Oh, and now I know why people need dental floss... Damn stuff gets stuck in between my teeth... I guess it's a miracle that I still have teeth...  I have no regrets, though. This is the kind of triumph that everyone needs in their life. To give something up because it's not good for you - even though you love it, well, let's just say that I'm sure my remaining two, okay, three - addictions will be easier to beat now that I have felt the joy of victory.       
     

    
</post>
<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       urlLink    Me... urlLink   
     

    
</post>
</Blog>