<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I am Livvy, myfiancee has cancer.        We found out in January that Andy has a large tumour inside his brain. An Astrocytoma Glioma say the Neurologists. I really did not want to start out my 2nd blog entry with this. I haveactually tried a few alternative begginnnings, but none seemed to work. I would hate for people to think that this cancer defines me... "Oh, it's the cancer blog". But I am going to have faith in my readers to realise that this does not define me.       Andy has had Radiotherapy,the tumouris not growing, but it is not getting smaller either. A waiting game. I'm actually doing quite alright at the moment. I feel that I have the ability to be able to concentrate on other things. Andy on the other hand is up and down.. Mostly up when he feelswell and mostly down when he feels sick.  Andy is a tall and lovely boy. I'm not sure what height he is but I'm 5'9" and he is a good head bigger than me.If you walked past Andy on the street, he would avert his eyes or look so intent on his destination that you would not want to bother him. My boyis noble and kind, butalso shy as a sparrow. Andy is from all appearances just like any other man, yet Itake great pleasure in the fact thatI know him sointimately and therefore to me, he is a strange and wonderful creature. He speaks to me so clearly without having to say a word. Different types of silences, the movement of just a few facial muscles or aslight pause in his steptell me stories of what it feels like to be under his skin.    I do not want to define myself by the role I play in his life. But by playing this role I am further exploring the intracacies of my own life and body. My limits,my (in)ability to surrender to an inner peace,myneed for meaning and fulfillment and thenever-ending rolling-on of aboth sublime andsuffering world.      "One day you will look in the mirror and greet yourself with elation"      
     
    
</post>
<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Livvy urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        I have just set my lovely one off to bed and am sitting down to write this, for what I guess might be useful for a few reasons...   1 - therapy (who needs therapy!? hehehe)  2- creative outlet (very underrated in today's society) 3- the chance to write my name on the concrete slab that is this world.     
     
    
</post>
</Blog>