<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      It's been a couple of days since i've updated... sorry about that. I've been really busy. Volleyball's finally over! Hopefully tryouts won't be too rough. In the end it doesn't even seem worth it to tryout. Even if I do make it, I know I'll never play. I don't want to be a quitter and quit my senior year, but I really don't want to play. I have no passion for it anymore. Summer league wasn't all that fun, my parents had to like force me to go cuz I never wanted to. Even when I was there I kept thinking, okay only 3 mores games and I can go home- i could have cared less about whether or not we won. It's just not me, I'm used to the competitive side, not the lazy one. Oh well, only a couple months and it'll all be over for good!   On a different note, I'm about to leave for Wisconsin!!! I'm so excited. We're going 'camping Naperville style'. Basically that means we have cabins and everything and electricity, but we're still out in the woods. There's so much fun stuff to do there according to Angel- a bunch of outdoorsy stuff- which is awesome! I checked the weather up online though and it's supposed to rain 3 of the 4 days :( Hopefully that won't betrue. We leave at 10:30, so I have a little bit of time to waste. I'm getting so excited tho, this weekend is going to be so much fun!!!!!!!   Cya Sunday~   Melissa   
      
</post>
<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Well its about 2 o'clock.. I talked my familiy out of making me go to Iowa with them. I was pretty impressed they caved in. It figures that nobody is home the day that I can do whatever I want to. Everyone is either on vacation, or working, or just not home. It's crap. Anyways,this morning I woke up and came downstairs. There was a baby mouse sitting at the bottom of the stairs. I just assumed it was dead cuz it didn't move for like 2 hours. I didn't really feel like touching it and nobody's home so I figured I'd just leave it there until my parents could take care of it..... Yeah I just came back down and its gone. so basically I have a baby mouse running around my house right now. My cats keep taking off running and it creeps me out cuz I just assume they're chasing the mouse. grosssss. I'm thinking i'm going to go hit up the beach! More later.... Melissa :-* 
      
</post>
<date>24,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
       Well this is going to be my first entry! I've read people's blog's from time to time so I figured I might as well start my own. I just got off work a little bit ago..... very long night. I think like 20 people came in the whole night so I was so bored!  I guess I have to help my parents move my sister in to her new apartment in Iowa tomorrow. It's going to be one longggg day. I wish I could just stay home- but my parents don't trust me home alone! Figures right?  I don't really have all that much to say. I probably should go to bed soon considering I've got to be up at 5 tomorrow :( Hopefully this wasn't too boring of an entry. I really don't have much on my mind and I basically was home alone all day, so I have no great stories. Hopefully something exciting will happen tomorrow and I'll have something exciting for y'all to read!  Goodnight!!!        P.S. Everyone should go out and buy the Kenny Chesney CD.... it's amazing!!!! Also, while you're out you might as well pick up the Ashlee Simpson one, because it's pretty quality too.        
      
</post>
<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I am bored out of my mind!!!! My mom won't let me go out since I have been sick.  I can't go to volleyball practice because if I did I know I would get sick.  People can come visit me, but only a few have offered and even then its only for a few hours cuz they have plans for the night anyways.  It's just all so boring!!!!  Chris has come to visit me almost every night.  It's been a lot of fun.  His friends are giving him a hard time about it, so he probably won't be stopping by tonight even tho he told me he would.  Angel has stopped by a couple times to watch movies, but she has work tonight so that eliminates that.  Ben stopped by the other day after lifetime.  We had a really good talk.  It looks like things aren't going well with him and Chrissie :( poor kid.  They're having their 'talk' tonight sooooo yeah.  Pat told me he would come visit me but honestly, I know I'd just get bored because I have like no energy and really the only person I want to visit me right now is Chris.    I feel horrible about missing all of these volleyball practices.  It looks so bad.  Honestly tho, I would not be able to handle them.  It's not like I'm just ditching out.  I told Scarpino that I would be back on Monday.  I wanted to try going on Saturday but my mom doesn't like that idea so we agreed on Monday.  I just want to get back to volleyball, back to feeling well, back to going out and having fun and away from all this free time.  I swear I've watched more Olympics than anyone my age because it's basically all that I can do.  It gets boring! I want to go out, I want to feel fine!  School starts on Wednesday. blah. I have no idea what's going on for the first day either.  It's all up in the air.  I know Angel wants to get ready together, but I want to go with Katie and Brenna and them as well so we'll see.  As of Monday my life is pretty much gone.  I have volleyball everyday, probably work every day I don't have volleyball, and then school on the side.  Gross!!    I'm going to go watch some more Olympics. Yessssss
      
</post>
<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I am bored out of my mind!!!! My mom won't let me go out since I have been sick.  I can't go to volleyball practice because if I did I know I would get sick.  People can come visit me, but only a few have offered and even then its only for a few hours cuz they have plans for the night anyways.  It's just all so boring!!!!  Chris has come to visit me almost every night.  It's been a lot of fun.  His friends are giving him a hard time about it, so he probably won't be stopping by tonight even tho he told me he would.  Angel has stopped by a couple times to watch movies, but she has work tonight so that eliminates that.  Ben stopped by the other day after lifetime.  We had a really good talk.  It looks like things aren't going well with him and Chrissie :( poor kid.  They're having their 'talk' tonight sooooo yeah.  Pat told me he would come visit me but honestly, I know I'd just get bored because I have like no energy and really the only person I want to visit me right now is Chris.    I feel horrible about missing all of these volleyball practices.  It looks so bad.  Honestly tho, I would not be able to handle them.  It's not like I'm just ditching out.  I told Scarpino that I would be back on Monday.  I wanted to try going on Saturday but my mom doesn't like that idea so we agreed on Monday.  I just want to get back to volleyball, back to feeling well, back to going out and having fun and away from all this free time.  I swear I've watched more Olympics than anyone my age because it's basically all that I can do.  It gets boring! I want to go out, I want to feel fine!  School starts on Wednesday. blah. I have no idea what's going on for the first day either.  It's all up in the air.  I know Angel wants to get ready together, but I want to go with Katie and Brenna and them as well so we'll see.  As of Monday my life is pretty much gone.  I have volleyball everyday, probably work every day I don't have volleyball, and then school on the side.  Gross!!    I'm going to go watch some more Olympics. Yessssss
      
</post>
<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      These last few days have been very intense.  I've been very sick.  I woke up Thursday with a sore throat which my mom gave me some medicine for.  Then I went back to bed and woke up again throwing up and with a high fever.  My mom took me in to the doctor and they said it was probably strep, so I went home with that medicine. Then they called me a few hours later and told me that they think it might be mono or something else, so I had to go in to the hospital and have some throat tests done, and then they took some bloodwork for testing.  It was a really awful day.  I kept throwing up and my temperature reached 104.6, so my mom called the doctor in the night to see what to do.  They made me come in the next morning.  She put me on 2 more medicines, and she wanted me to take some chemo medicine where you stop throwing up so that I could hold my medicine down.  That medicine was really expensive tho so we skipped it.  Basically the last few days I've just been sitting at home, sleeping, watching the olympics, and drinking water lol.  My eyes are bright red.  I broke the blood vessels in them with my high fever, so they're all bloodshot... it's really attractive let me tell ya.    Angel came to visit me the second day.  She brought me a little baby dog beanie baby!  It's so cute.  She's such an awesome friend!!  Then Chris came to visit me yesterday.  We just chilled outside and talked :)  Hopefully he'll stop by again today!  I really like this one!  He's been really nice to me even tho he only met me once before I got sick. :D    Anyways my mom called Coach Scarpino since there's obviously no way I can try out.  She was actually really nice about it.  She told my mom that I'm already on the team so that I just need to come for pictures Thursday and then come back for practices whenever I am able to.  I guess that settles my doubts.  I really wasn't sure if I wanted to try out or even play, but I guess now my mom settled that one for me.  Oh well, no turning back now!  I guess it's not a bad thing.  It'll be fun!  Well time for another nap... lucky me!  </post></Blog>