<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Lately everyday seems exactly the same. Kind of like how the guy in the movie Office Space feels. He will go to work and do the same things everyday, then head home and have the same routine. My day's are a little different by the fact there is always some kind of drama going on and thenI will be expected to fix it. I will gripe about it from time to time, but if I sit down and think about how I would act if I didn't have anything going on, I would be bored out of my mind. I honestly wish I could have a more relaxed life so that I would be a little more peaceful, but then I believe I would get bored and then cause something to mess up. LOL I never believed this until a couple of weeks ago, I got home from work, sat down on my couch , and began to thinkabout howI had nothing to worry about at the moment and that this evening was going to be so relaxed, and an early one too! As I sit there watching my favorite t.v. show CSI Miami (of which I haven't sat down and watched in a couple of months.), well I realize that my phone hasn't rang in a couple of hours. I thencheck to see if maybe it was turned off, but it was still working. As another hour passes by I start to pace around my apartment upset at nothing. My friend Ryan calls and starts to talk to me and I get a little of an attitude for no reason what so ever and eventually end up hanging up on him.......At first I wasangry w/him and going around bad mouthing him until my friendMicah asks me why. Isat there for a second and then eventually came to terms with the fact I had no reason to be upset with him. I thentried to sit back and list all of the people I'vebeen having my little problems with in my head and askmyself why. I realized after evaluating a few of my situations, that it's been me all along for the most part!!! Why do I do this?? I seem to cause a ton of commotion in my life then stress my self out, for no apparent reason.I will beworking on thisfrom here on out. I also noticed that when a friend or family membergives me a call and isupset or in some kind of trouble, I tend to make it my problemuntil everything isok and they are feeling better. I don't know, I almost feel like I thrive ondrama......        I didn't have a stressful day at all today and my goal is to keep it this way. No problems, no anxiety, no sadness, no worries! :-) or :-(But the question I ask myself is, Am I satisfied or am I feelingas if something is missing?            
     

    
</post>
<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I've decided that I really need to try and finish all the projects I start, before attempting to start another. Today was another Monday, but I have been doing a lot of thinking. I was having a fun weekend until yesterday morning when I was completely freaked out by a friend of mine. I am almost feeling like he is making himself my project, rather than a friend. What I can't stand is that I really don't know if he's a friend or more or less. He's very talented and caring, but only when he wants to be. Very self absorbed. Now, he's asked me tobe here for him and help him out with certain weaknesses of his own. I don't see how someone can sit there and spill their guts out to another person then turn around and go against everything they had just said. I am almost to the point in my life where I just can not be here anymore for my friend....It's starting to interfere with my life, plus if I need someone to talk to he is very rarely available for me. I have my own problems and goals to think about, not someone else's!! Especially when I'm feel as though I am being taken advantage of. I can be here as a friend and someone to talk to, but I don't think I will be running to be there for him if he can not be a strong enough person to go with his word. Everyone knows what's right and what's wrong. All you have to do is have the strength to do what's actually in your heart. I think he honestly is afraid of the outcome, but I say suck it up and do it!! No talk, just go for it. Don't tell me show me.........        I'm supposed to go see my 2 little cousins today, but I am having to reschedule. I feel guilty about doing this, but after the stressful weekend I was put through, I am feelinga bit tired and weak. I need to rest tonight, then go tomorrow when I get off work. I am always doing something I feel like. I need some "me" time, yet I don't ever get it. When I go home tonight, I have to go pick up my desk, bring it home, set everything up that goes w/my computer, cook dinner, then get ready for bed. It's crazy, I call that resting, or my "me" time......       
     

    
</post>
</Blog>