<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Everyone else has a recap ^^ and Ran wanted a new entry, so why not?   July 21st- Stayed with my uncle today so we wouldn't have to wake up at 4am to catch the flight. Nothing special, but when I went to the mall in Hagerstown to buy a new gba the game it came with wasn't in the box, so we had to go back and get a replacement. It was pretty funny, poor woman at the store appoligized so many times...   July 22nd- Woke up at 6am for the 9am flight...geez, I'll never understand why we have to be at the airport so early. We got at the hotel at about 3, sat there for about twenty minutes talking to the guy at the desk about how we reserved rooms though it didn't manage to show up in the computer. (This entire time other Mysterium attendees were sitting in the chairs behind me and yep, I had absolutely nothing to say...because I'm a n00b, ah well.)Went for a walk with mom and ended up seeing "Saved" which was pretty funny for that kind of movie. I finally got up the courage to talk to the group in the lobby at about uhm....maybe 9, can't quite remember. It was such a relief! Everyone was friendly and I felt at home immediately ^^. Eventually the staff made us move up to a hallway upstairs and we played the name game and such, stayed up until 2, then I was so tired and fell asleepas soon asI got back to my room.   July 23rd- I slept in -oopsy- until 2 or so, made it down to the lobby to see the group already there and talking so I sat down and tried to join in conversation, which wasn't too hard, like I said, everyone was extremely friendly. Eventually, after sitting there about an hour Bishi'aila checked in, woohoo! I broke off from the group to go give him andAarona proper greeting then weheaded off to theMerril library tour, which was pretty cool.We got back to the hotel and I changed into mylittlegamers shirt and went to laser tag. It was pretty funny howsome people got seperated from the rest of the group because they didn't make it on thesubway in time. I made faces at the ones still standingoutside of the car when we left,fun :P.Laser tag was great fun, though I could only play onegamedue tothe amount of people, bleh. I got 7th place inthegame I was in, for being a 1337 sniper. Blttotally pwned me though... XD Let's see, the rest of the day I spent withBish and Aaron, andthen the rest of the group after those two went to bed, which was fun asalways. Bedtime around 1.  -gonnafinish posting the rest later ^^ too tired-   
     

    
</post>
<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hm.....it seems like I should have something really good to put in my first entry....but regretfully, all I've got going through my head right now is how much I need sleep. Just got home from  urlLink Mysterium and....oh...my....gosh! It was incredible! I couldn't have had more fun anywhere else. As I came in as a newbie to the myst community(having played the one player games and the beta - close of URU, as Katey,but never posting on any of the forums.) It really was an interesting experience. I hope next year will be just as great ^^ I guess I'll provide details later, both about Mysterium, and about myself. But for now, sleepy time.   
     

    
</post>
</Blog>