<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Incidentally, one finds that in Siberia, the mole is not only a treasured pet and fashionable accessory, but also a religious idol.WhereasUS mole enthusiast websites are distastefully sponsored by mole exterminator products (for example, the Mole Pro Trapping System, $39.95)resembling medieval torture implements, Siberia popularly celebrates the Bowl for a Mole Festival every February. Here, thousands of contestants throng the streets of the tundra in traditional dress, singing the national 'mole anthem' unique to Siberia, and ending with the strident tones of"Burrowing everlasting, mole will live forever". The festival includes a mole market where pet-owners can invest in all manner of mole accessories, including mole leads and collars, as well as mole toothbrushes that keep those cheeky little goofy molars fresh. And for the mole stallion, there are opportunities to engage with mole hotties for nominal stud fees on this festival day. The bowling itself is watched by millions on their TV sets at home, and by hundreds at the enormous screens that populate the hills of Siberia. With prizes ranging from 'The Mole Experience', a hugely expensive 'live-like-a-mole' experiment unseen any where else in the world, to the complete mole set up, including an entire mole family, the competition is massively over subscribed in Siberia, and has to turn away hundreds of entrants.  For the moles themselves, Siberia isthe utopia they can only dream of in Western Europe and America, where moles are treated with prejudice and misunderstanding. Whilstpassage to Siberia is a hazardous activity for the Western mole, some few have completed'the long burrow', asthe legendary journey istermed in moledom, and are now immortalised in brass monuments that can be seenat the pinnacle of every mountain inSiberia. Here's to those moles, and to the generations that follow, continuing that long historyofcourage and commitment!    
     

    
</post>
<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       TodayI have been shocked beyond belief by a willful act of destruction in which an academic establishment has acquiesced in the murder of innocents. It is only right thatI should tell the story of those who cannot talk for themselves and will never be able to read whatI have written,despitevoraciously burrowing into the very foundations of this intellectual milieu with all their might. This is a tail of mistaken identity, of ignorance, ofmisunderstanding, of woeful misrepresentation and of despicable discrimination. This is a tail of shocking and never-before-documented political 'spin'. This is the tail of the mole.       It is a quintessentially British problem, the mole. Enjoying nothing more than a harmless burrow in soft soil, Britain's shitty weathercreates formoley the perfect habitat.It is not that the mole specifically targets 'the lawn' for it's tunnelling activities, but that we createhis ideal environment, and then expect him not tomove in. It's like leaving a sweetie shop open and unattended and expecting the kids to much prefer hangingout at the grocers next door. Now we wouldn'tplant some smallexplosions in the sweetie shop for those opportunistic little blighters with sticky fingers - so why oh why do we lace the lawn withtiny bombsin the hope ofobliterating those cavern-dwelling garden terroristsin the underworld? What's our problem with moley?       It starts early, this mole aversion. From a young age, we delight intorturingthe mole's favourite delicacy, that squiggly pink invertebrate the earthworm. Conditioning such as this is rare - but inBritain alone,Ihave heardof dedicated hardcore anti-mole babiesbeing planted in lawns andbrainwashed intoindiscrimate earthworm destruction, even consumption (the tally of this being found whole in the nappy - true story).Moley's crime? Daring to challengeBritish domination of nature, epitomised in The Lawn. Witness Wimbledon - here we see grass that may as well be concrete painted green, so unflawed isit's finish. Not a bugin sight oncentre court, noearth surreptitiously appearing beneath the green veneer.Now whatI would considera real challenge would beWimbledon played on the fieldat the back of my house - a negotiation of rabbit holes,45 degree slants, 2 foot long grass,sheep shit,and yes, mole hills. The tennis would be a lot more dramatic, with better, more extreme, injuries and some really dangerous falls. Perhaps we could even get moles to be line judges, so as towitness the players getting violent and turning on the referee - always the highlight of the Wimbledon tournament.       But back to the lawn: the irony, of course, is that we don't blame ourselves for this oversight in ecological planning: indeed,we cannot acknowledge that ourfundamentally flawed weatherproduction facilitiesin this country could in any way be responsible for the triumph of the mole.Instead, the mole gets it -without even being able to see who exactly it has offended.    Where else would blind, furry, industrious little insectivores (NOT rodents, this is blatent propaganda from the anti-mole hardcore) be wantonly and violentlyexterminated by controlled, cynical,explosions? Where else would a miniature furry creaturewho creates underground kingdoms that would not be misplaced in a Tolkien masterpiece be eliminated en masse for daring to expel the detritus of its art onto the Brish lawn? And how can we justify this continued, unlawfuldiscrimination against moley,our British institutionwho gives us something to whinge about and thus hold up our cultural stereotype? We wouldn't bomb the bloody hobbits. And moley looks easily as cute as them in glassesand a waistcoat.     
     

    
</post>
<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       So this is my first attempt at writing here, inspired by jaemie! here goes....  
     

    
</post>
</Blog>