<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Okay, so maybe I'm not employee of the month. But when it's time to work, I work hard. It's quite annoying when a particular person sees that there is stuff to be done, but chooses to stare off into "la-la-land" instead. They should thank their lucky stars I'm not their superior because they'd be canned on the spot if it were up to me.  You know what's weird? When you see little kids you used to babysit back in the day, all married with kids. No one wants to enjoy the single life anymore huh? God dammit, that just means I'm freaking old. Maybe I am past the finish line? Skurrry. 
     
    
</post>
<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I want...  A silver pocketbike because they're so rad.  A Hurley surfboard  a roundtrip ticket to Hawaii so I could use it there.  A Hattori Hanzo sword to slice mofo's that annoy me in half.  And of course, I want world peace :). 
     
    
</post>
<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I have been thinking a lot lately. Many "what if's" have crossed my mind. Should I leave them as "what if's"? Or should I follow my heart and find out? I hope the big guy can give me a sign or two. He never fails me in that department. 
     
    
</post>
<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Maybe I'm too nice, but it would be hilarious to bust someone out when they are yapping on and on about nothing but lies.  It's the same bullshit over and over again.  Save your saliva.  No one wants to hear it anymore.  It's old.  It's lame.  And most importantly, nobody's impressed.  Obviously they've never heard of that ghetto phrase, "you ain't gotta lie to kick it."  And yes, I'm somewhat of a bitch.  Tell me something I don't know already.   
     
    
</post>
<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      It sucks to see someone you love be so stupid!  But I can't criticize because I too was an idiot in the past.  I guess it IS true that the people outside of your little "love bubble" can see the flaws of one of the persons in the relationship.  I hope to God I'm never ever that dumb! 
     
    
</post>
</Blog>