<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						     Dear You,       Hola peepz.. I'm now at the bench at block 45... 15 min more, my lecture for Business Management will commence. Haiz... Today oni a few ppl from my class will attend the lecture. cuz after BCA workshop, most of us wen home or some, went to watch movies.. haiz... y?? Y??   Ai ya. Dun care lar... Now, I'm thinking.. thinking about wot to write for the blog. I have difficulty thinking about wot to write but wen i start to write, i'd write non-stop. haha...   Now... I'm anticipating for the time wen i can meet my bez frenz again.. if there is a need for u to knoe who they r, Nur Jannah and Nur Zahiah are their names... ekekeekekeee..... we planned to meet each other n watch the movie Ella Enchanted.. but i got money prob le... got no enough money to pay for the tix. haiz... long story le.. if type now, got no time le... i got lecture to attend, remember?? so now muz get ready to switch off my lappy... so, adios mi amigo...   

						
</post>
<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						     Dear Peepz,      sian ar... i dunno wot to write.. dun like diz kinda things...    actually i came upon diz blog thingy by reading into my fren's blog.. n i was actually forced into joining n creating a blog for myself... haiz! actually i have my own webbie and even a circle... a lot of information can be found there.. even pix.. so now u see the reason y i dun like to write diz blog thingy.. cuz itz a waste of my precious time.. haiz...    wotdahell.. i'm now sitting at the table at the atrium.. got diz bazaar thing ar.. n itz damn noisy lor... dunno wot performance they have somemore.. i tink itz the blowing the horns thing ar... haiya.. i dunno lar... but itz damn irritating ok! n i dun understand y people still clap after they finished a piece of their performance.. gosh... dun they know that the performance sounds awful???    wot m i doing here ar?? i should be going home... heez .. itz like 5:40pm now.. ended my class today at 4pm.. almost everyday me n my fren yanie will stay in school to use the lappy.. haha.. wot for?? use the internet of course.. itz free mah... so we should take advantage of the conveniency provided.. but wotdahell again, we can't go to kazaa, napster, etc.... firewall thingy.. so troublesome..   ei! i should stop now... should be typing Mohanan's testimonial.. haha. ciao!  

						
</post>
<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						     My name is AIN    This is where u can find my profile.. Read on..     Birthday..   15 February 1987    Zodiac..   Aquarius    Occupation..   Banking  Finance Student / Self-Employed    Hometown   Woodlands, Spain, Mexico, Cuba, Paris    Interests   Movies, Travelling, Outdoor Activities, Food, Espanol, Spanish Songs, etc...  V.E of course!    Companies   Previously... Motorola. But ever since I use my Samsung hp, I quit!!! Hahahax! Now in V.E. Will retire when i'm around 30++ (wow... dat'z wot ppl say think 'far'... haha)    Schools   Bukit Batok PAP... Madrasah Ar-Raudah... Lian Hua Primary... Admiralty Primary... Madrasah An-Nur... Woodlands Ring Secondary... Ngee Ann Poly...    Favorite Music   Jaleo, Y Todo Queda En Nada, El Beso Del Final, Pero Mi Acuerdo De Ti, Ojos Asi, Que Me Quedes Tu, Bailamos, Satellite (Nave Espacial), Cuando Seas Mia, Guajira (I Love U 2 Much).... Haiya... A lot larh... Basically i like to listen to english songs as well as spanish.. I dun really listen to malay songs except for some...    Favorite Books   Fictional books(mostly). Stories whereby I can play myself as the characters when I'm reading the stories... &gt;&gt; Forbidden Love, Harry Potter, LOTR, Romeo n Juliet, Macbeth, Hamlet, Julius Caesar, The Merchant of Venice, ... lotz arh..!!    Favorite TV Shows   Comedies... coz they make me laugh!! Got a lot larh, actually... Buffy... Friends... Spongebob Squarepants ...    Who I Want to Meet...   Peepz who can be a great and fun person to hang with... Whom I won't get bored easily... U maybe?? Gee...   Wanna meet peepz i know who was from WRSS... Add me up! Wanna meet those from ADPS... Add me!! Wanna meet those from LHPS... Add me la!! N of course those in V.E... Add me! Add me!! Add me!!!    Hahax! anytin, juz email okiez... ain4life@hotmail.com Da..... Oh yeah... Do write my testimonial! Those peepz out there who haven't write my testimonial, u betta do!!! Those who wrote b4, write again lar... hahaha!!!   

						
</post>
<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						     Heya Lappy,       now now... feeling quite bored liao ar... got nothing to do... heez... my cousin's also in sch.. but she's in the clubhouse... at at the canteen!!! haiz...      told u later we'll be goin down to V.E.. hmm.... wot to do there? besides meeting the peepz there. hmm... where to get the 5? by fri le...       u knoe.. i like to listen to spanish songs... dun really knoe why la... haha.. umm, i dun like to listen to malay songs that much. unlike my sis.. she's a jiwang fanatic sia... eeeeye! hmm... mostly i listen to english songs which my sis in turn dun like to listen to... hahaaa!    

						
</post>
<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						     Heya Frenz,       hehe.. im at canteen 1 now.. with starrylink745. hmm... she's supposed to attend lesson at 10am.. but den ar, dunno why le, i saw her at the canteen already waiting for me. haiz... she skipped again!! aiyo...      u knoe wat... later we'll be goin to V.E. i din plan diz lar. but den itz study break week.. n starrylink745 had told  sam one about it and he expects us to be able to come down.. he gave us a task.. as well as the big fren... haiz... dunnoe if i can fulfil it by fri... but of course i'll try!! if u nvr try, u'll nvr knoe...      heeheee.... juz now i logged in to friendster.. haha.. got 1 testimonial to approve... i knoe itz from Joel... haha... cuz the other time i met him i reminded him to write one for me.. :) but den i sent another message to him on friendster again.. haha... purposely one.. to disturb and pester him oni... :p he ar... very jovial type of person... i tink he suits his name lar... Joel the jovial.. kakakaaa.... and he's so skinny.. kept telling him to eat.. previously was from Temasek Poly la... but den he obtained PhD already... hmmm... hehee.... oni certain people knoe bout diz..      mi now listening to spanish songs from diz radio station ar.. online one... currently listening to Enrique Iglesias' Para Que La Vida.. hmm.. quite a nice song lar... i tink if starrylink745 listens to diz one, she would like it bcuz itz slow... haiz... i dunno why lar... she like doz slow slow songs... u knoe the other time i introduced her to El Beso Del Final by Christina Aguilera, soundtrack from Dirty Dancing 2: Havana Nights... hehe... at first she said dat she dun like spanish songs... kakaaaka.. but now she's hooked to the song... wahahahaa.... n got 1 more song i introduced her... by Son By Four... i also dunno who la. the song is Cuando Seas Mia... kekekee... i copied the lyrics in my previous entry... itz a nice song too... datz y i like... :p  

						
</post>
<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						     Heya Peepz,       mi now at canteen 1.. heheee... with starrylink745 beside me. hmm, itz study break u see... so i dun hav to come to sch actually. but why am i here rite now? itz because of starrylink745 lar. haahaa.. she got lesson at 1pm. and she need to submit her portfolio by 12pm. but she dunno how to submit it using cd. haha.. u see, she dun hav the thumbdrive. so she had to submit using the cd. i told her to use cd-rw so that she is able to erase back the contents at a later time wen she gets back the cd. but den, she also dunno how to use it. so datz the reason why i came today... to help her lor!      i brought the cd-rw, thumbdrive, and also The Twins Effect vcd. starrylink745 wanted to copy it. i explained her how to write her documents into the cd.. haiz.. how come she dunno?? lucky she hav this teacher to guide her... hehe! but in the end, she din go for her lesson at 1pm. partly bcuz i told her not to go... :p      am i a bad fren?? did i influenced starrylink745 in a bad way??? i dunno le... someone has to tell mi!      juz now i watched Hellboy using my lappy. haha.. i got like 6 to 7 movies in my lappy rite now. haha... so far my fav. there is The Italian Job. hmm... very bored le... nothing to do in sch. u tink i'm the kind of person who would come to sch to study during breaks meh?? i very lazy one u knoe.. very the slack! i dunno how i would cope during the common test next week.. yeah... next week. and i'm still lazying around and slacking... sometimes i feel that i knoe i hav to do something... i knoe that i hav to do hw. but den i dunno which one to do, and i dunno which one to start. and i dunno which module hav hw, and i dunno and very lazy to find out... haiz. very bad!      how to pass test like diz??? help mi le... i very blur one... should i go for consultation? ... -.-      now already 3pm le... goin to go home soon.. but will i be studying or revising??? i dunno le... but i want to but i'm scared the lazy part of me will conquer me again!!! oh shit! like troy... hahaha... and that reminds me of V.E again... haiz... the other time (on sat), i went back there with starrylink745. we were from sch. i was doing project with my frenz and she was at the library doin hw...      the big fren called us yesterday telling us dat we were to come down to meet  sam one. big fren said that  sam one has something to tell us... wot abt??? haiz... starrylink745 and i were kinda scared to meet  sam one, cuz last time we met, we cried... haha! dun ask y... hmm......... we wondered wot  sam one want to tell us..      we took bus 75 from sch. all the way there. i called the big fren to ask him where he was... he said he was at clementi... wot? we tot he already reached V.E. i was talking with starrylink745 for a while but wen i got back on the phone, guess who was on the line... it was  sam one!!!  omg! big fren was with him?! wot for??? so i spoke with  sam one... at first he was speaking in malay, trying to disguise himself... ooo please lar... i knoe itz u! the voice was so obvious... so i changed to speaking in english... n den he said 'u dun like my voice is it?' wah lao! wat sey...  

						
</post>
<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    -------------------------------------------------------------- Son By Four - Cuando Seas Mia --------------------------------------------------------------  Voy a desnudar tu alma beso a beso hasta sentir Que tu cuerpo se derrama como lluvia sobre mí Por el borde de tu espalda voy a dibujar mi amor Sin ocultar esta pasión Cada latido de tu corazón Cada suspiro tuyo me pertenecerá  CORO: Cuando seas mía ya lo verás, baby Todas las noches serán buenas para hacerte el amor Cuando seas mía en cada sueño voy a estar yo Te voy hacer buscar, pedir, rogar mi calor.  Voy a deshojar tus sueños como la más bella flor Voy a vivir para siempre como esclavo de tu voz Desde el arco de tu ceja hasta tu dulce intimidad Caricias yo voy a sembrar.  Cada latido de tu corazón Cada suspiro tuyo me pertenecerá  CORO: Cuando seas mía (solo mía) ya lo verás, baby Todas las noches serán buenas para hacerte el amor Cuando seas mía en cada sueño voy a estar yo Te voy hacer buscar, pedir, rogar mi calor  Entrégate y yo te haré vibrar Suplicarás que te ame másen mis brazos volarás, hasta el cielo llegarás No escaparás jamás...  Cuando seas mía ya lo verás, baby Todas las noches serán buenas para hacerte el amor Cuando seas mía en cada sueño voy a estar yo Te voy hacer buscar, pedir, rogar mi calor...  Baby vas a pedir, vas a pedir mi calor  Cuando seas mía...  

						
</post>
<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						     Dear :: neptunez ::,       ha haiz... sian ar... mi now at the atrium... on sunday le... wah lao! still need to go to school. earlier, i followed my family to Rosewood (the condo near our house) to attend a wedding function. haiz. my bros swam in the pool.. wah.. havin fun sia. while mi juz lookin at them.. after swimming in the pool, they go for steambath sum more! haha...      after that, my mom n bros went to my aunt's house in Boon Lay there ar.. while my sis n i went to NP.. haha... i forced her to come wit me... hehe... i come to sch today to do project le... tomorrow due date already... haha. so rushing one. so busy... haha... see! still can write blog some more... aiyo... i should do my project first... ok! den i'll come back here if i'm done with it! btw, Zixuan and See Leng is here too! :p    haiz... lotz to do sia.. i did the conclusions and the methodology part. very sian ar doing dat.. my sis was also fed up. ya la.. she did nothing there, juz sitting beside me and playing the games in my hp. until the battery  flat ! hmm... we reached home about 10.30pm like dat. i tink ar. haha.. my mom tried to call us, but cannot reach us because both our hp were low batt. huahuahua... luckily i dun hav lesson tomorrow... cuz itz study break wat... haha.. but lala has to wake up early, u see... heeheheee!!!   

						
</post>
<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						     Dear Lappy,    Hey ya peepz! I'm quite sian ar now... i'm at level 3 of the library in Ngee Ann. itz 1:38pm now... got iac at 8am. came a bit late. but the tutor Chan Yoke Khiong was very nice... he dun mind me coming to class late.. i tink today was the 2nd time coming to iac late.. haha... i like this tutor, man.. although he may seem a bit  ngiau , he's very funny and understanding too... kuakuakuaaaa..... datz why i nvr got bored in his class...   but den i get bored easily in cats lessons... hahaaa.. of course, the tutor is nice and kind and old, but datz the prob lar i tink of being old... they a bit nice one.. nvr scold one... so i also take advantage a bit lar... got one day i came late for cats about half an hour later.. purposely one... can come early but dun wan to... haha... i was with sharmaine and lucia in the library, watching Willy Wonka  The Chocolate Factory... heheee!! i love that movie ok. itz so entertaining and very homely too... i liked the setting...      i was supposed to meet my starrylink745 fren le today... but den ar, she smsed me saying she was at home n wasnt feeling well so she's not coming to school and therefore cannot meet liao la.. haiz... ok lor nvm lor... den i was supposed to meet diz 3rd yr student ar.. her name is Maz. last time i got buy bodyspray and facial scrub from her one... den i ordered another 2 more bodysprays... same fragrance one... but den ar, i kept getting replies dat she was sorry dat she couldnt get them and give to me... ok lor nvm lor... i understand one... ya, u should knoe one thing... i'm a person who's very understanding and patient one... unless provoked! hahaha!!!      so now, i'm alone.... haiz... u know wot? today ar, for iac and cats, oni 3 people from my class attended le... out of 7 people.. damn pathetic lor... compared to the other tutorial group who also share the same iac and cats class as us... wah! i tink dey got full attendance... ey... paiseh le... where the heck are my other classmates??? tsk tsk tsk.... juz now wen i entered msn, i got chat with Abraham. wah lao.. he said he was tired and need to rest for tonight bcuz he will go clubbing... lame lor... haha... but he was about to tell me the reason why he wasnt coming today yesterday while i was chatting with him... but den i logged off first ar bcuz got poa tutorial to attend... haha... n guess wot? Abraham din come for it... hahaha...      sianx... now chatting with Weipei and Abraham at the same time... hhee... Abraham's going clubbing later at nite.. at mohammed sultan. haha... wonder where dat place is... hmm...    

						
</post>
<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						     Dear Viewers,       i ended class at 5pm today.. in fact later.. was supposed to meet starrylink745 at the canteen at 5pm. but nvm lar.. she understanding one... :p wen i reached the canteen, i was like looking out for her... it was hard for me to find her.. haiz.. she's playing hide n seek with me again.. but den at last i saw her! seating there... haiz.. i tink itz bcoz she wore dark coloured outfits dat made it hard for me to notice her.. hahaha!      den i told her to follow me to sports deck bcoz i need to attend the fencing demo trial thingie... but den i had a prob! i dun know where sports deck was... i asked her lar. but den she oso dunno... 8(      so wot i did was i smsed back the person who smsed me regarding the fencing thing.. the day before. n so dat was how i knoe where sports deck is.. it is at the 3rd level at the sports complex.. haha! starrylink745 was worried dat she might meet her SW teacher there n refused to follow me go there.. 8(     but i got her to send me until near the swimming pool there. aiyo! u scared for wot la gerl? ... so i went to the place alone...  alone ... along the dark alley... woooooo! hahaha... but nothing bad happened.. kekekeee..        in the end, of course la i reached the sports deck... well... i was late.. more than half an hour late for the demo thing.. heheee.. so wen i got there, they were briefing abt fencing n everything... itz on every mondays... 5 to 7pm... wear sports attire... bla bla bla... den they showed demos on the different methods of fencing... itz very nice u see... intriguing too... i was overwhelmed! kekeee... the peepz there were also very nice n friendly... so, of course i'm joining fencing! u knoe, my first instinct is correct!! i should learn to trust my 1st instinct lar...      hmmm..... i realised one thing... i was the only malay there! oh... not again! i'm already the only malay in my class... n going to be the only malay to get to join fencing diz yr... hopefully more malays would turn up for fencing.. heheee! we were given the chance to try the few steps in fencing.. like the 'on guard' position.. attack and retreat... bla bla... they were going to change the location later u see.. but den i told starrylink745 dat i wouldnt stay until sooo long... but i stayed until quite long lar... haha... until 6.40pm like dat... ahhaahaaa.... poor star... kekeeeekekeee!      so i wen to meet her again... i was walking along the alley outside the co-op near the library there... starrylink745 said she'd meet me outside library... so i was like looking forward to meet her there... but skali i heard someone called my name. i turned to my right.. there were these 2 ladies talking to each other and i tot i was hearing things... skali i looked at them properly and one of them was starrylink745! aiyo... see. i din realise she was there.. i din see her! wah lao! she really likes to play hide n seek with me. hahaa! guessed it was the dark clothing again.      hmmm... so later we went to the library to use the internet.. wah! we stayed until quite late le... until the library was closing... until the auntie came into the room to tell us that the library was closing in a few minutes.. weee!!! haha! quite paiseh le.. so we packed our stuffs and got out of the project room at level 2 and realised that we were the only students left in the library... akakakakakaaa~~~~!   

						
</post>
<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    urlLink .::ain4life::.   diz webbie is a circle.. can meet a lot of peepz there.. from all over the world.. but first, u gotta sign up as member... dun worry, membership is totally free! u can leave messages/not</post></Blog>