<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>25,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink Mailee  and I managed to spend about a buck.5 at the mall today... bought out Nordstrom’s. Couldn’t stop shopping and releasing our aggressions towards men by releasing our credit cards to the registers. It was exhausting and we left with hurting feet and aching backs – but damn, we are gonna look good in these new clothes!   After a quick nappy nap and spruce up shower we embarked on our typical Sunday night... we spent it at Noche. Before we even got there we expected it to be an eventful evening. Little did we know just how eventful it would be.   Mailee was convinced Joel was going to break up with her (how can they break up, they aren’t together?)… she was almost too sick to even come. When we did get to Noche we got a table for 3 (Mails, Miche, and I) and had the hostess take away the fourth chair. This was, it’s girls only, boys can’t come and butt in. Unfortunately, that tactic only worked until Mike and Joel arrived. They quickly pulled up chairs and joined in. Joel seemed a bit distant, but I did not feel a breakup looming. Bruce showed up, but left a moment later with Mike to go watch the Red Socks play. The girls, Joel and I finished up our food and headed inside to the bar. That’s where things got rowdy.   So I wasn't the only one giving  urlLink Michele  some lovin... urlLink Blair  showed up to put the hard press on Mich. He’s so cute, but his persistence is becoming a bit overwhelming. Just as we were beginning to enjoy ourself (get drunk) and flirt with the cute boys, who walks in – Chris. POS! I had no problem telling him exactly what was on my mind. He hung his head, asked if we could be friends and listed to me explain that there is absolutely no excuse for his flakiness and flightiness. I told him I wasn’t interested in hanging out with someone who doesn’t follow through on what they say. He and his cheap ass suit walked off and left me to play with my  urlLink real friends . After coming back for two more rounds of beatings, he finally got the point and said he hopes that I will be his friend and that we can hang out next time I’m at Noche… yeah right.   Oh…so where was Mailee during all this??? Yes, she left with Joel. Apparently, they discussed everything on the car ride home and agreed they are equally infatuated with one another. They want to see each other more seriously and bask in their twiterpatedness. Gag… I guess she forgot that ‘boys suck, and that’s sad.’     
    
</post>
<date>23,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Crazy...  ALL NIGHT LONG       urlLink         It started out normal enough... Loca Luna. Is that ever normal? No...we know what Loca Luna means - it means we are getting CRAZY ALL NIGHT LONG. Who are these  urlLink people ? All I know is that when Joy heard " urlLink CEO " she bolted to his side and stayed glued there. It was nice running into  urlLink Pilar and Diego , though I think they thought we were a bit out of control. Oh well...   We caught a  urlLink ride  of our CEO and his minions to Formosa (?) where we thought we could party the night away... wrong - it closed at 3:30a. However, we did get to spend some quality time with our beefy bartender.   We got a little bit desperate when we were kicked out of Formosa... had to immediately make some calls to find the after hours joint. Called Mike D to get party line number... talked to Dan. Don't know who he was, but he put me in touch with Wayne. Apparently Wayne has a penthouse pad on Peachtree where we could party till the break of dawn... which is exactly what we did. But first there was one problem…   How do we get there? Hitch-hike of course! So into the car I get with  urlLink London  and his buddy. Holy moly, what was I thinking. Right away I asked London whether he was going to rape me and cut me into small pieces… NO. Joy and Mailee weren’t so sure, however, so they pulled me out of London’s car and into the Ford Taurus driven by a gay guy. For some reason they felt that the  urlLink Gay Taurus man  was safer than the big black dude in the pimpin Mercedes. So off to 171 Peachtree we go… with London following.   Buzzed up… What is this? Who the hell rents out a damn penthouse and has no furniture or anything but rugs and a desk? Weirdos, that's who! Weirdos who pass out random drugged (?) tattoos and want to have threesomes or foursomes with us. We hung out on the rooftop deck and I got in a fight with some random quack about sex… whether it is for procreation or pleasure. I actually polled everyone there to see what their last experience had been for… let’s just say they tended to agree with me – pleasure.   Anyhoo… we managed to get Mr. Masochist to take us home. I went to my bed and Joy and Mailee went back to Michele’s. They managed to stay up till noon the next day, whereas I went to bed about 7:00am. Dad called at 8:30a ready to go shopping. At 9 I rolled up and met him at the damn Pride of Dixie Antique Fair. Hell of a day… shopped till I dropped, napped then saw Madonna. Whoa.        See more pics  urlLink here .         
    
</post>
</Blog>