<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>26,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      In Capistrano Beach, the sun comes up, a light breeze enters the room drifting with the scents of sand, sea and fog. If I am lucky, my cats are quiet for a few minutes while I gather my thoughts, if not, someone gets fed quickly. At 6:30 a.m., I know I have about 16 hours ahead of me. Weekdays, that means from 9:30 to 5:00 in the office. A commute of an hour each way, an hour of getting reasonably beautiful. So, 8 hours is in search of that which supports the remaining 8 hours.  I have to feed the guys, Foster and Woodie. Usually some laundry, and I try for an hour of work out in the gym we converted out of my son's bedroom when he moved out. That bit takes the first hour of the morning, leaving 7 for me.  I have two horses who live in boarding stables, and visit them each night to make sure things are ok, and feed them the supplements that make me feel as though I am doing them some good. This usually takes about an hour, because there is always someone to chat with, or a stall to clean. occasionally you can find me with a pitchfork in a silk suit and Ugh Boots. On Tuesday and Thursday I ride, or work them from about 6:00 to 9:30, so there goes from 1 to three and a half hours, leaving me fromsix to three and a half on those days...  On Monday, I stop by the Stables to See Zephyr and Desi, feed them and scat home. I spend some time with my wonderful husband, sometimes we walk down to Pines Park and watch the sunset. A glass of wine, or crisp water with lemon, holding his hand at the spot he asked for my hand 26 years ago. This can last forever..... Who counts minutes at a time like that? There are those days that Istumble home, so tired from a day of pounding heads in court and just hope to see Glenn, who may or not be playing hockey... His games are usually in the wee hours due to the popularity of ice time. We scratch together something to eat.... I clean the dust of the stables, and sit for a while, and read or watch some TV.  Weekends start with that early morning Feed me alarm clock, 6:30 a.m., a quick dress and run to the stables for an 8:00 a.m lesson with Ellen. Desi is technical, so my mind is engaged when I jump him,holding him over the jumps like hugging a teddy bear. We finish, and may take a short trail ride. I can't give him as much time in the Orange groves as he would like, becauseZephyr is waiting for his turn.  Clean him up, put him in his stall, and turn to the old man. Z is over 20, and looks like an 8 year old. He is sassy, smart, and usually a bit off. We trial ride, he drags his feet on the way out, until he finds his favorite places, when he remembers how it felt to be an Olympic jumper. Then, he soars over the paths, changing leads through corkscrew paths burdened with overhanging bamboo. I sit low in two-point, duck my head, and give him light contact as I trust him to carry me safely home. He usually does.  I pace both boys into the wash rack, Desi is stubborn so takes a bit more time; clean some tack; and head home at about Noon.  I garden, shop, clean house [rarely] and live my life as though every minute was fleeting. I have joy in the doing.  My valuable time, my precious time, is in my hands to use, live, and enjoy.   
     
    
</post>
</Blog>