<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
        I got free stuff at the library yesterday! YAY! go me! what happened was I met up with a few guy friends and their sisters, totaly by accident and the library was having a media swap. And one of em had a buch of stuff to trade (like 20 things) and so he gave me a few and I traded to get some stuff. I got a Star Trek game, it's call "Star Trek; Captains Chair". I got the "Pink: Misundaztod" cd and I got "Free Willy" the first movie,and I got a Playstation game called "Silouette mirage" and an A+E movie about egypt and stuff.           In all I had a good time and it went really well, today I did nothing but sit around and I knitted a little but not much. And I have drivers ed tonight. And right now were talking about alcohol, and about half of my class has drunk. Personally I never have and I don't think I ever will, that's just the way I am. So that's been my day so far, I may write later. Bye!   
     

    
</post>
<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Hi, I'm back, I'm not at the library waiting for the 'talk' I guess it is to start. Is should beging in about 10 minutes.      I guess I'm really getting into this blog thing. I mean this is my second post in like 2 hours. Insane right? Anywho, UI guess I'm just bored, and I do random stuff when I'm bored. I'm hoping to get at job at the library, and I have an aplication to fill out, only thing is, i've never done that so I have no clue how to do it. But my mom said she'd help me out after I did all I could.       It can get pretty boring just waiting for stuff. Oh, I found my knitting. I was looking through my closet and I found a scarf that I had been working on around february, and then my grandma got sick so I had to put it away for a while and then I just forgot it was there. Really stupid right? Anyways, started working on it again. I even brought it with me here to the library.  
     

    
</post>
<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Hi, everyone. This is my first blog. I just started it today. YAY me!! **giggle** anyways, as you may have noticed, I type like I'm talking. Now that's not a bad thing but it may get on peoples nerves when I do do this. Also I'm not using my real name. Just for seceurity stuff, I'm not trying to be mean by not telling you my real name but I'm doing it for my own security. But  I can tell you my age, I'm 16, and I'm going to be 17 in November. I'm going to be a junior in high school this coming September.         I'm also going to be yaking about my arts + crafts stuff, I really like to knit aand draw, but I also love to read about physics and stuff like that. I'm trying to go to this knitting group near me, but it's on monday nights and I have drivers ed on moday nights until the middle of August. But hopefully when I get the time I'll go.      Well, that's all for know, I may write later tonight if something interesting happens. I'm going to an event at my local library and it's "Meet a Video Game Desighner". So I may write, type, w/e about it later.   
     

    
</post>
<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
        Hi everyone.  Sorry I haven't updated in almost a month.  Not that I think anyone reads this anyways, but the reason I've been gone is that I got really busy with drivers ed, and my grandmother ended up in the hospital, so I was a little distracted. 
</post>
</Blog>