<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I love football, when the NFL Season ends for the year I experience weekend withdrawl for a few weeks. The Miami Dolphins have been my favorite team since I was 12 (No never lived in Florida, always Ohio).   Snipe: Ricky Williams retires at age 27? Talk about making you feel like the Fins are not going to have a good year even before camp officially starts. Granted Travis will get some more time but let's hope he's up to it.   Snipe: The huge deal being made about Teresa Heinz Kerry saying "shove it" to a reporter. Now if she would have really shoved him sure that would be newsworthy.   Just like the whole deal made out of one of the Bush girls sticking their tongue out at a reporter. Or Edward's kid sucks his thumb. Wow at age four? Now if he was 14 sure let's talk about it.   In the same Teresa vein, latest news is more old history. Thirty years ago she said she didn't trust Ted Kennedy. Must be a slow news week if that is the best they can come up with.   urlLink http://news.bostonherald.com/dncConvention/view.bg?articleid=37308    Snipe: Ralph Nader being upset that he didn't get to go to the Democratic Convention. Aww poor Ralph well hey buddy maybe the Republicans will let you come to theirs since they did what you can't seem to do. (Get yourself on a state ballot)   Snipe: Badnarik not being allowed as part of the presidential debates. Sure he's the Libertarian candidate and he is going to be on all 50 state ballots so why not let him participate? Bush and Kerry afraid that people might say "Wow who is this guy? He makes sense!"   Now off to read more online newspapers.      
      
</post>
<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm a fan of snopes, I admit it. Since hate is a strong word I'll say I "dislike" email forwards, especially those that are false. When you tell someone the story they just emailed you or posted on a message board isn't true you getsome typical reactions. First group, get angry at you for telling them the story wasn't true this holds especially true for those that like to believe political based forwards that are large on fiction and short on facts. If it is a humor based forward they get mad when you point out Andy Rooney didn't really say that or George Carlin, and accuse you of having no sense of humor. (Even when you point out to them giving the real person who wrote it credit would have made it just as funny.)   Second Group, laughs about it and says sorry. Second Groupers typically end up becoming mini "snopers" and after they've been "snoped" a few times actually snope themselves.  And what is wrong with that? That's what we should all be doing unless we are writing fiction.   I admit I love to point this out moreso to the First Group. Especially those who are "fact haters" they want you to believe it because it makes their point.   I used to spend alot of time on the excite message boards, close to 40,000 posts, but I realized something. I rarely had a chance to just discuss what I wanted to discuss. So hence this blog creation, where I will post the lastest stuff making it's way around the net that is pure bs or part bs and some political snipes along the way.  I am a liberal, though not a democrat. I'm more of a "lilberal libertarian", I don't expect everyone to agree with me, but let's have some fun. Life is to short to not have fun.  So Welcome and I hope I can manage to not only entertain you but inform you.  
      
</post>
</Blog>