<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						   The summer semester is officially over - took my final yesterday... we'll see how that goes. BTW - I got a call from Jimmy D the other day. He wants to email me this letter. I'm curious, but I'm also willing to bet I know exactly what's in it.   Just checked my grades - 100% on my Algebra final! Yea for me.  Nise  I will be going to the Stitch  Bitch at Aalim Saturday - I REALLY need to get to work on my costume - I don't want to bring just the pieces! I also need to finish her bra. I'm hoping I can get some help with hemming my chiffon panel skirt. Wish me luck.  - Kirvi   

						
</post>
<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

						
						    Everyone says thatkeeping ajournal is good for mental health, good for the soul. Of course, I've never been much into what anyone else says (see profile, and a dictionary for the meaning of "introvert" if necessary.) Studying for my Algebra final this week - I have to take it by tomorrow if I want the extra credit points. Of course, I had to take tard-math due to my having enjoyed the 80's far to much. That and a 12 on the math portion of my SAT's. Think about that for a moment. Allow it to really soak in. 12, baby. Big 12.      After the total blow-out of a vacation I just had - wait, that could be misconstrued in this context. Strike "Blow-out," insert one of the following - "annihilation" "destruction on a global scale" "seventh outer ring of Hell". Ok, better. Now that I'm back, I can't believe I didn't buy any of the cowrie shell belts or beaded/sequinned wrap skirts I saw. I really hate to spend money, and I was pretty occupied with fighting that part of my personality that wanted to act like the child of rich, divorced parents - "you guys got me into this shithole - now compensate me materially for my anguish." So I didn't really buy anything much. Tommy did get me this beautiful carved statue, it's a man  a woman, very minimalist. And I got my tattoo finally. I say finally, like I'm the one who's been wanting one. Oh, I kicked the idea around, but T really wanted one, and he really wanted me to have one too. So I got mine first.  urlLink http://www.geocities.com/morrigandances/dragons.jpg        Well I should probably get back to work - which today means, studying for Algebra final while pretending to contribute to the corporation's goals. And stealing FudgeRounds out of the Atlas snack-drawer.      - Kirvi   

						
</post>
</Blog>