<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I'm a slob. My apartment is an absolute mess and disaster. How do I let it get to this point? I have always been like this. I remember as a little girl my Dad getting angry that I couldn't keep my room clean. One day after work, he got a few big, black trash bags and just shoved all my stuff into them. He told me that he was going to put it out for the trashman!! Actually, he just put them in the basement. There is a smell in my apartment that I can't figure out where it is coming from. eewww... I try to be more organized, more efficient, more clean; but, it just isn't working!! WHAT IS WRONG WITH ME!?!!? Are there other people out there like me? It's not that I don't likea clean place. I really love it when it's all clean. I feel proud, less stress, and like I've really accomplished something. Am I destined to be a slob forever!?    
     

    
</post>
<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Do you ever feel like the weight of the world is lying on your shoulders? I just feel like that lately. Having an intern finishing with me and feeling responsible for her performance after leaving my site. Also, being responsible for therapy for kids in the schools...It can just be overwhelming at times. To think, I have the responsibility to use the power of music to it's fullest to help "cure" my students. It's unbelieveable at times! Yet, so amazing as well. To see kids learn to talk and sign in music before anything else. There are no words to describe how that makes me feel, let alone their parents. Sometimes, the things of the world just saturate me. Tonight, I spent most of the night looking at clothes on the internet to buy. Not that I can really afford any new clothes for fall, or that I really "need" them. Yet, I wasted all evening looking at things and deciding which ones I needed to buy. With this society, it almost seems impossible to escape the materialism and secular nature of everyone around me. I feel the need to expand my business in the way the make themost money, not abouthow to help the mostchildren. It's discouraging. It's disgusting at times. It's frightening that this is what the world is coming to. And, it's so hardto not be saturated by it everyday.    
     

    
</post>
</Blog>