<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi everyone - Thanks to Stephanie forposting. I guess there is no way for anyone but me to post except to comment. I believe each of us can create a blog of our own and connect it to this blog somehow so we will all be able to post rather than just comment. For now, use the comments and we'll figure out how to arrange another way soon.  I have had an intense day today. I was triggered into an implicit memory this evening when I was relating a past life experience to a friend who wasin the past life. I told her how her life ended in this past life that we shared and then started to have the implicit memory emerge. At first, I didn't recognize it as an implicit memory but later, when I did a mood log on it, it was crystal clear. (For those of you whoaren't familiar with the termimplicit memory I refer you to the work of Daniel Siegel, M.D. and for the mood log, David Burns, M.D.) I wrote in my mood log the following:  This always happens. What happens?  I asked myself.  I want something from a woman, usually someting emotional, I don't get it and I get agitated . This is exactly what went on day after day and month after month in my relationship with my mother. I was stunned to see what I had written with knowing it. This is a clear implicit memory and I had been trying to see how what was going on with my friend was causing what I was feeling. Implicit memories always come to us as if they were being generated by the present circumstances which is completely erroneous. This is another building block of delusion. When I wrote this and read it and realized it for what it was, the emotions subsided greatly, completely really. In the past I would have spent a lot of time trying to work this out with someone else and probably frustrated them and myself thoroughlly. This sort of interaction has passed for relationship with me for my entire life. I am so grateful to be learning so many really useful tools finally. There is such amazing research that is bearing fruit lately. I am so grateful to have survived to be able to participate in this millenia.  Love to all, Gary 
     
    
</post>
<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi fellow bloggers. It is my intention to work out a few more ideas each night on how to proceed. I am hoping some of you will join in here when you are ready. The more input we have in the process, the more it will work for everyone. I would like group members to post a list similar to mine in my first post and then make a daily update of their progress or lack of progress for the day. This is what I will be doing and I am open to suggestions from my experience of doing it and from you watching me do it or doing it with me.  I did my meditation this morning even though it meant getting to work late. It is important enough to me to put work second even though I am very committed to my work lately. I did not watch TV even though I was tempted just a little. Women have been glowing around me lately but I am aware a lot of the time that this is a function of my love/lust addiction and not something to do with them. Not that women aren't beautiful and wonderful, they just aren't quite the mythical beings that my distorted percerptions can make them out to be. I have taken a pledge to stay out of romantic relationship for 6 months starting on July 15. This should not be too hard for me to accomplish but relationships have traditionally caught me unawares which means that I have cultivated them unconsciously. I don't want that to happen again since there has always been a large component of unresolve past history present in my past relationships. I prefer to enter even the arena of relationships consciously and with intention. My intention for now is not create a romantic relationship and to move away from anything starts to look like one for now. I had an episode of implicit memory this evening when my ex-wife gave me instructions to meet her and our daughter at one place and then went to another without telling me for 45 minutes. I waited and felt the building of implicit tension in my stomach. I know enough about these sort of situations to recognize that I was reacting to past trauma and to work on connecting with what I know about my past. I remembered being four and being left in a car in a mall parking lot. I hated it and crawled out and went into Sears to look for my mother. I knew she punish me but the punishment felt less threatening that being alone any longer. Whenever I have to wait I get agitated and upset. I believe this is connected to being left alone when I was young. I have an earlier memory of being left alone in my crib. I don't really have a clear memory of the incident but instead a memory of my step grandfather making fun of me when I was eight or nine. He was joking about a time as an infant when I found my own feces and smeared it onto my face and perhaps ingested some of it. I had a flashback when I heard him describe my state and had a hazy memory of the incident. It was a very painful incident to undergo at the time. My grandmother, his wife, chastised him and told him to stop but hushed the whole thing up as best she could. My family was very sick and abuse of this sort and worse was hushed up regularly.   Thank you for letting my share this with you. I hope it isn't too much for any of you. It affected me deeply and left me addicted to shame, hopelessness and misery.  Love, Gary 
     
    
</post>
<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Here is my first post. I will send you my list of intentions that I meditate on each morning.  I intend today to: 1. See clear evidence of my creative capabilities manifested in my experience. 2. See miracles in and around me. 3. Appreciate my life and Life. 4. Be aware of cravings for neuro-peptides 5. Gently resist those cravings. 6. Experience withdrawal symptoms as evidence of awakening. 7. Help others find peace and freedom. 8. See the light in myself. 9. See the light in others.  The addictions I have identified so far are: 1. Fantasy or real sexual and romantic contact with attractive women. 2. Misery and hopelessness. 3. Sugars and carbohydrates 4. Fear and worry. 5. Television/ media. 6. Poverty. 7. Harrassment and judgement from significant others.  I have been abstinent from all of these since I saw the movie on July 15. I have had a slip on the carbohydrates last weekend when I was with my ex-wife and my daughter. This is an amazing record for me. I have never identified most of the elements on this list let alone be astinent from them so long. My intentions are beginning to manifest in my daily life and I am beginning to see the evidence I intend. I am noticing that when I see the evidence of my creative capabilities that I also feel quite strange and often sick to me stomach. I believe that these are physical syptoms of withdrawal from addiction to neuro-peptides associated with failure and misery. Seeing my intentions manifest gives notice these elements that their days are numbered and they are not pleased to realize this. They send waves of distress through my body and seek ways to sabotage the process.  Please let me hear from you and send any support that occurs to you. For me, support does not at this point include specific advice about any situation I am facing or not facing in my life. Support for me is more about sharing common or similar experiences and giving encouragement to each other's efforts. Simply stated, support =unconditional love. If you are addicted to criticsm or complaining or withholding that is fine but please identify that in yourself and refrain from acting it out on others in the group. Love, Gary  
     
    
</post>
</Blog>