<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      God, he doesn't even want me to touch him anymore! It's so discouraging. So I spend my time on here, chatting, writing, surfing, doing whatever to keep myself occupied and distracted. The worst part about it is that my "friends" and family can't wait for our relationship to end. Every time I talk to them I can sense it in their voice when they ask me how things are between us. They've been wanting our relationship to fail from the very beginning. That's just great. I don't want it to end. I just want us to communicate. Why do we always have to fight? Things just aren't so wonderful. It's depressing. I wonder if he even loves me anymore?

     

    
</post>
<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        This blog is here mainly for my purpose only, and I'm giving you permission to read it. If you don't like what I write here than by all mean DON'T READ IT. It's that simple. I am not holding a gun to your head or forcing you in any way to read what I have to say. So if you have any problems with it than please don't bother me with your whining. I may post my opinion, which I fully intend to do and I would require you to respect that. I may post things that bore you or don't interest you, but do I really need to tell you that maybe this isn't something that you should be reading then?   
  Just like anything else, you have the power to decide what you listen to, what you read, and what you do. If you don't like what's on TV, turn it off. If you don't like what's on the radio change the channel. You have many options. That's the awesome thing about our country! I have the freedom to say whatever I want, and you have to the freedom not to listen. Have a great day.   

     

    
</post>
<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Princess:'(
  Crisp:hi :)...why are you crying?
  Princess:I don't know. I just feel crappy.
  Crisp:aww, well I feel crappy too...my neighbor kept me up last night 
 Crisp:and now I can’t sleep lol 
 Crisp:why do u? 
  Princess:just lonely I guess. I miss Aaron. I haven't been able to spend much time with him lately. He's going to work on Monday on his day off to hang out with people he works with and not me.
Princess: He has some meeting at work but it’s not required. 
  Crisp:awww({)
  Princess: and then he's going out drinking with all of his co-workers 
  Crisp:well that’s just unlucky
Crisp:what times does he work again? 
  Princess:yeah...:-Princess: well he's working right now until 11 and then his next official day at 3
Princess: and I have a virus
  Crisp:well u should go out and do something
Crisp:oh no
  Princess: what am I supposed to do?
Princess:go drinking!
Princess: meet some guys
  Crisp:I meant with Aaron
  Princess:when?
  Crisp: does he know u miss him?
  Princess:it all just sucks. So how are you?
  Crisp:well this is 2nd time I’ve been disturbed in night in 3 leap right through to feel ok
Crisp:but I guess it is the weekend.... or was
  Princess:why can't you sleep?
  Crisp:so hopefully I’ll be ok now the weekend is over
Crisp:music being played by neighbor and talking
  Princess:oh.
  Crisp:yea
  Princess:have you talked to them?
Princess:what time is it there?
  Crisp:I don’t really...we don’t get on that well
Crisp:1.23am
  Princess:um, call the non-emergency police and complain
Princess:Don't you have noise ordinances?
  Crisp:no..that would just cause more problems.... my building is for lth problems
Crisp:but don’t worry he's usually not to bad#
 Princess:they don't have to know you called. Aren't there other people 
Crisp:it will be fine
Crisp:I’ll put up with it as long as its only a couple of nights a week
Princess:(N)
Crisp:maybe ...ill ask
Princess:so what did you do this weekend?
Crisp:nothing...because not sleeping right thru....although Saturday I got 
Crisp:I’m just to tired
Crisp:to do much
Princess:bummer
Crisp:yea
Princess:I should go see a movie
Princess:or something
Princess:I don't want to stay here
Princess: maybe I'll go eat
Princess:Crisp:hmmm
Princess:not sure
Crisp:eat out?
Princess:no
Princess: I have leftover food my mom brought me
Crisp:cool
Princess:Chinese and lasagna (how do you sp?)
Crisp:lasagna
Crisp:yum!!!
Princess:e* words are weird
Crisp:that’s Italian for u lol
Princess:well English makes as much sense!
Crisp: yeah!!
Princess:Have you ever seen the Daily Show with Jon Stewart on 
Crisp:I don’t have many cable channels..7 free ones I think
Crisp:I have seen clips of it..it looks gr8
Crisp: is that the discussion progamme?
Crisp: discussion
Princess:actually it wasn't The Daily show-it was Crossballs, where they ing American and not English (English is what you speak in England)!
Crisp:ah cool...sound funny lol
Princess:Go to comedy central's website and you can see clips of 
Princess:hold on
Crisp: cool I will tomorrow..........I’m not staying long
Crisp:staying*
Crisp:ok
Princess: http://www.comedycentral.com/mp/play.php?reposid=/multimes/crossballs_105.html 
Princess: http://www.comedycentral.com/mp/play.php?reposid=/multimes/crossballs_105.html 
Crisp:it might take 10 mins to load
Princess: keep the link and listen to it later if you want
Princess:the second link is just the link to the show
Crisp:they're both same hehe
Princess:really?
Crisp:don’t worry lol
Princess::-$
Crisp:its loaded brb
Crisp: lol
Princess:(?)
Crisp:quite funny lol....cause I talked to some Americans on voice chat couldnt speak English lol...which they didn’t
Crisp:like...no I said they speak American not English....it was funny 
Princess:Yeah, the language in England and here are quite different 
Crisp:like shag lol!!
Crisp: a dance&gt;?
Princess:bugger/bloody
Princess:dink
Princess:I don’t now
Crisp:what’s a dink?
Crisp:lol
Crisp:to shag means to make love here lol
Princess:yes I know
Princess: remember- we had
Crisp:sorry .....lol.....not at this time of night lol
Princess:AUSTIN POWERS
Crisp:ahhhhhh!!!
Princess:I couldn't remember-I had to think for a minute
Princess:minute
Princess:LOL
Princess:I can't type
Crisp:I still have to see the 3rd one
Princess:Goldmember
Crisp:neither can I at 1.49am lol
Crisp:ah yeah cool
Princess:Um, yeah
Princess:So you haven't heard of dink?
Crisp:no!!
Princess: I heard it was in reference to *sounds like*
Princess:LOL
Princess:tip (slang)
Crisp:its American?
Crisp:lol no never
Crisp:or I'm getting old lol!!!!
Princess:Really!
Princess: It sounds English
Crisp: do u know rhyming slang ?
Crisp: cockney lol....
Princess:That's Irish!
Crisp:no London lol!!!
Princess:I'm drunk!
Crisp:ah ok!! haha
Princess: What? London? where's London/
Princess: LOL
Crisp:jooooooooooo heheh
Crisp:you are talking 'pony'
Princess:I see Paris I see France I see Johnny’s underpants
Princess:or is it
Princess: I see London, I see France
Princess:I see Johnny’s underpants!
Princess:LOL
Princess: :-P
Crisp::-O who's Johnny?! lol
Princess:You don't even want to know pony
Princess:I don't know
Crisp:pony and trap (its a small horse cart)
Princess: I love you man!(K)(L)
Princess:NONO
Princess:Never mind
Crisp:lol
Princess: It's a song about something else’s
Crisp:ahhhh ok!
Princess:Genuine
Crisp:lol
Princess:is the name of the group
Princess:yeah....
Princess:moving on
Princess:...
Crisp:lol
Crisp:zzzz
Crisp:lol
Princess:heard of it! I am NOT boring
Princess:when I'm drunk
Princess:I smoke
Crisp::P
Crisp::-O
Princess:when I'm on fire
Crisp:lmao
Crisp:u know lmao?
Princess:the cow?
Crisp:lol
Princess: lmoooo
Crisp:heheh :P
Crisp:laugh my arse off
Princess: no, I’m afraid we've never met
Crisp:u are funny when u are drunk
Princess:arse! Now there's something else we don't say-I mean really-
Princess:we say ass!
Princess:or trunk
Crisp: Irish Scottish and English ppl...oh and the welsh lol
Crisp:boot!!!
Princess:booty!
Crisp::P
Crisp:that’s over here now lol
Princess:bootilicios
Crisp:I heard that too :D
Princess:I....can...touch...my...chin...with...my...tongue
Princess:LOL
Princess:(A)
Crisp:I have a short tongue lol....:(
Princess:TMI???
Princess:Yeah
Crisp:tmi???
Princess:too much information
Princess:whatchatalkinbout
Princess: What am I saying?
Princess:LOL
Crisp:LOL
Princess:(K)
Princess::-P
Crisp:(K)
Princess:(Y)
Crisp::D
Princess:(H)
Princess:(%)
Princess:r:'-)
Princess: I have no idea
Crisp:xxxxxxxx uuuuuuuuuuuu0ssssssssssssss....oops cuz I just dozed off :P
Crisp:no really
Princess:if you're bored you're boring!
Crisp:I’m not bored I’m tired lol
Princess:NO:'(
Princess::-(
Princess::'(
Princess::'(
Princess:I have abandonment issues
Princess: you can't leave
Crisp:(C)(C)
Princess:huh?
Crisp: ok ill stay a bit longer
Princess:what is that?
Princess:cc
Crisp:coffee
Princess:are you drinking now?
Crisp:no
Princess:what does coffee have to do with you?
Princess:or me
Princess:or you
Princess:or me
Princess:or anything
Princess:do you like me?
Crisp:HEY!! I realized I have lost weight today...I’m almost thin again
Princess:I will require that you leave your house once a week!
Crisp:of course I like u({)
Princess:and I will live with you
Crisp:u will ?!
Princess:yes
Crisp:in my computer
Crisp:lol
Princess:I'm too big for your computer
Crisp:ok!!
Princess:maybe a computer from the 80's
Crisp:hmmm yeah
Princess:kkdkdkdksksjrokdjsdkfmeridfklasmkr
Crisp: :)
Princess:&gt;(
Princess:&gt;)
Princess:&gt;:
Crisp:REALLY:-O
Princess:experimenting
Princess:smileys
Princess:Detachable Penis
Crisp:It's less illegal here now
Crisp::-O jo!!! hehe
Crisp:lol
Crisp:lol
Princess:its a hilarious song
Crisp:ah! k
Princess: NO, I have one?!!!LOL
Crisp:ahhhh ooooooook :D
Crisp:lol
Princess:ahah
Princess:bibidybobidyboo
Crisp:she has one
Crisp: ;)
Princess:Julie Andrews?
Crisp:I expect so lol!!!
Princess:I think you have one
Princess:NM
Princess:ok
Princess:so
Princess: eating yet
Princess: cereal
Crisp:yeah...jumbo oats
Princess:lol
Princess:I don't want to know
Crisp:very healthy lol
Crisp:hehe
Princess:bad bad bad picture!
Princess:go away
Princess:uhuhuhuhuhuh
Princess:alrighty
Crisp:sulks in the corner
Princess:the picture dork
Princess:in my head
Princess:my head needs to go away now
Crisp:ok lol
Princess:how's yours?
Crisp:a lil blurry
Princess:I am just walking right into these~!
Crisp::)
Princess:what is that??
Princess:Someone taught me something once-do you want to know 
Crisp:yea!!
Princess:8==========D
Princess: Oyh ho
Princess: 8=====D
Princess:I am Jewish now!
Princess:LOL
Crisp:lol:S hehe
Princess:no that would be
Princess:8====
Crisp:hahaha
Princess:8====)
Princess:LOL
Princess:I didn't even mean to do that?
Princess:LOL LOL
Crisp:lol
Princess:rotflh
Princess:LOL
Princess:LOL
Princess:ow
Princess:it hurts
Princess:make it stop
Princess:Thank you!
Princess:I love you
Princess: you're so awesome
Crisp:::::::D
Crisp:so r u
Princess:You made me feel better
Crisp::D
Princess:oh my goodness
Princess:that was really funny
Crisp:lol
Princess:I am BAD
Crisp:1 more cig then bed
Princess:you are supposed to do that AFTER!
Crisp:u r SO naughty lol
Princess:You love me
Crisp:puts jo over his knee ehehe
Princess::-O
Princess:You're like Aaron
Crisp:lol
Princess:he does that all the time
Princess:nm
Princess: !
Crisp: oh really!!!!
Crisp:lol
Princess:he has a butt thing
Princess:thing
Princess:Call me
Crisp:tmi :P
Princess:right now
Princess: hi
Crisp:ill have to log off
Princess: are you serious!
Princess:wow
Princess:I was joking I thought
Crisp:lol...I’m half a sleep lol
Princess:I will wake you up!
Crisp:no lol
Princess:Yes
Crisp:ok
Princess:yes what?
Princess:LOL
Princess:I don't know what's happening
Princess:I think I'm manic
Crisp:me too!!
Princess:or something
Princess:LOL
Crisp:lol
Princess:I'm really hot right now
Princess:I need air
Crisp:ok
Princess:confused
Crisp: is air con working?
Princess:are you leaving me?
Princess:air can?
Princess:what's that?
Princess: I use it to blow my computer
Princess:I mean the keys
Princess:on the board
Crisp:I use the Hoover
Princess: um, vacuum?
Princess:tmi!
Crisp:yeah but air can is better
Crisp:ok
Princess:NM
Princess: so what's happening
Crisp:I’m sleepy
Princess: are you passing out?
Crisp:nearly lol
Princess:I need you
Crisp:ok
Princess:ok
Princess: for a good time! LOL
Princess:jk
Princess:so I will talk to you later
Princess:tomorrow?
Crisp:lmao
Princess:what is lmoo?
Princess:lmao
Crisp:ok... if I wake up lol
Crisp:moooooooooo
Princess:seriously, what is that?
Crisp:don't you remember?
Crisp:rofl...roll on floor laughing
Princess:but that' snot! LOL that's not lmao
Crisp:LOL
Princess:hi
Princess: who are you
Crisp:hi :)
Princess: what is lmao?
Crisp:I’m an alien
Princess:Lamaze
Princess:you're an alien
Crisp:isn’t that a game?
Princess:since when?
Princess: It's a breathing technique (spelling might be wrong)
Princess: for childbirth
Crisp:ahhh
Crisp:a friend had baby boy on Tues.
Princess:Crispy boy!
Princess:what is lmao?
Crisp:lol
Crisp:laugh me arse off me dear
Princess:little men around oven
Princess:OH right, the arse thing!
Crisp:what have u been drinking lol
Princess:I want you
Princess: do you have to be tired
Crisp:I’m here lol
Crisp:yeah :(
Princess:booger
Princess:snot knot
Princess:lol
Crisp:lol
Crisp:Princess::)
Princess:more pics?
Princess:for me?
Princess:yet?
Princess:yeah?
Crisp:ill take some when the sun comes out
Princess: of you! @
Princess: right now
Princess: hey
Princess: log me
Princess: log
Princess: onto
Princess: yahoo
Princess: and let me see you
Princess: !!!OL
Princess: Yeah
Crisp:lol
Princess:web cam
Crisp:u sure? lol
Princess:why not!
Crisp: I must look terrible
Crisp:lol
Princess: doesn't work
Princess: I'm on Meca®
Princess:hold on
Crisp:k
Princess:it's hot
Princess:hi!
Crisp:hi :)
Princess: you look fine
Crisp:gd
Princess:you have curly hair?
Crisp: yeah I been blow drying that doesn’t help
Princess: I didn't know that
Princess:Go drink something
Crisp:curly on top
Princess:alcoholic
Crisp:no I won’t sleep then
Princess:then we could have fun!
Crisp::)
Princess:smile!
Princess:Don't pass out
Princess:you should keep it on all the time!
Crisp:lol
Crisp:big bro
Princess:there is a delay
Princess:I'm watching you!
Princess:but it's slow
Crisp:lol I know
Princess:maybe when you get cable!
Princess:good thing you can't see me!
Crisp:I cannot afford it
Crisp:lol!!
Princess:wait, I thought you were going to get it!
Crisp:I was
Princess:(K)
Crisp:(K)
Princess: I feel weird
Crisp: can u see the lavender background?
Princess:I'm not drunk anymore
Crisp:ok
Princess:huh? in your app? it looks green
Crisp:maybe
Princess:curtains
Crisp:app?
Crisp:no in the messenger window
Princess:apartment (ap)
Princess:no
Princess:I can't
Crisp:ok
Princess:where did that plane come from
Crisp:hehe
Princess:I'm flying over there as we speak
Crisp::-) 
You have asked to share this background with Princess:. Please wait for a lt+Q) the pending invitation.
Princess:ssssssssmokin'
Crisp:lol
Princess:anyway, are you calling?
Crisp:if I feel ok
Crisp::)
Crisp:what time is good
Princess:not now?:'(
Crisp:u joking
Transfer of shared background is complete.
Crisp: ?
Crisp: it might disturb my neighbor
Princess:nah
Princess:why
Princess:why would that disturb your neighbor
Princess:are you going to yell at me?
Crisp:no..thin ceiling/floor
Princess:you're cute
Crisp:I should really go to bed now its 3am
Crisp::D
Princess: um, yeah tomorrow (my time) at around 3. What is that your 
Princess: think fast!@
Crisp:um lol
Crisp:I’ll work it out in bed lol
Princess:excuse me!
Princess:good night
Crisp:its ok
Crisp:good night :)
Princess:save this
Princess:thanks
Crisp:have some coffee lol
Princess:no save the conversation
Princess:and eme tomorrow
Crisp: I have
Princess:love you
Crisp:ok love u



     

    
</post>
<date>28,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        urlLink http://volunteer.johnkerry.com/mysite/?ref=380232   Here's that more on Kerry that I mentioned:   Welcome to my Kerry page! I'm glad you are here. I am supporting Kerry because of everything Bush has done wrong! I don't want to imagine Bush getting another term being in control of our country. He has used us and treated us unfairly and unjustly. He has used our military for his own personal agenda, not for the good of our country or anybody else’s country. He is greedy, and money hungry. And he is most certainly NOT a Christian by any degree. I highly recommend seeing "Fahrenheit 9/11". It exposes the evil things that Bush has been associated with since his father was president. Who knows what else he has conspired. Unfortunately I have somehow positioned myself to be surrounded by conservative Christian republicans. I have been firmly informed by those I used to call my friends that there will be no support for Kerry from any of them. They are blind and close-minded, and that I cannot support either. They have decided to belong to the Bush cult. So, I will essentially be starting from scratch. I am still a Christian, but I do not have to be a republican to believe in God or Jesus. I believe in loving ALL people regardless of who they love. I believe in the God given right to freedom, the freedom to think for yourself, to make your own decisions, and to say whatever you feel like saying. I believe in the Constitution that this country was founded on. I believed in what this country stood for before Bush took over. I want to believe in it again! I believe it is wrong to legally force your own beliefs onto other people. It is dangerous to try to create a society of people who think, act, behave, and talk like everyone else. We are diverse. We are all different, and we are all imperfect. And that is what makes us great. So, if you can join me in supporting Kerry, not only will Kerry be grateful, but so will I. I need to find a new group of friends who are open minded and kind. I hope you have a wonderful, fulfilling day in whatever you may be doing!  

     

    
</post>
<date>06,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I just want to feel wanted, for who I am, forever, because I don't think I ever have. 

She Is His Only Need

Lyrics by: Dave Loggins

Billy was a small town loner
Who never did dream
Of ever leaving southern Arizona
Or ever hearing wedding bells ring
He never had a lot of luck with the ladies
But he sure had a lot of good working skills
Never cared about climbing any ladder
He knew the way in a small cafe, found the will
He met Miss Bonnie
And a little bit of her was a little too much
A few movies and a few months latter
The feeling got strong enough
They didn’t own a car
So it must have been love
That drove him uptown for a diamond
That’s when he started goin’

(Chorus)
Over the line
Working overtime
To give her things just to hear her say she don’t deserve them
But he loves her and he just kept going overboard
Over the limit to afford to give her things he knew she wanted
‘Cause without her where would he be?
See, it’s not for him
She is his only need

Ring on her finger and one on the ladder
A new promotion every now and then
Bonnie worked until she couldn’t tie her apron
Then stayed at home and had the first of two children
And my, how the time did fly
The babies grew up and moved away
Left 'em sitting on the front porch rocking
And Billy watching Bonnie’s hair turn gray
And ev’ry once in a while you could see him get up
And he’d head downtown
‘Cause he heard about something she wanted
And it just had to be found
Didn’t matter how simple or how much
It was love
And, boy, ain’t that love just something
When it’s strong enough to keep a man goin’

(Repeat Chorus)

Over the line
Working overtime
She is his only need
His only need
Overboard
Over the limit
Just for her
She is his only need
His only need

     

    
</post>
<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      What is happening to me? This isn't who I am! I am practically cheating on Aaron (whom I still love-I SWEAR I DO) but yet I don't feel the least bit guilty! What is wrong with me? Have I lost every ounce of morals I ever had? I want to make things better between us, but this certainly isn't helping. I am so confused. I am not the kind of person that purposely tries to hurt anyone I love. I just rely on the wrong kind of people. I'm in a relationship; I should be going to him and talking to him about what's happening.
I mean, take last night. I am talking to another guy all night and Aaron walks in. How do I explain who I was talking to; so late; why? Why are there wet t-shirts in the shower? Why am I acting so weird, so abnormal? I am such a bad liar! I can't be convincing, especially when I'm put on the spot like that. I DON'T WANT TO LIE, what am I talking about? I don't want to be in this situation at all. I know it'll catch up to me eventually.

     

    
</post>
<date>04,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm tired. Hey come check me out on myspace  urlLink http://profiles.myspace.com/users/5708509  There's not much happening in my life...just spending a lot of time on myspace. We need to find another roommate.

     

    
</post>
<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      We're fighting again so my day has started lousy. I didn't plan on this blogger to be all about my fucked up relationship. Why am I still with him? Oh, 'cause I have nowhere else to go. The whole thing is just completely ridiculous. I think I'm starting to hate him. Can you believe that? I'll just keep living here until something better comes up. Who cares what I think anyway? He doesn't. 
     

    
</post>
<date>01,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Well it's after two o'clock on Sunday morning and I'm waiting for my mom to come and take me to the hospital. What is happening to me? I am retaining fluid in my feet again. I don't understand this. I've gained way too much weight in the last couple of days for this to not be a problem. I can't afford this. I don't have health insurance anymore (thank you Oregon!). I need to go to work tomorrow. This just doesn't make any sense. I guess I'll find out soon enough what is causing this problem. All I know is that it isn't good. Gawd, and Aaron is being a total asshole about it! It's like I have to argue about EVERYTHING with him. I asked him if he'd take me to the hospital tomorrow but I guess he's just too darned busy, doing god knows what. I mean he doesn't even have to stay there. Just drop me off.
I should go now.

     

    
</post>
</Blog>