<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>31,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey yeah i  know you get to come over cuz you are already here..lol....so yeah there is  like nuthin to do here so yeah.. i dont knwowhat i am syaing but it is about sumthin....~*bYe*~ 
    
</post>
<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Hey gurl,      My parents said yes, but first i gots to go do the dishes and pack, kay!!! I am glad that i finally get to leave the house!! Wb     I     ♥     Matthew     &amp;amp;     Kevin!!!!   
    
</post>
<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Hey gurl,         what r u talking about it just being your luck? N*E*way it'll probably just be my luck that i won't get to stay the night out there, b-cuz my mom has been home for about 30 min. and mark still hasn't brought it up yet you know. And i got in trouble 4 not doing my laundry,b-cuz i was going 2 be nice and let my sister finish theirs before i did mine. i would call, but i don't want to get into anymore trouble, even though i wouldn't kno why i would be getting in trouble b-cuz its not like i'm grounded from the phone or ne thing i am just waiting for them to make up their mind and i don't want to do anything else to make them want to so no, yah kno? Well ne wayz i am just sorta rambling on now so i guess i'll publish this post now!! Buh Bye     I     ♥     Matthew     &amp;amp;     Kevin!!!!   
    
</post>
<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        hey     you know what??? do both..call me and write it on here... i said dont give this one out to anybody but they will be able to see it on our profiles but that is only if they look hard enough at the profile..you know..but yeah i was watching sabrina and i am going to watch degrassi next and degrassi.tv still wont let me in their website anymore and i have no idea why!?!?! which makes me kinda mad...but oh well..and dont make fun of my spelling...my spelling is just bad because i type faster than i am supposed to or something like that..yeha so this is totally about nuthing but oh well...yeah so practice your tenor and then call me and write me to tell me what your mom said...lylas..ttyl..and ronnie mite come over but with my luck probably NOT  urlLink   urlLink     
    
</post>
<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Hey this is cool,     So we are not going to tell anyone about this site right, cuz yah i didn't really here what you said on the phone? I think i am going to go practice my tenor for a lil bit! Hey but if my mom says yes do you want me to post it on here or just call you? The real reasons why i wanted to go back to skool was to see Matthew and Kevin!!! (lol) So hey i gots to go practice but i'll get back on when i'm done, kay!!!        I  ♥   Matthew &amp;amp; Kevin!!!!   
    
</post>
<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       He ashley!!    this is a blog for both of us you know so instead of talking through emails we can talk through this blog....i thought it would be a good idea.. but yeah...  
    
</post>
<date>20,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        hey dude...guess what???matthew is an idiot.....i cant believe he cant get in the blog thingy...i thought it was really easy but i guess his computer doesnt like him...but i really dont know...and i want to stay at your house saturday night...and oh yeah...shawn is a big perve...and yeah i think that is nasty......but yeah are you mad at me????cuz you are like not talking to me as much and crap like that..and yeah i really do hope your brother will get the block off of your email..~*bYe*~   
    
</post>
<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
          H e y  ! ! !     
    
</post>
<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       hey i think that your bro is checking your email....haha!!!and i hope matthew reads her blog cause then that would be hilarious....hey yeah i have to go cuz like uncle ronnie is here and i have to tell you what he said..  
    
</post>
<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Hey PeRsOn...      I can't believe that you waited so long to tell me about M.W.!!! N*E*wayz what is 'his' email address  .?.?.?. j/w Today was awesome, despite the fact the Mrs. Krauskopf tried to screw it up by, sending me to the office,   if yah kno what i mean.!.!. Oh yeah, I can't believe that Shawn is like that!!   But, i am not going to think ne thing bad of him until, i make sure all of the facts are straight, so yeah... Ne wayz i'll c yah l8terz.!.      I     ♥     Matthew     *&amp;amp;*     Kevin!!!!       -  A s h l e y     
    
</post>
<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       he  y ashley....it was supposed to be a hint...DUH!!!! wh are you acting stupid about everything all of a sudden???? it is kinda reminding me of samantha...and that is not a good thing..... yeha i hink taylor likes him and in fact i am pretty sure cuz i asked her.....i think they are going to go out by the end of next week..and i will bet on it if i have too...but i wont just in case i do have too....i went to walmart at like 9 to like 10:30....yeah and when we came back guess who was here????   matthew does like courtney but then he says not really because of what she acts like and stuff like that but i have no clue what is going on in his head but you never know if he likes you or not....  KEITH and uncle ronnie no other kids just him and uncle ronnie which i think is sooooo ironic....but that is me....and if you read my other blog thing then i think it says something about you and samantha...and matthew...but yeah i    guess i have nuthin important to say.....i have no idea what i did...i also have no idea what the heck i am talking about....but yeah i guess see ya...   ~*bYe*~ for now.....  
    
</post>
<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Hey Kirstin,        What is up with the *hint,hint* thing with Kevin? Is it supposed to tell me sumthin'.?.?.?.  I think Matthew likes Courtney again.  I don't know about the Shawn thingy,   but i am gonna ask Taylor if she likes him tomorrow, kay.!. Oh yeah I think i know who Samantha likes, but i don't   want to put it on here so call me if you want me to tell you!!! I saw Samantha and Meredith at   Wal- Mart. Last night was so funny because at like 11:00pm my mom, Laurie, Heather, Shellie, and me all went to wal-mart, and guess who we saw.?.?.?. It was hilarious, Gage was wearing these neon shoes,   and he had to keep walking through the thingys to see if he was stealing anything or whatever.   And they kept going off so we were all cracking up, be-cuz he had to take off his jacket, his shirt, and sumthin' out of his pocket   before he realized that it was his shoes. Well N*E*wayz you should have been there.!.!.!. Well c yah soon!!      I       ♥     Matthew     **     Kevin!!!!      -   A s h l e y         
    
</post>
<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       i think kevin likes you a lil bit more than he said he did....*hint,hint*  and yes it is true about the space center thing..i mean like everyone knew about it except for you which i still think is kinda weird cuz there was a lot of ppl that knew he was going to but i really dont know........you can still like sean or however you spell his name...i dotn care cuz you have more of a chance than i do so dont even say anything....i like him and everything but i will get over it soon enough.....samantha likes somebody else but she wont tell me...yeah..soooo wat's up??? i wish something good would happen to me instead of everything bad...i hate skool and i have to ride the bus to it tomorrow...so it kinda sux....i think so at least....well i guess i will stop since i have like everything in the world to say........yeah right...~*bYe*~  
    
</post>
<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       hey i jsut know things about them...they are not hard to read if you now what i mean...i guess you probably donr but that is just what i am guessing...yeah it sux about sean or however you spell his name but it shouldnt matter cuz he is like brand new...yeah and monday i am going to ride the bus to skool so i wont be late or anything...oh yeah and i was talking to sean and asha on the bus porch on friday and yeha you know ow i ALWAYS stand beside her and put my arm on her shoulder???? well he did the same thing and i thought she was going to fall over cuz she thinks he is cute...yeah and the thing with matthew is that he likes someboody but he really doesnt want to get rejected about anything cuz hew thinks that he is like the best at a lot of things you know and if one thing goes wrong then he will probably regret it...and yeah kevin is just too hard to read sometimes but if you talk to him more than you do he will be easier to read in a weird kinda sense...and i told you what we talked about so that means you cant tel sean or w/e that i like him and you can like him too if yo uwant as long as it doesnt turn into an obsession cuz i already got that covered...lol.....  
    
</post>
<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        who do you think matthew likes??? and y do you think Kevin likes me, or what give you that impression??? Even though i never got to finish tellin' you the whole story about IPC... okay i have decided that i am gonna finish tellin' you the rest of the story... Well N*E*wayz i already told you the part about why i got in trouble, so i will just put what happened after that!!!   Okay the teacher said: of course Ashley wasn't paying attention be-cuz she was talkin' while i was tellin' the instructions, but then she also said that all Ashleys' talk!!!  And that is when kevin jumps in with: Then, its not her fault!!! I was shocked that he was actually tryin' to stick up for me    .!.!.!.  But ne ways as soon as you can write another blog please answer my questions about Kevin and Matthew???   Well i guess i'll c yah on Monday!!!   Sorry about Shawn liking Taylor or whatever he calls it.?!.?!.      I     ♥     Matthew     **     Kevin!!!   
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       hey i know he is hott with like a billion t's.....and he doesnt like taylor self he practically loves her...but yeah i am going to carolines tonite so yeah cuz i cant ever go to your house...i think he is hott and you cant tell him!!! i think that matthew kinda likes somebody but doesnt want anybody to kno...and kevin is just weird cuz i really think he likes you....and oh my god i do not obsess over him...atleast not around him and you need to not tell him and i know you think he is hott so you need to stop worring about me and like him if you want but it isnt like he likes me or anything the only person he likes is taylor....GOD...i wish i was her...lol.....well i g2g but if you read this like before midnight and i get it then i will read it and publish something else tonight at carolines cuz her parents have internet....~*bYe*~  
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Hey gurl,     Is that true about Matthew? and what about the Space Center thingy? Well N*E*wayz did you know the Shawn is smarter than Matthew in math?, 2 me that is just crazy, be-cuz matthew had like all 100's last year.!.!.!. I really like Shawn but i am tryin' to make myself stop, considering you like him sooo much!! But i really do have 2 admit that he is  hottt with like 50 billion t's, if yah know what i mean.?.?.?.!.!.!.*.*.*.       But i don't have a chance with him, be-cuz he likes Taylor Self or just wants to be her *friend*, but either way, he probably still wouldn't like me!!! Well ne wayz howz it   hangin'.?.?.?.      I   ♥   Matthew!!!!      I     ♥     guyz!!!!        -    Ashley     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        R u still there. ?.?.?.   
    
</post>
<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       hey ashley...i can't tell you!!!hey ashley...i can't tell you!!!hey ashley...i can't tell you!!!hey ashley...i can't tell you!!!hey ashley...i can't tell you!!!hey ashley...i can't tell you!!!hey ashley...i can't tell you!!!hey ashley...i can't tell you!!!hey ashley...i can't tell you!!!hey ashley...i can't tell you!!!hey ashley...i can't tell you!!!hey ashley...i can't tell you!!!hey ashley...i can't tell you!!!hey ashley...i can't tell you!!!hey ashley...i can't tell you!!!hey ashley...i can't tell you!!!hey ashley...i can't tell you!!!hey ashley...i can't tell you!!!hey ashley...i can't tell you!!!hey ashley...i can't tell you!!!hey ashley...i can't tell you!!!hey ashley...i can't tell you!!!hey ashley...i can't tell you!!!hey ashley...i can't tell you!!!hey ashley...i can't tell you!!!  
    
</post>
<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
        Hey Kirstin... please tell me?!?!?!?!?!?!?!?!?!?! Hey Kirstin... please tell me?!?!?!?!?!?!?!?!?!?! Hey Kirstin... please tell me?!?!?!?!?!?!?!?!?!?! Hey Kirstin... please tell me?!?!?!?!?!?!?!?!?!?! Hey Kirstin... please tell me?!?!?!?!?!?!?!?!?!?! Hey Kirstin... please tell me?!?!?!?!?!?!?!?!?!?! Hey Kirstin... please tell me?!?!?!?!?!?!?!?!?!?! Hey Kirstin... please tell me?!?!?!?!?!?!?!?!?!?! Hey Kirstin... please tell me?!?!?!?!?!?!?!?!?!?! Hey Kirstin... please tell me?!?!?!?!?!?!?!?!?!?! Hey Kirstin... please tell me?!?!?!?!?!?!?!?!?!?! Hey Kirstin... please tell me?!?!?!?!?!?!?!?!?!?! Hey Kirstin... please tell me?!?!?!?!?!?!?!?!?!?! Hey Kirstin... please tell me?!?!?!?!?!?!?!?!?!?! Hey Kirstin... please tell me?!?!?!?!?!?!?!?!?!?!     I     ♥     Matthew     **     Kevin!!!!   
    
</post>
<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      hey i know someone who as your teachers...ALICE... this is her schedule: 1-2: Long 3:Krauskopf 4:Machala 5:Jazz Band B lunch 6:Loney 7:Symphonic band 
    
</post>
<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       i really hope you dont think i am that stupid...lol...i mean you put that on your other bloggy thing too..but yeah i guess i will post mine too even though my dad doesnt want it on here..  i have locker 224 and it is by dicks room or the shop room  Period#1 Algebra 1 PAP Franta   Period#2 IPC PAP Machala   Period#3 Soc Stu PAP Krauskopf   Period#4 P.E Brown   Period#5 Spanish B Kuempal   Period#6 Eng/La/Rdg Anderson   Period#7 Eng/La/Rdg Anderson   i have b lunch too...but yeah i think i have spanish history and lunch with you and thats it...but that is better than last year...~*bYe*~  
    
</post>
<date>09,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
         Hey gurl... I got my schedule!!! I am so excited...I got like 6 new pairs of pants, 7 skirts, and 9   10 new shirts...for school!!   Oh yeah, i didn't get the black chucks i wanted... instead i got these    awesome new vans!! N*E*wayz i said that when i got my schedule i would post it so here goes:    Period#1: English: Mrs. Long Period#2: English:Mrs. Long Period#3:Soc. Studies:Mrs. Krauskopf    Period#4:IPC:Mrs.Machala Period#5:Spanish:Mrs. Kumpel Stupid c: lunch    Period#6:Algebra:Mrs. Loney Period#7:Symphonic Band:Mr. Heaslet         BY THE WAY IF YOU HAVE ANY OF THE SAME CLASSES AS ME LET ME KNOW</post></Blog>