<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>30,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
       I like surfers, but I do not like skaters. Skaters reach another level of annoyance within me that will not cease its wrath. Sure, they are attractive looking specimens but that is not enough to send a wind of calm in the ravaging fire that has become the subject of my rampage.       Skaters are stupid. I speak for the vast majority of them, but I'm sure at least 1.5% are not as incompetent as I presume. When you look up, past their Converses, past their Dickie pants, past their FOX t-shirts, and past their adorable beanies, you will see nothing but ungrateful, whiney, and corruptible behavior. Generally speaking they are but mere suburbian pre-pubescents who construct a paradise of concrete, rebellion, broken teeth. If anyone defies their "paradise" (i.e. parents, the government, "the preps"), they use their Superhuman Powers of Juvenile Insolence in order to get back at those who don't share their shallow and idealistic beliefs.       For example, I know a young man who went to biology class with me a few semesters ago. Everyday he would wear a navy blue kanga hoodie which had the screenprinted words "SKATEBOARDING IS NOT A CRIME." Of course it's not, you unhygenic baboon. However, skateboarding  is  a crime when abandoned lots and pedestrian walk ways clearly state "NO SKATEBOARDING" and yet you go ahead and do it anyway. Has the numerous injuries of past incompetence limited your reading skills?! Read it, BUCK-O. Don't even bring up the point that the government is secretly trying to bend you into its capitalistic tastes, you are just plain dumb. Use your common sense! Why do you think they posted up "no skateboarding" signs? Because you'll hurt someone!! Just as I'm about to hurt you right now!!!       Bikers, however, are almost as bad as skaters, but I guess the engineering flaws of the skateboard are much more flawed than a bicyle thus causing incalculable contusions and needless deaths of precious few braincells, which I doubt would be put into use even if they were rescued by a thousand lifeguards.       /end rant.       Today was rather uneventful. My sister will be gone for seven days. She's in Chicago right now visiting my aunt (my dad's older sister). That means I get the room to myself! Joyous relief. Now I can stay up as long as I want just as long as I go to sleep at ten! I expect to spend intimate hours playing my guitar and reading rejected books from a local high school. Or dancing.       I have taken a keen fancy to dancing lately. It's sort of like a mix between pop dancing, hip-hop dancing, and having a convulsion. Actually, it's not really dancing. It's flailing around like a monkey.            = Cristie  
     

    
</post>
<date>29,July,2004</date>
<post>


       
        Hello. If you have found this weblog, it is most likely from my recommendation in real life. I established this so people I know can see what I'm up to without actually having to ask "how are you?" thus saving time, energy, and sanity. I'm not the concise verbal type, so you can sympathize the innocent fool who actually does ask "how are you?" and gets slammed by a three hour speechpertaining to the injustices that are caused in the world, what sort of injustices are caused, and why the people who cause these injustice need to be neutered.        I'm not sure how often I'm going to post, but it will be fairly frequent. It will mostly be about nothing or weird thoughts that I have during the day. Frequency also correlates to how many people are actually reading this. If no one reads my stupid words, then what use is it  really ? So if you do  indeed  read this, please post a comment or at least tell me. Pictures might be involved somewhat. Depends really.       I forewarn you,  beware of my bizarre sense of humor quickly.  You will recieve no mercy from me whatsoever. I'll also try not to say bad words.       Otherwise, let me reintroduce myself. My name is Cristie Pirote. I'm currently seventeen-years-old. I want to have a pet chihuahua so I can name him Mr. C and a pet hamster so I can name him M.C. Hamster.I listen to rock music (like Muse, Radiohead, Stabbing Westerwards, Pearl Jam, The White Stripes... etc). I am a workaholic. I like to draw weird pictures. I like write stories. I like sleeping. I started this blog to save me from boredomwrapped in summer vacation.       "Getting-To-Know-You" hour is over.Whew. I'm glad. I was afraid we were going to start braiding each other's hair for a moment.       = Cristie   p.s. Isn't this a great change from all these weird cards/letters I've been sending you people?  
     

    
</post>
<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Hi you. Haven't been talking to me lately, have you? Are you angry at me? Please don't be mad. I meant well when I poisoned your drink with anti-freeze. If it's any consolation, I hear anti-freeze really tastes good.       I had a gynormous sinus headache yesterday. I took two tylenol PM pills and that conked me out for about fifteen hours. I woke up somewhere between the eight and tenth hour, but I went right back to sleep. Lately, I've been having so many headaches. I think it's because I'm always outside in the afternoon, sweating my guts off, and I don't drink enough water.       Yesterday was school registration. Nobody except my old algebra teacher recognized me. If I wasn't so tired and typically irritated at waking up, I would've laughed very hard. People whom I've known since forever (probably two to six years) were there but they didn't say hi. That made me sad. Not really. I didn't say hi either because it takes up too much energy.       So yeah. Pretty much it: school registration, tons of homework, headache. Oh. And I'm on the verge of getting myself a job. I won't say much more than that because it's not final yet.       I'm boring myself now. Here's a picture I drew a while ago:          urlLink        Tell me if you can see it. If you don't, I'm sacrificing this computer to the technology gods. I'm sorry about my crappy handwriting ... and the lack of actual humor in this comic strip ... and the bad drawing-ness of the swing chain. I actually made six strips involving these two characters who have no names. I call them the Goth and the Preppy, even though he's not a goth and she's not a prep. Weird.      Have a nice day and try not to trip on the cow on the way out this time okay?       = cristie  
     

    
</post>
<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
      Ow, my sinuses hurt. I'm think I'm slowly getting sick. I always wake up with a sore throat or something. It hasn't completely gone away and it's always there. I don't like remembering to take my vitamins because most of the time I can't.   Today was such a nice day. It was breezy enough, the sun was hardly peeking through the cloudly sky, and it was all around good. It was a nice day to go outside ... and then go back inside ... so you can say "wow, it's nice to go outside" but you never really do. That's what I did. I actually went OUT with Sunday. My sister took my cousin and me to the Florin Mall and the Romano Macaroni Grill.   Florin Mall shouldn't even be called a "mall." It should be called "The Building Where Ghetto Stores Congregate." Half the good stores were closed like Walton's Book Store, K B Toys, and whatnot. JC Penny is closed down, Nordstrom closed a loooong time ago. Sears is still there. We went to Foxnoor, Catwalk, and all the other junior clothing stores where I'm sure local strippers and prostitutes load up on the latest fashions. Arden is doubly better than Florin Mall. I'm not even sure what even holds Florin Mall up. Passed by Happiness Is .. and bought myself a CD wallet for 6.75.   Romano Grill has alright Italian food. Our food took an abnormally long time to arrive so our waiter (a very nice looking thirty-something guy named Vince) and the manager (a not so looking forty-something bald guy who had a terrible sense of humor) came over and apologized profusely for the wait. On all tables were crayons and a paper placemat so dinners could draw to entertain themselves. The waiter and the manger seemed to appreciate my artsy-fartsy interpretation of the olive oil bottle, the pepper shaker, and my glass of strawberry lemonade. Food came and we ate ourselves full. Somehow food tastes better then you're starving. While we were waiting for our dessert, we complimented all the nice-looking waiters and busboys. We teased each other for a good ten minutes about how cute they all were. Y'know, usual girl stuff.   Otherwise nothing else interesting. This post has been boring so far. I think I'll do that later. Right now I have to look at Homestar Runner before lightening strikes me dead.   = cristie  
     

    
</post>
<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Greetings, earthwad.       No sugar and no caffiene makes Jack a dull girl named Cristie who sits at the computer all night, trying to squeeze out interesting anecdotes from a mundane life. I think I'll just ramble on and on about nothing-in-particular until something interesting spills out.       Got my bag. I scoured Arden mall for my bag. All the stops: American Eagle Outfitter, Abercrombie  Fitch, Other Stores, and Wilson's Leather Place. I don't even remember. Many stores I went to, vast lands I have traveled, many foreigners I have encountered. Be proud of me, I didn't insult anyone directly. I did find my bag though. A forty-nine ninety-nine leather messenger bag I got at the Wilson Leather Store. I hate cows. They need to die. (I'm kidding.) I got a free water bottle too. That was awesome.       I also got to be on the Channel 3 news. You know how there's the KCRA experience and Walt Gray gives you the news at Arden Mall? I was there. I got to be directly in back of Walt Gray behind the glass thingee and I WAS ON TV. Unfortunately, when the camera shot at me, I was trying to blow spit at my four-year-old cousin. Not an attractive start to a Hollywood career.       I don't like the mall, otherwise known as the Breeding Ground to Conformity. I don't like the stores and I don't like the people in it. I also don't like the fact I never have enough money when I go to the mall. That certainly hinders many things. Like purchasing for example.       = Cristie  
     

    
</post>
<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       Tomorrow I shall begin the search for a perfect messenger bag. I searched the 'net for some ideas last night (ended up sleeping at two o'clock in the morning) but most of which were around sixty-dollars. Mmm.... I guess a well manufactured bag is a good investment ... right? I have about four hours and the entire Arden mall to accomplish my goal. Let's hope I have enough of patience and an iron tongue not to throw vulgar and creative comments at the slutty-looking consumers of today's brainwashing, capitalist media. My throat hardens whenever they walk past giggling and throwing about random words like "dude" and "Oh my GAWD!!" Uuuuggghhh.       Around two days ago I had my hair chopped off. Not all of it, but it was a good sized trim. It closely resembles the haircut I got the beginning of this summer, but shorter and more pixie-ish. Today I got my new glasses. I look like Uber-Girl Nerd 2000. Just saying the words  uber  and  2000  makes me a nerd even without the glasses. My nerd glasses and short hair makes me look like an effeminate Japanese guy with an oddly shaped chest. I have to try harder to make myself look more feminine, not like anyone cares, but then again what else shall I do with my hard-earned boredom?       Here's my  GAMINE GAMEPLAN  (catchy, no?):       Wear more lipstick.    Simple enough. I can wear the lipstick, it's just a matter of re-applying which I don't do that often enough because I don't bring a mirror around with me. Re-applying lipstick without a mirror means my lack of eye-hand coordination will kick in, and I will look like an absolute moron with lipstick all over my face, consequently with none on my lips where it's supposed to be.      Try not to tell sick jokes as much, if ever.  No more sick jokes, Cristie. My vocabulary and inflection should be that of a good ole Christian gal, not a drunken sailor on crack. No more hanging around demented people with limited vocabulary. For some reason, I feel as though I should not hang around people who welcome hygiene as much as a broken leg. Poor hygiene is a factor that quite possibly affects their verbal deficiency. So if you want to be my friend, please consider using soap once a while. Maybe all the time.     Hang out with girls more.  This is hard. It's not because I don't hang out with girls. I  do  hang out with female companions, but they're not really the type who discuss make-up and boys and whatever it is that females discuss nowadays. It's just that I need some positive, floral scented influences rubbing off on me. I need someone to chagrin me every time I do tell a sick joke. I need someone to compliment my clothing and teach me how to giggle. And no I don't giggle, I  cackle . There's a significant difference.     Accentuate chesticles and other womanly features with skirts.  After/if I get married and have kids, I will not have this curvaceous body that I am now blessed with (I know you're snickering... stop snickering). I will have gained weight that will be a pain to work off, and my chesticles will be sagging and my hips will span the entire state of Rhode Island. I am seventeen. I am at the blossoming zenith of womanhood. TIME TO SHOW IT OFF.      Stop swearing.  Actually this has nothing to do with being feminate, but I have to do this anyway. There's nothing more unattractive about a lady than having to add asterisks after the first letters of two particular four-lettered word if ever it's being transfering to paper. Granted I  do  know how to exhibit creative insults without profanity, but nevertheless I must harness the profanity when it tries to take hold of my tongue. It will be as hard as  shizzny winkettes , but I must try.     Enough of the subject. I will be the primary informant if my little experiment works.       Today was not too exciting. For one, I had to wake up. That always ruins my day. I don't remember much besides the searing 103 degree heat. My aunt, my four cousins, my mom and I went to William Land Park for the Annual City Employee Picnic. We got eight free tickets from Mr. Coons because he works for the City planning and creating traffic signs and such. We started off for the park about two, ate something, went around the park with our free bonus passes. We had free entry to the Sac Zoo and Fairy Tale Town. Again, still fuzzy on the details. I vaguely remember seeing oddities like the sun but otherwise I felt like I was walking around with a bag on my head.       Random thoughts: Send two letters by tomorrow.... Tomorrow is Friday, right? ... When does the bloody Olympics start? .... School registration is next Tuesday.... I'll bet no one will recognize me.... Mom needs help to get a digital video camera... Ecstatic... MUSE IS SO AWESOME...       Okay, I'm done.   = Cristie      
     

    
</post>
<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>


       
       I'm bored. Bite me.       ~*~ First, the basics. Of course. ~*~     What's your name?:  Cristie     How old are you?:  17     When's your birthday?:  June 22nd, 1987     Where do you live?:  Nowhere special     Are you a guy or a gal?:  I bet you couldn't tell by the name.      ~::~Your looks~::~     What color is your hair naturally?:  Dark brown with reddish highlights     Is it dyed right now?:  Yes     What color are your eyes?:  brown     Do you where contacts or glasses?:  glasses     If you where contacts, do you where colored ones?:  n/a     How long is your hair?:  at my neck now. i need to get it chopped     How do you usually where it?:  down or messed up     How tall are you?:  5'6 i think     How much do you weigh?:  last time it was checked was 118 lbs     What size shoes do you where?:  8 1/2 - 9 inches     What style clothes do you usually where?:  it's hard to explain. unmatching mostly     What are you wearing right now?:  shirt, shorts, and mandatory underwears     What jewelery do you where regularly?:  my watch     Have any piercings?:  only my ears     Tattoos?:  no     Are your nails painted?:  only my toenails      #~#Would you or have you ever #~#     Dive into a pool of jello?:  i would     Get a tatoo?:  never     Try and get on Fear Factor?:  NOOO     Try and get on some other reality show?:  yeah, but I'd be the first to get booted out     Pierce your tongue?:  sure, but take it out right away     Go bungee jumping?:  no     Parasailing?:  sure     Sky diving?:  yes     Scuba diving?:  no     Ask someone out?:  i would     Fly an airplane?:  i would     Fly in a hot air balloon?:  i would     Try and get in the Olympics?:  i would never     Eat a bug?:  I have      ::!:: About your crush, bf/gf, etc. ::!::     What's their name?:  none ... but I'll make up one just for you     Are they a boy or a girl?:  boy     What's their favorite color?:  black     Favorite animal?:  uuhh... a cheetah??     Favorite pass time?:  playing in his band     How long have you known them?:  for a while     Do you talk alot?:  no, he hates me     What size shoes do they where?:  13?     What color is their hair?:  black     What about their eyes (the more detailed the better)?:  yes, he has eyes     Do you like their style of dress?:  most definitely     Would you change anything about them?:  uuhh... he could probably move out of his mother's house by now     Do they sleep with stuffed animals?:  yes, because he says it resembles me. awww!!     How tall are they?:  taller than me     What's their favorite food?:  aha. i could so easily say something perverted, but I'd say sushi     Favorite song?:  anything by muse, because he's cool like that     Favorite sport to play?:  he's a surfer. heh heh.     To watch?:  anything on adult swim     Favorite band?:  MUSE     How old are they?:  older than me     Do you think you'll marry them someday?:  No. he sucks.     Are you in love?:  he's imaginary, but not Dave, my imaginary friend.      &gt;~</post></Blog>