<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>02,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Mmkay... well ujournal is going crazy and I can't post on it and Becky says that like my uj is screwed up itself, SO... I made this here blogger whateveryoucallit and so it might be temperary? Who knows... I just wanted to post my La Honda entry SOMEWHERE so yeah...       Ok so I wrote this a while ago... yesterday...      Must state the obvious… must state the obvious… okay! I’m baaaaaaaack! Woohoo! Yippee and I’m here to stay… that is until August 12th when I leave for Philadelphia for my cousin’s wedding… yay! But yeah… La Honda…  I guess I’ll start from the beginning. Umm… first of all my classes were:  Sr. Choir Sr. Orchestra  Lunch  Jr./Sr. String Ensembles Sr. Art  Yepyep… So like I love Choir in some ways cuz Shawn is just the cutest little thing ever. He’s the choir director haha… but he’s gotta be the most adorable 30 year old I’ve ever met. Ahahaha… and so yeah me and Fern, Bill, Sam, this girl Anna who I just met today, and this other girl I don’t know all played with the choir for this one piece. It was raining though and so my poor violin is soaked… ugh and I’ll hafta fix that heh… but it was still really fun oh yes… and poor Shawn was made fun of at Skit Night… it was really cute though haha and I don’t think he took it the wrong way. Choir’s so much more fun though than last year…  Senior Orchestra… so much to say about that but I won’t. Umm… I made second chair of the 1st violins which is cool, Fern got first of course haha. She’s really nice. Omg… the conductors Vince and Kate drove me crazy the whole week… I won’t say anything more though… it just made me miss Villa a little bit. Just a teeny bit. Lol… so yeah the concert went well too… some pieces I barely played though cuz I was too busy holding up the music from blowing away with my bow. Ugh that damn wind… but yeah I just love the cello section. They’re so cool man… or like… at least the first stand cuz those are the only people I know lol. Sam and Bill. Awwww… adorable Sam. He’s too cute when he plays. And little Billy… he’s pretty cool. Vince always calls him Billy… that’s so sweet.  Omg! I just loved our ensemble group. It consisted of: Fern, me, Katie, Sam, and Bill. I swear… I think I’ve been in everything this year at La Honda with Fern, Sam and Bill. It’s like we come in a package. When one of us is playing in some ensemble, all of us are playing. The concert went well for that, too. I played 3 numbers, which is like a lot, but Fern played 4 so haha. Lol yes, and I got pictures too but that’ll come later. We played this weird Schubert piece I think… and then this “Song of October” where the second violins fell off the stage during the performance *eek!* Laugh Out Loud… and then that one famous Brandenburg Concerto where like everyone played and it was so cool.  Uhhh and then Art. Nothing much to say. It’s pretty much self-explained. Well not really but there’s just nothing to say about it.  For Skit Night… omg I just loved our skit… it ended up pretty stupid though and we got second to last place, and uhh… the last place people got “Gonged” or disqualified. Heh. But yeah… I thought it was cute at least.  Man there’s really not much else to say. I can just see everyone going “Oh darnit! *Snaps fingers*” when I say that haha. And yeah… so that was another year of La Honda.  Angela got a ujournal! Woohoo!  ~Laurel~ 
     
    
</post>
</Blog>