<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       美國時間星期日(6/6)下午快3點時, 跟著阿姨, 妍慧和一個美國女孩, 有了第一次在養老院當義工的經驗.  當車子抵達養老院時, 在門口就遇到幾位老人家正在"享受"日光, 兩個坐輪椅, 一個躺病床, 坐輪椅的老奶奶, 手裡把玩著香菸, 似乎正在想著要不要點了抽, 而躺在病床上的爺爺, 則在旁邊的看護幫忙下, 一口一口的抽著那"飯後的一根煙"吧!  阿姨很熟練的馬上跟那位把玩香菸的奶奶聊起來, 但奶奶感覺起來滿depress的, 言語中透露著些許淡淡的憂傷, 我因為第一次, 實在是笨的不知該說些什麼, 只能笑笑的跟她打招呼, 嘴巴跟腦袋沒連線, 呆笑的樣子我想一定很好笑吧,  進入醫院後, 我很驚訝的看到一個滿年輕的年輕人, 坐在輪椅上跟其他人聊著天, 看著他, 我雖然滿懷疑問但還是安靜的跟著阿姨往另一邊走廊上的病房走去, 阿姨說, 其實今天我們suppose要有一張院方提供的名單, 名單上的人是他們認為目前為止最需要關心的老人家, 但也許是承辦的小姐疏忽了, 所以我們並沒有任何的方向要往哪裡去, 於是阿姨就帶著我們邊走邊探頭望每間病房, 我看到有些房間是空的, 有些房間則住著四位老人家, 我也發現沒有一個老人家是站著走的, 不是坐輪椅, 就是躺著由護士推著走.  醫院裡好安靜喔, 走廊上每走幾歩就會看到一些老人家坐在病房門口, 也沒幹麼, 也不說話, 我們就在邊打招呼邊走的情形下停在一位躺在活動床上的老奶奶旁邊.  這位老奶奶很……開朗吧我想, 阿姨跟她聊天, 她有問必答, 臉上也保持著笑容, 真的是一位很可愛的老人, 她的情形並不是很好, 耳朵似乎受過傷, 沒了外觀而和臉連在一起, 但我相信並沒有傷害到她的聽覺, 因為她一直都能跟我們有說有笑, 這樣來講, 應該是沒問題吧, 老奶奶的右腳節肢, 左腳也可能因為少動而萎縮, 就跟我的手臂一般細, 雙手的手指已經變形僵硬而沒有了作用, 老奶奶說如果現在我們碰她的左腳, 她一定會痛的哇哇叫, 所以阿姨就笑笑的跟她說 : ok, ok, we will never touch your leg. Don’t you ever worry about that! 呵~佩服阿姨風趣的談吐, 逗的老人家直笑的合不攏嘴.  老人家跟我們說, 人老了, everything fall apart. 我看著她, 心裡想, 人老了, 真的只能這樣嗎? 由此可知健康的重要, 年輕時如果不好好保養, 老了很難有本錢跟病魔打鬥, 聊了一下天, 由於阿姨的餐廳忙, 所以今天並沒辦法待太久, 我握著老人家的手, 笑著跟她說下禮拜一定再來看她, 阿姨也說要帶她喜歡的西瓜過來, 我看著老人家, 默默記著她的病房號碼和病床, 給了她大大的笑容後, 結束了我第一次的養老院之行.  回程中, 阿姨說其實醫院的另一邊, 住的多是車禍受傷的年輕人, 正好解開我之前的疑惑, 而老人家的笑容到現在還清楚的印在我的腦裡, 她的親切給了我很大的勇氣要持續的回去陪伴那些老人們, 我相信他們都很可愛, 都希望有人能聽他們說話, 我想, 我的作用就在這裡吧. ^___^  
     
    
</post>
<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      To minimize disappointment, Americans prefer to present a negative message indirectly.  However, different culture may have different way to tell a bad news.  In Chinese culture, it is not easy for people to say “no.”  For example, when a manager say “no” to an employee, the employee may take it very seriously and may be hard to get over the emotional damage caused by the word.  Moreover, “no” for some people may means, for instance, “not to see each other anymore.”Well, from my point of view, everyone have the right to say no. In business, only do things that we can do and things that need to do.    
     
    
</post>
<date>14,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       The word, “Goodwill,” is such an easy word, but is hard to put in practice because it concerns with many elements that allows us to have good communication with others.  Everyday, people have to do many tasks in a limited amount of time.  Try to think about it, would you want to spend time on a letter with negative tone or with an impassionate person?  People rather choose companies who assists are able to provide good service with efficiency. There are thousands of different businesses out there in the world, and I believe that “goodwill” will be the key element in communication that will keep any company moving forward.  
     
    
</post>
<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Face-to-face communication safe time for company to search the new employee, unless the manager would love to see this person and talk to he/she face to face. Therefore, many companies rather choose to see the written document first, instead of just schedule the meeting. Second, I do not think the expense of “face to face communication” is the main reason. The reason why the company does not like to have meeting often is that it is not convenient and take too much time. 
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       繁忙的城市, 緊張的情緒, 造就了多少不安定的心靈,多少人為了學業, 為了事業, 甚至為了家庭在打拼, 也許肩膀上有千斤的擔子壓的你喘不過氣,也許很多事情對你似乎頓時失去了意義, 但親愛的你, 天天又天天, 有多久你忘了為自己用力的呼吸?別忘了窗外有藍天, 夜晚有星星,還有那鄉間花草的香氣, 以及那一大片綠油油的草地,這一切的一切, 都期待著你的親臨, 盼望著你的身影……  
     
    
</post>
<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       I believe that action speaks louder than words.  In business world, people not only need to be careful about their word choice but they also need to pay attention to their body language.  Good communication can only occur when people are calm and are able to talk and understand each other.  Sometimes, body language may signal the wrong meaning and thus lead to misunderstanding between parties.  
     
    
</post>
<date>10,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       Everyone defines the meaning of challenge differently.    Somebody might think that moving to a new place is a challenge, but other may consider a challenge as achieving something that no one can accomplish.   For me, challenge is learning how to interact with other for different social occasions.  
     
    
</post>
</Blog>