<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
         This is part of a chapter from a story I'm writing. It's just a random part...enjoy! *~*wHiT*~*               S    he decided that she needed a breath of fresh air, so she stepped outside. She walked down the dark alleyway to the main street, and she sat on one of the stone benches that lined it. She leaned back and relaxed, breathing in the cool night air. She looked up and saw that it was a half-moon, and shuddered. Faber doesn’t have much time left, she thought. I wonder how much he has left to pay… She heard music in the distance, a slow Italian serenade. She closed her eyes and enjoyed the melody for a minute, tapping her foot in rhythm. All of a sudden, she heard a voice say, “May I have this dance?” She opened her eyes and Faber was standing before her, his hand outstretched.  She smiled, saying “Very well then,” and took his hand. He led her to the middle of the deserted street and stopped. Then he put his free hand on her waist, and Sienna put hers on his shoulder. They danced through two whole songs, never saying a word to each other, but smiling the whole time. Then Sienna asked Faber, “What do you feel?” “Feel?” he repeated, puzzled. “Happiness?” “Yes…,” he said uncertainly. “Anger?” “Toward my father,” he replied. “Love?” she whispered. Faber immediately let go of her, pushing her away. “Love is nothing to me,” he whispered, and started walking away. “Faber!” She yelled, running to catch up with him. He stopped and fell to his knees, his head bowed. “Faber, what’s wrong?” She asked, kneeling beside him. “Love is wrong!” he cried. “It’s a mistake!” “Maybe sometimes,” Sienna said softly, taking his hand, “but not now.” She gently squeezed his hand and let go. Faber looked at her and said, “I do not feel right. There is a knot in my chest.” “That,” said Sienna “is love.” “I cannot love!” he yelled, and stood up. Sienna stood up and took his hands. “Faber, you can love,” she whispered, drawing nearer to him. Faber closed his eyes, and seconds later he felt Sienna’s lips brush against his, but he quickly pulled away, whispering, “No.” He backed away, and Sienna let go of him. “Why can’t you understand?” Then he turned around and went back to the theater. Sienna did not follow.    
    
    
</post>
<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
         Here we go, hot off the press, the 2004 HHS Vikings football schedule!           Aug. 27~Wyoming Rogers~     Sept. 3~Fennville     Sept. 10~Wyoming Kellogsville     Sept. 17~Comstock Park     Sept. 24~ Kent City     Oct. 1~ Allendale      Oct. 8~Wyoming Lee     Oct. 15~Blue/Silver crossover     Oct. 22~ Forest Hills Eastern                That's all the info I have! Hope it helps!       
    
    
</post>
<date>11,August,2004</date>
<post>

    
        I could tell you that I'm having the time of my life right now. But it would be a lie. I'm BORED! It's rainy and 50 degrees...in the  summer ! That's not right! Ok I'm done fuming now. This is my blog...I've never done a blog before. So it probably sucks. Yeah, ok, that's all folks.       ~Whit~   
    
    
</post>
</Blog>