<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
             yayy.love yiling lots=)  she promised me a crazy cow layout!!!           i simply love  yiling             the pretty  purple  is there to highlight your name        had prata day and tingyu is a beeeg fat albino elephant with a pea sized brain!!!(she was food rationing but she ate   more than usual  )          thats all for now :)   
     

    
</post>
<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i love my cows.they look  cute and spastic  which is so like me :) and the whole layout is so bright :)  i forgot to put in money in my wallet(which is  extremely empty)  so i had not even a  single cent   to eat and my handphone too.It was okayy as i had brought  tuna .yea.but i forgot to bring the  bread .so ended up eating from the can of tuna and it taste so salty.still, it was nice and filling for a reccess :)      so had speech training during reccess.i am sick of my role!!!i feel disgusted  gazing lovingly  at nicole all the time (i think i grossed nicole out too) art was pretty interesting with carin going on and on about kim.she sure hates her ALOT.      then had training.ouchh.i am having stomach cramps from all the pt.well, it was more like dance lesson no. 2. considering all the stretches we did.yayy.i like playing doubles with leyi :)       i need to fatten my taggie.i am so jealous of its figure now.yiling please help me with my screwed taggie!!!     
     

    
</post>
<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      you always seem so happy,spirited and cheerful even when you are down.you just brighten up the day for people just like lightbulbs.no matter where you go, or where you are, i will always remember you as the big  yellowish  lightbulb that brightened up many days of my lives.leave happily.smile.don't cry.you look awful when you cry :)   *note: change the encoding if you can't see    just after you went offline 当你 started playing on my playlist. don't ask why.it played itself        如果有一天 我回到从前 回到最原始的我 你是否会觉得我不错  如果有一天 我离你遥远 不能再和你相约 你是否会发觉我已经说再见  当你的眼睛眯着笑 当你喝可乐当你找 我想对你好 你从来不知道 想你想你 也能成为嗜好 当你说今天的烦恼  当你说夜深你睡不着 我想对你说 却害怕都说错 还喜欢你 知不知道  如果有一天 梦想都实现 回忆都成了永远 你是否还会记得今天  如果有一天 我们都发觉 原来什么都可以 无论是否还会停留在这里 也许可是让我想得太多 也许该回到没我 梦里和相遇 就毫不犹豫 大声的说我要说  当你的眼睛眯着笑 当你喝可乐当你找 我想对你好 你从来不知道 想你想你 也能成为嗜好  啦 啦 我想对你说 却害怕都说错 还喜欢你 知不知道 啦 啦     anyway,  this is the canto version of 好心分手  是否很惊讶 讲不出说话 没错我是说 你想分手吗 曾给你驯服到 就像绵羊 何解会反咬你一下 你知吗 * 回头望 伴你走 从来未曾幸福过 赴过汤 蹈过火 沿途为何没爱河 下半生 陪住你 怀疑快乐也不多 没有心 别再拖 好心一早放开我 从头努力也坎坷 通通不要好过 来年岁月那么多 为继续而继续 没有好处还是我 若注定有一点苦楚 不如自己亲手割破 是否不甘心 首先给撇下 换了你是我 你忍得到吗 捱得过无限次 寂寞凌迟 人心态早己看得化 也可怕 Repeat * 从头努力也坎坷 通通不要好过 来年岁月那么多 为继续而继续 直接不过承认错 若勉强也分到不多 不如甚么也摔破 难捱就无谓再拖 好心一早放开我 从头努力也坎坷 通通不要好过 来年岁月那么多 为继续而继续 没有好处还是我 若注定有一点苦楚 不如自己亲手割破 
     

    
</post>
<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i love chinese i love chinese.please let me pass!!!!!i'm desperate to pass.uh.left so many blanks that the whole paper might as well be CLEAN and NEW and left untoched.  had some breakfast thingy in the morning.the food is *speechless* $2.it is so not worth it.the soyamilk taste  weird. its abit sour i think.  ponned training yest. cuz my ankle was hurting.so went seline's house to study instead.awww.warner is simply adorable and extremely tamed!!!plus he is in love with bert!!!heehee    hmm.booking chalets now.i reallyy hope that 210 chalet would be well,    sweet     minus the cliqueish stuff and let everyone bond.bahh.but i'm still looking forward more to 6A's one :) heehee.who knows what sort of funny stuff might happen again?  6A is forever so exciting and interesting with all the dynamic characters and lively people :)  Life is always full of surprises :)   i'm hooked onto olympics!!susilo rawks!!i shall stay up to watch the gym finals tonite!!!!  
     

    
</post>
<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      wheeee!!! cross country was  CANCELLED  due to heavy downpour!!  well,wasn't really excited anyway.supposed to buy gummies and walk together with seline.it sounded more like a leisure stroll with food and the usual talk :)  school is pretty interesting today.watch some communist show with carin making all the funny remarks :) then yicky screened infernal affairs for us!!!thanks sylvia for bringing the disc  so after school went to far east to eat the delicious chicken rice with  the newly weds, best man and flower girl.  (i'm the bridesmaid!!!:)). took some newly weds neos and was about to go when nicole's mum called us to tell us about the stormy weather conditions.dearest seline had called to tell me that the race WAS CANCELLED!!!:) then it was followed by lots of confirmation calls...blah blah blah...we deceided to walk to heeren and beloved carin left us halfway through.aww.  tingyu is so  gullible !!she spent like so much time on the phone trying to tell whether her teammates were tricking her about the race still being on.after that someone paged for her to meet at the women's accersories section and her whole team appered to follow her!!!nicole and andris were trying to escape from tingyu(since the team was only following tingyu) and they left me behind with tingyu and her whole team!!!yea.somehow they left us and we went back to tingyu's sweetheart andris who was hiding together with nicole. went window shopping for a while before getting tired and taking a break at mcdonalds.then we still wanted to stay so tingyu and me thought of a wonderful story to tell to nicole's mum to persuade her to let nicole stay with us x).walked and looked around for nicole's mum present while dicussing about what to wear for speech training.yayy!!andris and i have the same taste!!!so the theme for the 3 bimbos would be  classy and elegant with glitter and butterfly prints !!!  after that went over to j8 while andris went home.the 3 of us went around squishing all the toys *grins* n icole is violent too!!!BEWARE!!! bwahahaha.walked around for a bit before tingyu's father came to fetch us.thank you my sexy and super sweet tingyu for offering me a ride home!!!btw, tingyu's sister is so much like tingyu!!!  oh.li jia wei got into the semi finals!!! 75% medal hope  for singapore!!!feeling so happy now!!my legs are aching so i better go sleep and wake up again to watch olympics!!i'm hooked on it!:) 
     

    
</post>
<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      i'm so angry at that irritating north korean t.t player.  she has been screaming like a banshee throughout the whole game!!!!!!!!!!according to huizhuang,she sounded like a   chicken being raped    sniffsniff.now the chance for silver and gold is gone.hope that li jia wei can clinch bronze.ahhhh!!!she played so well!!!! thrashed the nkorean 11-0  x) too bad she din get in!!!!!!i was throwing the seeds of the rambutans i ate at the tv(in the nkorean's face)  now in no mood to do anything.we should start mourning and skip school on monday if she din get bronze.or maybe wear all black as it would be " sad day for lijiawei and singapore ".sighhhhhh  oh yea.read what mj and audrey said.made me laughed so hard:  MJ:  but nvm!!! she and susilo will get married and live happily ever after!!  MJ:  train together and live together with one another for support!!! -----------    MJ : i bet she's talknig on the phone with ronald  Audrey : hehe      Audrey : no lah  Audrey:  ronald maybe there already  Audrey : to hug her  Audrey : and ronald will ask: "are you alright?"  Audrey : then lijiawei: "wo hai hao"     Audrey:  but since they're both learning chinese and english now respectively,  Audrey : i believe ronald will ask in a english accent:"ni hai hao ma?"  Audrey : then lijiawei will speak in a cheena accent,"i'm alright"  Audrey : she knows broken english  Audrey : haha         Audrey : really so cute right  Audrey : one speak english the other speak chinese the children will be bilingual   Audrey : like alexteo and angweeling  Audrey : they converse lidat lor  ---------------------------  WAHAHAHAHAH.audrey is cute :) 
     

    
</post>
<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      oh yea.forgot to mention that  ANDRIS LOOKS PRETTY IN ANYTHING !!!! :)  heehee.tingyu should be extremely proud to have a wife as her.bwahahahaa.i shall put the newly weds picture up!!!  hmm.its been 1 day since she left.wonder how's she is doing over at taiwan.sigh.some of the things we saw today like the winnie the pooh bear,the froggie and anything yellow reminds me of her.i think i took her presence too much for granted that i never really did treasure.anyway,i wish for the best for you.hope that you would be  really really  happy over there :)   
     

    
</post>
</Blog>