<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Hima and Abhi go to Subway for some hand-crafted delights. Upon entering, Hima scans the front of the store and happily finds no shady Indian man working the register, which had too often been the case in the past. There seems to be a shady Mexican, but she is not concerned. Hima and Abhi proceed to the Sandwich Artist’s counter. The Seemingly Desi Girl working there shows a quick grin and waits for the order.  Hima: “Hi, still figuring out what we need.” SDG: “That’s OK; I’ll put on my gloves while you decide.” Hima: “OK, ready.” SDG: “Will that be one or two sandwiches?” Hima: “Actually three. A six-inch Wheat, six-inch of that Italian bread, and six-inch Honey Oat.” SDG: “OK and what will you have on those?” Hima: “Chicken breast on the Italian, a Chicken Teriyaki on the Wheat, and Turkey for the Honey Oat. Can I get extra turkey on that?” SDG: “You want double meat you mean?” Hima: “Yes.” SDG: “Is the turkey sandwich yours?” Hima: “Um, yeah.” SDG: “I like turkey too! But I don’t know how you eat that Honey Oat bread, it’s too sweet. Where are you from?” Hima: “Uh, we live in Baldwin. Oh, but my parents are from India.” SDG: “Oh OK, you look Indian. What do you want on the plain chicken sandwich?” Hima: “Just lettuce and mayo. Where are you from?” SDG: (mumbled something) Hima: “Mexican?” SDG: Haha! You think I’m Mexican? Never got that one before. Jose, she thinks I’m Mexican!” Hima: “Uh no, I thought maybe you were Indian, but didn’t want to assume. Then I thought I heard ‘Mexican’” SDG: “I said ‘Pakistan’. But my grandparents, like my mom’s parents, they’re from India. From Gujarat, you know Gujarat?” Hima: “Yes. Oh, you can add honey mustard to that Chicken Teriyaki.” SDG: “So you were born here?” Hima: “Yeah.” SDG: “How old are you?” Hima: “Twenty-five.” SDG: “Wow! You don’t look that.” Hima: “Yeah I get that, some people think I’m in high school.” SDG: “Are you married?” Hima: “Uh, no. See, no ring.” SDG: “Yeah well I don’t wear my ring at work, gets messy.” Hima: “So you’re married?” SDG: “Yes. So, are you even thinking about marriage?” Hima: “OK for the Turkey sandwich, can you add lettuce, tomato, onion…..”  I don’t know what inspired this woman to get to the point of asking my opinions on marriage while making my dinner. At first I thought she was just friendly, but then I realized that “Seemingly Desi Girl” and “friendly” is not a default match. Then I thought she wanted me to be her friend, and then for a second I thought she just plain wanted me. My final conclusion was that she has some male family member that everyone is trying to get married off, and she figures she might as well see if her store’s patrons fit the bill.  Harold and Kumar may have gone to White Castle, but I doubt they encountered anything like this!   
     
    
</post>
</Blog>