<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    I love this picture!!! I think about it now and this had to be one of the funnest nights in Quito, and maybe all of Ecuador. hehehe. Eva, Ashley, me, Kavita, Fernando, Felipe, Negro, Jose in the front, and Leo!  urlLink    
     
    
</post>
<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    A typical hillside in Ecuador, with all of its houses urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    A pretty view out of Kate and Vickys room in the Hosteria Samzara urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Some grafiti that says something like handing over my world means to give up the bible..... I think..... urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    A street in Riobamba urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Angela showing her mountain of jewels urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    The web of love urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    This is me with my latin men....hehehe, Jaime, and Paul, very funny picture urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Jaime, Kate, and Ashley in the cool club that the guys took us to when we came back from the Galapagos urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    This has to be the most hilarious picture ever!! i love it. Kavita, Vicky, Chip, Angela, and Ramsey urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Fernando (with a beard), and Ashley urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    The blue church that we stopped at in Quito urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    A church and the full moon in Quito urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    This is the cuddle crew, during our cuddle fest 2004!  urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    The road to Papayata, the hotsprings urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Fernando, Kate, Alejandro, and Ashley, at the gas station on our way back from the hot springs urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Kavita, Kate, Angela, and Ashley on the Chiva in Quito urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    The hawk that kept on scarying the parrakeets away. urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Kate and Ashley sporting their sexy knee high boots at the resort in the Amazon urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    The grupo at the waterfall in banos urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Kate, Ashley, and Kavita.....along with teen-age mutant ninja turtle, as kate ashley and kavita, and just about anyone who saw him would say. urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    partying it up in Banos urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Part of the group in a dug out canoe urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Kate, Angela (eating kates hair), and Dylan on the Napo in the Amazon urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Kate and Kavita sporting their sexy knee high boots urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Flamingos!!!!! This is on Floreana Island, i love flamingos urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    The dining area of our boat urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    The group on Floreana Island urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    A huge albatross urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Hanging out on the nets urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Kavita, Kate, and Angela urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Galapagos rocky beack urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Espanola island and all of their sea lions urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Kavita imitating a sea lion urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    sea lion pup urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    The cactus forest.......very beautiful urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    This is nearly the whole group playing a game of cards on the Nemo: Vicky, Ramsey, Dusty, Chip, Sam, Eva, and Angela urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    The group on a very cool island in the Galapagos: Chip, Ramsey, Vicky, Ashley,Eva, Me, Dusty, Angela, Kavita, Kate, and Dylano urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Kate and Ashley urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    A spectacular sunset in the Galapagos urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    The entire group on the back of the Nemo, our last night in the Galapagos urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Fabricio the drunk and the rest of our wonderful crew aboard the Nemo urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    The goup doing community service! urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>13,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Hola everyone!!!! this is my Ecuador page with nearly all of my pictures......theres a lot, but they are pretty cute!!!! So yeah i hope you all enjoy it......I had such a great time and i love to share it all with everyone! Love ya! urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Me and Kate....we were standing on those wretched little pillars that they have in Quito, and they were supposed to be in the pic, but Patrick kinda cut them out....hehehehe  urlLink    
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    In the truck going to Papayata. urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Vicky with her extremely cute niece. urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Me and Eva in the train at Nariz del diablo!! urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Dylano and Rambo in the back of the truck on the way to Papayata.......we were having the cuddle fest 2004.......ahhh memories urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Dylano, Dusty, and Vicky in the best falafal place called Aladin. Que Rico! urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    On our way to Papayata the hotsprings, our very last night in Quito urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Patrick and Rachel in the chiva!!!! urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Kate in front of the Chiva!!!!  urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Sam, vince, and Kavita chillin in the church courtyard taking a break from the chiva urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Ashley and Fernando.......Que Lindo!!! (Just imagine Fernando saying it.) urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    The last day i saw Luis........he was so cute  urlLink    
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Luis playing the guitar for me.....he was pretty good urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Luis........what else can i say.....Luis urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Most of my family urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    This is the whole family. Vickys dad was my uncle, and Emily, from the other groups, parents were related to my dad as well. urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Mi amiga Karla y yo before we left in the tiny bus to Quito urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Karla and my mama cooking....they were spectacular cooks........que rico!! urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    This is a mural representing the Spanish Invasion........I dont really know exactly what it says though....... urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    here is me out in front of the oldest church in Ecuador, it was built with the Spanish Invasion in 1530 something urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Me posing at a picture of an Incan King urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Here is my mama y yo en Cajabamba urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    My little sister Anabel at the lagoon. urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Here is my papa and me at a lagoon in Cajabamba urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Mi mama y yo at mi casa en Riobamba urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Riding a horse at the despedida con mi papa Gilberto urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    My mama Sonia, mi amiga Karla, y mi hermana Anabel at the despedida urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Mi papa y yo at the despedida urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Me dancing with my papa at the despedida urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    The group singing Guantanamera urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Poor little innocent Cuys.......poor little innocent cuys........  urlLink    
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    All of the girls smiling at the top of the equator monument urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Some of the girls just chillin: Kavita, Eva, Sam, and Kate urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Sam stradling the FAKE equator urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Me (sam) stradling the REAL equator urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    The whole group outside the monument at the mitad del mundo urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Eva, Ashley, y yo eating lunch at the mitad del mundo urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Me, looking kinda funny after climbing to the top.........look in the corner, doesnt Ashley look funny! hehehehe  urlLink    
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    The Train to Nariz del diablo......yes it is a train, not a bus urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Everyone jumbled in the back of the truck up to start our 3 hour hike up Chimborazo urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Dusty lifting some heavy weights urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    A crazy sea lion that chased Eva  urlLink    
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Galapagos urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    The cool blow spout on Espanola island urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Another pretty pic of the Galapagos urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Eva, Sam, and Angela on the Nemo urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    Some masked boobies urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    can you see all the iguanas in this picture?? theres about 20 urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    An iguana and the Nemo.........que bonita urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    A cool blue footed booby urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    A cactus and the sunrise urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    I love this picture.......Ramsey, Dylan, and Eva making sure that they all have on enough sun screen! urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    A very beautiful beach on Espanola island in the Galapagos urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    What a cool picture of the group in a dug out canoe on the very cool lake  urlLink    
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    The whole group by a huge tree!!!! urlLink   
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    A beautiful pic urlLink   
     
    
</post>
</Blog>