<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       I met Mi-suk at the cafeteria yesterday afternoon. We spotted Young Kyu with a friend nearby. We sat together for a while before he left with his friend. He came back later  shared his lunch though I'd a sandwich. We discussed Korean  Singaporean politics (of all topics!)  he left again to study. Though I'd work, it's good chatting with Mi-suk. Later, we met Young Kyu  Thamar outside the cafeteria. I bought Mi-suk Tiramisu gelato  got myself my favourite pistachio. Thamar tried some but he preferred chocolate stuff. Mi-suk  Young Kyu then invited Thamar  I to dinner.    We watched a bit of Bruce Almighty. Dinner was superyummylicious, though I ate less pork stomach. As it was late, I accepted Young Kyu's invitation to sleep overnight. Opa's vacanted room smelt of cologne. It's been 7 days since his last night in Sydney. Mi-suk  Young-Kyu got me settled in very comfortably. At 11.30pm, I snuggled into the bed, entered slumberland quickly  slept for a good 9 hours.  A warm bed is a great way to end a day.   
     
    
</post>
<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
        Last week, I learnt another interesting fact about emotions during Dr. Fitness’ Psych lecture. It’s termed ‘motor mimicry’ where people tend to stuff like accents, body language, even slanting at the mere mention of the Leaning Tower of Pisa! A psychologist realized that she was feeling down more frequently because she’d been mimicking her depressed patients’ posture! So if you want to feel happy, smile at people around you to get a return smile, smile to yourself when there’s no one nearby,   smile at the screen! Yes, SMILE! (Am I getting a hint of a smile?)    Smiles are an inexpensive way of looking good.         
     
    
</post>
<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       For as long as I can recall, I ate raw tomatoes for the 1st time! The last time one entered my mouth was last year, when Ah Li let me try 1 of her baby tomatoes. I gagged  spat it out.  Anyway, I was so hungry today (despite munching on chocolate rolls  passionfruit tarts oh no) that I bought a ham sandwich at my school cafeteria. There were 2 slices of raw tomatoes inside. I was extracting them out with a fork when I thought: why don’t I just try it for once? I dislike being fastidious. So I chewed the sandwich readily. It wasn’t so bad after all! Perhaps the ham got some of the taste out but still, I’m glad I’m no longer tomatophobic!  La vida es una buena adventura!   
     
    
</post>
<date>17,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       My 1st entry is the one dated 11 August 2004, but today’s the official commencement date! I don’t know why I decided to try out blogspot.com. Perhaps it seems pretty easy to use? Or perhaps, I just want a site where I can note down events significant to me, maybe not to others, so this place isn’t a secret but it’s not important to me whether others read it or not. I’m not sure whether I should let my friends know about this site. The more readers, the more inclined I feel to type entries that will interest them. (shrug) Anyway, I’ve done enough blogging. It’s getting late,  I should start mugging. I’ve got Ling, Math, Music,  Psych to do  I haven't started!!        Planning ahead is one matter; carrying out the plan is another.   
     
    
</post>
<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       I just got an email from mom. She keeps reminding me to pray to God on relationship matters. She allows me to enter a relationship now, but I hope she’ll respect my decision on staying the way I am now. Naturally, there'll be an occasional fleeting thought of romance, but I like the independence, the liberty,  the future’s so unpredictable. While reading the Bible a few days ago, God seemed to be encouraging me to try out the missionary field. Stuff like that can change my entire course of life so it’s best if I’m not leg-shackled to anyone, or vice versa. Yea!        Don't say "I love you" if you don't really care, don't say "For all the days of my life" if commitment's not there.              
     
    
</post>
<date>16,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       I got to know SM at the numeracy centre. He’s from Taiwan, studied English in Vancouver for 2 months 9 years ago,  he’s doing Actuarial Science now. It’s a pity people from Hong Kong  Taiwan don’t regard themselves as people from China. He was really friendly, mingling with so many people there. I’d like to be more amiable, but it’s embarrassing when one forgets names. I forgot Ivanka’s name last Friday, minutes after she told me. I’m pretty satisfied with the amount of work I achieved today. I did about 6 hours' of work (yay!) , though I feel that without that $20  Psychology experiment I participated in, I could’ve accomplished more. I just feel that, if I don’t earn my own pocket money, it’d put a strain on my parents’ income overtime. My home stay rent, transport fares  tuition fees are costly enough.            A smile  a friendly conversation can brighten a dull day.     
     
    
</post>
<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       Opa called!  Though it was late (gulp), it was a pleasant surprise  I was glad to hear that he ‘d safely arrived in Korea. I don't miss him terribly, but selfishly, I wish he was still here. Bible study won't be as fun without him! But nonetheless, his happiness is more important  it's good he's gone back to Korea to finish his Architecture degree.       A simple, warm gesture that shows ‘I care’ is but a phone call away.    
     
    
</post>
<date>15,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       I called Bastian  WH to wish them happy birthday. I couldn't call them at GMT +08.00 as it was already past midnight in Sydney (GMT +10.00). I'm glad my calls were a pleasant surprise! It’s the 2nd time that I’ve wished Bastian before WH. Bleah. Nonetheless, it's wonderful that I’m still WH’s dearest friend. YZ left me a note last Monday that I was her best friend. Though I was pleased, it doesn’t really matter how many people regard me as their best friend, but it matters whether my dearest friend still regards me as hers!         My friends’ joy is the best 'thank you' I can get. I don’t want presents in return. I just want them to spread their joy to others. Likewise, God doesn’t want us to return His grace with sacrifices or adherence to rigid laws like circumcision or fasting. He does, however, want us to spread his love to those around us.    
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
        Ever since I watched ‘Strictly Dancing’ on TV, I’ve become intrigued by professional dancing. ‘Strictly Dancing’ covers dances like the jive, salsa, cha cha, samba, meringue, paso doble, funk, rock n roll, hip hop, jazz  pop.  Anyway, I was so fascinated by this pair of Latin dancers I saw outside the cafeteria, that I collided into a pole! Ouch, my pride hurt! I hope no one noticed!         Many of us can relate to this incident.  At times, we're so engrossed in something that looks captivating from afar, that we fail to see the obstacle before us till it's too late. Consequently, we collide into it,  we stumble.     
     
    
</post>
</Blog>