<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      My new cubemate is making me ill. For all of you folks out there who don’t spend 15 hours a day in a mind-numbing office (even though the two people who actually read this do), a “cubemate,” is someone you share a cubicle with. In my case, our workspaces are right next to each other and we share the little wall that comes up next to our desks. If I look to my left I’m staring at her. And given that I’m not sitting near any windows, I stare at her a lot.  Not that she’s bad looking. She’s Asian, weighs about 90 pounds, and has that bubbly “I just graduated from college and this is my first real job” radiance and naiveté that people seem to respond to. Except for me. I like her, I guess, but after the 5th question she asked me in as many minutes, it kinda got old. Especially since she does it everyday. I’ve been at the company for about 2 years, which is lifetime in Hollywood, so I’m considered a bit of a “veteran.” Which apparently means that you can ask me annoying questions all day and I’m supposed to answer cheerfully. The problem is that I’m not really a cheerful person by nature. I guess I’m nice when I want to be, but the whole reason behind wanting to become an agent is so I don’t have to be nice all of the damn time. But now I’ve got this new Hollywood virgin fawn next to me and all of the sudden I’m den mother.  And the guys love her. LOVE her. I’m used to the busty blonde girls who work here getting all of the attention, but the Hollywood Asian fetish is something that I haven’t quite encountered head on yet. I knew about it, of course, one of my best friends is half Asian and half Black, and Black guys love her because she’s “Black, but not really”(Direct quote, people.) So I always knew it existed. But this is totally different. This is White men salivating over her. I mean, even her boss, who had a passionate hate-filled relationship with his old assistant, (I had my own love-hate relationship with her – she was a bit of a nutcase) LOVES LOVES LOVES her. The smiling, the laughing, the jokes, it’s all extremely annoying. Even when she fucks up, it’s, “oh, it’s okay,” when my former cubemate would’ve gotten a tongue lashing of epic proportions. Not only does it make my work experience exponentially more boring, the ongoing love fest makes me want to puke violently all over my desk.  But I can’t blame the girl. It’s the honeymoon period, of course. In 3 months she’ll be evil and bitter like the rest of us. Lucky for me, I like being evil and bitter. I’m the cool but crazy black girl in the office that the other assistants know not to fuck with. And now here she comes and it’s “Kid Sister and me.” She's fucking with my reputation!  Our male coworkers aren’t making this situation any easier, either. She’s the new office hottie, so everyone wants to take her to lunch, everyone is planning drinks, and there is a steady stream of guys walking past the desk just to check on her and “see how she’s doing.” Barf. I’ve never been the office hottie though. White boys seldom fall for loud mouth black chicks, no matter how cute they are. (Yeah, I said it. I’m cute.) So I’ve always been “one of the guys.” I’m that chick you can talk to about how hot other chicks are. The only play I get is from the other black guys in the office, and unfortunately, they all work in the mailroom and nary a one of them negroes drives a $50,000 Benz.  I’ve always been fine with it though. I like being the girl who forces the white boys to treat her like an equal. I like the fact that some of them are afraid of me. And I like the fact that some of them actually do think I’m hot, but they’d never hit on me because they don’t want to get cussed out. One of these days I’m actually going to have to negotiate some important shit with these fools and I don’t want them simply regarding me as a hot piece of ass. Actually, scratch that. They can regard me as a hot piece of ass all they want. I’m not above using my feminine wiles to get what I want (and I have to use them a lot because of this meager paying ass job). They just know that they will never get it. And I really like that.  So I’ll sit back, answer her stupid questions, and watch her bat her pretty little eyelashes at my cohorts. In three months this company will have chewed her up and spit her bony ass out. And there will be a new hot chick in the office.  This is Hollywood. Everybody gets their 15 minutes. 
    
</post>
<date>18,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Last night on the phone my best friend asked me if I planned to live in Los Angeles for the rest of my life. We were exchanging witty commentary on the Olympics, and I don’t remember how exactly we got to said question, but it was an interesting thing for me to think about.  I’m originally from Washington DC, I lived there for 12 years before being brutally uprooted by my parents and relocating to Los Angeles. In the mind of a 12 year old half way through middle school, that was the worst possible thing to ever happen in my life. Besides the fact that I had been friends with the same group of girls since the 2nd grade, that really cute 14 year old in my karate class had FINALLY started paying attention to me. To say that I was devastated would be putting it lightly.  I hated LA with a dire passion my first 3 years here. All of the sudden I was in the world of palm trees and BMWs (and I’m talking about the cars that the spoiled ass chemistry failing 16 year olds at my private school drove), and I definitely did not fit in. I couldn’t comprehend a 13 year old having a party thrown for him in an airplane hanger because he had learned to recite 10 lines in Hebrew. I had a great time on the indoor bungee cord ride though.  The sun was what got me. Hands down. After a couple of years, I would go back to the East Coast to visit people and be FREEZING MY ASS OFF. I discovered Jamba Juice and Coffee Bean. I learned how to drive in an empty beach parking lot. I fell in love for the first time. And then after a while, it just felt right. After I graduated from college (45 minutes east of LA), there was no where else in the world I wanted to live.  My friends now all agree that I am decidedly an “LA Chick.” My godfather upstate refers to me as his “LA Dolly.” And I’ve stopped flinching when people refer to me as being “Hollywood.” I have to admit. I don’t walk anywhere, I hate going to establishments without valet, I have my beloved Jamba Juice every Saturday, I refuse to wear socks in the summer (and I never wear pantyhose under any circumstances), and I’ve encountered both Hilton sisters at a party on more than one occasion. I’m hooked.  Not that I consider it a bad thing though. Like every other person in LA, I work in “The Industry.” Except I actually have a job. A cruel, draining, thankless job as an agent trainee at a top five talent agency, but I enjoy it. My job is a lot like this city. Most of the people you will come across are fake, self absorbed jerk-offs with a minor sense of moral responsibility at best, but there are pockets of people here and there who actually enjoy what they do, love the “art” (if you dare to refer to Alien vs. Predator as “art”), and are really and truly dedicated to this business for all of the right reasons. And for the record, I do consider money a justifiable reason to be dedicated to something.  I’m so LA. 
    
</post>
</Blog>