<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>22,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    This is Charly with our little ones... The German Shepherd is  Moma , and the little white one is  Bebé . They make us so proud...
     
    
</post>
<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
       urlLink    My first button is ready!!!  I know it´s not the best design, but it´s my first one, and I´m very proud of it.
     
    
</post>
<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      Ok, so I still can´t make my blog look as I want it to look, but i´ll keep it updated the same.  So this are my works in progres:   N° 1:    urlLink     This is how my Sophie is going.  I figured that if everyone else was doing one, I must have my own! It´s the first time I work with circular needles. Here we don´t have those! And if we do, we only use them for finishing collars or so.    N° 2:    urlLink    OK, this is a terrible picture, but I hope the sweater doesn´t turn out so bad.  This a merino sweater wich needs a lace finishing once I´m done with the sleeves (halfway done).   N° 3:    urlLink    I´m  proud of this one. This are my new pillow covers. I must make five of these. One is done and seamed already   N° 4:    urlLink    This is the most boring scarf I have ever started.  It´s a 1x1 pattern.  I hate it, but it was a request from dad.  I think I´ll finish it for next winter (june 2005, here).   N° 5:    urlLink    This is my Grace´s back.  It´s made of synthetic angora.  You wouldn´t believe the softness of this yarn... I´m knitting it along with  urlLink Lisa  Yeah! I have just put her link! This is a whole new discovery for me...  I´m exhausted now. That´s all
     
    
</post>
<date>19,August,2004</date>
<post>

     
      I´ve been knitting for a year now, but I discovered the internet knitting sites only a month ago. For quite a long time I´ve been reading other people´s knitting blogs... First I had to learn what a blog was... Then I found out there were lots of girls that shared my passion all around the world... And at last I became an addict to knitting blogs too! So I decided it was about time I started my own knitting blog. The only problem is that I can´t write a perfect English, and I know nothing about blogs! So I´ll do my best, please be patient!  Now it´s time to introduce myself and my beautiful boyfriend, Charly.   urlLink     This is us. Aren´t we the cuter couple in the world? At least in Argentina we are! 
     
    
</post>
</Blog>