<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>23,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    opening ceremony urlLink   
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Silver medalist Anastasia Kelesidou of Greece celebrates on the podium during the medal ceremony of the women's discus event on 22-08-2004 urlLink   
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Gold medalist Natalya Sadova of Russia, silver medalist Anastasia Kelesidou of Greece (L) and bronze medalist Irina Yatchenko of Belarus celebrate on the podium during the medal ceremony on 22-08-2004 urlLink   
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Hristos Meletoglou of Greece competes in the men's triple jump final at the Olympic Stadium in the Sports Complex in Athens on 22-08-2004 urlLink   
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Fani Halkia of Greece competes in the women's 400 metre hurdle semifinal on 22-08-2004 urlLink   
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Pyrros Dimas of Greece receives the medal for the men's 85 kg category weightlifting event at Nikaia Olympic Weightlifting Hall in Athens on 21-08-2004 urlLink   
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Sofia Bekatorou and Amilia Tsoulfa of Greece (centre) celebrate with their gold medal during the medal ceremony for the women's double handed dinghy 470 finals race on 21-08-2004 urlLink   
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Sofia Bekatorou and Amilia Tsoulfa of Greece celebrate with their gold medal during the medal ceremony for the women's double handed dinghy 470 finals race on 21-08-2004 urlLink   
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Vasiliki Kasapi of Geece shouts out as she successfully makes a lift in the women's over 75 kg category weightlifting competition on 21-08-2004 urlLink   
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Vasiliki Kasapi of Geece jumps in the air as she celebrates successfully makes a lift in the women's over 75 kg category weightlifting competition on 21-08-2004 urlLink   
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Aryiro Strataki of Greece competes in the long jump discipline of the women's heptathlon on 21-08-2004 urlLink   
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Stilliani Tsikouna of Greece competes in the women's discus final on 21-08-2004 urlLink   
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Anastasia Kelesidou of Greece competes in the women's discus final on 21-08-2004 urlLink   
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Anastasia Kelesidou of Greece competes in the women's discus final on 21-08-2004 (a) urlLink   
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Athanasia Perry of Greece celebrates after the women's triple jump qualifying round on 21-08-2004 urlLink   
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ΑΘΗΝΑ, 21 Αυγούστου - Ο Πρωθυπουργός της Ελλάδας, κ. Κωνσταντίνος ΚΑΡΑΜΑΝΛΗΣ και η Πρόεδρος της ΑΘΗΝΑ 2004, κ. Γιάννα ΑΓΓΕΛΟΠΟΥΛΟΥ - ΔΑΣΚΑΛΑΚΗ παρακολούθησαν τον αποψινό αγώνα Υδατοσφαίρισης μεταξύ των ομάδων Ελλάδας και Αυστραλίας στο Κλειστό Κολυμβητήριο του ΟΑΚΑ.  Μετά τη λήξη του αγώνα, συνεχάρησαν τους Έλληνες παίκτες και τον προπονητή της Εθνικής ομάδας της Ελλάδας, κ. Sandro CAMPAGNA, για την νίκη τους επί της Αυστραλίας.  
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      Women's Discus Throw : Comments from medallists  22 Aug. 2004  ATHENS, 21 August - Comments from SADOVA (RUS),  KELESIDOU (GRE),  YATCHENKO (BLR)  Natalya SADOVA (RUS)- Gold medal  On what she was expecting to do at the Olympic Games final  "I expected to win. And to throw near 68-69 meters because there have been good results this year in the discus throw. There were a lot of strong athletes chasing a medal in Athens"  On the competition  "My coach and I  both expected that my first two throws would be the best at the final. But it did not work because I had problems with my technique. At my fourth try I managed to get it together and in the final two throws I was feeling very strong"  On how she feels after winning the olympic gold medal  "Just now I start to realise what happened"    Anastasia KELESIDOU (GRE)- silver medal   On how she felt during the competition  "These are feelings that you can't describe if you don't live it. I thank God that I had the chance to experience this. It was amazing. I want to thank the people that came to the stadium for their help and support"  On whether she is disappointed with winning a second silver medal  "I am always trying for the best result. I really wanted the gold medal, but being on the medal podium for the second time at the Olympic Games is also very important. I am thankful for that"  On whom she wanted to dedicate the medal  "To all the Greeks. I wanted desperately to win a medal for my country. And especially to my parents and coach who have supported me all these years"  On whether she was distracted by what happened with KEDERIS and THANOU  "It is really sad. But I stopped reading newspapers and watching the TV, because I had an aim and I had to concentrate."   Irina YATCHENKO (BLR)- Bronze medal  On how she feels winning the bronze medal  "Of course I am happy with that. The bronze is also a medal" 
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Kalliopi Ouzouni of Greece prepares to throw during the woman's shot put qualifying round, at the Ancient Stadium of Olympia in Olympia, Greece on 18-08-2004 urlLink   
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Aryiro Strataki of Greece competes in the 100 metre hurdle discipline of the womens heptathlon on 20-08-2004 urlLink   
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Hristos Meletoglou of Greece competes in the mens triple jump qualifying round on 20-08-2004 urlLink   
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Fani Halkia of Greece competes in the women's 400 metre hurdle event at the Olympic Stadium in the Sports Complex in Athens on 21-08-2004 urlLink   
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Fani Halkia of Greece is seen after the women's 400 metre hurdle event at the Olympic Stadium in the Sports Complex in Athens on 21-08-2004 urlLink   
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Savvas Panavoglou of Greece competes in the men's discus qualifying round on 21-08-2004 urlLink   
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    PYRROS IN SYDNEY 2000 urlLink   
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ΑΘΗΝΑ, 21 Αυγούστου – Ο εθνικός ήρωας της Άρσης Βαρών  Πύρρος ΔΗΜΑΣ  δεν μπόρεσε απόψε να είναι ο πρώτος αρσιβαρίστας που κέρδιζε το χρυσό μετάλλιο σε τέσσερις συνεχόμενους Ολυμπιακούς Αγώνες, κέρδισε όμως τις καρδιές του κοινού που τον ζητωκραύγαζε στο κατάμεστο Ολυμπιακό Γυμναστήριο Άρσης Βαρών της Νίκαιας.  Ο 33χρονος αθλητής, παρά το καταπονημένο του σώμα, πήρε το χάλκινο μετάλλιο στην κατηγορία των 85 κ., πίσω από τον George ASANIDZE από την Γεωργία και τον Andre RYBAKOU από την Λευκορωσία.  Με μία συμβολική κίνηση μετά την τελευταία του προσπάθεια, ο ΔΗΜΑΣ έβγαλε τα παπούτσια του και τα άφησε στο πλατό, ώστε δείξει ότι αποχωρεί από το άθλημα.  Ο ASANIDZE, που ήταν τρίτος στο Σύδνεϋ λόγω σωματικού βάρους πίσω από τον ΔΗΜΑ και τον Mark HUSTER(GER), προηγείτο στο αρασέ (177,5 κ.) και αύξησε τη διαφορά του με 205 κ. στο επολέ-ζετέ, σηκώνοντας συνολικά 382.5 κ.  Ο RYBAKOU, οποίος νωρίτερα την ίδια ημέρα στον Όμιλο Β είχε σηκώσει συνολικά 380 κ., πήρε το αργυρό μετάλλιο, με τον ΔΗΜΑ (377,5 κ.) στην τρίτη θέση.  Το σύνολο του νικητή ήταν 7,5 κ. λιγότερο από αυτό που σήκωσε στο Σύδνεϋ.  Ο  Γιώργος ΜΑΡΚΟΥΛΑΣ  (GRE) απέδειξε ότι μπορεί να είναι επάξιος διάδοχος του ΔΗΜΑ, χάρη σε μία εντυπωσιακή εμφάνιση κατά την οποία σήκωσε συνολικά 372 κ., και παίρνοντας την τέταρτη θέση λόγω διαφοράς βάρους από τον Κινέζο YUAN Aijun.  Τέσσερις αθλητές δεν μπόρεσαν να ολοκληρώσουν τις προσπάθειές τους, όπως ο Ρουμάνος Valeriu CALANCEA, ο οποίος είχε υποστεί εξάρθρωση του αγκώνα κατά την Αθλητική Διοργάνωση του Δεκεμβρίου στη Νίκαια. Εγκατέλειψε για προληπτικούς λόγους ύστερα από ένα αρασέ 160 κ.  Ο Τούρκος Izzet INCE δεν ολοκλήρωσε, έχοντας αποτύχει και στις προσπάθειές του στο αρασέ, ενώ ο Αυστραλός Sergo CHAKHOYAN απότυχε στις τρεις προσπάθειές του στο επολέ-ζετέ .  Ο ΔΗΜΑΣ, μαζί με τους Norbert SCHEMANSKY (USA) και Ronny WELLER (GER) είναι οι μόνοι αρσιβαρίστες που έχουν κερδίσει μετάλλια σε τέσσερις συνεχόμενους Ολυμπιακούς Αγώνες. 
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink      LEONIDAS SAMBANIS IS INNOCENT    urlLink        ΑΡΘΡΟΓΡΑΦΙΑ   urlLink http://www.in.gr/news/article.asp?lngEntityID=560513   urlLink http://www.in.gr/news/article.asp?lngEntityID=560786lngDtrID=246   urlLink http://www.ekathimerini.com/4dcgi/_w_articles_politics_100016_21/08/2004_46305   
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    O Iakwvou sto plevro tou Sambani yposthrizontas oti prokeitai gia provokatsia.   urlLink    
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Arneitai kathgorhmatika th lhpsh apagorevmenwn ousiwn o Leondias Sambanis  urlLink    
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Tzounto 17-8-2004 urlLink   
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Tzounto 17-8-2004 urlLink   
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Tzounto 17-8-2004 urlLink   
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Tzounto 17-8-2004 urlLink   
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Katadyseis 16-8-2004 urlLink   
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Katadyseis 16-8-2004 urlLink   
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Katadyseis 16-8-2004 urlLink   
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Katadyseis 16-8-2004 urlLink   
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Katadyseis 16-8-2004 urlLink   
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Katadyseis 16-8-2004 urlLink   
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Albert of Monaco urlLink   
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Spectators urlLink   
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Katerina Thanou urlLink   
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Katerina Thanou urlLink   
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Katerina Thanou urlLink   
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Flame arrives in the host city urlLink   
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Katerina Thanou urlLink   
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Katerina Thanou urlLink   
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Gianna Angelopoulou - Lambis Nikolaou urlLink   
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Gianna Angelopoulou Daskalaki - LamBis Nikolaou urlLink   
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Gianna Angelopoulou urlLink   
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Gianna Angelopoulou urlLink   
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Stadium urlLink   
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Denis Oswald - Spyros Capralos urlLink   
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Evzones urlLink   
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Albert of Monaco urlLink   
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
       urlLink    Thalia Prokopiou urlLink   
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2004</date>
<post>

	 
      ΜΕΤΑΛΛΙΑ ΑΓΩΝΩΝ  urlLink http://www.athens2004.com/el/OlympicMedals/medals  ΜΕΤΑΛΛΙΑ ΕΛΛΑΔΑΣ  urlLink http://www.athens2004.com/el/OlympicMedals/medals?noc=GRE  Η ΟΛΥΜΠΙΑΚΗ ΜΑΣ ΣΥΜΜΕΤΟΧΗ  urlLink http://www.athens2004.com/el/ParticipantsTeams/newParticipants?discipline==GREname = 
    
</post>
</Blog>