<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>29,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       yesterday we put in our first order to the t-shirt place... cmg, post no bills, mei-mei, and oakland done by 3/5, see an example tues or wed 
    
    
</post>
<date>27,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
        note:      A)  So we should have two hard copies, 1) to give to them to match the color and to make the screen, and 2) to show them exactly where and size that we want it.  and digital files just for fun.    B)  We should also separate the item into piles ahead of time so we're not doing it at the store.    C)  Inventory, we should also keep track of what shirts we're printing into what graphics.  
    
    
</post>
<date>27,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       yesterday i picked up 2 orders at AA mary took one L/S shirt, esther took one L/S shirt. i took none (yet) 
    
    
</post>
<date>26,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
        Rules  Regulations:   one item per person per color without graphics.  If the item you want is of graphic, then you get to pick one per graphic.  regardless of color.    so this case of my 2 asphalt shirt, I need to put one "back in" for the graphic.  that sounds okay right?  and makes sense?  so everyone gets one without graphic, and one with.  I gave my sister one of the pink, since she funded the first purchase.  that should also be a rule, who ever funds the purchase besides us, should be able to get their pick of the items, like the same rules apply for them for that order...  on a side note, I really like the L/S sheer shirts, it's really comfy, and the sleeve length is long how I like it.  
    
    
</post>
<date>25,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       today is marked... 
    
    
</post>
<date>24,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       6307-long sleeve-asphalt M/OS 12.  ordered... 
    
    
</post>
<date>24,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       2nd, the order:    3308 olive ( tank top) 3308 Creme (Tank top) 5300 Asphalt (pj pants) 5300 Red (pj pants) 2102 Asphalt (t-shirt) 1301 White ( p.e. shorts.) __________ $468.60      total /2 = $234.30 Each, ready to pick up anytime after 10am tomorrow.  
    
    
</post>
<date>23,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink chao's restaurant's website. Izakaya Japanese Tavern  apparently the weeble wobble is their logo besides their name. 
    
    
</post>
<date>22,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       orginally we thought of using the asphalt for the CMG, but if you think that it won't go well on that, then perhaps we should use it on the organic tanks that we're going to purchase on wednesday.  what color for the asphalt then?  would white work?  would it be hard for the graphic people to turn it white and back ground asphalt?  the psd files transfered into tiff files when i save them on my computer it should be okay right?  I really want to just buy the screen printer now, perhaps we should call it and ask about its financing...I've got about $1000 credit that I can charge...ergh!  where's all my money?? 
    
    
</post>
<date>22,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       way to go esther!!  I knew this is why we came to you with graphics!!!  You're the best!  :: big grin:: 
    
    
</post>
<date>22,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       *total for 2nd merch order $477.60 *Half of that is $238.80.  Mary pays half, Vicky pays half.   I'm also thinking that since I have the money right now, i should get the web service, and not just the domain...but...I need to survive the month of March, and we haven't even started March yet, and I'm poor again...if I had no debt, then I wouldn't have to pay for that...I could just spend more freely...kinda...i hate money. 
    
    
</post>
<date>22,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       *decided to buy more merch on Weds, and have vicks pick them up on thursday... *graphics by monday...   
    
    
</post>
<date>16,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i was about to write this on the vickyhsu blog, but its a business thing so im writing here. last night mary asked me some questions then i got all ambitious and stayed up too late (since i had to work at 7 today) finally doing our business office stuff. this is what i did: -itemized the expenses so far. so far is just the shirts, the website fee, and office supplies for me and mary -minutes/a timeline for our business. i only got thru january but ill finish today. its a good thing we have blogs and diaries and planners otherwise we'd never remember anything. -made files for everything 1. expenses (office supplies and AA) 2. suppliers (so far just AA)  today i will complete the minutes/timeline and email them to u to look over 
    
    
</post>
<date>15,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i agree. but different font..check it out esther 
    
    
</post>
<date>15,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink I like the designs of this website , I mean it's simple but easy to navigate and pleasing to the eye.  i like how there's that little pattern, but the colors change between the different web pages, but the pattern stayed the same. 
    
    
</post>
<date>13,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Vicks and I had good ideas for shirts for our worker for when we opened up the store..it's super adorable!!!   
    
    
</post>
<date>12,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       nice meetings guys... 
    
    
</post>
<date>11,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       look at what i found through blog advertisments...   urlLink woven label and hang tags.   I know you probably won't see this until after the meeting, but i thought I'd put it here right now.  I think i'll go with them for right now, cuz well it's "local" and well...yeah like that.  i know there are more, but i just like this one...what do you guys think? 
    
    
</post>
<date>10,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Hi...so we meet again on Wednesday after school and work for all of us?  at a dinner place...I don't know what dinner place, but business meet?  to talk about the hang tag, and the label in more detail... 
    
    
</post>
<date>09,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       my brother's explanation of the difference between palm os and miscrosoft (pocket pc): palm os is more like a pda, for notes, schedule info, like a day planner. pocket pc has more pc functions, like a mini laptop, hence its name pocket pc.   so it depends on what you want. but at their most basic levels/quality is the same. another factor: more functions=more expensive. pocket pc's generally cost more. so decide what you want to use it for and then you'll know which one to get.  "how to buy a pda" http://www.pcworld.com/howto/bguide/0,guid,11,page,1,00.asp  "buying guide : handhelds" more comprehensive.. http://www.pcmag.com/article2/0,4149,4134,00.asp 
    
    
</post>
<date>09,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       okay i know I said that I didn't want to be front woman of our operations, like with the name, but you know that store B.Luu, that's her name, and that's her store...so maybe it'll be okay...  Okay so until the next time, I'm fine with MLee...  shall look through the phone book, the chinese phone book for the hang tag and woven labels... 
    
    
</post>
<date>08,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       what's the difference between the palm os and the microsoft. pro and con list...   and you can purchase one today, if you've got the moolah 
    
    
</post>
<date>08,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       ....i kinda wanna buy it today....ehhh 
    
    
</post>
<date>08,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
        let's have a meeting all 3 of us soon...  heres the skinny on palms:  the main thing is the operatiing system 1. microsoft or 2. palm os  the only important thing is that all 3 of us agree on the software. then we can choose whichever palm we want for ourselves. i kinda want to go with the palm os but it doesn do Word or Excel or Outlook. but is that important?? i dont know   
    
    
</post>
<date>08,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink okay these are cute, but selling for $37.00?? I'm not sure that I'd pay this much for it, but I suppose if I wanted this shirt I'd pay this much for it...    urlLink I also like the gray and the pink together.  Maybe not the design, but I like the colors together...like how Vicks likes the Asphalt and that blue...    urlLink I really like the lime/pink polo...am i lame or what?...oh! OUTKAST won album of the year, I suppose since they performed twice that means they are going to win...anyway I want to make polos...   OKay I see these people as competition, but not really, everyone's got enough money to spend, and the girls we're targeting will still buy the items even if they've got no money...let's send in our stuff to Girlshop when we get the merch made. 
    
    
</post>
<date>07,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I think someone else should do the website... 
    
    
</post>
<date>07,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I saw the apparel label as well, but I wasn't sure where they were located, and their forms were TOO technical for me.  I mean, I'm not really sure what I want on the woven label, perhaps we should talk about that.    I thought we'd have the lamb logo, and the Mlee, inc.  and what else?  what colors?  Asphalt color for the lamb logo, and the Mlee, inc.  Simple in colors!  and about how big do we want it?  I suppose for the underwear it should just be Mlee, Inc.  Would that be too weird?  Or, should we just have the logo in a tiny form.  We should just have the logo on then on the side, it would say Mlee, Inc.?  But then bigger lable we could have a bigger logo, and the Mlee, Inc under.  what do you guys think?  I like the namesake one, only cuz it was easier to navigate around.  and i kinda like that it's iron on, but the logo custome made ones aren't iron on, we'd have to get someone to sew it...another step.  argh.  Maybe the embrodiery place will just have that, and they can sew it on as well...perhaps we should design some, by we i just mean esther, and then go to the places around our casas and ask if they can design and sew it on at the same time...that would be less time.  damn, this project is turning into a bigger and bigger.  Like I never knew there was so much I needed to think about.  and I didn't know there was so much additional than the shirts and what not...this is hard...argh.  Hang tags, woven labels...what else is there??  what else am i missing?  I'm tempted to say we should just forget the labels, but it's like a mark.  i just never thought about it that way that's all.  I want someone else to research and developing...and someone supply me with some money...my head hurts from all the thinking.  yay you're on!!!   
    
    
</post>
<date>05,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       wow look at esther r  d. 
    
    
</post>
<date>05,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       yay. i'm on.   ne way, did you call any other label places?   http://www.namemaker.com/customwoven.asp  http://www.clothing-label.com/index.htm  http://www.clothinglabels.com/index.asp if we wanted high quality, this place seems good. they seem to know how to work with text as images rather than just word processor text.. but they've got names like oscar de la renta, and hangtags for calvin klein, nordtsroms.  p.s. i was thinking that i saw the classic girl labels before and i figured out where. the pajamas pants that thuy got me for christmas are the classic girl brand, with embroidered letters. 
    
    
</post>
<date>05,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink woven labels?  they can't do logo though... but cheap.  
    
    
</post>
<date>05,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       The shop that I went to said any form is okay.  so i'm guessing most likely you should have a digital copy for the sake of the records, but then drawn...only if you've got a scanner or you work on the computer.  I'm not sure how you output your graphics.   Vicks and I also decided to purchase more shirts.    also i think we should ask the people if they test printed so then we can see them...perhaps we should all go as to convey what we wanted...i should find a place that's open on the weekend, or at least saturday...right?  this is a lot harder then i thought... 
    
    
</post>
<date>05,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i was going to call Mary but then i smartly realize that its 130am and maybe not everyone but me and the other workers are up at this hour. 
    
    
</post>
<date>05,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I've made "handmade/homemade" hang tags.  I think they are super cute, although not in color...I'm a genius! hehe.   anyway, I think we should use them for at least the first couple of batches, and I guess if this company becomes more busy, then we'll get them printed...sounds good huh?    Vicks picked up the merch today...all we're waiting for is the graphics.  I really wanted to just drop them off at the printers, but I had no designs to drop off...oops.  Vicks, perhaps this Sat. we should go to that embroider that is on gale to see if you like any of their fonts, and figure out how much embroidering would be, if you're up to. Only cuz you had that idea of the font in your head.  Es...would you be able to design by this weekend?  I wonder what format I need to give to the printers?  Like paper format, or Digital okay??  I suppose I should ask huh?  I wish it was closer to my house, that way I can just drop by...but it's not.  anyway those are my business thoughts today. 
    
    
</post>
<date>04,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I can not get beyond t-shirts with letters...i need more help...anyone?anyone? 
    
    
</post>
<date>03,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink practice website?  have you noticed that all my websites look alike??hehe with tables and stuff...  
    
    
</post>
<date>03,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       It's under a totally different web hosting company, called ipowerweb.com.  they are currently my host for emdotlee.com.  i find that their service is better, and that it is located in Santa Monica.  It's just domain name registering right now...I've grabbed it.  and when i get more money, or when the designs are ready, i'll turn it into a website. 
    
    
</post>
<date>03,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       whereyougetthat.com  under your registration on yahoo or mine, mar??? 
    
    
</post>
<date>03,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Our order will be ready for pick up in three hours...from right now...it's 1:30pm.  But if not today, then anytime tomorrow.  We are so in business now.  the total is $402.00 and here's what I ordered.    3308 red  3308 asphalt 8301 white 8301 red 5300 red 5300 powder pink  all in dozen quantity and M/OS size.  we now also have an customer number with them, and so next time we order, we just give them the customer number.  I sounded dumb when i said that we didn't have a company name, but then later said oh yeah we do...hehe.  Such a retard.    I think my next step is establishing the website, whereyougetthat.com...i shall go browse the internet about that now.    So Vicks you just need to pick up the envelope with the money, which i will get later, and the directions and the order, just so you know what you're getting.  that is all...i think...i'll write later if I find more stuff that's work related.    We've got Merch! 
    
    
</post>
<date>03,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       yeah ill go but i told u that already 
    
    
</post>
<date>03,February,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Yay me!  the first post for Mlee, Inc.  I researched today for business cards.  I figure those I can just go anywhere really, cuz they aren't that expensive.  While I was researching for that, I also found these promotional printing that companies can do, and I thought of other ideas.  as in catalogues...but perhaps we should just do a online catalogue.  do you think we should set up another website fully devoted to it, instead of just using my emdotlee?  we'd call it, whereyougetthat.com?  what do you think?  So as soon as Esther gives me the logo, then we can go ahead and get the business cards printed.  I also looked into Hang tags as well...look at me being productive.    something else i thought of is that perhaps Vicks, i'll just give you the cash, and you go down to their warehouse and pick up the items, because I don't trust the colors that we have, i'd rather go down in person, but I can't cuz they're operating hours are 8-5:30pm.  what do you think?  You'd be up for that, operations??  On Thursday or Wednesday, which ever day you're off.  I'll give you all the info... anyway, if not, then I'll come up with a new plan.  Yep, so away we go!!! 
    
    
</post>
<date>30,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       we've all got email addresses...esther@whereyougetthat.com, vicky@whereyougetthat.com, and mary@whereyougetthat.com...but i don't really need one as it just goes to me anyway...and i've forwarded your esther@wygt  vicky@wygt to your prospective emails...the hotmail one for esther and vicks aol one...if you want it changed to another address let me know. or you can access it through their webmail as well... urlLink http://host167.ipowerweb.com:8080/webmail/index.pl  
    
    
</post>
<date>29,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       whereyougetthat.com shall be up shortly...until then please visit  urlLink http://host167.ipowerweb.com/~whereyou  when i said up shortly i meant just the basic page...perhaps if you gave me a design i could be able to make something similar...i still haven't talked to the girl about webmastering.  perhaps we can still use the ghetto style again...ergh.  i wish i was a professional...ghetto me. 
    
    
</post>
<date>29,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       the kelly green does not come in the 2102 style...but the rest okay.  here's the order. 6307 olive M 1  5431 white M 1 5431 asphalt M 1 5431 Navy M 1 3308 White 24 2001 Asphalt M 24 3308 Fuchsia M 12 ________________ total $296.85 
    
    
</post>
<date>27,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       have spent the past hour making business cards for me...i like them, so i think i'm going to use them for myself.  i don't need esther designed ones...no offense esther.  i just don't want to make more work for you.  and to vicky, did you want one designed for smooth from esther...  to end this, i know we wanted professionally printed ones, but I've got these business cards just sitting around, so why not use them...(hey i'm a gray blob)...(no chet!)...i liked how they came out...so yep. i'm going to use them, ghetto style. 
    
    
</post>
<date>27,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i am not taking Sunny home tomorrow...so I'm free to move about the cities once they leave...should we mini meeting before or after or whatever? 
    
    
</post>
<date>25,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i have dled a whole bunch of fonts off of fontalicious...read the details...if we're planning on using them for merch purposes...we should pay..their $15.00 postscript deal...what you think? 
    
    
</post>
<date>25,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i think i submitted a proposal regarding the ipowerweb upgrade, but I'm not sure about that, they have not sent me any email regarding the changes...we shall see huh?  I guess I just wanted a response right away. 
    
    
</post>
<date>25,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       party details in case anyone needs to access them on the fly  Chomp Rockin' Sushi and Teppan Grill 181 E Commonwealth Ave 714-738-3511 714-738-3513 fax www.chompsushi.com  owners: dan lauriano and cameron irons manager we talked to: jacob (on 3/24/04)  Esther's 14 1. cyn 2. jane b 3. jessica 4. thuy 5. lina 6. julie 7. matt/gf 8. aaron and friends 9. sisi 10. candice 11. greg 12. nick 13. andrew 14. it wasnt on the list but im assuming u know  Mary's 14 1. isabella 2. trisha 3. carrick (he-he) 4. ryland 5. may 6. stella's son 7. angela 8. april 9. caroline kuo 10. joyce from 205-206 11. harry 12. april and vanessa 13. ray (from wahoo's) 14. melissa from whittier  Vicky's 14 1. anny 2. najam 3. paul hsu 4. john ruste 5. marshall 6. annie (my trainer) 7. erin welty (my original trainer) 8. will/jessica 9. amber/paul 10. chae 11. my brother/bren 12. dj dax! 13. nick 14. lee, if he's not in town toni, if i cant find her aaron chang 
    
    
</post>
<date>23,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i can't see the bunny logo... 
    
    
</post>
<date>22,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       first sale ever on my end...  date: 3/23/04 @7:41pm  customer:  Carlos Chang  Order:   Post No Bills, Asphalt -$15.00 CMG, Red - $10.00 Oakland, Red - $20.00 Mei-mei, pink - $20.00 total ==================$65.00  form of payment: CASH  P.S. I discounted the pants cuz he's poor, and bought a lot of stuff...for his girlfriend.  i gave him the girlfriend discount. $10.00 off the pants!  that is all.  Yay first sale ever!!!  It was bizarre. 
    
    
</post>
<date>22,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       wednesday is good for me to meet. i should be able to send all the comps late late tonight. so check for it tmrw.  for mary: we should scan the bunny page and pull the background paper out so we can use it as B/W and in other colors. you can do that if you know how in photoshop, or you can scan it and give it to me.   what are crooket prints? as in offset/not in the middle of the shirt? 
    
    
</post>
<date>21,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       1. then let's ditch the pretty/cute shirt idea for now. we can do it later.  2. you can scan it if you want. but i dont want to give the printers the original, so we'd print out a copy anyway. i just thought to have esther scan it so she can put all the files on ONE cd.  wed is good. anytime. let's get down... 
    
    
</post>
<date>20,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       to vicks: a few question regarding homework...  1...you were actually the one that wanted to pretty/cute shirt, so perhaps you should think of the design...I just wanted letters, they could be arial font, infact they are arial font in my head. 2...why do i have to give esther the bunny sheet? just so she can put in the computer?  but i thought tsw likes hard copies...well i suppose we're supplying both formats.  i'll just bring it along so we can talk about it again...  meeting at wahoos, they let  you just sit there and chat forever or esther's house, or vicks house...my house is out of the question.  meeting whenever is fine...i don't have much to do, esther's got this whole list of things...wednesday? our usual time. 
    
    
</post>
<date>20,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       denied again...From: cut+paste   Date: Sun Mar 21, 2004  07:14:33  PM US/Pacific To:   Subject: Re: Consignment Application  Thank you for taking the time to fill out the cut + paste Partner in Craft form!  I received the application you sent and took a look at your items.  ** Unfortunately, at this time, our consignment spots are currently full for this month.    I've received a lot of great applications for the program and wish I could take them all!  I'll hold on to your consignment forms and hopefully we can work together in the near future.  Thanks again!  If you have any questions please feel free to contact me! Keep up the great work!  xoxo, jenny    C U T + P A S T E P.O. Box 380-464 Brooklyn NY 11238  www.cutxpaste.com info@cutxpaste.com     on 3/14/04 4:36 AM, doraemonblueblue@yahoo.com at doraemonblueblue@yahoo.com wrote:  redirect: http://www.cutxpaste.com/frame_thankyou.html  name: Mary Lee  company: mlee, inc - bunny  site+url: none  item: t-shirt  selectname: Clothing  retail+price: $25.00  quantity: 5  material: cotton  measurements: 22inch tall X 15 inch widest  photos+or+description: where you can see the photo of the shirt http://www.emdotlee.com/postmerch.html  special+notes: these are printed on american apparel merch.  Most of our shirts have a meaning behind them, the post no bills shirts come from NY, this is just our first batch of merch, once our graphic team is less busy we'll crank out more merch.  your+profile: we're three girls that thought that we wanted to start our own clothing line and it all really started with this shirt, the post no bills shirt, we were walking along the streets of NY  thought we'd like to wear this.  We just feel like our graphics is much better than some of the stuff out there, and what's better than wearing something you're proud of.  We're a prefect team, we all bring together our specialty, graphics, business  ideas...us together just works.    
    
    
</post>
<date>20,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       FOR EVERYONE NEXT MEETING'S TOPICS  1. decide together shirt and print colors 2. how many of each shirt 3. how to market (i think we're ready!) 4. crooked prints? yes or no 5. mary give esther the bunny sheet 6. all go over list of shirt ideas mary made last night  any other topics? what day to meet? 
    
    
</post>
<date>20,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       TO DO FOR VICKY: 1. buy printer tomorrow at office depot after work(i get off at 5:350p) 2. think of boys clothes names and ideas for future shirts 3. mission statement 4. press kit 
    
    
</post>
<date>20,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       TO DO FOR ESTHER: 1. prints:    1. i bunny bunny or i heart bunny    2. where you get that or whereyougetthat or whereyougetthat.com    3. sheet of bunnies (mary has this)    4. pretty/cute (mary has more ideas on this one)    5. post no bills (for boys, just enlarge the print) 2. bunny logo to put on all shirts 3. where you get that logo 4. later prints to work on and think about -don't forget to water the carrots! on thought bubble -chubby bunny, fluffy bunny -shirt with the bunny hiding like we talked about (we can even include this shirt in our next batch) -crooked prints 
    
    
</post>
<date>20,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       TO DO FOR MArY: 1. think of exactly what you want for the "pretty/cute" shirt for esther to design. and do u want that shirt in with this next print batch? 2. estimate how many shirts you want to buy and what colors. we said end of this month to buy next shirts right? also, dont forget to include asphalt boy shirts for the "post no bills" shirt. 3. look at wood cutting catalog when it comes, or think of products you want to purchase for next printmaking club meeting 
    
    
</post>
<date>20,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i requested a DANIEL SMITH catalog for the po box and for my house so we'll get 2.  last night we watch matt 13 screen print shirts at csuf rm 180 2-story art building after the very first ever printmaking club meeting. we also had a meeting afterward in the same room. see my notes for what we went over.  i will post on here everyone's tasks later tonight. i have to collate and see what everyone needs to do.   WHEN IS THE NEXT MEETING? 
    
    
</post>
<date>20,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       *i like to read *read more *what's the hold up?  VOTE! *hug me *go away *i miss you *put your hands where i can see them *i'm hungry *surprise me *i'm a dog person *I'm a cat person *it's my first time ( i think this one has been done before...but we can do it in japanese and that'll be cool.) * call me *i need new clothes. *make it go away *i love you ...i'm going to think somemore, just off line...and while watching return to me. 
    
    
</post>
<date>20,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       vicky's tasks: -mission statement rough draft -rough draft press kit -get a printer cuz i dont have one anymore 
    
    
</post>
<date>19,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'm an "impressive girl?"  awwwww...  like a press kit...??  I don't get the concept oriented design...but I suppose I don't need to, I don't design.    how important of a person?  within the circle of the young hollywood, we're actually closer then it actually seems, we might be able to impress an young hollywood!!  I mean we live near enough to all the hubbub we CAN do it...  i've said this before but I'm going to say it again, Perhaps this first batch of clothing should be used as promotional pieces, not all,  but some, and at the next meeting we'll come up with a mission statement and stuff, and then we'll be in production for impressing very important ONE person.    hehe...I'm an impressive girl...I never thought so...hehe... 
    
    
</post>
<date>18,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i think we need a mission statement. like what type of clothing we want to sell... what we're all about. and for the name, we should go with somewhat high impact, something people will remember. i always have trouble remembering fallout's name. i guess i'm trying to say that we need a corporate identity... it can shift and evolve over time, but we should start with at least one thing that we want to stand out for.  also, i think the next shirts we make, should be concept oriented, because in terms of sales, if someone is forced to make an intellectual connection in a concept, they will probably remember a design more. (that statement is directed towards me, i suppose). i think once we actually have an audience, the shirts/pants we have will sell just because people will want things from our company, but we have to be somewhat established first. so in order to stand out and to get our name out there, we need at least one  product that is memorable. so that other companies/clients associate our name with a concept/design/identity.   WE JUST NEED TO IMPRESS AT LEAST ONE VERY IMPORTANT PERSON. and i KNOW we can do that, because we're very impressive girls.   the nametags are very nice. very professional and clean. i like a lot. i guess we just need to add a logo. but otherwise they make us look like we know what we are doing. 
    
    
</post>
<date>18,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       have AIMd melissa, the webmaster, about the tank.  got her address and will mail it out tomorrow also wrote her a letter... 
    
    
</post>
<date>15,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i think "E PARK" is perfect for the boys line 
    
    
</post>
<date>15,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i got receipt books from greg. 2 sets of 200. they are old. but how much do receipt books change really. 
    
    
</post>
<date>15,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i'm tired of name changes, let's just pick one, and stick to it...  i sent melissa their previous webmaster an IM regarding the shirt.  I told her that we made a shirt and would like to present it to her as a promotional piece, and was wondering if she'd like to accept it.  got her away IM so logged off, shall try later. 
    
    
</post>
<date>14,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       chubby bunny was brought up yesterday. lets have a discussion about it   chubby bunny  
    
    
</post>
<date>12,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       well just emailed cut  paste about doing consignment...they take 40% of the profits.  probably will be rejected cuz we're not handmade, but maybe they'll like it and sell for us anyway...here's to hoping. 
    
    
</post>
<date>12,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i heart Rippa...is this bad that I want to bite other people's ideas?  I really need to learn how to silk screen...help please?! 
    
    
</post>
<date>12,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i think we need to send our samples to target the audience we have in mind. cuz girlshop seems like they do a lot of high end stuff, even tho their website looks ghetto. so like urban, fallout/beach access and i can't think of anymore... where they sell shirts at reasonable prices.  but i'm glad we sent something out, cuz its a NO if you don't even try. so yay. 
    
    
</post>
<date>11,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       yesterday went to first ever full blown rose show in santa clarita at some place called the chicago bar on soledad canyon rd. www.fullblownrose.com. gave jessica (cousin's friend) one asphalt CMG tank and one asphalt MEIMEI pant. we're going to chalk it up to promotion and marketing. 
    
    
</post>
<date>11,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
        denied ..."Thank you for your interest in Girlshop.  Girlshop was designed with a very specific consumer in mind -- a niche audience that we know intimately. Naturally, we are very careful to remain faithful to our original vision and to select items that will appeal to this market.   Although fond of your merchandise, we do not feel that it is a perfect match for Girlshop.  We appreciate your time in sending us information. We are glad to know about you and will certainly keep you on file.  Sincerely,  Girlshop"  
    
    
</post>
<date>10,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       have sent an email to buyer@girlshop.com regarding our items...wholesale prices...well I guess we'll see what happens...we need more merch!!! 
    
    
</post>
<date>10,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       guy shirts...but currently we're doing girl shirts.  we need famous girl people.. is boy shirts the way to go?!  I like girl shirts though, cuz I like to be able to wear them...  Isabella works for a magazine, maybe we can give her the two shirts and ask her to wear it for work and "advertise" for us?  She works for Sphere magazine...  were you thinking Giant robot editors?  Cute ideas for shirts...now we just need to learn to silkscreen...i know I know that's always how it is...  I can not scrap money for the website hosting...perhaps more towards the end of March...until then... 
    
    
</post>
<date>10,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i want to make shirts that say: "DON'T CRY, MARTH, DON'T CRY" with a picture of martha   we can just do a few handmade on silkscreen.  there could be a whole series: "DON'T CRY MICHAEL, DON'T CRY" (EISNER) "DON'T CRY GRAY, DON'T CRY" (DAVIS)  "ITS MY PARTY AND I'LL CRY IF I WANT TO" sex and the city! 
    
    
</post>
<date>09,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       maybe we should send the shirts to magazine editors. u know how they have their free stuff to review... or we can give the shirts to famous people to wear, but there's no guarantee that they'd wear them.  anita started by making shirts for the guys in the band. she would give one out along with her business card, and do a little shpeel and if they wanted to get more, she would start charging. she sells for pretty cheap tho, and so far she has a lot of her shirts going to the phantom planet guys.   WE NEED TO ADVERTISE!   the only other thing is selling to stores. nordstroms? we just take samples to stores and try to sell to them. its less profit, but its more sales, and its fewer people we need to make personal contact with.  
    
    
</post>
<date>09,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       should we open up an ebay store?  we can set our prices at where we're selling them??  or just still do the auctions and just set the price at where we would be willing to part with?  to sell some?  i think it's hard to sell on ebay when you're doing the cheap way...so maybe we should nix that idea, but but but, we're not selling...how do we get the word out??? 
    
    
</post>
<date>09,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i heard from anita that the show is sold out.. so i checked the website.. which says it is sold out. so is this a problem? are we just going anyway?  
    
    
</post>
<date>08,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       vicky doesn't like the repeative of bunny bunny, nor did we really talk more on this, perhaps on Wednesday, but for now I suppose bunny on everything...we can keep it simple black outline  then have it interchangeable with other colors, like we can use blue or pink or whatever we feel like, just the main logo is the black...I like the black on blue where you test drew for the tattoo.why don't we talk about this some more at wednesday before the EBE show.  tired now, shall sleep or try to sit there and conserve energy... 
    
    
</post>
<date>07,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       nm.. i looked it up.. wednesday. thanks ne way. 
    
    
</post>
<date>07,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       question: so i should just do everything with the bunny? any color preferences?  and when is the EBE show again? 
    
    
</post>
<date>07,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       the updates look great. good on the text formatting.    what about a dark blue to go with the lighter blue. try 003366, 000066 (this one is really dark)  or green 333300 
    
    
</post>
<date>07,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I gave the red oakland to my sister because I didn't want to wear it out, i already have a pair of red pants....just for your records sake, even though giving it to her is like me having it. 
    
    
</post>
<date>07,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I changed the website a bit more...neater, more information...I'm not crazy about the maroon looking color...need help?  what color would go good with that 99ffff color? 
    
    
</post>
<date>07,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       while i was sleeping but brain not sleeping i thought maybe we can call it Bunny B, or B. Bunny.   
    
    
</post>
<date>06,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       eye!   good job on the website... i  do  know how much time it takes to build a website, and that every little thing takes forever. so the hours you slaved over it are definitely appreciated.  and i know you said you didnt want to hear it but there has to be some constructive criticism in order for the best possible product... and i know htis is just a first draft, so i'm gonna point out things that i think need changes from this initial point: i think later on there needs to be a homepage that's seperate from the merchandise page where we have all our stuff. just so that we can add whats new, post updates, links to about the company, contact, distribution, etc. and then from the homepage there could be a link to the main merchandise page that shows all our stuff, like how it is on the homepage right now. but thats a navigational issue.  i like that theres different colors for tanks, pants, and shirts, the only downside being that it might not always complement the color of the clothes that are being posted. we can figure that out later tho. i think the periwinkle blue for the tanks background doesn't work for the shirt colors, but i just dont like that color to begin with, so maybe its just me.  and i think the font needs to be changed. its alright for the headlines, but it doesn't function well for smaller text. just in terms of versitility, courier doesn't work because there are not enough variations for the same font. for example, futura comes in like 10 different varieties of thickness... light, book, medium, bold, heavy, and extra bold. plus italics, expanded and condensed versions of each thickness. which means that you can mix n match any of them, in order to emphasis different things, and you're still allowed uniformity. courier just doesn't have that luxury. i like the typewriter look of courier, in which case american typewriter might be a good second choice. its similar to the look it conveys, but it has those different variations. if you don't have that font, i could probably get you a copy.  otherwise, its great. i'm glad we have a website, and it works and you can buy things from it! which is what we need. so thanks. 
    
    
</post>
<date>06,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink Before you dismiss my ghetto sample website, i would like everyone to know that I spent forever on this.  i know the pictures are not uniform, nor is the website uniform with the size of the picture, it was hard work.  It's not easy taking the picture, editing  putting it all together with the links...if you've done a website before you'll know that a simple website is not as simple as it seems...that's all...   I know that my websites pretty much look a like, but there doesn't seem to be anyone else volunteering to do it,  we don't have the budget for a paid website..we barely have the money...you know each page takes about half an hour starting from editing and making sure all the links work...argh.  I guess I just don't want to hear criticisms for this because of the hours that I put in.  I already know that it's not professional looking, I'm not a professional web designer, i never claimed to be, and as for my photography, it's hard to have a professional one when all I have to work with is my room  bad lighting, and no equipment.  I don't even have people to work with...I'd like to have a "professional" photo shoot, but it just seems like we don't have the time for that this weekend.  and well I've got no vision for it yet?  Are we possibly doing it in Vick's backyard again?  I guess what I'm trying to say while beating around the bush about it is that I worked hard to me on that "graph" of inventory that I wanted to show people, but then you were like, well your way of doing things are crap  it doesn't matter anyway there's no need for that, and we don't need to see it, you don't keep good records anyway.  Hurt my feelings why don't you...Sorry to hash out at you here...but it just popped up while I was thinking about the website. because you often say blunt truthful things that hurt...sometimes the truth hurts...examples are 1. the website thing which I just talked about.  2. the let's leave the designing to esther...I mean I know I'm not a graphic designer, but you don't have to sit there and bash my good intentions.  I was just excited about making shirts, and I wanted to try them out...argh, basically you're saying that I sucked at picking out letter and placing them...you know I've got not  a lot of selections at Michaels when trying to pick out stick-ons.. I know I'm not a graphic designer, but the shirts that I was fooling around with had nothing to do with the shirts that we were making, I was just having fun, you don't have to squash it.  should I go on with the whole truthful thing...I'll write it on my blog cuz the rest doesn't have anything to do with the company. 
    
    
</post>
<date>05,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       i was going to say...  i need figures for the hang tags. just rough ones for the expenses. and for your graph paper for your own inven. 
    
    
</post>
<date>05,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       order # 11089117 order date: 3/6/04  $34.00   s-6649  9X12 Polybag w/ back flip 1M/ct   qty 1. $ 2.64    tax $ 8.50    shipping _______________ $45.14     total paid with wamu check card/debit card/visa   Ship date:  03/08/2004 
    
    
</post>
<date>05,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       eye...but i want to have a proper discussion about it all three of us. this wed????? before/after EVE show?  i want lame hangtags for my clothes!!!! 
    
    
</post>
<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       I'm going to make the business cards and hang them with my clothes, since we're going ghetto style with this first batch, i'm just going to go ahead and do it...and I also think we should change our name from mlee, inc. to Bunny bunny...cuz bunny now means love.  and we can use the bunny bunny shirts as our logo shirt as well as a easter shirt...everyone agree say "eye"  "eye"  i like that a lot better then mlee, inc.  to me mlee, inc was a bit lame.  and we can keep the website the same as whereyougetthat.com, but now we can change the logo to the bunny you know THE bunny.  It's cute, i like it.  you like it, you like it, we're all in agreement right?  bunny bunny...yes, no?  answer me damn it!  so here i go making my lame hangtag  holepunching them with my 1/16" hole puncher...if you want lame hangtags for your pile of clothes let me know...if you want to make your own, that's cool... 
    
    
</post>
<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
        urlLink business card specs  est...for u, i think we can use these people, they have tiny orders  postcards...you design it, and they print it.  guess where i found these people??  hah blogger as well, blogs...the useful adverts...I love it. 
    
    
</post>
<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       So i've sat this for the entire morning  thought about how much we should charge, and I've come up with a formula based on how much it cost for us to produce it, and honestly, I'm not sure that it works that well.  I mean  this formula makes the shirts cost less than the tanks to produce, because the tanks were a bit more than the shirts, it's the material that's why...and so i want to charge like $25.00 a shirt  charge like $20 for the tanks.  but...i'm not sure about that.  I've come up with two numbers.  $22.75-tank $42.25-pants $20.75-shirt  $29.00-tank $54.00-pants $26.00-shirt  the bottom set of number sans tax, the top with tax.  Okay so here's what I t 
    
    
</post>
<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       went to printer today to see sample...shirts done tomrow. (i kno u said it already but i write it for me) :P 
    
    
</post>
<date>04,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
        *logo  - the sheep??  *woven label  - i'm thinking this is just the logo  MLee, Inc.?  *hang tag  - this will be like the tags from Paul Frank, cuz he's my idol, where it says "thanks for buying me," and "logo on the other side."  not necessarily the price tag...so this one we should mass produce professionally. *personality price tag - this is where we put what it means and/or why we made the shirt  the price tag maybe. *business card?? - is esther designing this,  we're also mass producing these?  500 each was Vicky's idea. *Website - WYSIWYG, that means what you see is what you get.  we should work with someone on this...everyone it seems like dabbles a little, no one really does it really good on a regular basis  we're friends with and would spare their time for this...ergh  I bought a 1/16 inch hole puncher  tried it out on the previouslly made cards that I was going to use for the hang tags...I like it, it punches the small holes, but I need to figure out a way to punch it so that it does "injure" the other parts of the paper.    are we doing the hangtags   Woven labels professional?  i guess that's the question.  I guess if we had the money then we can...I guess it's all up to me then to ask for the money...I need to tell her about my car anyway...it's making the put put put noise.  If we don't get the money I guess we're doing it homemade...If I was artsy I'd homemake everything...  oh for future to think about.  When we set up the website store, we should think of what boxes we're going to buy, or are we just using the prioriety boxes, you get those for free but you have to use their service, and if we sell like out the back of our cars, what bags are we giving people  tissue paper?  i have a catalogue that we can skim through at our next casual meeting.  Guess what?!  We can actually wear a CMG tank to a EBE show!!! OMG! Are we all wearing one??  Technically we can all wear one in a different color, it would make more of an impact...  I feel kinda bad now for making money off of someone's name...I suppose that's the whole point of stardom...I mean I'm sure all those people  that make the money from the tshirts that says i heart so and  so isn't paying residuals to the so and so...right??    Speaking of money, I'm going to sit here  think about how much to charge people.  Hehe, we're like selling shirts in the back of Vicky's car! Haha!!!  Hilarious!    We get the merch tomorrow!!!!! 
    
    
</post>
<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       ok, i should be able to get something out by this weekend. i can work on it tonight. i'm gonna be in the lab for most of the weekend. so i just need to do the  logo  and the  hangtags  for now, right? 
    
    
</post>
<date>03,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       hi busy esther...can we have the company logo?  So i can get started on the rubber stamping  the woven label for our shirts?? Pretty please!  and another thing not directed at Esther at all, we need a website...and someone to design it.  I want a brilliant one...anyone know someone brilliant??  Some pay might be involved...since none of us are getting paid...  aisheee...such hard work, and no money...it's a good thing I really want this to fly off the ground, or else I wouldn't work this hard...lets think about  the next printing already...  when did you say you'd be more free est?? Mid march?  aiy busy esther...our company relies on you...there are pros  Cons to that...::hungry::  * time line chronicall...Vicks called the printer, they said samples tomorrow...apparently they print all the shirts in one day, and it takes forever for the screen print making part...but I think if it required changes in the sample, then the due date will be pushed back to next week...I guess this is what we get for perfection...the whites shouldn't be an issue really, I think POST might be the one we really need to look at...colorwise that is...position well that's another issue huh???  I guess we'll see it when we get there...  so to sum it up, 1)esther, company logo, por favor, 2)everybody-let's all think about color  graphics at a meeting something soon, and 3.) brilliant website soon.    thank you everybody!!!  over  out! 
    
    
</post>
<date>01,March,2004</date>
<post>

    
       this is from a craigslist screen printer..."I'm located in Laguna niguel my rate will vary on what you want, turn around will also vary on the quantity you want and!</post></Blog>