<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>25,April,2002</date>
<post>


	 

      I'm finally getting this site a bit more towards what I'd like it to look.   dammit well...  I've got to go camping this weekend. *sigh*...  i like camping and all, but...  it's gonna be so cold :(  I'm sure I'll have much to tell Sunday....  i'm out...  ali

    
</post>
<date>24,April,2002</date>
<post>


	 

      mmmmnnnn....   nYA!

    
</post>
<date>24,April,2002</date>
<post>


	 

      Wee!  My first post...  this has been such an ordeal...  i need to learn perl etc, cause i was SO CLOSE to running greymatter or movable type or one of those programs off of my site, but NO!!   (dammit)    I just couldn't get perl to work right...  well, neither could my incredibly smart hacker brother either...  so i'll just go with this web based prog for now...  Now i just need to figure out how to ftp to my own computer...   this shouldn't actually be too hard (oh God...  i just cursed myself)...  So, for now I will host it at blogspot...    Ugh...  late at night..  must work in AM...  must sleep...   Ali

    
</post>
<date>04,May,2002</date>
<post>


	 

      Just got back from seeing Spider-Man..  Loved it! :)  It was just a great movie...  action-packed and full of humor...  Tobey Maguire was excellent as Peter Parker/Spider-Man - he did a great job showing the outsider/geek side of Parker, which made the transformation into Spider-Man very satisfying...  The only thing that really stuck out in my mind as amiss about the movie was Kirsten Dunst.  I've seen her in other movies and she looks cute, but in this one, she just looked awful compared to her other appearences.  I don't know what it was... probably the red hair.  She doesn't have the coloring for it, but it was necessary for the role...  also, it looked like they rushed through makeup...  in a couple of shots her lipstick looked like it wasn't even covering all of her lips which made her lips look really small.  I felt bad for her, she's a cute girl and she looked sick in this movie.  I'd be pissed if I was her...   Maguire on the other hand...  He looked awesome :)  I heard he did a lot of preparation for the movie, and it shows ;)  Very cute...    So, it's been a spider day unfortunately...  in the car on the way to the movie, a spider freaking crawled on me!  I was so grossed out...  first, it was on my jeans and I freaked out and brushed it off...  and then I didn't see where it went, and then it was on my arm...  I freaked out and brushed it off again (then my brother killed it...  or he said he did)...  Then, after the movie on the way home there was one crawling on the outside of my window (eww)...  and then when we got home there was one dangling in the hallway outside of my room (eww)...  David killed those last two also... but, eww.  I hate spider days...  weird that there were so many on the day that we saw Spider-Man though...  and eww eww eww, i still can't believe there was one crawling all over me...  eww..  now every time I feel a little itch or anything I'm sure that there's a spider on me...  eww.  

    
</post>
<date>03,May,2002</date>
<post>


	 

      I've been busy revamping the rest of the site to mirror the latest incarnation of this page...  I think I'm pretty much done for the day though...  gonna head out soon to see Spider-Man, can't wait! :)

    
</post>
<date>03,May,2002</date>
<post>


	 

      I had to make a big decision last night:  Should I go see Spider-Man opening night at the local theater or wait for the next day to see it at Crossgates?  If I went last night I'd get the thrill of seeing it  opening night , but I'd have to go to the theater at Clifton Park Center, which sux.  If I waited until the next day, I could go to the big theater at Crossgates and see it on a better screen in stadium seats with digital sound.  So, it came to this: did I want to waste my first Spider-Man viewing at a sub-par theater?  The answer was no.  I'm going to go see it today at Crossgates.  I am dissappointed that I missed opening night (I love seeing a movie opening night, it's just so exciting), but I'll get to see it opening weekend at a great theater.  I think I made the right decision :)  (This post was a total parody of an 8th grade essay on a big decision...  although sadly the content was all true)

    
</post>
<date>03,May,2002</date>
<post>


	 

      guess what?       I'm  urlLink Jubilation Lee   urlLink What X-Men Character are You?   

    
</post>
<date>02,May,2002</date>
<post>


	 

      Well, I guess they're going to give me one more chance at my job (my words, not theirs)...  I better not suck it up again Monday....   dammit 

    
</post>
<date>02,May,2002</date>
<post>


	 

      I suck.  I went to work today and we started a new scoring project where you have to use the computers to score.  They gave us the usual examples of how we're supposed to score based on what the state that we're scoring for says and then sat us in front of the computers to take a test.  The test gave us responses to the questions that had already been scored, and we had to score them.  Our scores were supposed to match exactly with the state's scores at least 70% of the time.  Well, I failed the first one, but that wasn't too bad 'cause most of my group failed that one too.  But then I failed the second one, which pissed me off royally.  I mean, I really thought I was scoring right...  so they gave those of us that failed again one more chance...  and I failed  again .  I really really suck.  It was most embarrassing.  I had to leave work 2 hours early 'cause they didn't have any work for me, and now I don't know if they want me to come back Monday or not...  I have to call...  ugh.  With my luck today, I'm going to call and they're going to tell me not to bother.  :(  I suck.

    
</post>
<date>02,May,2002</date>
<post>


	 

      I'm in the middle of changing the look of this site...  please excuse the mess...  I've decided that I don't want to use any templates, and I'm coding the look by myself...  so that's why it'll look pretty simple and sparse...  but that's ok, 'cause I really like simple and sparse anyway :)  Please let me know if you hate the colors...

    
</post>
<date>01,May,2002</date>
<post>


	 

      I really need a new computer...  well, not really, mine works fine...  but i really  want  a new computer...   urlLink this  is the kit I'm lusting after right now at tigerdirect.com...  

    
</post>
<date>01,May,2002</date>
<post>


	 

      Blah...  I get a random day off, and it's raining...  SUX...  So, I work at this place through a temp company where we grade tests from all across the US, wherever they have a contract with at the moment.  The stuff we grade are essay questions from standardized tests that the kids really don't want to take...  well, we just finished up grading writing tests from a Western state yesterday and we are going to begin grading tests from a Southern state next...  They began grading Science today, but I'm not grading those, so I got the day off (which kinda sux)...  I go back tomorrow to start grading Social Studies...  kids write the funniest things, cause they're all in a hurry to get stuff down (they only have 45 minutes per essay) and so they never go back and read what they've written...  or sometimes, they're just so self-centered that they don't realize what they've written sounds weird or wrong....  here are a few examples:   "I don't give a flying Swahili Showgirl what they think"  "I am one of those people who would mentally die if..."  "... friends seem to be changed as often as your underwear..."  (an 8th grade girl on puberty)"...girls are mocked as their chest grows larger and their monthly cycle arrives.  Boys can be chastised for their voices getting deeper and other unmentionable things."  "If you are popular like me, it's a little easier to grow up"  "I decided that I would ask my parents that night after sucking up"  "It hurt, but it was so cute"  (an 8th grader)"I was a real idiot, back in 7th grade"  "My whole life has gone to poop"  "In short, I think this whole censorship thing is gay"  "Curfew: a nice way of saying I don't respect or trust your decisions."  These Western kids do some weird things too...  there was one kid who wrote that his favorite toy from when he was a kid was a steel rod that was expandable, and that he used to like to sleep with it but it had to be under the covers so that it didn't fall out of bed and he liked the way the cold steel felt against his naked thigh and he would wake up wanting ice cream...  then he went on to say that one time he went out to the barn and shoved it down a sheep's throat but then the sheep swallowed it and he was sad...  but a few days later his dad came in with the steel rod covered in poop saying that the sheep had passed it and the kid was so excited that he took the steel rod into the bathtub with him to clean it off and he scrubbed his rod real hard to get all of the poop off of it... and then he brought his rod to school with him but a bully took it from him and started probing sheep with it...  that was the most disturbing essay I read, it was by an 8th grader...  eww...  i've heard that like 10% of kids that grow up on a farm engage in some form of beastiality, and that's so gross...

    
</post>
<date>01,May,2002</date>
<post>


	 

      I stumbled across this really cute little site:  urlLink Sensitivity 3.0 .  You must go there just at least to see the adorable Flash Neko-Chan...  it's so so so so so cute...  (  urlLink     Isn't she cute?  She's a pretty pretty princess....  just like me ;) We decided at work today that I am a princess.  That's ok with me.  I'll own that title.  :)  Just ask Tim...  he'll tell you that I'm a princess (or at least I think I am)...

    
</post>
<date>30,April,2002</date>
<post>


	 

      I'm a very passionate person...  unfortunately, my passion for any one thing only lasts as long as my attention span will allow...  and that's not long...  So far, I've been able to keep interested in my little site here for a week, and that's amazing.  Hopefully I'll be able to keep this up...  But normally, I don't last that long...  in fact, I didn't even last long enough to finish that post, because I flipped the channel and  urlLink Felicity  was on.  I haven't seen that show since the first or second season.  I loved the first season when Felicity was with Noel, but then she ended up with Ben, and I HATED it.  But this episode ended up with Felicity  traveling back in time  to be with Noel.  That rules.  I hope they don't screw it up now...  

    
</post>
<date>30,April,2002</date>
<post>


	 

      I'm such a freak...  I sit here and watch shows on  urlLink VH1  like behind the music or some other hour-long show devoted to a band or an era...  and I become a huge fan of whatever the show was about for like the next hour (at least).  I've just watched an hour-long show on  urlLink VH1  about  urlLink Bon Jovi's   Slippery When Wet  album, and when it ended I was all about  urlLink Bon Jovi ...  I started looking around for my  urlLink Bon Jovi  CD, and thinking that I was going to have to start downloading some more  urlLink Bon Jovi  mp3s...  But then another show came on, and I forgot all about it...

    
</post>
<date>30,April,2002</date>
<post>


	 

      Everything today is about  urlLink DDR ...   dammit  We got let out of work 4 hours early today which both sucked and it didn't...  it sucked 'cause i lost the money, and it didn't 'cause... well, who doesn't like to leave work early?  So, Michelle, Dave and I went to Crossgates and ate at  urlLink Houlihan's .  A few other people from our table were supposed to come also, but they never showed up :(  Anyway, had a good lunch, but then after I really wanted to play  urlLink DDR , and they have 5th mix in front of the theater there...  but i still can't play :(  I just want this ankle to feel better already!!  So we walked around the mall and didn't get anything...  I guess Dave was really bored... typical male :)   When I got home today my little brother, Greg, was down in the basement playing  urlLink DDR ...  and all I want to do is play!!  Ah well...  I suck for jumping on my trampoline I guess....  

    
</post>
<date>30,April,2002</date>
<post>


	 

      On a lighter note...  I'm so happy it's Tuesday :)   urlLink That 70's Show  is on tonight, and then later,  urlLink Smallville .  YAY!!  ...  more later...   

    
</post>
<date>29,April,2002</date>
<post>


	 

      I can't stand it...  I'm going insane!!  I need my ankle to be better....  It's all numb and ugly looking!  And worst of all, it's weak...  and  ALL I WANT TO DO IS PLAY  urlLink DDR !!!   I'm  SO  jealous of anyone who has full command over their feet....    dammit...  

    
</post>
<date>29,April,2002</date>
<post>


	 

      Took a quiz to find out which Disney princess I'm most like...  turns out I'm Belle from Beauty and the Beast...  It's pretty true, except for the "brown-eyed girl" part...    urlLink    Which of the  urlLink Disney Princesses  are you? 

    
</post>
<date>28,April,2002</date>
<post>


	 

      On another note...  my sprained ankle (I did it the friday before last jumping on the trampoline) doesn't really hurt anymore, which is good, but i seem to be losing some feeling in it, which is bad...  I have it soaking in a "Dr. Scholl's Luxery Footbath" right now (it's like a mini-whirlpool for your feet) so hopefully that should help...  i also should probably go to the Dr...  but we'll see about that...  

    
</post>
<date>28,April,2002</date>
<post>


	 

      Today sucked...  well, actually it wasn't that bad... I just wanted to go back to bed this morning, but I had to go to work...  then i left the house late and i got to work right at 8:00 when our manager-guy was giving a lecture on being prompt and working hard...  work went fast, which is a plus, but all day i was in a badish mood cause i had to go to the dentist right after work.  My appointment was for 4:30, and work only lets out at 4:00, so i had to speed all the way home and i made it to the dentist's office right before 4:30...  and then i had to wait for a half an hour.  That just sux.  And then, to top it all off, after i get in there he's trying to get a crown on, and it turns out that since he didn't put a temp crown on at my last appointment (when he kept grinding my GUM!) my teeth have moved and this crown was now useless.  So now i have to go back again for him to grind my teeth (GUM!) again and measure for another crown etc etc...  SUX!  But, after i got home i had chinese food (fortune: "your love of music will be an important part of your life") and Tim called and i felt all better...   

    
</post>
<date>28,April,2002</date>
<post>


	 

      I just finished posting the pics from this weekend's camping trip to the page.  Follow the "April Camping" link off of the Photo Album page...  (see links to the left </post></Blog>