<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>15,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ever have one of those days when you feel like you could say just about anything to anyone? Yesterday I did. And it totally backfired on me.  Now normally, when I am in my grocery store, I keep to myself and do my business. On this day I was at the fish counter, paroosing the fine selection of salmon steaks and noticed that there was a customer waiting. This guy was just standing there, stoned cold, staring at the fish. There wasn't a clerk around, so I walked over to the deli to get someone to help me. The clerk sees me, and starts to walk over. As we're walking back, he says 'who was first'? In a very animated manner, I say 'well, i came over to get someone, but he was waiting, so he can go first, so yeah, go ahed man!'   The guy waiting kind of smiled and said 'thanks...'. So the guy orders 4 jumbo shrimp.  I look at the shrimp and say 'Wow! those are REALLY big, eh?!'.   And no response.  I was all set up to start joking about the size of the shrimp, i felt primed and full of humourous ammunition. I was ready for anything. And I got shot down.  I should have known better than to start a conversation with someone who didn't have the balls to go ask the Deli clerk for some help. 
      
</post>
<date>14,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      In case you've never met me before, I should warn you. I should warn you that I can be what some may call a smartass. Oh, for the first little while, you'll think i'm just your average normal friendly neighbourhood chick. But after I've gotten to know you, i will insult you in a demeaning manner. And it's all for humour. 
      
</post>
<date>22,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Last night, I attended a party with people from work and some other friends. We were celebrating the opening of the May 2-4 long weekend (Victoria Day). It can be a bit problematic when you start drinking at 4 pm. In the end I think we all had a good time.  About half way through the night, I was standing in the kitchen making a drink (surprise, surprise). We started talking about traveling, and one co-worker who is becoming a citizen brought up an interesting issue. He has lived in many places, some where wars have happened, and his point was this: you don't realize how important or precious your life is unless it's in danger. People who live in countries where they know their life could be taken away within minutes are far more serious about life, they treasure it.   Here, in Canada, we are so easy going and laid back because we have nothing to fear (or so most of us think). I think this also makes us a bit complacent about life. We get wound up in trivial issues like what do I wear today, what diet should I be on, or which car should I drive. If only some of us could see other places, and experience the life of someone who treasures it, maybe our opinions on multi-culturalism and the importance of our own lives would change.   There always has to be a balance though. Even though we may be a bit complacent, because our lives are not in danger we are more laid back and we don't care what place someone else is from, or what religion they are, or what colour of skin they have. As long as everyone had a drink in their hand, and someone to chat with, we were all fine.
      
</post>
<date>20,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I work with a group of fairly intelligent, well-versed adults. Today 3 of us attempted to assemble a small, child-sized desk from Ikea. It took 2 attempts for us to get it right.  I think that assembling Ikea furniture brings out people's true talents and faults. There are the people who take one look at it and say 'no, I'm not helping.' Those are the smart ones, the ones that know better than to start assembling a desk at 5:30 on a beautiful spring afternoon. Then, there are the people like me, who jump right in and say 'I'll do it!' just because I had nothing better to do and I'm sick of looking at a computer screen.   My new rules for assembling Ikea furniture: 1) One sole person is in charge of the project. The other person is only there to help with holding, accessories, and passing you the allan key. 2) Always read the instructions all the way through before attempting to build your item. 3) Never take advice or help from people other than your assistant. 4) If you screw up in assembling, blame it on the assistant. 5) Always have beer ready for reward at the end of the assembly process.  We finally assembled the desk, it is waiting in all its glory to receive the Imac testing station tomorrow. Now if I can only get that network cable to reach....
      
</post>
<date>19,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I am trying out this new online dating site called  urlLink LemonTonic  - it's connected to your .net passport account. So far, I've only completed the profile, but already I'm thinking to myself that this is way too limiting. I had to answer a series of questions to narrow down what type of person I am, and who I am looking for. I am sorry, but I don't think that I can sum up who I am in 35 questions. Especially when none of the choices in the drop-down menu describe my answer. I suppose that I had to get as close as I could. (it's like horseshoes...)   They say you can play games, chat, surf the web together. I would rather actually go outside, in the fresh air, and go for a walk to see who's on my street corner. Talk to that guy with the strange tatoos. Ask him what the hell he does for a living. See if I feel that feeling, you know, the one in the pit of your stomach that's trying to tell you something. Somehow, I don't think you can simulate that online. My view is that we're human - we've got so many other senses to use, and the net inherently doesn't allow us to use them. Touch, smell, pheremones intermingling.... These are things that have always been important to me. In my opinion, the world needs more real connection. Let's use what we were born with: instinct.  The one thing that I think would make the LemonTonic site better is allowing more room for creativity with your answers. If only I could say what I really meant from the outset, then maybe I could get an even better match. And that one nerdy guy would stop showing up in my search results.
      
</post>
<date>17,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      You've gotta love public transportation. It's full of interesting people, sights, sounds, and of course, smells.  I got onto the subway this evening to go downtown and the first thing I noticed: the smell. It's that smell that permeates old subway cars, and makes you wonder, is that urine? Sniff. Wait, don't sniff. Again, is that urine? It smells faintly like it, just enough to let you know that it's there. But it could just be the funk of the old subway car....  As I'm sitting in the seat, I start wondering to myself: am I sitting in the pee-spot? Could this be the precise area that an incontinent old man could not hold it in any longer? I wondered, and I wondered. What could have made the smell? Was it that old man, or was it a newborn baby? Or maybe someone's dog got freeked out by the sound of the wheels screeching against the tracks as the train took the big curve at union station... So many possibilities.  I realized that by the end of the trip, I couldn't smell it anymore. Oh no, now I'm going to leave the train smelling like pee and no guys will want to talk to me.  So I get to the bar, and guess what. NO guys talked to me. So I decided to go home early and blame it on the pee-train.
      
</post>
<date>16,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Today was one of the greatest days I've had in a long time. I had the opportunity to be with my family, and to be reunited with some family members that I haven't seen for a very long time. I don't know how, but my mom managed to keep it a secret, not letting anyone know who the "specials guests" were. I was thinking and thinking, running through family members and old friends who the special guests may be. When they arrived, my brothers and I were pretty shocked. I almost started crying when through the patio door walks my grandmother whom I haven't seen in almost 10 years. She was accompanied by my aunt and cousin who I hadn't known ever - the last time I saw her, I was probably about 2 years old. It was great to get to see them. I feel like I have found some surprise family members. Thanks Mom!
      
</post>
<date>27,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      I was looking around  urlLink LemonTonic  again today, really analyzing all those little pictures that guys put up of themselves there. I was looking at their faces, then I started looking at the backgrounds. You can learn a lot from those details... Here are some tips for you guys out there, if you want more or instant interest:  1) make your photo a bit different - Tilt your head a funky way, or make it black and white or sepia tone. It also helps if you have a good friend who's a photographer and can take a kick-ass, well composed photo of you.  2) limit the background - I want to see more flesh! It really pisses me off when like 75% of the photo is your grandma's cottage and 25% of you. A better Ratio would be 75% of you and 25% background.  3) take note of the state of the room - I get really turned off when I see your dirty laundry on top of your mattress, or your dirty dishes piling up in the sink. Cmon, save that until after you know you've got the girl, and she can bitch you out for it.  4) wood doors as a background - No. Just don't do that, please. It reminds me of my parents basement.  5) basement windows - We can tell when you live in a basement apartment. Girls are perceptive that way, the short curtains give it all away.  I like things in 3's or 5's, so I'll end the list there.  What should you take from this? Well, it depends on what type of woman you want to attract. If the type of woman you'd want to attract would care about your photo and what's in the background, then man, you've got some work ahead of you. Go find yourself a photographer friend and beg them to take some practice shots on you. If you really don't care about how you look, or you think that you look great already (again, girls are perceptive, we can tell how confident or phoney you are) then you don't have anything to worry about. A little effort goes a long way....
      
</post>
<date>26,May,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Check out my friend Steph's new blog here &gt;&gt;&gt;&gt;  urlLink MysteryGrrl  </post></Blog>