<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>03,August,2002</date>
<post>

     
      August 3, 2002  Ahhhhh.... I'm still speechless.  Miss Juliana was less than 5 feet away from me.  Her performance went by too swiftly for me to capture every note that was invoked, I was in utter amazement.  It was breathtaking.  I hope the pictures came out alright and clear, though the shutter was slow.  Check back by tomorrow night...  Today was magazine day.  For the past few weeks every magazine subscription of mine have all been delivered to my apartment on the same day.  The previous spreading of the periodicals that was once enjoyed is now lost to the inundation of reading that I now endure due to mr. postman.  I am now faced with all of these choices.  I hate decisions.  I cant even decide on what belt to wear between 3, let alone pick what I want to read for the next few hours out of a choice of eight.  I like magazines, but I love free magazines.  I have perfected the art of the "3 months free" promotion that a lot of online stores or credit cards offer.  I have been getting Time, Newsweek, and US  World Report for free for nearly a year now thanks to MBNA.  Jane has been appearing in my mailbox as well for about 5 months, but I do not remember ordering it or even filling anything out for it, but it kicks, so i don't wonder.  I actually pay for Rolling Stone and CMJ.  CMJ's New Music Monthly is my bible.  Every issue comes with a compilation cd of different types of artists, from techno to rock to celtic, you never know what you'll get on the cd though the magazine is more rockish.  The staff is defnitely the most talented music reviewers I have ever encountered.  Plus they're not contradictory (cough cough RS RS)  and know their stuff.  It's like Christmas once a month.  Cosmo and Sports Illustrated also come hither, though not addressed to me.  I have kidnapped them and made them my own even though I don't really read them, I never know when I may be bored.  Or need to attack a fly.  But then the whole swarm of magazines also poses a space issue.  I can't throw away RS or CMJ once I am finished with it.  So my bathroom has become quite the library of entertaining music knowledge.  I just better not find any pages missing... 
     
    
</post>
<date>02,August,2002</date>
<post>

     
       August 2, 2002  "I don't always have a clear idea of what I want. I have to struggle to find out because it might be important." Juliana Hatfield  Its only a few hours after I wrote the last entry, but this is cause for excitement.Its is now 12:09 am and it is officially JULIANA HATFIELD DAY!!!!!!!!  She is the reason for my fascination with music.  I first heard of her in 1993 and was just amazed, she was the first musician that I delved myself into, she fascinated me.  And 9 years later, I have the opportunity to see her perform.  Live.  Miss Juliana with be merely feet away from me.  Words cannot describe it, so I am not even going to try.  It will just belittle the emotion.  I will write further on my Juliana tomorrow after the show.  The musician that I idolize will be under the same roof tonight at the North Star Bar.  Wow.    "I feel like I'm too comfortable being alone. I feel like I should hang out with people more of the time. I feel really guilty about that." - Juliana Hatfield  
     
    
</post>
<date>02,August,2002</date>
<post>

     
        August 1, 2002  ¡§i've never been to mexico  i never learned to see the sky the way you thought i could listen to the radio they're singing songs about mexico i'm singing songs you'll never hear¡¨ ¡V vaco  I just got back from Cancun.  I can¡¦t believe I went to Cancun.  It was all spur of the moment sponteniety, a trip planned in less than 48 hours.  Though I have flown a handful of times lately, flying still scares the bejesus out of me.  I¡¦ve taken physics, I understand the concept.  BUT HOW THE HELL CAN THOSE GIGANTIC METAL BEASTS STAY IN THE AIR!?!??!  So I made the 3 hour trip to Mexico a booze cruise.  I have to exploit first class to all of it¡¦s potential, so I made use of the free drinks on board and drank the entire trek across the continent.  I was a very happy and calm passenger º.  Though flying scares me, I am fascinated with the window and love looking down below.  The Gulf coast is just amazing.  Teal blue water with the white sand was just breathtaking from the air.  Late in the evening the sky turns an amazing purple and orange shade complementing the sea grean and white foam, definitely one of the most colorful and vivid images I have ever seen.  Tuesday night it stormed and I sat on the balcony and watched the lightning dance across the water.  It¡¦s extradinary to imagine what is out there, beyond our small circle of familiarity and what sights we miss by enclosing ourselves.  Importance is in the small details.  Which reminds me of one of my favorite move quotes in which I will leave you with.  Though I don¡¦t eat quarter-pounders or smoke, but you get the idea.  I will let you in on more little glimpses later.    ¡§I take pleasure in the details. You know... a quarter-pounder with cheese, those are good, the sky about ten minutes before it starts to rain, the moment where your laughter become a cackle... and I, I sit back and I smoke my Camel Straights and I ride my own melt.¡¨ ¡V Reality Bites    
     
    
</post>
<date>02,August,2002</date>
<post>

     
      July 27, 2002  The Swedes deserve thanks for many thingsnamely chocolate, good music, and IKEA.    Every so often I have to make the trek to IKEA, and pay homage to the domestic gods.  I didnt need anything, but you always come back with something practical when you visit the blue and gold building that is Mecca.  I think half of my apartment is IKEA.  For example, today I purchased a frying pan (we have a few, but you can never have enough, especially not 2 of them for $6.95), circular containers (we just love our containers in this apartmentmake food to last a week, hide it in the fridge and find it 3 months later), bamboo (why do I keep getting plants, my room is like a forest), and a green neon dish scrubber shaped like a daschund (to match my neon green dragon noodle scooper that I got a few months earlier).  Quality.  Its like a bonding experience.  All the shoppers frantically carrying their measuring tape and gold and blue oversized bags to each display of kitschy mass produced items of household goodness.   
     
    
</post>
<date>08,August,2002</date>
<post>

     
      "And we live in a beautiful world Yeah we do, yeah we do We live in a beautiful world"  I went to see Coldplay last night at the TLA.  What an amazing show.  I have no idea what to write about though because regardless on how well I depict the performance with words, it will pale in comparison to what was experienced.  What a passion driven performance.  Coldplay rawked.  1 Giant Leap was the opener.  "Opener".  It was a projection and began with Bono introducing the piece,  then four songs followed, with Michael Stipe and Robbie Williams doing a ditty or two.  In between "songs" were interludes on how to make the world better and actions that have hindered self development.  One Giant Leap.  Good concept, but not as an opener.  The crowd booed at it and made snide comments about the film. Everyone expected an opening live band, not a tutorial.    But the Coldplay roadie said it best when he joked "What?!  Are you afraid of fucking learning something?!"  
     
    
</post>
<date>07,August,2002</date>
<post>

     
      "I've been so damn tired....It went down at the May parade"  An hour and a half till my radio show and I am exhausted.  This shall prove interesting.  Hmmm...perhaps a donut and coffee run before hitting the studio.  I have nothing really important to say, just trying to keep myself entertained before I spin some discs.  :-)  When I surround myself with the music though, I'll wake up.    I bought a new toy today.  A refurbished Minolta SLR camera.  My previous capturer of glimpses saw its demise a few weeks ago when I dropped it.  And the zoom lens fell off.  And it started making weird whirring noises.  I should have known then.  But no, I had to keep taking pictures with it and I was surprised when they came out all blurry.  Silly me.  I am excited though, I get to devriginize my camera at the Coldplay concert tomorrow night.    Codeplay. In concert. Sold out in less than 5 minutes. Codeplay.  Live.  Woo!
     
    
</post>
<date>05,August,2002</date>
<post>

     
      So when I came back from Cancun all I wanted to do was shower and sleep and eat.  But no, I was greeted by a swarm of ants in my room.  And they weren't marching.  So I released my angst by crushing them with my index finger.  Ahhh...what power I possess over the mighty ant.  The gross thing was when I shook my keyboard about 10 ants fell out. Dead, dead, dead, dead........  So this fiasco has been going on each time I sit at my computer.  For the past few days I go though my ritual of mass destruction then go on my merry way on the internet.  Every so often I discover a straggler.  But there aren't a lot of ants, no more then 10 at my initial sitting, then a few throughout the rest of the day.  But they are only around my desk, no where else.  So about ten minutes ago I destroyed three of them, no worries, it wasn't a harsh death, very quick.  But this one ant was carrying a piece of food.  I couldn't crush him.  I felt bad because I think I killed all of his friends.  I figured I would let this one go because he was brave enough to venture out and find dinner for the ant crew.  They were all probably watching me, the master of their fate, cheering him on and taking bets on the time of his demise.  So I let him go.    But tomorrow he better watch out....
     
    
</post>
<date>16,August,2002</date>
<post>

     
      It's Seeking Homer night :-)  These guys rock, you should definitely check them out.  The rest of the summer is going to be good because I will be spending half of it in various venues :-).  I haven;t seen Seeking Homer play in months, not since their last Grape Street gig.  And tonight they're playing at the Logan house, which is always a great place to get the drink and groove on.   Another highlight of my upcoming week will be seeing Jonasay play again, this time closer to home in Philadelphia at the North Star bar.  These guys are dangerously talented and supergreat.  I have been listening to their upcming cd nonstop, so you should go to a show was well and see what I am talking about :-)    On a related note, my radio show went so well today.  My listeners are great.  I got quite a few phone calls from random people (aside form the people i actually do know) just wishing me luck and saying how much they enjoy the music.  So thank you so much for listening, it means the world to me and I am so elated that you enjoy what I play.  Thank you.
     
    
</post>
<date>15,August,2002</date>
<post>

     
         urlLink        
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2002</date>
<post>

     
      I went to a concert last night....GASP!  Karen scored free tickets from her internship at WB News for the Vanessa Carlton/Third Eye Blind/Goo Goo Dolls show.  Melissa and Rick came as well, and it was Karen's first concert.  "You have been living with Miranda for a year and this is your first concert?!?!?!?"  - melissa Though I am not really into any of those bands like I am with others, a good time was had by all and we definitely got our groove on.  :-)  I'm pretty boring right now, not much to say.  Summer has gotten slow.  Less than three weeks till school starts again.  Big bad senior year of college.   Yikes.  Natalie, our fourth apartment mate is moving in as I type.  She is really great, 5th year student studying poli sci and education.  I think this year will be great, we all seem to get long uh....i almost typed great for the third time.  Um, this year will be brilliant.  She was in two classes of mine last year and needed a place to stay and we had an open spot.  She's really sweet and fun.  Yay us.  Ok, time to pick out some music for tommorrow.  It's a Thursday and it oddly feels like a Saturday.  You should listen to my radio show.  Everyone should.  It will be a big radio-dj-listener ditty.  3-5pm fridays  www.wvud.org
     
    
</post>
<date>12,August,2002</date>
<post>

     
      I think I have an addiction.  I bought 3 CDs today.  Well, technically 5 if you are counting individual CDs.  It's practically a sin to leave really good music on the shelf.  So I am actually helping others buy buying it.  In more ways than one.  I bought the latest Ash,   Free All Angels, the new Samples, well, it's not new, but its an anthology being released tomorrow, three discs of pure Samples bliss.  And some fool sold a used Stone Roses CD to Rainbow, so of course I snagged it.  Yay for new music.
     
    
</post>
<date>11,August,2002</date>
<post>

     
      What an awesome weekend.  So tired, but I am so glad I got to spend a lot of time with  the greatest people.  You guys rock. Deer Park, O-2, Paradigm, Finnegans, 5208 porch..............................................  Finishing half a bottle of vodka yourself in 3 drinks is not good..... Philly is Phun Happy Birthday.
     
    
</post>
<date>21,August,2002</date>
<post>

     
      So I finally have glasses again.  I lost them, noooooo, I misplaced them a little less than a year ago.  But all is good now.  I feel so much taller now though.  I have problems with steps.   It was my depth perception that was screwed up (yes yes, remember the Mr. No Depth Perception skit on snl...?!) so I have learned to compensate for it.  But then when your vision is magically corrected, you forget that you have adapted.  I can't tell you how many steps I have tripped over in the past 24 hours.   Well, now you all should feel safe now that I can tell where cars are when I drive ;-) Driving at night was a problem with all those glaring lights! It builds character.
     
    
</post>
<date>19,August,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Blue jean baby, L.A. lady, seamstress for the band Pretty eyed, pirate smile, you'll marry a music man Ballerina, you must have seen her dancing in the sand And now she's in mine, always with me, tiny dancer in my hand  Jesus freaks out in the street Handing tickets out for God Turning back she just laughs The boulevard is not that bad  Piano man he makes his stand In the auditorium Looking on she sings the songs The words she knows the tune she hums  But oh how it feels so real  Lying here with no one near Only you and you can hear me When I say softly slowly  Hold me closer tiny dancer Count the headlights on the highway Lay me down in sheets of linen you had a busy day today  Blue jean baby, L.A. lady, seamstress for the band Pretty eyed, pirate smile, you'll marry a music man Ballerina, you must have seen her dancing in the sand And now she's in me, always with me, tiny dancer in my hand 
     
    
</post>
<date>18,August,2002</date>
<post>

     
      The Seeking Homer show was awesome :-)  I met Mickey, she is a neato girl, we adopted her for the next two days :-)  We made signs so we could be superdorks and give SH a laugh on stage.  It was definitelty crafty.  Check www.mirandaland.com in the next few days to see the pictures...  So then we decided "hey what the hell, lets just drive to the beach and see the benefit show on the beach on saturday" Sleepover at my house :-)  Ok, i hate new jersey.  sorry.  but i do.  5 hours of driving.  I didn't think asses could fall asleep.  
     
    
</post>
<date>30,August,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Galileo358: i have a womb Galileo358: and an ovary Galileo358: 2 in fact NiteSky81: agggghhhhhh Galileo358: fallopian is a fun word to say NiteSky81: i want all this in my profile! Galileo358: fallopian NiteSky81: hahahahaha Galileo358: how is your fallopian doing today? Galileo358: fine, thank you NiteSky81: OH MY GOD! NiteSky81: STOP! NiteSky81: YOU ARE INSANE!
     
    
</post>
<date>29,August,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Last week of summer vacation EVER
     
    
</post>
<date>29,August,2002</date>
<post>

     
      I don't think I really enjoy malls. Everything is just the same thing, just different labels, different prices.  So I go shopping for a few hours and was releived when I discovered an Urban Outfitters.  One hundred and eighty minutes after I started shopping, I went to my car with a UO bag with a pair of jeans and a shirt.  Yay me.  I think I maybe went into 6 stores total.  I don't know, I just seem jaded by the whole mall thing, too much sameness too much unorginality.  Says me who wears jeans and a black shirt nearly every other day.  And I like the guys t-shirts at UO a whole lot better than I do the girls shirts.  Though i still came out with one, I tried in vain to find extra smalls that I could shrink in certain styles, but I didn't come out victorious.   And another factor to the whole mall thing.  I went into Sam Goody and FYE and they suck.  I tried to find a few cds to see how much they were there, but noooo, nothing i looked for was there.  And surprisingly their prices are much higher then Rainbow's.  So leave your mall and come to Newark DE and quench your music thirst at Rainbow.  I didn't even bother asking anyone there about my quest.  Didn't want to interrupt their glazed over faces by having them look on the computer for titles that they should know off hand.  Sam Goody did have fun stickers.   I'm watching Jimmy Eat World's The Middle Video.  Why doesn't anyone have an underwear party? The roommates and I have decided that we are going to have a halloween party.  You have to dress up though.  And bring either candy or alcohol.  A trick or a treat ;-).  Melissa and I will be Pussycats.  Think Josie and the Pussycats.   As we were talking about the Halloween party we were watching that show on MTV that rots your brain...Sorority Life, yeah that's it.  And it was the formal episode.  So we also thought it would be funny if we had a formal at our apartment.  hell, everything else goes here at 5208, why not that!? ;-)  Oh wait, because all of us would be dateless except for Natalie and we would just end up dancing with each other which is no different than any other night.  Oh wait... But yeah, Halloween serious, formal, no just kidding.  C'mon, we're not that low.  ;-) Have a good night!
     
    
</post>
<date>26,August,2002</date>
<post>

     
      I bought my books today.  And a planner.   I buy a planner every year thinking each time that I have new and blank pages for me to graffiti upon and document my trials and tribulations on....but usually after the second week the planner transforms from a reminder book to a coaster.  I have a pretty good memory and super mental calendar skills that using a planner is usually a mockery.I look to my left and I see my marbled purple planner...with a blue cup sitting perfectly in the center.  Sigh. Again, I buy my books every semester and do I read them....?  Sometimes.  I don't understand how one book, not even a book, an UNbook can cost $75.  Maybe if it had a cover it would be worth $75.  But no, it is a stack of papers wrapped in plastic, which is about half an inch thick, and with holes on the left hand side.  Kind of them to pre-punch the holes in the paper.  And that will probably be the book in which only one chapter is assigned.  $75 to read the summary at the end of the chapter.   This semester should prove intersting, usually I take a bunch of television classes or all political science classes, but I threw some variance in there this time.  I'm almost done....more on college later.  This is my fall. Public Speaking Theories of Mass Communication Early Modern European Intellectual History International Human Rights and Film
     
    
</post>
<date>02,September,2002</date>
<post>

     
      I have one full day of my last summer vacation ever left. I can honestly say that this has been the most memorable summer that I have had.  Thank you.  I don't even know where to begin.  Do I group by events, by people, by time...?!  i ma all about groupings and lists and yet here I am with no idea and where to start. Melissa's house was my second home :-)  And i got to complain a lot there.  And ponder.  And drink.  I think I am lucky I didn't get alcohol poisoning. "Damn, I can smell the vanilla from here" - melissa "Oh no no no, I am wearing vanilla." me "Dear, no, that is defnitely your beverage I smell from all the way over here" -melissa :::12 hours later::: "so i looked at the vodka bottle this morning..." (half full) - me "yeah that was definitely all you" -melissa "how the hell did i even get home!?" - me yeah...that was a fun night....  What else hmmm..... Many a night at the bars with Nate then stumbling back to muse over life and all of its shortcomings Michelle's graduation and playing softball at the gathering...sitting outside of the point....at XPN being so jaded about John Mayer and realizing that we have "remember when stories"... The whole Mayer Kahuna experience...ice cream, running down the boardwalk, talking to random people, drinking and dancing and singing  Movies, ice cream, and playing with dead raw fish with Karen and Cari And being at the beach with Kristen FIREWORKS! trekking to the football field with Kristen, Cari,and Nate...then Bennigans.  Cari got 50% off at Bennigans always for working there.  yay for Cari. Playing in Newark with Dan and..."All I want is a fucking beer".... Rides up to Ryan's and the Bistro and galavanting all over Philly.  And seeing a real life GOLD PIMP!  Sitting outside of Jim's steaks at 3am.  Then trying to find my way back to his house at 4 am because someone was too drunk to show me the way.... Spreading the love at WVUD....early early early drives to the radio station at 2 am with 5 cups of coffee just so i can play music on the fm, oh but then i got daytime hours! and i love everyone who calls me and Ims me while I am on the air to tell me how much they enjoy the show.  I love doing it and I am so glad I can share it with all of you. Jonasay.  What can I say, you guys are awesome.  Thank you for letting me tag a long on the road.  Much more fun to come. Mark rocks.  -Glue. Coldplay.  Wow.  I cannot say anything more about that show. Ours.  Stuffed at the Khyber, but at least we found it!  Could barely see, but it soudned incredible... Seeking Homer.  Always a crazy trip.  Went with the whole concert crew for this one.  Michelle, Dan, Nate, Tim, etc.  We kidnapped Mickey, who drove all the way from Massachusetts :-)  And so her and i were dorks and made a sign for the band to make them smile.  Then there was a big sleepover at my house that night before we all drove a few hours to see them again...yeah.... Juliana Hatfield.  My Juliana.  I waited ten years to see her and I finially did.  I met some really cool people at that show and it was just an amazing night of music. And of course Pat McGee Band.  It wouldn't be summer if i didnt see them.  But instead of the usual 20, I saw them twice.  sad face.  They spent most of the summer recording.  But it was enough to see a really awesome show.  Scott gets a hold of me after I get off work and says, "hey lets go to NJ"  So we did.  We met at King of Prussia and luckily he had a map.  Because we really had no idea where we were going.  But after three hours of good conversation and good music we arrive at the venue.  And it looked rad.  A little club right on the beach with bamboo and pools and bars everywhere.  And we meet up with Matt then make our way to the front row in time for Granian.  And such a good PMB performance with new songs and such.  And it was Ben's 22nd birthday.  So of course he goes on stage and gets pizza.  Pat gives him a glass of Jack and says "Here, you have to finish this jack of glass..."  yeah.  It was fun. A sick sick sick show.  :-)  So we leave and replenish ourselves at 7-11 and jet home.  I think i went to bed at 6 am.  But one of the best days of the summer :-) Karen scored tickets for the Vanessa Carlton / Goo goo dolls/ and third eye blind concert.  Getting lost in camden was enjoyable.  we never had so much culture!  then drinking out of guitar glasses and dancing like silly girls...and rick.  karen, me, and melissa danced like silly girls i meant.  a fun show and karens first concert.  yay for karen! Half priced  burger nights at Deer Park.  Yum. Ok, fine, veggie burger.  Still a burger. And half priced appetizers at East End.  Especially the stuffed pretzels.  Even though they do not agree with Nate. East End.  The establishment of the summer.  East End rocks.  Hard.  Oh summer....I don't want to see you go.  :-(  Thank you to everyone.  You are amazing and you let me have fun.  :-) 
     
    
</post>
<date>01,September,2002</date>
<post>

     
      "Well, there's a dreamer in my dreams Swinging from the beams With a light shining off the snow Well, there's a singer in my heart Burning up the charts With songs about things we all know"  Do yourself a favor and see the documentary of the making of Wilco's Yankee Hotel Foxtrot.  I Am Trying to Break Your Heart.  So good...so real...so raw.  Now I really can't wait until I see them in Philly.   I went to the Ritz Bourse to see the film.  I love the Ritz.  They have Toblerone bars.   
     
    
</post>
<date>01,September,2002</date>
<post>

     
      And i know i will probably regret this but who the hell cares...  ok so don't you hate it when you find out all this shit about someone you used to go with and you really can't do anything about it,because what can you do but be really pissed or hurt or upset, you know? But it really doesn't matter anyways, because regardless on how you feel, it changes NOTHING!  GRRRRRRR!!!!!  Why does everything have to be so tough!??!?! I don't deserve this, I'm a good person :-/
     
    
</post>
<date>01,September,2002</date>
<post>

     
      I love Newark Delaware. Shut up.  You may be making fun of me, but it is truly super.   After working at the music store til close, James and I go over to to Grottos to meet Nate.  Then Bob and Fin show up.  yay.  I am three drinks in.  And when you have M  M's for dinner those 3 drinks really do you in.  So then we progress our night to Deer Park. Cover?!!?!??!  No, we don;t know the meaning of a cover.  So we leave.  But I steal a menu.  word.   EAST END!!! Oh my favorite watering hole.  Oh how I love you.  A few strong drinks later and I am ready to go.  April Pedrick, you rock.  And now I am home after a long night.  But east end is fun and my type of people.  yay for east end,  hip hip hooray!
     
    
</post>
<date>13,September,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Happy Friday the 13th!!! I love Friday the 13ths :-)  My birthday is exactly a month away.  But not on a Friday.  I just like creapy dark stuff.  But nothing creepy and dark happened today.  Unless you want to discuss my inability to cook.  That is pretty scary in itself.  The first time I used my stove in my apartment I burned myself.  I think I still have a scar :-/.  Every morning is a constant battle with my cream of wheat.  You have to boil the milk first, so I keep it on the stove at 9.  and it slowly cooks, then like a volcano, I get a mound of white foam across the stove.  It just explodes.  Ok, it doesn't explode...it rises pretty quickly then by the time I grab it it already spilled over onto the burner then it smokes up and if I am lucky the smoke alarm doesn't go off.  It's all about the timing.  I shouldn't be able to handle hot objects that early in the morning. Then the peanut butter incident today.  Did you know that peanut butter also explodes?  I left it in the microwave a bit too long and it kinda just popped and splattered all in the microwave.  That was a first though.   And I still haven't mastered the art which is omelette making.  It just looks like scarmbled eggs with cheese and mushrooms.  Not an omelette.  It looked like the sad remains of an omelette gone bad. My mom doesn't think I eat so she send food about every week.  Just stuff in boxers or freezer stuff.  Food more on my level. :-)  If it be prepared, heated up, and served in six minutes, then it's a Miranda Meal.    Maybe tomorrow I will stick to toast.
     
    
</post>
<date>11,September,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Damn it's been over a week since my last blog, that is an unusually long time for me! :-) Well, it's officially septmeber 11, 2002.  A year.  wow. And where were you? I remember that I didn't wake up to my alarm and I almost misse dmy Italian class.  But I did miss it.  I woke up and started getting ready when Karen told me that a plane had crashed into the towers.  The towers.  I had thought she meant the Christiana Towers, i was loopy, i had just woken up.  But we turn on the tv and every channel...it was amazing.  It was hard to conceptualize.  It was about 9 am.  And we watched it all on tv.  karen and i are total media/tv whores.  we had 5 televisions in the house and everyone was on a different station.  all of our computers were on different sites.  Everything moved so fast.  Talking to so many people on IM, especially peopel that I hadn't talked to in months. Eerily everyone reached out to everyone that day.  My mom works for the government and she had tried calling but we couldn;t get through to each other.  Then we had the brilliant idea to grab a video camera and GO OUT THERE.  Go outside and tlak to people, to be there, to witness.  So karen and i run to the studio (i was news director at the time) and grab our gear and go.  The weirdest thing was that out of a campus of 20, 000 people, no one was outside.  Conveniently UD was having a blood drive that day.  We went there, we went and talked to random people in Trabant, and Professor Begleiter.  Just trying to make sense of it all.  My most vivid memory was going back into the studio and seeing Carlos.  We had a few channels on in the tv studio and me, Karen, and Carlos watched all of them.  Then we all looked at one screen.  It was a close up of the towers.  But somehthing was different.  We look closer...and we see bodies falling out of windows.  And absolutely nothing could be said.... I remember the day after Tom and I had gone out on Main Street and went to the drug store and bought a ton of stuff to be sent to the FDNY.  The DE Book Exchange was sending a bus out there and it was our opportunity to give.   But since then, I have grown.  I have expanded my vision to beyond my circle of sight and ventured out to understand the events that caused the disaster.  Ask me about them.  I have discovered the meaning behind all of this and the motives and reasonings of our enemies.  More personally, I have remained connected to those I have not been close to prior to 9/11.  If anything at all, 9/11 should teach us all to broaden our perspectives.  Realize that there is more going on that your circle of friends or your work or what the latest trend is.  Realize that there are consequences that come with actions that you may not agree with.  Realize that there are many sides to an issue.  Realize that anything can happen.   Since then I have done everything I can to enjoy what I do and to have fun.  No regrets....
     
    
</post>
<date>21,September,2002</date>
<post>

     
      So Melissa's mom caused a state wide bomb scare.  Her mother runs Frightland (www.frightland.com) a huge haunted house shin dig that goes on every fall.  She sent preview passes to Delaware media, politicians, and schools.  She sent the passes in a box shaped like a casket.  With a handwritten label.  And no return address.   Schools got let out early...bomb squads were called in....politicans hid under their desk.  All because most were sent from the Dover post office.  I got my package safe and sound.  It came with a severed hand. Way to cause a ruckus in the entire state of Delaware, Debbie ;-)   But all were amused and all is well.   
     
    
</post>
<date>20,September,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Today was a great radio show.  If you didn't know already, You can hear my show every Friday from 3-5 pm on 91.3fm if you are around New Castle County, DE or on www.wvud.org Started off with a little Matt Nathanson as the opener.  Usually I have the air studio to myself except for Rob and Sean making me laugh, but noooo today there were about 7 different people all at one time.  Not that it matters, but it makes me a little shy and nervous haha.  Then I had to transmit one of those "this has been a test of the emergency boradcast system..." yeah right smack dab into the Doves.  Smart, very smart.   Callers!! I LOVE CALLERS!!! And they called!! Just asking what I was playing and words of encouragement.  Wow, everyone rocks.  I get more and more callers each week.  Thank you thank you thank you. And I had a person who wanted to chill with me while I did my show.  He had awesome taste in music, but unfortunately I don't think I caught his name.  So I am sorry, but you know, he did refer to me as Rainbow Girl ;-). I was going to have an on-air interview around 4, but something happened so I was frantically answering phones and playing music and talking and trying to figure out what was oging on when Rabs and Dennis from the DC area band Flood came in randomly to drop off some flyers about their show tonight.  So what the hell, did my first in studio interview and it went pretty well for being so impromptu.  So today defnitely was trying on my DJ skills ;-)  It was almost flawless but it was nearly great.  Thank you so much.
     
    
</post>
<date>20,September,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Apparently I let others down when I do not write frequently, so I apologize.  I will catch you up. :-)  Why? Because you are great.  Let's seeeeeeeeeeee...... My days blend together so I have no idea what has happened haha.  Karen and I drove up to Baltimore randomly to see Mark  Michael from Jonasay play for a few hours.  It was a lot of fun, cute little place.  Well worth the speedy drive.    I gave my first public speech for my class yesterday.  3 minutes went by so quickly and I think I sounded like an ass.  Oh well.   BUT let's go over a rule of life.  if you are a musician, and especially if you don't play in like a year, you keep the damn gig that you booked.  YOU JUST NOT SHOW UP!!!  Quite sad when you go to a concert and see the usual crowd who has seen a certain band for the past 4 years, a band that practically defines your college life, and gaze at an empty stage.  Definitely not cool.  But Melissa, Rick, and I went to East End last night.  I lvoe the East End.  I think I have said many times before.  And I ran into someone who I have not seen or talked to in years....very cool though ;-) East End has yummy cheese fries.
     
    
</post>
<date>15,September,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Oh what an awesome day.  Start at Rainbow Records and end at East End and in between a road trip and a concert. Work was fun, always is.  The Nate and I trekked to Baltimore to see Cinema 8 pmay the Volkswagon festival.  They were great.  I guess I should start at the rest stop... So I guess I have this "habit" of misdriving, it's not that I drive inattentively, it's just that I have misadventures.  Like not even seeing red lights, for example.  Well, I went through the truck part of the rest stop and was trying to figure out how to get my little Cabrio out of the maze of big rigs.  Apparently there was an innocent bystander standing in my treacherous path.  In slow motion, Nate brought up his arm and pointed at him telling me to watch out.  The poor guy was like a deer in headlights and was so startled that he had froze and jumped up.  Of course I hadn't, and still haven't been able to get that image out of my mind.  Poor guy.  I think he shit himself. Amazingly we made it Johns Hopkins University.  Alive.  We almost died when I had to cut across oncmoming traffic suddenly onto a road I couldn;t see.  there was a guy on the telephone right on the corner.  I think he said "Damn that crazy white girl don't know how to drive.  I think she tried to kill me."  I saw the whites of his fearful eyes.  Nate said I am not allowed to drive in unfamiliar places again.  Oh, and I hate mapquest.  What gives.  There is n exit right off 95 for JHU, but noooo they want to take us 15 miles through Baltimore.  Regardless we found the place.  And Michael rocks and got me a press pass and a VIP ticket to get in, so we enjoyed a very cool show.   On the drive back we missed an accident by minutes and beat the ambulance there.  So Nate and his kick ass EMT self went and helped the people.  Luckily no one was seriously injured, but it looked like one doozy of an accident.  The we were entertained by Radiohead and Wilco.   Hello exit 109.  Hellow Newark.  Hello East End.  So we end the night with 1/2 priced burgers and drinks at East End.   Yawn.  I am tired.  Good night.
     
    
</post>
<date>15,September,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Last night was Nate's 25th birthday.  :-)  Obviously, we went to East End.  It's pretty awesome when you run into people that you haven't seen in months...years even, and nothing really changes.  That's the beauty of East End.  Always seem to be running into someone....and they have a pretty kickass juke box chock full of good music. Going to Baltimore this evening to see Cinema 8 play.  I'm excited.  I get to play photographer.  
     
    
</post>
<date>27,September,2002</date>
<post>

     
      It is pretty sad that I cannot even recall how many times I have run from the Scrounge to some other part of campus.   Well....we taped the first episode of the THIRD season of Center Stage.  I can't beleive it.  Thank you to Cinema 8.  I can't even conceptualize on how great this season is going to be.  So of course when we have to lub hundred of pounds of equipment a quarter mile, it rains.  No, it doesn't rain, it pours.  Hard.  So Dave, Matt, and Aurora took the equipment to the scrounge while I engineered the studio class.  Dave calls from a payphone saying that we need more battery.  The concert was going to start before i could get there so he said for me to just bring it when i come. No no no no no.  SO I have 20 minutes.  Countdown begins. I quickly grab all the canon batteries i can, shove them in a trashbag, tell the professor that i am going to run to the bathroom, then I run out of Pearson, and down Academy to the Scrounge.  Running like a banshee holding a trashbag.  I got beeped at.  Twice.  But i made it, soaking wet and out of breath, but I made it.  Then I ran back.  No questions ask.  There are no obstacles for Center Stage. The show went soooo well.  Well, besides my loss of hearing......Nothing like standing right in front of the speakers with a headset that only amplified the sound for two hours.  Yeah, I cant even hear myself type.  It's a wonder that I am not deaf now.But the show was incredible and the guys are great.  A thousand thank yous.  It will be airing October 9th at 11 pm on STN.  Hopefully I will be able to get a short clip or two onto the website.   Oh yeah, and we had to take all the quipment BACK.  And the only thing worse than taking the equipment there in the rain and coldness and darkness is that it has been raining for 5 hours since we got there which only means the puddles got bigger.  We were soaked, but it was fun.  This was great. So today I gained a few things..... almost deafness and pnuemonia oh yeah and a kickass crew and show!!
     
    
</post>
<date>24,September,2002</date>
<post>

     
      As a tv/radio person, I live by the clock.  Time is very important. I try to use every available second for all it is worth.  I think I have perfected pushing time.  In my fourth year as a college student I think I have devised every which way to extend sleeping time.  Take this morning for example.... Class is at 9:30am I have to leave by 9:15 am. I HAVE to check my email when I wake up, minus 5 minutes....now down to 9:10 I don't wear what I wore to bed, but something equatable...today, a t-shirt and adidas pants (a university uniform if class is held before noon), minuse 3 minutes...now down to 9:07 didn't shower the night before, will save that for AFTER class ;-)  2 minutes.....9:05 No time to brush teeth, mouth wash and a stick of gum will suffice until 11 am.   See, it's almost an art.
     
    
</post>
<date>22,September,2002</date>
<post>

     
      I really can't cook.  Who ruins pasta!??! Oh yeah, me. So I didn't know how this whole "having a kitchen" thing would work out last year.  Handing my try to ladies in hair nets was so much easier.  So was scooping out salad from a big bowl.  Burners......oven...heat....what a concept. I have mastered a few meals that keep me alive and not starving.  One, I thought, was pasta.  Oh so easy, oh so thought free.  Just boil and heat.  Oh no.... Lately I have been making a lot of pasta and just fridging it so I can just nuke it later.  So this afternoon I was boiling water, then put a whole box of pasta in.  Usually it takes about 10 minutes.  About 30 minutes later Karen came in telling me that she thinks that my pasta is done.  Oh it was done.... Screw it, I drain the wilted water sogged bits of pasta and put it in the fridge.  After hours in the TV studio I was starving... So I take out the pasta container and all the pasta kind of form together into a brick like shape.  So I cut myself a square and ate. How the hell have a survived a year independent?!?!  More musings on my "independence" tomorrow with such adventures as laundry and ironing......
     
    
</post>
<date>22,September,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Nate's profile says this:   From Mir Cat's Blog- I guess I have this "habit" of misdriving, it's not that I drive inattentively, it's just that I have misadventures.  Yeah babe, keep telling yourself that. Meanwhile, I'm still trying to clean my pants up from the last time I rode with you.       
     
    
</post>
<date>22,September,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Oh what a fun filled day yesterday....AND IT WAS A 21 DAY!!!  Yes, I still do that.... So at noon I hit the road.  In the Cabrio for the trip to VA: The Clarks, Jonasay, Radiohead, Brand New, Wilco, Andy Stochansky.....yes a wide mix. I love rest stops, they are the highlight of my trip.  Free maps free maps free maps. Hello Virginia.  I love Virginia.  Arlington was nice, found the club ok and free parking on the weekend.  What more could I ask for.  Met up with some peopel at the Juliana Hatfield show.  Oh she is so beautiful and talented.  She played solo and I was a mere five feet away.  Oh yes.  She pulled out some old favorites and unreleased songs.  It was magical. :-) So then I had a few hours to kill before heading to Centreville for the Jonasay show.... So I found a coffeehouse and read for 2 hours before I discovered a music store.  So I hung out there before heading onto I66 once again.... Hi Centerville.  Hi lots of deer and horses.  Hi wrong way down the highway. But alas I found the Shark Club :::insert Jaws theme song here:::  And Jonasay but on yet another rocking show, despite intial sound difficulties.  I hope the pictures came out ok.  The highlight of the show was when Justin told some drunk lady "How about this, at night i will come into your place and interrupt you while you are performing".  Haha.  No, i take it back, the highlight of the show was Mark's setlist on drywall. :-) And checkout the Excentrics...Technicolor....whatever they are now, if i wasn't so damn tired i could have enjoyed them more, but they really rocked.  Thank god for comfy couches. 120 miles later (one hour, forty minutes) i was home.  
     
    
</post>
<date>05,October,2002</date>
<post>

     
      I can't beleive that my birthday is next weekend.  Wow.  Gee, can you guess where I will be?  Yeah, more than likely East End.   My birthday is also on Homecoming, everyone celebrates with me!!   But Sunday is Recher Theatre, so mark it on your calendars.   Got it!? East End Saturday (see, technically midnight...), then Recher Sunday. See you there :-P 
     
    
</post>
<date>02,October,2002</date>
<post>

     
      I went and saw Seeking Homer last night.  And the night before.  Word. I finally got to finish taping them for Center Stage and I can even describe how good it turned out.  I have such a wonderful crew.  Seeking Homer is one of my favorite bands and they are the greatest guys so I feel very fortunate in being able to feature them.  The interview was great.  ahha.  So Aurora and I decide to pack up and haul ass to baltimore to Fletchers.  Parking is fun.  Especially during a festival that we didn't know about.  Took me like 20 minutes to parallel park without hitting the curb.  But yay we made it.  Why is it always a victory for me to find places?!? The show was great, despite them not getting to Dilemma or Astray ;-) .  Got lots of great pictures.  They sounded awesome and it was such a cute little venue.  The Can't Hang came on.  Fun stuff fun stuff.   Aurora and I found a new hobby.  And trying to remain "professional" is going to be hard hahaha.   But I do beleive the highlight of the night was......ZOMBIES!!! Oh geez....!
     
    
</post>
<date>02,October,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Again....i have to quote Nate quoting me.... this was in his aim profile today:  From Mir's Blog:  while driving back, less than 5 minutes from my apartment I hit a damn raccoon. Look, you either go left or right. There is no dancing in front of my headlights. I tried to miss him, I really did!! I just didn't anticipate his tango!    Yeah, I agree with that sentiment, but saying "Oh well, his stupid ass should have got out of the way" after hitting it is a little uncalled for.           
     
    
</post>
<date>30,September,2002</date>
<post>

     
      One of the highlights from the beach trip... I CAN DRIVE REALLY!!!!  But as we were in Rehoboth, Nate screams this to the wanderers from my car.... "You better watch out!! She will hit you!! I've seen her do it!!!"  And of course while driving back, less than 5 minutes from my apartment I hit a damn raccoon. Look, you either go left or right.  There is no dancing in front of my headlights.  I tried to miss him, I really did!! I just didn't anticipate his tango!
     
    
</post>
<date>29,September,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Dewey Beach Music Festival Oh what fun..... Nate and I drove down and met Josh at the beach. Where?  Down by da beach....BOOOYYYYEEEE!!!!! Started at Watertown to see Juniper Lane but unfortunately one of the members got into an accident on the way.  So we go to the Cork.  But not without playing "don't ever let me dance like THIS" on the side road to the Cork.  The Cork was loud.  Off to the coffeehouses and the Lighthouse.  Great music there and wonderful people.  Met so many industry people and musicians.  Thank you for new music to play. Off to the Rudder to see Jonasay.......... Great show as always and the naked cowboy loved them.  They rocked till the lights came on.  
     
    
</post>
<date>12,October,2002</date>
<post>

     
      I think this will be one of the best weekends of the year... Homecoming...seeing everyone will be craziness... My birthday..... Jonasay CD release....  I am so fortunate to have so many amazing people in my life.  Thank you.
     
    
</post>
<date>11,October,2002</date>
<post>

     
      ahhhhh Homecoming weekend....when else can you go to Pathmark at midnight on a Friday night and actually stand in line with other people all holding breakfast food.  Eggs and Kegs.  And all the store brands.  Cheapness is where its at.  But we're not having eggs or kegs.  We did that two years ago.  We're now tailgating.  But instead of BBQing...since we're starting at 9 am, we're soing the breakfast thing since we're not allowed to do the grilll thang because of the drought.  It was also like a small little family in the liquor store.  How many different things can you mix with OJ?  I can't wait to see everyone again :-)  I can't beleive how lmuch time has passed and how far we have travelled.  What a long strange trip its been....
     
    
</post>
<date>11,October,2002</date>
<post>

     
      RickSavs: ha RickSavs: what's that from? Galileo358: the playground i call my sanity RickSavs: does it have swings? Galileo358: and a merry go round Galileo358: sin round and round and round Galileo358: spin Galileo358: sin too Galileo358: but spin mostly RickSavs: weird RickSavs: very RickSavs: weird
     
    
</post>
<date>10,October,2002</date>
<post>

     
      I like to make to-do lists so I feel a semi sense of accomplishment and fulfillment while I cross tasks off.  Makes my life seem sort of in order and prioritized.  I make a new list every few days and tack it right to my computer monitor, because, if you know me, I am always here.  At my computer.  Wherever I go, there I am! But sometimes, when my list seems extremely difficult, I add mundane thinsg to my list.  Like "brush teeth", "make brita water", and "water plants" so that way I still feel fulfilled and worthy of my time by corssing of things on my list, even though I would do them if they were't on my list. I get by on little victories.
     
    
</post>
<date>09,October,2002</date>
<post>

     
      I set off the smoke alarm again.  And this wouldn't have happened if the maintenence man would have left the damn thing on the floor.  See, I had set it off so many times before that I just ripped the sucker out because it was annoying.  We have about ten in our apartment, so there was defnitely no chance to burning to a crisp. I had a candle burning.  yes, a candle, and yes, only one candle and the damn smoke detector went off.  I look over and its a burning inferno, but still ONE CANDLE! So I grabbed the thing, surprising i remeber to cover it with something so my hands wouldn't sear off, and threw it in the sink.  No more candle, it was a flaming mess. 
     
    
</post>
<date>09,October,2002</date>
<post>

     
      I think October is my favorite month.  I love Halloween.  I went to Pathmark and bought a few bags of Halloween candy.  The best Halloween candy ever are the Russell Stover Peanut Butter Pumpkins.  Spooky. I love the weather, cold and blustery enough for a sweater, but not so much the jacket.  Leaves start to fall and the trees are always swaying with the wind.  You can see your breath and your nose is always the first to feel the bitterness.  But it's refreshing.   The days get darker earlier and you find more excuses to go outside. Pumpkin carving...apple picking...haunted houses...  
     
    
</post>
<date>09,October,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Here I BLOG, there I BLOG...Everywhere I BLOG BLOG....  I am writing from WVUD.  Ohhh a REMOTE BLOG ;-)  And Friday I will being doing a remote broadcast talking to wanderers :-) Come visit me in Newark....This isn't going to help my anxiety much! But now I am going to Bennigan's and then buying music at Rainbow.  hey, I have to keep my store in business ;-) Here is what I will buy and you should to: Beck, Sea Change; Rhett Miller, The Instigator; Bright Eyes, Lifted...; Marc Copely, Limited Lifetime Garauntee; and some used Smitths and Morrisey albums. :-) Gotta love the discount.  So now Batgirlmust depart.  Swoosh!
     
    
</post>
<date>08,October,2002</date>
<post>

     
       Come pick me up Take me out Fuck me up Steal my records Screw all my friends Theyre all full of shit With a smile on your face And then do it again - ryan adams   yup, that sums it up.
     
    
</post>
<date>08,October,2002</date>
<post>

     
      I love our little music store :-)   We're moving...once again, no more books, just music and down the street.  Ahhh...yet another week of moving, but only good things can come of this. And it was awesome to hang out with everyone outside of Rainbow.  And hearing crazy stories.  And letting Raf know how silly we actually are.  And bashing customers.  Oh wait, we don't do that... We call the music register place the pirate ship.  I wonder if in the new place if we can wear eye patches, pirate hats, and carry a bottle of rum.  Wait, we drink in the store anyways.  Hahaha...last year around Christmas there was this "random" bottle of scotch in the back, and we all would drink from it but not all admit to it (we would always go in groups of 2 or 3, never alone, we're not that lushish!) and so we all found out tonight that we all contributed to the drinking of the scotch on the job.  and sneaking galsses of wine....then owen would say "dammit, just drink it, no one cares!" oh man, crazy times crazy times.   But Rob broke the nutpen.  The nutpen has been a part of Rainbow for over a year.  A bic pen with a metal nut around it.  Rob got fed up and broke it.  It was a sad sad sad day for the nutpen. And see....i thought it was common knowledge that i thought a certain guy with a wife and kids that always comes into the store was really hot.  The Raf asked me if i was "fucking nuts".  Yes, "fucking nuts" was the correct term he used. And Terry Potts.........Terry is an older man that hits on all the girls, and older, i mean like 80.  And he creeps all the girls out.  Well, we decided next time we're just going to tell Terry how incredibly hot he is and if he will unbutton his shirt for us.  Slowly.  Seductively. And tomrorow will be another fun night in Rainbow. 
     
    
</post>
<date>07,October,2002</date>
<post>

     
      My computer is sick :-(  It has a virus.  No idea how I got the damn thing, but I can;t get rid of it.  My virus protection stuff sees the virus but does nothing about it.  It says it cannot delete the corrupt file.  Anyone want to help me? :-P  On a better note.  I am taking up stock in wawa coffee.  I was editing Center Stage form 11:30 am til 1:30 am.  Yes That is 14 hours.  Oh wait, I went to lunch.  Minus 2 hours.  And technically I didn't work on it during my meeting, so minus another hour, but thats still TV stuff ;-) .  And sports was using the editors at that time as well, so ok, maybe not a complete 14 hours, but still that is 12 hours i was in that damn building! BUT IT IS DONE!!!!! The first episode on Center Stage is done done done done done.  And it is mucho excellente.  I work with the greatest people.  :-)   Mondays just shouldn't exist.  I mean, it is not like anyone ever takes Mondays seriously.  It's just an extended Sunday. And my weekends always start on Wednesday.  So I guess my week constitutes just Tuesday.  Damn the work week.
     
    
</post>
<date>06,October,2002</date>
<post>

     
      I don't know if last night really happened or not. It was so amazing and unreal.   Charise and I have been looking forward to the Ryan Adam's concert for so long, thank you Dan for tickets.  Dan rocks.  Hard. SO Charise and I leave Delaware, listening to the Ours cd the whole way up screeching and creaming and saying "oh my god" the entire way up 95 and 476 haha. Ahhhh...Popeyes french fries.  So Cajunny goodness.  Then Dan calls.  Uh oh!  Melissa forgot our tickets at home but they will buy us new tickets.  Oh no it's sold out! "Hi, do you need tickets? I have two for the third row in the pit." CHA-CHING! He didn't look sketchy, he had a card, and he walked us to the door.  AW YEAH!! Charise and I went insane.  The show was one of the best I have ever been to.  I had my jaw dropped most of the time.  Sounded so perfect.  None of the radio songs yay, and all of Heartbreaker and just all musical goodness.  He gave out 4 guitars.  Yeah.  Four.  Guitars.  Some girl shouted out that he had a nice ass and she got a guitar.  Damn, what would I get if I told him he could have my body haha.   And we got "Come PIck Me Up" for the closer, one of my favorite Adams songs.  Soo so so so so so good. 
     
    
</post>
<date>18,October,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Money is more powerful than knowledge. So I am skipping class tomorrow to work at the record store.
     
    
</post>
<date>17,October,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Now added to my long list of "things that Miranda should not be allowed to play with": hot irons.  Let me embellish..... I am cursed with naturally curly hair, so I straighten it every morning with a straightening iron.  As I tam typing this, I have two large burn marks on my forehead.  I look like freaking Gorbachev.  I also have a scar on my foot and a permanent triangle on my forearm.   On the bottom of my left foot I have a bubble that has not gone away in months.  You see...I plug in my straightening iron, but since my sink does not have space on the edges, it heats up on the floor.  Yeah...early in the morning, I am not that swift, I accidently stepped on it.  Oh I woke up right quick. And the arm.  Two years ago I was ironing my shirt while it was on me.  Oh come on, I didn't want to take it off and i didnt have an ironing board.  Well, I missed and the tip of the iron singed my arm.  Hence the triangle.   Now that I think about it, in my mom's house, I left an iron mark.  I dropped the iron onto the carpert and the carpet is made out of synthetic material so the iron melted the carpet into a nice glossy triangle.  The couch is over it now. So now ironing has been added to my list of "Problems Miranda has with Domesticity".  We have already tackled cooking and ironing, laundry is next.  Stay tuned.
     
    
</post>
<date>15,October,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Now my rant.....and I am sorry melissa i have tried to make my last few blogs amusing just for you since i know it is the highlight of your day, but i feel like blah  Too make a long complicated story short, I had Mono a few years ago but it was misdiagnosed and because of that misdiagnosis, I now have Chronic Fatigue Syndrome. It has no cure and can take months to years for it to go away if it ever does.  I don't have bouts of it too often, only a few times a year, but it is triggered by stress and usually hits me hard.  Yeah, I am going through it now and I can't even explain the pain that I am enduring.  The throat is always the worst for me.  And 4 cups of hot herbal tea in the past hour has done squat.  And I hate medicine.  I always use medicine as a last reserve and try to use natural remedies to make everything better.  But with what I have , it isn't viral, so it's not like anything would help, just mask the pain.  So grrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr................ And i was going to find a medical list of symptons so you can share my fun, but found some cool stuff on WebMD that I didn't even know before and so now i feel like i sounded like a doctor up above.  i will leave you with some informational medical gibberish so you will feel fulfilled and entertained.....hopefully by the time you are done reading, i will be asleep... - Chronic fatigue syndrome (CFS) may develop without warning in a person who has not been sick. In some cases it develops after a viral illness, such as mononucleosis (mono) or influenza (flu), or after a period of unusual stress.  - Forgetfulness, memory loss, confusion, or difficulty concentrating. Sore throat. Tender lymph nodes in the neck or armpits. Muscle pain. Joint pain without redness or swelling. New headaches. Unrefreshing sleep (waking up feeling tired or unrested). Fatigue that lasts more than 24 hours after exercise or exertion at a level that the person was able to do in the past without fatigue.    
     
    
</post>
<date>14,October,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Sunday didn't really effect me, it felt like my brithday was on Saturday and we celebrated on Saturday, so Sunday was just an ordinary day.   Played with the horses, went home for breakfast, cleaned, concert. Jonasay's CD Release was on my birthday, yay for everyone!!  Aurora and Burket and Heather and I trekked down to Towson for the show.  Road trips are always fun and we had a blast.  They put on a really great show and its awesome that my friends are getting into them.  I think Aurora's night was made after a certain comment....she then replied with "Yeah, that could not have been said better....."  I don't think the roar of laughter was needed ;-) So great meeting so many people and putting faces to names.  I am drained so I am sorry for the lack of color in my musings..... But it was defnitely a passion driven performance which was just incredible.  The band played nearly everything and a good time was defnitely had by all.
     
    
</post>
<date>14,October,2002</date>
<post>

     
      No idea where to begin so I will probably post several times before I fall asleep.... Let's start with Saturday.... Yay for Michelle coming down.  We all  tailgated for breakfast.  I think the morning started off right when Michelle, Double A, and I started shrieking at the moth I thought was a stick flew.  At least we were at a red light.  We find a great spot and started to eat breakfast.  I had brough bagels.  Frozen bagels.  Right out of the freezer.  Whoops!!  So we made our way around and it was so great running into people I hadn't seen in a while....especially girls from the team and old COMM majors.  I always run into Lauren at the craziest places.  First met her....damn, was it four years ago!?!?  Yes, we met at a concert, Pat McGee Band of course.  Strange how PMB is linked to practically everything in my life haha.  And we've hung out and randomly see each other ever since.  So very cool.  So before noon we were plastered.  Then to grottos.  Poor Karen we terrorized her!!  She has these pants that she claims are too small....so i had to yell out "nice ass karen" a few times (or so i was told, i don't recall) before she had to tell me to pipe down that it was a family restaraunt.  So we go back and nap to begin part 2 of homecoming (and celebrating my birthday ;-) )  So yeah....Kates then East End.  And soooo many people came, thank you guys so much i had a great time :-)  I had to split my time between outside and inside of East End because the group slit up, but it was just so wonderful to be with everyone.  Thank you.  And you would be proud of me, I gave up drinking...yes again...so I didn't drink anything after noon.  Oh geez, how many times has that sentenced been uttered.  Not by me i mean, but who says that!?!?  haha ok...on to Sunday!
     
    
</post>
<date>14,October,2002</date>
<post>

     
      "Pretty eyed Pirate smile You'll marry a music man" elton john  so many things to write about.... but i am not feeling well and i need to go edit, but i will blog for you when i get back to my senses.  For I have seemed to lost them. 
     
    
</post>
<date>25,October,2002</date>
<post>

     
      thank you jen...it's all about the candyland http://www.x-entertainment.com/archive/quickies/26/index.shtml
     
    
</post>
<date>24,October,2002</date>
<post>

     
      And bingo rocks my socks.  And so does pinball.   East End is like Cheers.
     
    
</post>
<date>23,October,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Yeah, there are a lot of things that melissa and i find funny, but apparently not everyone laughs with us.   We watched Kundun in class today adn talked about Tibet and China after the movie.  There was this leader in China whose name sounds like "Who Ya Banged".  So of course after hearing the prof say this a few times I really wanted to make a comment to Melissa, but I bit my tongue.  I look over at her and I can tell she wanted to laugh, her face was getting red from stifling laughter.  So i lost it and that made Melissa break as well.  Yeah we were the only 5 year olds in the class that laughed. Come on, where's your sense of bathroom humor?
     
    
</post>
<date>23,October,2002</date>
<post>

     
      I love it when I can't make it to a certain concert (::cough cough pat mcgee band:::) that I get the show on my computer so shortly after.  Thank you guys, you are the best.   "Well I thank you for the chat...we all do what we do just to get by, we all see what we see never to ask why....................."
     
    
</post>
<date>22,October,2002</date>
<post>

     
      And I just read jen's Blog.  It has nothing to do with dinner.  I forgot that October 21st is one of my favorite days of the year, but it was a good day indeed despite the craziness.... from jen... "Today is producer-rant Sunday :) Or, every Sunday is producer-rant Sunday. I didn't have any stories for my show, nor did Brittany, and Whitney didn't have any ideas for hers. So we did the convesation-through email thing we do best. I swear, Brittany, Whitney, Miranda and I have had too many STN conversations through mass emails to each other to count :) I guess that's what happens when we each work on 5 shows, huh :) "  My favorite is how we make fun of other people through mass email.  A note to youself..... Don't be a freaking idiot loser dork face or you won't get made fun of.  Thank you. Oh yeah and there is no candyland to be had in the studio.  Especially not when you rock the ice ice baby.   
     
    
</post>
<date>20,October,2002</date>
<post>

     
      It's now 2:41 am and I have barely slept in the past few days.  I think I have insomnia.   You know you have spent too much time around cameras when your initial thought to most events is "damn, I wish I had a camera".  How many times do I say that a week!?!?  And one of the most important rules is to say that in front of the STN crowd and not your "normal friends" and yes girls, I definitely did do the finger quotes.  I went to the Scrounge with Jen, Whit, and Brit (and yes I did it in that order so it would be kitchsy that it rhymed) and was so disoriented.  It throws me off kilter when something you were once familiar with alters so you are thrown off balance.  I seriously had to pause to reflect on how I must think about my actions instead of acting on instict in the Scrounge.  I just got so overwhelmed that I joined Whitney for quesadillas.  With the grande mexi-meal, you get beans and rice.  Once Whitney saw the beans being plopped onto the plate she promptly changed her order to the "un-grande".  I updated Brit that Whitney was not getting the grande and I used the finger quotes and Whiteny informed me that no finger quotes were needed, that she definitely did not want the grande-ness included with her mexi-meal.  The grossest part of dinner was when my orange juice bottle stood "completely" "upright" when I "stuck" it "upside-down" in the "beany mess".  I wish I had a camera. 
     
    
</post>
<date>20,October,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Yes....I just found the Breakfast Club on TNT.  I barely go beyong channel 19 and my certain few channels, but low and behold there is a gem on 12.  I rarely stray from my dependable channels, though there is usually nothing of quatlity on.  Funny how I am a broadcasting major and don't watch tv much.  The HBO's, Comedy Central, and MTV 2 get all the action from my remote.  And since I found a great movie on TV, I will share with you my favorite movies, in no order, but eight is great.... 1. Empire Records (how much does this remind you of Rainbow....?!) 2. Good Will Hunting 3. Shrek (not my buttons, my gumdrop buttons!) 4. To Gillian on her 37th Birthday 5. The Emperor's New Groove 6. Down to You (cheesy teen film, but its all goodness :-) ) 7. Best in Show 8. Sixteen Candles
     
    
</post>
<date>20,October,2002</date>
<post>

     
      I just slept about 20 hours in the past tow days.  Being sick sucks.  I will share with you the troubles of having a cold..... Sleeping....yeah the whole process makes you even wonder if it is worth attempting to sleep.  First off, you can't breath through your nose, and if you can breath through you're nose it burns and there is whisteling, which won't allow you to sleep anyways.  But still, you can't breath through your nose, so you must sleep with your mouth open.  My throat has been killing me, so breathing through my mouth just worsens the issue.  On the same topic, the nose.  It doesn't run symmetrically, no one nostril always has the be the winner.  It's always one side that runs and the other doesn't.   So that determines which side you sleep on so that you don't have to grab the tissues as much.  And if you are compulsive and obsessive like I am, the side you fall asleep on is a big deal.  We're not even going to start on the muscle achiness. But my mom is the coolest because she brought over green and oolong tea.  Yay.  With the power of the leaves, I will be back in action tomorrow, but for now, it's back to bed.
     
    
</post>
<date>27,October,2002</date>
<post>

     
      ok, nat ei s making me get off the computer since i ave a habit of being nostalgic and IMing and emailing random people on the computer when i am not of righ tmind.  i will catch you on the flip side with more misadventures with MIRANDA!
     
    
</post>
<date>27,October,2002</date>
<post>

     
      i saw whitney at the loop!!!! and jen writes this in her blog and i love them all to pieces :-) :: Tuesday, October 22, 2002 ::  Yay for STN girls :) I had dinner with Miranda, Whitney and Brittany tonight, and it struck me how well we all knew each other. I could predict when Whitney was going to make the "what the hell was that face", when Miranda would laugh, and when Brittany would try to explain herself to us. And the funny part was, I think that was the very first time the four of us did something together. It's just that when you work with someone so much, and you go through the same things that they do (and no one can understand the hell that is STN unless you've been through it, period:) ) you really do form some kind of freakish bond with them. And I mean freakish in the best but oddest way there is :) But I love my girls, don't know where I'd be without them.
     
    
</post>
<date>27,October,2002</date>
<post>

     
      just got back from th eloop..  i am not going to correct my typing.  nate say sfir me to write "nate made an ass of himself as usual. "  He is on by bed now and sleeping iver, but on on my bed.  he is "the guy on the couch again"  .  the loop totally rocked and of course i have marked on my body (my hand particularlty) where i have a bruise but have no idea how i got it.  i was josie from the pussycats!!!! YAY!!!! melissa used my id.  Silly loop people, she got in everywhere.  everyone was there, it was greate to see everyone again..........Anne-Ashley, Michelle, Jason, Meliisa, Rick, Nate, Felicia, Marty, Tim, Nina, etc so on and so forth had such a good time thnak yuou :-)  and of course i am sure everyone will be baxk at the logan house again shortly :-)
     
    
</post>
<date>08,November,2002</date>
<post>

     
      JonaDAY part one.... it's almost midnight on thursday night and its really funny how aurora and jen have tomorrows activities in their away messages ;-)  Oh oh we;re addicted to AIM.  We're COMM majors, what can I say...but these made me laugh...then I will talk about the previous JonaDay's excursion... Aurora: i'm at cookseys filling up on some hops and grains...hehe...celebrating early for Jonaday!! :-D Jen: Study study study, what else is new :-)  Feel free to IM me, I'm here Tomorrow is Jonaday #2!  How fun :-)  Ok, time to spill it...but since I am a COMM major, I will play the role of GATEKEEPER.  You figure it out.  I think the foreshadowing of the night occured when Aurora, Matt, and I went to pick up the vehicles.  I had a new minivan, while the truck looked like it was built in 1970.  I don;t think matt appreciated my Jed Clampett reference ;-).  But we got our gear in and we were ready to roll!  First stop...Wendy's.  Fries and Frosties rock.  Then onto Jersey....then I realize that I have no idea where we are going.  We all thought the others knew.  Oh well, we'd find it, even in the dark raininess!  So we get to Glassboro and find the school but cannot find the RAT.  yeah the freaking renovated rat.  I'll get to that later.  So Matt was following me, though I had no idea where we were going.  As Jen pointed out, our quest around campus looked like a scene from the video game Simpsons Road Rage.  he went the opposite way down the street and went in the entrances where I said to avoid and we could never catch up!  But alas, we found the parking lot..... Same old same old setup.  Everyone was great.  Ohhh the funny part.  So Aurora was getting the Canons ready when she asked for me to come over.  So I was asking why, and she kept repeating for me to come over.  Me, and not Dave.  So then I was worried!  We're all crowded around Aurora (except Dave ;-) ) to see that the eye piece of the camera was dangling off!!  NOT GOOD!!!  (we avoided Dave since he is the wiser of us all and very protective of the equipment and we did nto want to start panic).  But yay for Justin having superglue.  Oh come on, we're STN , did you really expect more from us? ;-)  JonaDAY part 2 tomorrow.....this should be an adventure.  McGuyver style. 
     
    
</post>
<date>05,November,2002</date>
<post>

     
      also, while driving back from king of prussia, melissa informs me that "there is not one time that i am in the car with you that i do not fear my life"
     
    
</post>
<date>04,November,2002</date>
<post>

     
      I swear I need to write a book about the adventures at my record store... We have our list of crazy customers..... This one apparently I met last year but I don't recall him, but he remembered who i was.  Fair enough.  So its awkward conversation then he leaves.  Then comes back.  then leaves again.  Jamie, Charise, and I stand around befuddled.  Then the creepy man comes in (mind you our male managers aregetting a real hoot out of this) and says "hey, can we go out for coffee soemtime".  We look at each other not sure who he was talking to, so I grab some cds and start running some info on them, Jamie grabs the phone, and poor Charise is left defenseless while she lies to him telling him that she has a boyfriend.  We then goes on to pester her about it and then says "well miranda wont go out with me, so why don't you".  Charise is trying not to laugh and jamie and i are avoiding eye contact because we don't want to start crying.  We then leaves, but not before shouting "its ok, i have plenty of lady friends".  I swear, the three of us were on the ground while raf mocked the poor guy.  It was all I could do from not laughing out loud.  And the best part was was that customers stopped and stared at the whole ordeal.  
     
    
</post>
<date>04,November,2002</date>
<post>

     
      I know you are dying to know the funniest thing i have done all semester is.  And oddly enough it doesn't invove me making an ass out of myself. So i am in my room quietly reading when my roomate natalie comes in with a water balloon and a twinkle in her eye. She wants to throw it off our balcony and hit cars.  i want to hit people.  So we round up the roomies.... We fill up a few and arm ourselves. I live in a four story apartment building with two sides to it.   The first attack..... natalie and i run to the 3rd floor balcony on the stair case and hit a car aiming for the open sunroof.  We miss, but the car still gets wet.  We need something better.... Second attack..... We see a car of girls unpacking things from their car.  perfect.  We run through the woods behind our house.  Of ocurse we're dressed in pajamas and sandals because its 1 am.  We run all the way to the top of the floor....and bombs away!  Oh yeah it was great.  People screamed, things got wet.  Oh shit! Time to run!  Not knowing how to escape since there is only one out, oh we were smooth and got home safely. Mission accomplished.
     
    
</post>
<date>04,November,2002</date>
<post>

     
      So on Friday Jonasay came down for my radio show.  It was great, thank you to everyone involved. So after my nervous breakdown and three cups of coffee, everything went well. Rob had tagging Satellites come in for a session in production room 1, and he was going to leave everything up for me to use.  Oh would have been great if the band he brought in wasn't 2 hours LATE!  So I figured if they are out by 3 i should be good.  No.  Let's begin at 2:30.  This is in no way aimed at Rob, its just a funny situation on nothing goes the way i plan ;-).  So I am trying to figure out when the hell am I supposed to do.  Then Dave says "oh yeah just have them play in the studio".  Oh yeah sure.  Nothing like fitting anything that should make music into the cubicle I call an air studio.  But it worked and it rocked.   I received so much positive feed back, especially from random people that I do not know, that it made my day.  Everyone enjoyed the work of my crew and how the studio session was hard to differentiate from the cd.  yeah that crew was me.  only me. haha So after we go to East End.  Like Disney World, it's the greatest place on earth.  Then to Chestertown.  My mom called and left a message on my phone... "rock stars have kidnapped my daughter" name that movie. speaking of that movie....ryan made me laugh.  so the mom that was in almost famous was in beyond rangoon, which we were watching the other day.  So in the middle of class the mom comes on screen and ryan yells "don't do drugs!!" (a quote from almost famous).  yeah, only him and i laugh.  i swear i think my professor thinks i am a 5 year old dumbass.
     
    
</post>
<date>04,November,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Ok, due to popular demand, I AM BLOGGING!!!! Hmmm, so what to write about...? I told Melissa I would write about our wonderful mall excursion.  I don't know why I shop at malls.  We walked three hours in King of Prussia mall only for us to buy stuff at 2 stores.  And it was the two stores that we came to see.  And we have banned Christmas.  The Christmas season should NOT begin before Thanksgiving.  there is nothing Christmassy to be had in the month of October. None.  It should be ghosties and ghoulies and goblins.  Only to be followed by cornucopias and crisp leaves.  Only after the turkey is cut and the last drop of eggnog swilled should there be any good will and merryment.   Soon we'll be celebrating Christmas right after 4th of July.  
     
    
</post>
<date>16,November,2002</date>
<post>

     
      I started my day at 4:40 pm.  Yes, in the evening.  Well I guess when you go to bed at 6 am that doesn't seem so bad. Last night was a Jonaday.  I have a headache so I don't know how much I will type, but we will see where we will end. Aurora and I went to the Recher Theatre in Towson then off to Bohagers in Fells Point for a second show. Great show at Recher and it made Aurora and I realize how awful the sound on our video is.  Ok, not awful, but not great.  Curses.  Or maybe the fact that we listened to the music for more than half a day numbed our ears, but we were a little discouraged, but still all is well.  Then Bohagers for the "Rock my STyle" fashion show.  Um, I hope I don't even rock any of the styles they displayed.  I was slightly frightened.  Then back in the van.  Since Mark is cool he gets to drive our saucy van.  Damn rain.  Damn my headache.  I apologize for the brevity.  Nothing like a 2 am diner stop.  Only to be followed by a rainy jaunt in the paddocks with the horses.  Finally got to see his horse :-)   i'll write more later.  Hi Advil.
     
    
</post>
<date>15,November,2002</date>
<post>

     
      More misadventures of Rainbow....let me just make you all aware of a simple rule...if you are creepy, don't try to pick up unsuspecting girls.  I can't tell you how many times the Rainbow girls get attacked by the creepies that stroll into the store.  We need to have an alert system.  I think I wrote about this one guy before, the one that keeps asking a different one of us out...well I was putting away cds in the overstcok boxes when I overheard that oh so familiar voice.  Jamie was the victim this time...  So in order to not be seen by him, I had to escape.  Apparently I am his favorite.  So I had to freaking crawl from the side of the store to th eback of the store where he couldn't wander just so I wouldn't be confronted.  Oh and George....  we all figured that maybe he wouldn't find us since we moved, but he did.  And he paid us a visit yesterday when we opened.  We need to prepare ourselves for George, we cannot fend for ourselves when we are barely awake.  The best plan of action for getting rid of george is just plain ignoring.  I know i know, it sounds mean, but c'mon every freaking day he stays in and bothers us for like an hour.  Oh and sexy Terry....at least you can carry on a decent conversation with Terry even though he smells and his eyebrows stick out.  He trapped Jamie and I in the rap section and proceded to tell us how nuce we looked, hey at least he is complimentary, and how if he wasn't over 60 he;d take us out. DAMN!  haha.  Raf (our manager) told us that next time we oughta start un buttoning our shirts and start touching him and stuff.  Or maybe each other.  haha.  I think he would have a heart attack right in the store! Ok, it's past 2 which means I should be at the radio station soon....
     
    
</post>
<date>12,November,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Nate tells me that blogging should be my highest priority. Melissa, Rick, Nate and I went to see Lewis Black on Tuesday.  So freaking funny, he is one of the guys from The Daily Show with John Stewart on Comedy Central.  And I didn't appreciate the fact that they all stared at me when the opening comedien brought up something I did.  For example... Apparently I use double words a lot....such as, and I take this verbatim... "I didn't kiss him kiss him...I just kissed him".  yeah they all had a hoot.  Sometimes you just need the affirmation! :-)
     
    
</post>
<date>12,November,2002</date>
<post>

     
      All of my days have seemed to blend together recently.  Work. Sleep. Eat. Concert.  Not all in that order and not all entirely in one day.  Especially sleep. Haha.  But again, was another day at the record store, i swear I think I have worked 10 days straight there. Don't get me wrong, I love it, but it was hard for me to figure out what day Sunday was.  Mondays adventures were a lot more enjoyable at Rainbow so I will write about that after...  Sunday...work from open to 4 pm then off to edit the jonasay tape.... 6 pm, i change into my pajamas and pack up my coffee maker because i knew that it was going to be a long night.  Dave and Aurora show up shortly after and we start the long grueling task of editing.  Ok, let me set the scene...we have about 2 hours of footage that goes onto a video cube.  This is all located in the hell that we refer to as "The White House".  This building was the President's old house that was converted into the editing rooms on the 2nd floor.  We have one room with the editors and another room with computers and a very scary bathroom.  And it smells.  We worked so hard on this video.  It's nearly perfect.  It's incredible.  around 11 pm we ran out of coffee.  11:30 the pizza came and we ate in the hallway because we couldnt stand to be anywhere tv related.  Then back to editing.  3 am came so quickly.  Then a storm.  We lost our senses shortly after that.  It was hilarious, both Aurora and I couldn't even function anymore or do menial tasks, like talk.  We figured that we should just work throughout the night to get this video done.  It was too perfect to leave alone.  At 8 am we were done and so happy we nearly cried.  nothing like listening to Jonasay for 14 hours.  More than half a day we worked on it staright.  I think we have lost our minds.  We're such dorks that we even had "favorite parts" because you know, watching for 14 hours we should have been sick of it hahaha.  Ugh and WISH.  SO that was the first clip we loaded since it was the first song.  But the editors were screwy so whenever we double clicked a certain thing, it would revert back to the first clip loaded, which was "Wish".  Wouldn't have been a problem, but everytime we expected a different song it was "Wish".  It haunted us.  And at 5 am the last thing we want to see are clips in random places where they should not be! haha.  There was even one time we werefooled...it was the audio for a different song...but oh no, the cube was too wise and underlayed the video for Wish.  That damn song hates us ;-) So yeah after the marathon and the perfect video, i went to bed at 9 am and woke up at 2 pm to go work at the music store.... It was Jen, Max, and I.  There is a reason that Raf doesn't schedule Jen and I to work together.  We made ninja stars out of old cds.  I love Rainbow.  Where else do you get paid to listen to Boston and make deadly weapons? And today...I had a fun filled day at Rainbow again :-) This time Chris was defenseless against Jamie and I.  Jamie told me I couldnt leave work this evening because I made her laugh all day. And the UPS man is on our hit list.  And no, not the hot one with the wife and kids (man, that guy can NOT keep coming into the store with his uniform on....) but this other one that sat outside of our store for like an hour with all of our cds in the back of his truck.  you cannot do that on pearl and jay z day, we had angry customers that i didnt want to deal with!  I also don't think Chris enjoyed me and Jamie serenading him.  But I do love our new store.  I thought our stalker window would be bad...the whole front of the store is now a window.  Raf caught me staring out it the other day, apparently for too long, and informed me that people can see me watching them.  Whoops!  It's like a fishbowl.  I;m a fish.  I want to be an angel fish.   
     
    
</post>
<date>12,November,2002</date>
<post>

     
      I am sooooooo sorry!  Apparently I have been disappointing my loyal FANS by not blogging more often on my misadventures.... Ok, what to hit.... JonaDAY part 2  Drove the van.  Yes, again.  See the brakes and acceleration are very sensitive...oh and mapquest sucks.  SUCKS SUCKS SUCKS! But we found the place and unloaded and thinsg were perfect.  Semi.  Until I lost communication with my crew.  I know they were talking about me ;-)  I don't even know what to write.  The filming was so incredible, I have an awesome crew.  The band is great, everything just went well.  Aurora got pulled up on stage and I thought she was going to pee herself.  As she stated "I know I had this shit eat grin on my face". Hahaha.  Oh wow, its so hard fo rme to put it into words, but I was so extremely pleased...So on the way back...hit a possum.   Hmm...Saturday I worked at the record store then edited.  Fun Fun. Sunday...Oh Sunday... sunday bloody sunday... this deserves an all new blog....
     
    
</post>
<date>18,November,2002</date>
<post>

     
      if i have learned one thing the past few days it is this.....    Life is a mystery to be endured, not a problem to be solved.......  
     
    
</post>
<date>18,November,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Robert Mirabel is incredible.  I went to the Grand Opera House last night to see his performance and was deeply moved.  He incorparted rock and jazz and hip hop genres into his new age style and captivated the audience with his sheer talent.  Robert is a Native American and his entire performance displays his heritage through the instruments, dancing, and outfits.  Between songs, he told stories of his culture.  Words cannot even begin to describe the evening.
     
    
</post>
<date>29,November,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Happy Thanksgiving :-) I am thankful for a handful of things.  And fortunately for you this will be brief because I am sleepy... I am thankful for the people that are in my life.  I am surrounded by the most honest, fun, and lovable people.  It's taken years, but I have finally found you.  My friends mean the world to me and I am so very glad they are in my life.   I am thankful for being healthy.  Both mentally and physically.  It's been a while since i have been truly happy.  Too long in fact, and this is one holiday season where I really have a clear mind without remorse or fear or depression. I am thankful for great music.  It's really a driving force and this past year has opened up many doors for me and has allowed me to expand so much and appreciate so many different styles.  It's a part of my being, not merely entertainment or distraction.  Too many people lose sight of that.  The beat goes on, whether its the drums or your heart.
     
    
</post>
<date>29,November,2002</date>
<post>

     
      "Sometimes, I wish that I was the weather You'd bring me up in conversations forever And when it rained, I'd be the talk of the day" - john mayer  I am surrounded by the greatest friends in the world.  More on that in the next blog.... It was John Mayer day :-)  Brit got a few tickets fro John in Philly and I wasn't going to go.  I couldn't deal with the 15 year old girlies after seeing John so intimately previosly.  Michelle and I can't recall on how and when we got so jaded, but we have.  But Wednesday's performance was nothing short of incredible... Pick up Brit and Jen and Holly in NJ with no problem.  We hit the diner before heading over the river to Philly.  I think it is customary for the waitress of any diner to insert the word "honey" into every sentence.  Off to Philly, find the venue with no problem.  He played in the Temple Basketball court, though it was comparable in size to the FU center.  Sold out.  Fourth row.  Word.  But oddly it was the farthest away I have ever been.  It was Brit, Jen, and Holly's first time seeing him,so it was exciting :-) Maroon 5 were really good.  I have heard good things about them and i have played their cd in the store, but it was the first time I saw them live.  And John....played acoustically the first few songs with the opener being "Love Soon".  I do not want to give the 15 year old girlies any credit so i will not discuss them at all :-)  Then the band came out.  His setlist was incredible, old songs, new songs, and non album songs.  "City Love" right into "Covered in Rain" was amazing.  His whle performance and musicl talent was just amazing.  I think Brittany and I were the only girls in there staring at his hands instead of his face haha.  I did the whole phone thing too, I admit.  Only one song though haha.  I have never cried at a concert and the people that cry during concerts annoy me.  I beleive it was John Mayer where this girl was bawling the whole time nad I just wanted to punch her in the face and give her something to cry about.  But during the encore during "Comfortable" I almost shed a tear haha.  I held it back though.  Just the whole John Mayer/Tom thing and the past few crazy John years got to me.  And it was odd because it hadn't before.  And I will delve into that more later.  Maybe tomorrow. Now the even more fun stuff... So we parked on the fourth floor of the parking garage.  Which means 30 minutes of waiting.  Haha, the best thing was when we got into the car and trying to figure out what to listen to and Jen and Brit chose Jonasay which then Jen proceeded to say that if John and Jonasay played together it would "be the bestest concert ever".  haha yay for jen.  So then I see this guy walking and inform the car of his hotness.  They agreed.  Then a girl followed him.  Boo.  But he opened up the door for her and simultaneously we exclaimed "awwww!".  The for the next 20 minutes we hypothesized about the hot boy.  I let him pull out in front of me.  Then we decided to follow him.  Jen wrote down his license plate number.  Are you scared yet...?  We got bored so we went to McD's.   Now I know why they made me drive in the city.  As Jen put it "hey, we're not dead yet, but if I was driving we'd stil be in center city, you're a city driver."  See, you just have to be aggressive.  Cutting across traffic, cutting people off, it's all about the city life.  Some dumb butt stopped in the middle of the lane and waited.  I am not going to wait, I am going to get past him.  Silly suckers who waited patiently.  And yay for go go gadget accelerator.  No way I could have gotten my exit (without any warning no less, it just jumps at you) without swiftly driving across three lans of traffic at a turn when the light turned green.   Back to NJ then DE...bed at 3 am.
     
    
</post>
<date>29,November,2002</date>
<post>

     
      SUNDAY "I wake up everyday, go through the same routine  Go to work, come home, what does it all really mean?" pmb  Wake up and walk to work.  One of the highlights of my day is my walk to work.  It's about a half mile and about 3 songs depending on the cd.  The familiar sights and sounds and people make it feel like home.  Too many people around here either take the town for granted or totally ignore what lies within the streets.  In ten minutes I pass the skater kids outside Switch with a flying mermaid on the wall, the tarot card man on the stone fence, and colored chalk drawings on the sidewalk.  My favorite aspect of our new store are the fishbowl windows.  For hours I can watch the town go past me.  People watching, lights changing, time passing.  The stores that surround Rainbow are like a family, we all have the same customer base and all know each other.  I can't even count how many times we have left one store to go to another while still working.  The walk to work reminds me of the secluded bubbles that too many people immerse themselves in.  And reminds me where home is.
     
    
</post>
<date>29,November,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Saturday.... Couldn't sleep and woke up around 10 am, after going to bed around 6 am.  Since I have had the past few Saturdays off, the weekend has become my big shopping day.  It's about 20 minutes to the grocery store I usually frequent....really cheap organic, specialty, and foreign food so I make the trek...so I figured what better way to spend my Saturday than flower and food shopping.  I am sorry, Pathmark just doesn't have quite a selection in soy, falafel, and thai foods.  I also love my grocery store because of the hot older men that also shop there in the early morning.  But wait, they are mostly gay and shopping with their partners.  Oh well, it's double the looking pleasure at least.  And I found red sunflowers to brighten up my room.   After a few fun filled hours back home to enjoy a few more hours of sleep before heading to Baltimore for another Jonasay show.  My mom was going to go with me, but had gone to PA instead.  Melissa, Rick, and Epler and I braved 95.  I don't appreciate the negativety towards my vehicular skills less than five minutes after they get in the car.... So we get to where the venue is but need to find parking.  After we passed the adult movie theatre (XXX Adult Film Hits $2) with a hearse (1972 era) in front of it and the Gun  Pawn shop (trade in your bling for a bang...) (hehehe I just came out with that witty remark ;-) ) we found a space.  At least we were wearing our neutral gang colors. I was kinda hesitant to go in, for I was quite uncertain of my previous nights endeavors....but all was well :-)  Fiesta Red. And driving home...no one was on the road, I was going 80, not fast for 95 north.  Pass a state cop, I brake.  He pulls out, follows me, then lights flare.  I'm scared shitless.  Charise and I talk about what we would say if we ever got pulled over, but yeah, all of that wen't completely out the window when the cop came over.  I got away with a warning.  yay.  I think it was because I have a clean driving record (shut up, thats not too surprising!) and I was wearing my glasses (i dont have any restrictions), he didn;t smell alcohol, and we all had our seatbelts on.  Yay for the little things. Drive home, go to bed.
     
    
</post>
<date>29,November,2002</date>
<post>

     
      Oh geez, I have not blogged in a while.... "I'm writing you to catch you up on places I've been..." -john mayer  I guess I will start in chronological order....I have been horrible at this lately...so a new blog for every exciting day...  Let's go into the time machine to Friday...  Off to Arlington, VA to see another Jonasay show.  I'm laughing at myself just thinking about writing the misadventures of that evening.  First off, we got lost.  Imagine that, me driving and not getting from point A to point B obstacle free.  A novelty. Get to the wonderful Iota and it was packed which was great.  Hello vodka and coke.  Great great great show, the best one I have seen them put on so far.  I really have a lack of color commentary when i write about an event a week later.  Bear with me.  Aurora was in SC and we did the whole cell ohone thing during a concert.  No one did that five years ago and now everytime I go to a show there is at least one person holding up their cell phone during at least one song.  It's like an added person at the venue.  A call saying "i wish you were here and now you are".  Now that I think about it, I beleive I do that a lot.  I wonder if I look like a dork.  I just sat here for a few minutes trying to recollect the first time I did the phone concert thing and remembered when Nate called me and held up his phone so I could hear the radio in LA.  I believe he was in a pool hall and John Mayer was on the radio, well, before he was on the radio now.  That was a first.  Mobile to mobile radio experience.  So yeah a few drinks later....see, I haven't really drink drank drunk a lot lately, one factor being time, the other money.  So here is where the embarrassment begins....I don't quite remember all of it, just slight recollections, so here we go.... I had to give Michael two copies of their Center Stage video, but after the show I looked in bag and found no videos.  SO I tell him that I have no idea where the videos went.  He then informs me that I already gave them to him after the show.  After the show?  What the hell, it was just after teh show and I defnitely didn't give them to him.  But he said I did, so I must have, but where did those minutes go.....?  I don't even know how long this ordeal lasted, but I kept showing Justin my striped socks and talked to Mark about various forms of wildlife.  Mark told me that he most enjoyed when I staggered towards him saying that I wasn't driving.  No, really...? :-)  At another point, I handed Aurora my phone where Justin proceeded to tell her that I was "fucked up and never saw that side of me before".  Haha.  Hmmm I am sure that if anything esle comes back to me, I will inform you.... Onwards to the parking garage!  Did you know that parking garages in Arlington close at 2:30 am?  Yeah, well we didn't.  I told the security gaurd in my drunkeness how we were from Delaware and not there and HAD to get out.  I guess he obliged.  I remember riding in the elevator and getting off on the wrong floor and running to not my car... Babbled in the car a lot, I tend to do that, at least it's semi coherent bablle when I am sober, when i am drunk I think its more like aimless sleep talk.  Then I pass out.   Hello Newark and the sunrise.
     
    
</post>
<date>08,January,2003</date>
<post>

     
      oh geez...it's been over a month! lets seeeeeee..........updates melissa's birthday rocked as do llama sweaters.... a wonderful new years journey with mark and jonasay in south carolina working with MSNBC with Chris Matthews and Hardball (upcoming news!) logan house rainbow losses more on all of those in the coming week.... my head is spinning
     
    
</post>
<date>16,January,2003</date>
<post>

     
      and the MSNBC Hardball broadcast is over....for now... way to shut out your constituents in the cold with your 300 minions, Biden... met a lot of wonderful people, thank you
     
    
</post>
<date>06,February,2003</date>
<post>

     
      damn, its been yet another 60 minutes.  I cant tell you what happened between there and here. My eyes are burning though and I have been leaning on my left arm for way to long so now that side of my body is numb and I am kinda contorted on this chair.  Which  I have managed to save myself from falling off it several times now.  I am atop of a metal and carpet floor here in the radio station and going from the computer to the cd players I push off the counter and wheel my chair across the room.  Unfortunately I have to cross the threshold of the metal plate and carpet.  Nearly tumbling to the ground everytime.  But I haven't.  I did lose my shoes about 35 minutes ago though.  They are somewhere in the hallway. SO I made coffee.  No, I heated up coffee.  In our microwave that is from 1987.  I hope I don't start glowing green from the nuclear waves.  But my mug would not fit into the small confinement of the energy box.  So I found a cubelike container that fit.  I had sugar.  But nothing to stir it with.  Ah. My pen.  And I think it slightly melted.   Speaking of fun with heat.  So I learned that cardboad does not belong in the oven.  The hard way.  Well the other day, Melissa, Karen, and I ordered pizza.  We later decided we wanted to heat it back up so I took control over the kitchen.  I just took the Papa John's box and placed it in the oven at 350 degrees.  Yeah, about 15 minutes later we smelled somehting burning.  I thought it was perfectly fine to take the box out of the oven, wile Karen and Melissa started yelling at me.  It makes sense.....its like a little incubator.  Who knew you couldn't place paper in almost fire.  So last night I made one of those frozen pizzas that have the cardboard on the bottom.  But see, its ok because I didnt realize that there was cardboard on the bottom, so I totally was not at fault.  So yeah about 20 minutes into it, i smell something burning, but just ignore it.  Shortly after the smoke detector goes off.  What the hell.  The kitchen is smoke, of course.  Look in the oven, take the unburnt pizza out...then find my culprit.   come on, its been a while since i have had a kitchen misadventure, it was about time for a new one.
     
    
</post>
<date>06,February,2003</date>
<post>

     
      almost an hour later.... i am listening to the new Nada Surf album now.  They're playing with Sondre Lerche.  Not on the albu, on tour.  I want to see that show.  Speaking of shows.  Ah, the Saint in Asbury.  What a cute little club.  Small, intimate venue that is very receptive of orginal bands.  Gotta love that.  And the staff was so extremely nice.  Saw Green to Think and Graham Colton, two amazingly wonderful bands.  I have been a fan of GC for quite a while now and finally got to see a full live performance. yay.  Maybe I will own my own venue.  After I win the lottery.  Haha, I just remembered when Miss Jen, Aurora, and Jim and I went to Ben Folds.  We like to play the game "in my venue..."  Of course it would be named Mirandaland ;-)  Complete with a Ferris Wheel.  Hahaha I just remembered.....on the way to Asbury, in the beginning on the trip on 273 I was aggravated by traffic and I casually told Aurora and Tessa that when I have my own country all major highways will be ten lanes.  Aurora said that that was the first time she ever heard that phrase uttered.  Again, it would be named Mirandaland ;-).  I was about to compile a list of things we say that probably are never uttered, but then again, I have to stop myself because this site has become way too big and too many people are looking over my shoulder haha.  I know I have lost my dignity numerous times lately, but there needs to be a gatekeeper.  Two more hours and I am doing fiiiinnnnneeeee.   
     
    
</post>
<date>06,February,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Ahhhh...lovely WVUD doing an overnight here from midnight to 6am and thought I would check in.  Have the coffee and donuts.  God, I love this industry :-) Maybe I will write in every hour just to keep my sanity haha.  Nothing like a spontaneous drive to Asbury Park last night, only to get to bed at 6 am and wake up at noon and to broadcast till 6 am.  Sleep is such a luxory these days haha.  It really isn't necessary.  A caffeine IV does just fine.   So I am doing the good old apartment search right now.  Debating in staying in Newark and living in the apartments connected to my record store...haha yes, I could wake up ten minutes prior to starting the work day...or just heading to the Baltimore/DC area.  Is it time for me to find a practical job already!?!?!
     
    
</post>
<date>19,February,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Aurora and I apparently picked something up at the Hilton.  And she didn't drink from the Captain.  haha but now we both have raspy throats.  Hahaha.  We took one for the team. It's going to reach nearly 70 in Wilmington NC this week.  Sweet.  While Delaware is freezing with be soaking up some semi-rays. I told Karen that I just need to keep a packed bag next to my door.  Kind of like what pregant women door.  So that if I am in a rush, I can just grab it on the way out.  Filled with all the necessities, such as clothes, toothbrush, underwear, and a poof.  Can't forget the poof.
     
    
</post>
<date>18,February,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Damn the snow plows.  Everyone in my apartment complex is pretty much plowed in.  I love where I live.  First off, whenever snow falls, usually you see cute little snowmen or snow forts.  nope, not here.  Here you see snow porn.  It's amazing the art you can create with snow.  And getting cars out is another story.  We usually don't get enough snow to justify purchasing a shovel, until now.  So we must get creative on how to get cars out.  Brittany had a BYOB party to get Peebur out...Bring Your Own Bowl.  That didn't last long.  This morning I saw everything from trashcans to pots to brooms to shovel out the trapped vehicles.  My favorite was the group of guys using a keg bucket to scoop away the snow.  Fine work boys. So after being trapped for two days, I needed some more music.  As if all the cds I came away with from the MMC wasn't enough.  Here is what I picked up from my store....went in to pick up cds and ended up working a few, gotta love Rainbow :-)  This is what I got... USED: The Beatles- Past Masters One, The Beatles -Past Masters Two, The Cars -Greatest Hits, The Police -Ghost In The Machine, Seeking Homer -Paradise (I know I know, I have had this disk since it came out, but it snapped right in half!) NEW: Jesse Malin - The Fine Art of Self Destruction, Virginia Coalition - Rock and Roll Party, Brendan Benson - Lapalco 
     
    
</post>
<date>18,February,2003</date>
<post>

     
      PART 1 ok, this was all out of order, now its in order.... Well well well, not even sure where to begin....one of the best weekends ever is coming to an end....and I still consider this Monday night as a part of the weekend since the Blizzard of Oh Three has kept me captive inside... and of course keep in mind that i have no idea who is reading these and it pains me to have not be as detailed :-D  Aurora and I had the pleasure of using a Durango during the trip, in which I quickly named the "Go Go Durango".  I refrained from using an Aussie accent.  And after all this time we are still speaking to each other and she hasn't killed me yet, haha.  We stop on the way up to Harrisburg for coffee and pizza.  Coffee and cigarettes (besides music) are our main addictions and we defnitely could not have survived the weekend without them.   "Cigarettes and chocolate milk These are just a couple of my cravings Everything it seems I like's a little bit stronger A little bit thicker, a little bit harmful for me" rw So we make it to the Hilton without getting lost, which is an incredible feat.  Finding parking, on the other hand, was more adventurous.  So we go to the check in counter.  As people came in for the conference, they gave out the rooms, so we heard the two counter people discuss where to put us and whether "should we put them there?!?!" to which Aurora and I reply "YES! Put us there!" seeing how whatever they were talking about was sure to be interesting.  So they laugh and gave us room 521.  It's all about the numbers.  We got off on exit 19, which is Aurora's favorite number, and room 521, if you add all together (5+2+1) equals 8, which is my favorite number....yeah.  So we go in, drop our stuff off, do a squeal, jump up and down...oh wait, that was me.  Aurora told me to calm myself.  We go downstairs and in the meantime I call Phil (from Lloyd Dobler Effect...there are going to be a lot of names, so I will do my best to identity them) and I leave a message saying where we are.  I then call everyone else who we know will be there to tell them what room number we are.  Phil then calls back saying that the band is in 520.  No fucking way.  Way.  So we partially unpack and meet up with Mark (from Jonasay) to hit up some shows.  Aurora was unable to get into the Gingerbread Man so we walk back to the Hilton.  She lights up and goes on on why she hates her parents for not getting it on earlier so she can get in places.  So two guys and a girl (wasn't that a tv show...?) come out of the Hilton, talk to us, hands us a CD and tells us to come to their show. I ask if Aurora can get in, they say "sure, she can carry a box".  So off we went into the van.  The kidnappers were Tim, Michael, and Jen from mellowheadblue and were great great people from good old Arlington VA.  Jen boosted up my confidence in possibly moving out there.  It's so very strange how everyone that I have encountered lately has been all connected in some sort of way.  Folded Under, also from Virginia, was next.  Oddly we had just missed Phil there while we waited for Mark outside.  Mark then kidnapped us, and we went to the Firehouse to see Fighting Gravity.  Ran into Michael Sauri (Cinema 8) and surprisingly he wasn't too cool to talk to us ;-) .  Off to the pizza place with scary drunk people.  Then back to the Hilton.  Thursday was low-key since not much was going on.  Go back upstairs and Mark decided to see if LDE was really next door.  Aw yeah they were.  Aurora and I knew that this weekend would definitely not be the same now....A few later, it was Aurora, Mark, Phil, and I talking in our room witnessing Phil's drunkeness.  The night before, the girls of 5208 had decided to make cookies and well, we kinda miscalculated so I had an abundance of baked goods, so I brought them with me.... Ok, my inability to cook deserves its own new paragraph...So we had made cookies and I had brought cookies.  But see...yeah I am not that adept in the kitchen as we all know from my misadventures.  So we didn't have table salt, but I had sea salt.  Hey, it's all the same, right?  Nah....seal salt really doesn't dissolve or mix well, so the whole cookie eating was made entertaining by salt surprises in the cookies.  Ok, back to another paragraph... So yeah we're all just talking being entertained by Phil's devouring and leaving cookie messes everywhere.  It's soon 3 am and Mark leaves and Aurora and I walk him down to the lobby.  She smokes, then we head to the elevators.  On the way, this group approaches us, and it wouldn't have been as intimidating if they weren't two inches from us the whole time.  They won't leave us alone then the security guard come sup, and they still won't leave.  Then Mark comes in to save the day since he left his cell upstairs.  Disaster averted.  Yeah, still around 3am.  Aw yeah, Rusty (LDE) comes to visit.  Then Phil ventures back and uses our bathroom.  We had free trial sized stuff in the bathroom and we noticed that half the mouthwash was gone and wefound it odd that he went to use the bathroom and then the mouthwash disappears.  He wou'dnt fess up ;-) oh but we know.....  4:30am rolls around and we decide we need to get some sleep since the early morning shows are starting to air.  As we're trying to go to sleep we hear knocking from next door (LDE's room) so we do the knocking back and forth thing for an hour.  This was the start of the knocking and the sharing.  The whole weekend 520 and 521 were pretty much just one room and just barged in whenever and used everyones stuff and whenever we wanted to play with the other we just knocked.  or if we wanted to wake them up.  or bother them.  anything really haha. Set the alarm for 11 am but nooooo at 10:30am a certain someones cell phone goes off and all we hear is Rusty.  Damn him and lack of sleep!  Javi (LDE) comes in our room shortly after.  Did we even lock the door that night?!  Wearing the same clothes as the night before.  So the three of us are talking then decide to go downstairs to the lobby.  Aurora and I both still wearing what we wore to bed.  Nothing like looking half dead at noon in the Hilton lobby in our pajamas amidst a bunch of professionals in business attire. Yeah.  For some reason all I carry with me downstairs is my cell and Hilton card.  Not expecting a phone call, Phil calls.  "mirandaaaaaaaaaa can i shower at your place?!".  Go upstairs and he is waiting in hallway.  Hilarious.  Blah Blah Blah, we all get ready then go downstairs for breakfast...I think at this point its about 2 pm.  Food takes too long so we play with breadsticks.  The Real Torino.  They take too damn long so we go to the Neato Burrito.  Ahh yeah, anything named the Neato Burrito has got to be excellent.  And it was.  The Game Players: Aurora, Me, Rusty, Jessica (friend of LDE and we (me and Aurora) kidnapped her as our own), Phil, Jen (LDE promo/merch/all around girl), and Todd (more music group promotions) had a wonderful culinary experience. Haha.  Avoid the nachos and buy lots of Snapple.  Where the hell did Javi escape to?!  After lunch, Rusty, Jessica, Aurora, and I hit up the panels and talked to lots and lots of people and got fun stuff.  It was great meeting some people who I knew by name and not by face.  Signal Fading is a great great resource that everyone should check out and embrace.  Off and on we met up with the LDE crew before we decided that it was time to go back to the rooms.  Impromptu practice session in 520.  Donnie was either asleep or on the phone the whole time.  We love how he never talks unless he is on the phone....Rusty, Jessica, and I go out and get reinforcements....cigarettes, alcohol, and poofs.  The three of us (girls that is) all seemed to have forgotten our poofs at home.  Poofs are a necessity.   Come back, all just chill in our room, talking and getting ready.  I took a shower and notice that the mouthwash is now in the shower.  Phil and the mouthwash...whats the deal?!?! Haha.  See, there is a rule, and usually it's "you can see us before we get ready and after we get ready, but you're not allowed to see the transformation".  Nothing like having everyone come in and out and Rusty and Javi and Rod chilling with us as we're trying to straighten hair, find clothes, and put on makeup.  No offense and no hard feelings, it was just funny :-) Then we leave for the Crowne Plaza... and i must start a new page, break this piece up ;-) PART 2 So yeah.... We leave to go see Capitol Air at the Crowne Plaza who put on a very good performance with their new tunes.  Forgot to mention that Aurora and I ran into CA at the club the night before, so out of 30 venues and 300 bands it was cool to randomly run into them and hang out for a bit.  Matt (CA) had snazzy new blonde hair.  Walk around....we decide to go grab food before the next round of shows, so we find a chinese restaraunt.  So we go in and order and we find it odd that on a Friday night we're the only ones in there.  Oh wait...because it was Valentine's Day.  Oh Geez. Hahaha.  Off to more shows in the cold...... LDE at the Crowne Plaza.  They looked extremely nervous and despite various sound issues sounded good and pulled off some new stuff.  And the duct taped banner stayed up! :-)  There was a huge turnout and I saw some very obvious positive reactions.  Left to go see Jonasay while Aurora checked out more stuff.  Even if it was slightly frightening.... Jonasay played at Gullifty's and of course that venue is always behind and they went on about an hour late.  They looked exhausted.  Oddly Justin had a friend also from DE.  Sound issues for them as well, so hey, at least the MMC was being fair about it ;-).  Stayed to watch Pepper's Ghost from Philly.  Throughout the past few four years I have seen them in various places.  Same sound, same show.  Nothing bad, but nothing great.  A little after 2am I leave for the Hilton again...and this is where the fun begins....after hours and hours of seeing shows and networking, it's time to let loose and have some fun... So I arrive at the Hilton and run up to the room and pass a million people.  Drop the stuff off, grab the camera, the Captain in one hand, Coors Light in the other...it's time to party.  So everyone at the conference is pretty much on floors 4, 5, 6, 8, and 9.  The part was on the fourth floor.  Yes, I said floor.  not rooms, but just in the hallways.  Aurora, Jess, and I were mainly together with April (one of the girls who worked the conference), and Rusty,  Everyone was just in the hallways talking and drinking and having a great time.  All sorts of musicians and industry people and it was wonderful just to have such a basis with everyone.  the party was also in the elevators as we went from floor to floor.  We saw one guy with nipple rings and a banner as a daiper, some canadiens, and a very happy graphic designer among others.  We try to find javi so we yell "Javi" all up and down the floors until we think we hear him and Jess discovers that she hears him in the elevator haha.  The one thing about Javi is everyone knew who he was.  Everyone know who LDE was so that was very awesome for him.  Blah blah blah, hanging out on the floors...then we go upstairs to the 5th floor.  Oh yeah, we all have this on video as well as film.... We run into Rusty and Ken (Heat), and a few other guys then they errupt in some free style hip hop/rapping for a while.  This was awesome.  We sat there for like 30 minutes just watching them create new beats and lyrics.  Spontaneity was the essence of this conference.   Aurora runs back to the room which was right in front of the freestylin' corner and comes back and exclaims that no where else in this hotel smells like weed except for in the 520/521 wing.  That is on film too. Again we wander the floors.  I have the Captain with me.  The Captain, like Andrea L., was a dirty dirty whore.  If anyone had mono in the Hilton, then we all have mono since i think every single person on floors 4 and 5 drank out of the bottle. Around 4:30ish we come back to Aurora and my room....where it's let's see, out of the people we knew...me, Aurora, Jess, April, Ken, Rusty, Javi, Rod, and random guys.  Talking talking drinking drinking blazing blazing.  "JAM SESSION!!!!"  All of a sudden we have guitars, congas, a violin, and amps in our room.  And there is a mini show and jamming and talking and just greatness for a while.   Around 5:30ish Steve, Ken, and Dave from Green To Think come in with Gilligan.  All with some Yuengling.  This is why they are great.  So yeah, we're all chilling then the room starts clearing out around 6:30 except for Aurora, Ken, Steve, and me.  Something about Elephant Games (which Aurora had to remind me of today since I had no idea what she was talking about) haha.  So the four of us spent some time hanging out, making fun, and talking.  Trying to finish up a music crossword puzzle proved difficult.  I havent even looked at it yet, maybe I should to see the craziness.  Saturday morning cartoons starting coming on.  Then we realized that it was past 7 am.  Time flys by when you're having a great time :-).  Haha we told Steve he better watch out on the message board..... ;-) So then they turn off the lights and tuck us in...star sheet!?!? and it's 7:30am.  They leave. Aurora and I talk.  We see that we still have congas, amps, and a violin in our room.  She gets up and needs a cigarette but can't find a lighter.  "all i need is something that fucking makes fire!" bed time : after 7:30 am wake up: 10:30 am thanks to our wonderful neighbors :-P  another blog to finish it up.... PART 3 You should be reading these in order! So we wake up to the bustling of the LDE next door.  Knock knock knock.  We're dead.  And Hilton coffee isn't that strong. Good byes are rough. But off to see some more music. 4 more bands. I think we went babysitting.  Never before have I felt so old.  I hope I never acted like a stupid 15 year old girl at a concert.  Stupid 22 year old girl is more adequate ;-) hahaha.  I love how when Jen, Brit, Holly, and I went to see John Mayer last our ages slowly reverted as the night progressed haha. So needless to say we were cranky, obnoxious, and tired.  But once Graham Colton went on, we awakened. The whole conference all of LDE, except for Donnie I think haha, informed us how Graham Colton is NOasis.  It is too sad to even write.  But as we listened we heard the "inklings" of other songs in some of GC's work.  We won't let the man get us down. Then Justin (Jonasay) comes up to us.  What the heck?!   But GC put on a great show, not as good as Asbury, but a good setlist to an energetic crowd.  And after the show, oddly Spare Dimes was playing. Hung around for a bit, then headed home. SOOOO SLEEPY! Hit the bed around 4 am. Thank you Blizzard of Oh Three.  ok ok ok i have a part 4  So when we checked into the Hilton, they gave us the "Rules and Regulations" this will shortly be on my site (www.mirandaland.com), but in the meantime...   "Posters, flyers and stickers are not permitted to be distributed or placed around the hotel" hahaha yeah right! I think the town of H-burg was definitely littered that weekend and LDE was probably responisble for most of that! Those rebels....   "MMC7 and the Hilton willnot tolerate the defacing, damage, or destruction of the property or premises of the hotel or conference venues" - after the security people realizes that they were outnumbered, they left us alone and ogled at the hoodlum that was occuring. we have a picture of the security people holding broken stuff.   "Use common courtesy towards all hotel guests, especially late at night" - nothing like a good v-day ruckus
     
    
</post>
<date>26,February,2003</date>
<post>

     
      so Jen wrote this today and I figure I will let you read and I will comment on it because it relates to what i was going to write about....  Tuesday, February 25, 2003 Posted 3:41 AM by Jen  Producers learn never to take anything for granted. Having enough people to operate a show for instance, is never a given. Tonight we had five people as crew and two of them had to be on camera at times. You never take equipment working for granted. Even the most simplistic of machines, like a VCR, could spaz out at any moment and leave you as helpless as if you had no cameras at all. They decided to freak out tonight, with 7 minutes until show we discovered they weren't taping video and by luck Whitney noticed a switch was in a different spot on one vcr than the other. However, we couldn't get it to stop playing spastically as if it needed tracking, which we didnt know how to fix. Andy had to go on air and apologize after the commercial breaks for anyone that just had a seizure due to the flashing colors and moving picture. Most importantly, you never take time for granted. I remember Miranda had a blog ages ago saying that since time is such a priority in production that she tended to see her life in a countdown, like she had 38 minutes until class, and 2 to get dressed in and 4 to eat in and so on. Kinda like how Will saw everything as units of time in About a Boy, but I won't go into that again :) I missed the lesson on managing time, but I think I have an appreciation for it of some sort. I hate going to bed because there's so many other productive things I could be doing, but I treasure my 1.29 hours of naptime if I ever get them. An hour wait for food means an hours worth of social time before hand. Maybe its not the time I'm concerned with, maybe its the rationalization of it. I can rationalize not doing anything for that hour because I'm waiting for food. I can rationalize taking a nap because I didn't get much sleep the night before, which I can rationalize by saying staying up late was worth it because I got to write in my blog or talk to Scott or look at that website or play that game that I normally woudln't have had the time for. It sucks to get in an argument with me because I can rationalize anything in the world. I can rationalize the fact that the show didn't go as smoothly as we all would have liked because it wasn't my fault the vcr's turned schizo on us and we worked through the setbacks to put out a good show. Because in a year, no one's going to remember the technical problems we had, they'll just remember the manatee wanted to have sex with Andy, and in the end, that's all that matters...  ------------------------------------------------------------------------ Well first off, my OCD would only allow me to count down anything with a zero or five, but besides that... it is true, working with television and radio, everything is a countdown and it all has to do with numbers.  Everything is perfectly timed.  In all aspects.  It always reminds me of the movie Castaway...."We live by the clock and we die by the clock".  Numbers are all too important to me.  And I guess it just goes with me nature of packing all of my day with something.  Anything.  Epler pointed out that I "don't deal with with being idle" haha.  It's been like that for years.  Sleep is only a luxury because there is just too much to get done, enjoy, and experience.  I rarely know what the word "downtime" means.  I guess that is why I was so glad to actually get that snow storm, my life was forced to take a break.  Which is my perfect segway into my weekend....Don't have any regrets and use up your time to the fullest extent.... So I had some free time from work so Aurora and I decided to go to.....NORTH CAROLINA!   We left rainy cold Delaware at noon on Sunday.  From DE to North Carolina there are ONLY 3 signs for a Wawa at the exit.  And all are around Richmond.  There are two after Richmond.  Sadness!  We get to UNCW to visit Sean around 8:30 that night.  Go out to eat and hang out and fall asleep around 5am.  Aurora and I have been sick since Harrisburg (damn, was that ONLY a week ago!?!?!?!) so the coughing and sneezing and rough voices were quite appealing I'm sure.  We leave for Carrboro in the evening.  Jonasay and Graham Colton.  See we had to go, how often would they be playing together?!?!  I had my voice while Aurora had a sexy rendition of hers which didn't allow her to whisper very well so it was difficult to talk about people or make fun of anyone without being obvious.  But I think we succeeded.  Aside from Michael and his vagueness it was a very fun night.  We'll figure this one out...... Leave at 2 am to come back home to Delaware.  I taught Aurora stick shift so we could switch off.  After stopping at a random gas station filling up on coffee and Mountain Dew, I caught my second wind near Richmond and kept on going.  Cruise control is a very nice thing to have.  Saw the skies change from night to day and it reminded me on how much I love driving and being out while everything else is asleep.  Haha actually the last time one of those instances stick out is after I was at the beach in July with Jonasay and trekking on the beach...odd how everything comes around full circle.  Hit rush hour traffic in DC around 5:30 am.  Two sleeping cranky girls does not make the roadways safe!  Damn people.  Accident in Baltimore.  Made it home by 8 am.   Stuff we listened to on the trip, for your inquisitive mind: Beatles, Jesse Malin, Jonasay, Brendan Benson, Howie Day, Virginia Coaltion, Green to Think, Better Than Ezra, Pat McGee Band, ok, i forget the others...grrrr 1030 miles...45 hours...whew! 
     
    
</post>
<date>23,February,2003</date>
<post>

     
      chicks flicks and pizza  that somes it up...though we never got around to the movie :-)  Brittany, Aurora, Whitney, Karen, and I got to finally hang out outside of the television studio and catch up and relax.  Haven't heard that word for a while.  I swear the conversations we get into.  And its great to see how such different people can get a long so well and have a great time.  Though we're all sick and tired and worn out and water logged, we kept it going till the wee hours of the morning.  In a few hours I will be heading off to North Carolina.  I'm sure the misadventures will land up on here.  Last night hung out with Melissa, Rick, and Chris at the East End.  The good old East End.  Definitely one of my favorite places in Newark.  Didn't think I drank that much, till I came home and hung out with natalie.  See Cari later on... "so did you have fun last night?  All i heard was a "woo" from you when you walked in and I knew it was a good night.  Then I rolled over and went back to bed". argh...it's times like this that makes my impending move to DC seem so hard.  In time answers will come....  But now, time to sleep this sickness away!
     
    
</post>
<date>12,March,2003</date>
<post>

     
      I love the fishes 'Cause they're so delicious Gone Goldfishin'!  sorry had to do it.....
     
    
</post>
<date>11,March,2003</date>
<post>

     
      I found the two greatest food products on Earth. Ever.  EVER. Go Bananas Snapple Juice Beverage  Pop Secret Honey Butter Popcorn. And you know what the glorious thing about the Snapple is!? That I have only found it in various Wawa's....Philly...Newark...Virginia.   Wawa is wonderful in so many ways.  For one...the vast assortment of Snapple.  Free ATM.  Cheap-o gas.  Coffee.  Clean bathrooms.  Wawa is most definitely the Mecca of every trip.  The southern most Wawa is right outside of Rishmond.  See, you get a little frightened because for a while, you do not see signs for Wawa off of 95, then right before Richmond, there is one.  Then you get back on 95 and once you thought you would be leaving Wawa until your arrving trip, there are three more after Richmond.   You see how often I drive.
     
    
</post>
<date>11,March,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Aurora says this: "I think i'm getting stupider.  It's the station; they always said Television kills brain cells....Watching television is like standing near a microwave, and working at a station is like getting into the microwave" I spent 14 hours today working, for the most part, on television related activity.  We ended the night off right by getting our usualy Margherita's pizza and watching tv and talking.  Margherita's is hands down the best pizza ever.  Screw you corporate pizza.  And again, after spending hours at the tv station, we find ourselves still talking about...mostly...television.  It's a sick sick cycle.   And it's bitter cold outside.  Damn you Spring, get here quicker.  We all pile into the car after and sat on my ice cubes of seats.  Aurora told Brittany to sit up staright because then it would be as if she was dancing to the music and not really shivering.
     
    
</post>
<date>10,March,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Wow, Brittany has been so good about blogging everyday.  While I, on the other hand, am not as diligent.   Saturday was exciting.  Brittany made a new word....she claimed her arms and back hurt from all this "IKEtasticness".  You and your dirty mind, we're talking about filming. Friday night Brittany and I ordered pizza and watched the U2 Elevation tour DVD and caught up with all of "projects". "I can't live with or without you..." wow. I have such an awesome crew working on Center Stage.  And I bet you are all wondering how Saturday turned out. We were to film Ike (www.ikeonline.net) at the Northstar bar in Philly for their cd release party.  We usually have a van or a Liberty or a Durango to haul all of our gear in.  Not this time, I was notified that all vehicles that we usually use were taken, so time to use Aurora's Cherokee again.  Last time we packed that thing up was the Lloyd Dobler Effect show.  So Aurora and I woke up at the crack of dawn...ok, ok, ten am is  really  early!  We head out of Newark for Murderkill to pick up the Cherokee.  Yes, Aurora technically lives in Murderkill ;-).   I swear I need to grab hold of my anxiety.  We loaded up with everything we needed and headed over to Wendy's for the ritualistic prefilming dinner.  Let me introduce the players...Aurora, Brittany, Eduardo, Epler, Rob, and myself.  Jen and Scott were to meet us at the venue.  After the slight panic of me not having my glasses...do I ever remember everything...we hit the road to PA.  Brit and I listened to U2 on the way up and talked about her bluntness and honesty.  I give her so much credit and she has my utmost respect for blatantly telling a certain someone how she feels and what she thinks.  So many people are so hesitant.  Way to go Brittany. I think time stopped while we were driving to Philly because we got there in about 30 minutes, a half hour before we needed to be there.  I don't think going 95 on 95 had anything to do with it.  Got to the venue and loaded in with record time.  Things were going all too smoothly for me to be unconcerned haha.  Epler stayed at the venue to sleep while the five of us (Rob, Eduardo, Aurora, Birttany, and me) went to find a Wawa.  Oh come on, you couldn't expect a roadtrip without a Wawa stop could you?!  Coffee and subs later, we were waiting in the Cherokee while we watched Jen and Scott drive past us 5 times.  Finally we met up at the venue.   We had about an hour to kill and we were parked on a shady street in Philadelphia.  It was too cramped in the Cherokee so we loiter outside on 27th Street.  brittany was scared so she stayed inside the vehicle.  She decided she wanted to join us, but when she opened the door, the alarm went off, with all of Philly's finest to witness.  Nothing like bringing attention to ourselves.  So 7 of us are cold and all want to fit inside the Cherokee now so we unflod the seat and climb in. I can't belevie we sat like that for almost an hour.  Out of all the random conversations that occured, Eduardo's was the best... Brittany mentioned that in the Census, Hispanics were considered "caucasion" and were not such a minority anymore and stats show that Hispanics will soon be the majority.  Eduardo then pipes in saying he agrees.  He said that they are such devout Catholics and do not beleive in birth control.  Also the young drinking age and cluture also contribute to the rising Hispanic numbers and that they are slowly taking over and to watch out.  He was quite proud.  It was hilarious. So we go and film to a nicely packed Northstar Bar.  The production went so very well and I am so proud of everyone working on it.  It meant the most when I saw a crowd watching my monitors rather than the stage. Stuck around for a little bit after the show, then loaded up and headed out.  Missed the exit for 95 and took a nice little tour of Philly.  A group of guys in tuxedos ran past my car, then turned around and blew kisses at Brittany and I.  What was going on?!!? It was oddly strange.  Then in Newark, the same thing happened again.  It was oddly weird.  Not bad, just funny.  Aurora calls me up, she is still right behind me, and asks what the heck Brit and I were doing haha.  Then I almost hit someone. Everyone invloved in the production was great, from the crew to the venue to the band to the management.  Thank you.   
     
    
</post>
<date>03,May,2003</date>
<post>

     
      And this past weekend...Dewey Beach style.....but i have to go work in the record store so I can support my lifestyle, so I wil catch up on blogging 
     
    
</post>
<date>03,May,2003</date>
<post>

     
      And the next weekend....Jonasay played at the Logan House.  So the crew all comes and a good time is had by all.  I swear these would be longer if I actually wrote them on time!  Key players: me, Michelle, Nate, Karen, Tim, Jesse, Wade.....  Upstairs downstairs drinks upstairs shots downstairs.  Whew.  There was one victory...I think this is the first time I have came home from the Logan House remembering how I got home and not throwing up.  yay.  Hang out with the guys after.  Found Mark after he disappeared and we watched "the others" get thier mack on.  Entertaining.  We leave.  Justin and Mike crashed at my place since they were playing up in Philly the next night.  the guitar was busted out, as well as some gymnastics action.  Too much to even write.  I threw away piles of beer cans in the morning.  And i think Justin is th eonly one who drank them haha.  Wake up, eat breakfast at noon at the East End.  Drama at the breakfast table.  Show is now acoustic.  Problem solved, on the road to Philly.  Stuck in traffic.  I'm sitting in the back of the van and I look up and I see a Green To Think sticker above my head.  Small world.  Not that many band stickers in their van, just venues, so go figure.  We were heading to NXNW in Philly for their show with Sister Hazel.  Cute place.  Suzanne and I walked around fun filled Germantown Ave.  Show starts, took a bunch of pictures (which did not turn out AT ALL since my battery died).  Head out with Brooke and a drunken Mark.  :-) Go to a Wawa, of course.  Cause a ruckus, of course.  Get lost, of course.  Head home.  Only to take a "nap" then head to DC the next morning.  
     
    
</post>
<date>03,May,2003</date>
<post>

     
      A few weeks after that, the Center Stage crew went to Philly to film Green to Think at Doc Watson's.  I lose the van keys, multiple times.  But we do our usually Wendy's run then 95.  Scott and Marissa were able to join us this time and witness the chaos that is my life haha.  We had to park the vans behind the venue, which wouldn't have been a problem if the driveway wasn't 5 feet wide and our vans being a whopping 5 foot 1 inch wide.  but we made it thru no problems....yet.  We load in and set up in record time.  Damn I love to CS crew :-)  We filmed an awesome show, despite some sound difficulties.  We had a pretty hilarious interview.  Either they clam up or spill all, and we defnitely got the better end of the bargain :-)  Of course I couldn't hear a damn word they said, so I just waited till they all looked at me.  A lot of vagueness was revealed...hmmmmm.    But you all will have to wait till its done and airs :-) So we head home.  After about 20 minutes of trying to get OUT of the narrow driveway.  head home.....then Aurora hits a critter.  I swear, is nothing sacred!?  We broke a van and there was puffs of fur and blood on the bumper.  No one would let me film it.   But all in all a great night, from good times to GTT to good friends to road trips.
     
    
</post>
<date>03,May,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Hahaha so in addition to that last story, both Lauren and I had remembered that date, April 5 as being the PMB show in Newark three years before.  It was like a reunion.  Ok, how many times have I writen that!?!? So I think her and I were the only ones who remember that whole day starting with traant, then the parking lot, then Deer park then the parking lot again.  And beer,  beer through a straw...beer in a pitcher...beer being dumped on people......damn time flies.
     
    
</post>
<date>03,May,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Let's see what else happened...oh yeah, so a few days later....  Aurora and I drive up to Fords, NJ to see Finch do an instore at Vintage Vinyl.  We get there and its swamped, so we decide not to stay.  Pat McGee Band was playing in Princeton which was on the way home, so we decided to stop there as well.  took us about an hour to find out where they were playing, but we found it and snuck in.  Chardy found me immediately and it was bittersweet.  And Lauren!!!!!  Lauren is great, I met her a few years ago at Ursinus.  her and I will ALWAYS be PMB dorks.  She stood next to me at a show a few years ago and we started talking and we realized that we had both gone to UD.  So we started going to some shows together.  the famous PMB Deer Park stop involved Lauren as well ;-) If you see any pictures on my site with myself in it, more than likely, Lauren is in them as well.  We have run into each other occasionally in the past year, but hadn't scheduled any shows.  Ironically she is good friends with Michelle's boufriend Jason and we all last spent Homecoming together.  So Lauren was tehre and she snuck in too and it was odd.  So we go up and I swearl it was like Ivy Girls Gone Wild.  Princeton girls should not drink.  Ever.  because they cannot hold their alcohol and they become lesbianesque and bothersome.  I guess i am being hypocritical, but for PMB shows, I always LOATHED the drunken assholes at the shows and could never understand why people would want to drink so much at the show and not enjoy it.  But of course, if you are a loyal reader and have read about my escapades at the Logan House, you see that I am being contradictory.  I do stupid shit, but I don't think i have ever been so shitfaced that I am an utter asshole.  or at least, when I am, haha, i am not in the front few rows of a show.  I am in the back not bothering the people up front.  There, that being said, i wil continue.  And they ended with "Where the Streets have No Name".  it was amazing and I ate my words.  there has been a lot of word eating lately.  I didn't exactly boycott PMB, but the change in music, the subtraction of AL and Johnathon and the alteration of the 'crowd" has changed the whole scene for me.  But man, I have missed it and I realized it then.  A lot of me has been involved with various aspects of PMB...from hitting the road to bars to the music.  it's defnitely been an influence on the past few years.  i can't even begin.....  So yeah we had to jet out of there and be in Baltimore by 9 pm because I was being merch bitch for Army of Me that night at Fletchers.  i can't even tell you how many times I have eaten a Wawa dinner while speeding down 95.  i swear, those two weeks, 95 was definitely my bitch.  Good times at Fletchers.  Army of Me and 33 West were really cool.  Head home because I think I worked the next day.  I can't remember.
     
    
</post>
<date>03,May,2003</date>
<post>

     
      ::::::::::::Spring Break 2003::::::::::::::::::::: (end of March, beginning of April) was in Maine.  Wooooo.  So this is the first time in YEARS that I had a full week off from anything...riding competitions, work, etc.  So Aurora and I had decided that since everyone else was heading south, that we would head north.  I had wanted to go back and visit Boston and New Hampshire while she had family in Maine who she wanted to see.    OH WAIT, the night before Aurora, Fin, Dave, and I drove to DC to see Lloyd Dobler Effect and Jonsay headlineline at the 9:30 club.  Aurora and I had been looking forward to this date as well as avoiding it for a while, since the Millenium Music Conference probably.  haha nothing bad, but we thought it would be odd for both entities since so much was divulged at the MMC.  But a good time was had by all. We got to see a lot of the freinds we had made at the MMC and it was a mini reunion.  Ahhhh...the MMC...what a great weekend....(see blogs from mid february haha) ok, back :-)  sorry , mind wandered....  So yeah, Jen and Jess were there and it was great fun near the front.  Good shows all around.  Thank God Aurora was DD that evening.    OH WAIT!  Right before that show, LDE played at the Logan House.  Good old Logan House.   Logan Hosue is the second best place, right next to East End.  So again, it was a reunion at the Logan House.  A bunch of my friend who I haven't seen in a while came out to that show.  Plus we got Aurora in.  Damn, now that I look back at it, that was a crazy night.  I think I utterly embarrassed myself and Melissa and Rick were asked to never come to the Logan Hosue again.  Let's see, who was there....myself, Aurora, Nate, Michelle, Jason, Christina, Rick, Melissa, Ali, Gabe, Marty, Fin, Bob, Rob, Eric, Beth, Karen, and Christina (part 2).....damn, we packed the place.  We pregamed at the apartment then headed up.  Aurora got in, yay.  Nothing like back doors :-)   I had a drink that was more like a big shot and I think I should have been done there.  but noooo.....not when you're with the LDE boys.  Rusty bought me shots.  Shots with lots of stuff in it.  I think I remember dancing.  i remember creepy guys.  I remember having Fin and Rick and Eric save me.  Upstairs downstairs upstairs downstairs.  Sitting on the stage with Phil and not being able to get up.  More shots.  Gabe then got kicked out of Logan House for drunkeness but he escaped back upstairs for more shots, so Kamikazes all around.  Then he got hauled off and Melissa and Rick and Gabe were told to never come back.  (we're going back tonight! haha)  I think the music stopped around this time.  I dodn't remember anyone leaving.  I remember being "backstage" on the "balcony".  Then as we were leaving...................yeah.  Aurora told me days later what i said.... And I think Mark had gotten another drunk phone call...?  Oh no, Aurora had my phone and called him.  OH because it was right after on stage, Phil goes to begin another song, looks over to where I was and says "I'm Mark Williams from the band Jonasay" and I think he began Gone Away.  Only two of us there got it, but it was hilarious.  There's this thing where the two of them, when they call me, will sya that they are the other , and I swear if i didn't have caller id I wouldn't know the difference half the time.  haha.  Aurora and my mother have gotten into that as well.  But I can tell the female voices apart from the male voices ;-)  But phil is getting more multi faceted.  he has stepped into the shoes of Graham Colton while leaving me messages.    Oh yeah, so back to ...um...spring break.... So we decide to head north.  and at the 9:30 club show Michael said that they were playing up in orono, which is right near where we were staying.  Fancy that.  So Aurora and I left on Sunday, a mere 4 hours after we go to bed from the 9:30 show.  Hit a Wawa then the highway.  Good tunes in the player and good times in the car.  We hit up Vintage Vinyl, this really awesome record store in Jersey.  Finally found a Ryan Adams album I was looking for.  We almost got shot at a rest stop in Connecticut.  Aurora was at the ATM then we hear a Middle Eastern man fight with some NYC kids.  All you see are parent covering up their kids heads and running.   It was hilarious, in a way....  Hit rain and snow.  Stayed at Aurora's cousin's place at UNE.  We ordered Papa johns....we were STARVING.  So after waiting hours for this pizza that was way late and way expensive, we paid part in change.  he wasn't pleased.  The next day we hit up New Hampshire and I played photographer.  Before we had left, Aurora had seen a license plate that said "Oh Maine" so we felt it necessary to shout that out every so often.  OHHHH MAINEEEEE......that was Tuesdays fun.  There was an inch or two of snow on the ground.  And we saw steel dinisaurs in some guys yard.  Oh trust me, this is all on film.  Then we went to U of ME to see Jonasay play.  After the show I had wanted to head home, I figured we were already up and that the 10 hour drive woul dbe more doable at night with no one on the road.  Aurora had wanted to stay and wake up super duper early.  We talked and figured we would head back to DE then.  So we were all talking before we're leaving.  And Justin is staring off iinto space.  or we thought he was.  (sorry , have to do it)  Aurora has on this jacket.  With pockets.   And her hands are in the pockets.  Then after Justin is silent for minutes, we hear "it's likea puppet show" as he is staring at her hands in her pockets.  But it doesn't look innocent.  Then we all follow his eyes and realize where he is staring.  Nothing can be said.  The Aurora says "yeah, they sometimes do that".  Justin tries to save himself, but fails ;-) And all was saved.  I missed the context of this, but Mike and Aurora apparently will always have Maine. And something about doing it like lobsters.  Then we kidnap Mark and head home.  We go and get gasat this place that was pretty far away from anything.  Before we had left we got the lecture from Aurora's dad about losing keys and how I should have a spare set.  Has anyone clued this man into how often I lose keys!?!  Well, I jump out to get some coffee because its 1 am and we have 10 hours ahead of us.  Aurora jumps out to smoke.  Mark gets out to pump gas.  After a few minutes in the gas mart thingy we come back to find the car locked.  The keys are on the drivers seat.  The spare set is in my bag.  And Mark locked the doors to protect our stuff.  Fun in Maine.  So after fooling around in the mart thing, we have to call a locksmith.  He saved the day.  Who does that 600 miles from home??!??!?!?!?!?! So back on the road, time to head out.  We stop to see Megan again at UNE.  Driving driving driving.  Amazingly I made it from Maine to NJ.  Without getting a ticket from the hordes of cops we passed.  Listen to some good tunes, had good conversation.  pretty damn tired.  We all hadn't showered or changed in a lot longer than what we should have.  Got to DE around 11 am.  Damn, we drove all night.  Aurora leaves to go home, while Mark and I explored Newark.  Went to Rainbow then ate lunch at Homegrown.  Then we took the Cabrio out for a spin to Towson.  first time this year the top was off.  Word.  Got to Brooke's and plpayed with the horses.  then to the mall.  then ate Chinese.  then to a record store.  Shit, we haven't slept yet!?  Then off to DC then back.  I slept FOREVER. WHEW
     
    
</post>
<date>10,May,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Well, I don't even know where to begin. Last night was a great night.   I can't even begin to write right now on how much PMB has been a part of my life the past few years.  If you know me, then you would know, but if you don't then you will read about that all later.  But yes, PMB played an outside show in Newark last night.  Lauren and her boyfriend came down for the show and Karen, Melissa, and I ran into everyone there.  It was just a good time.  It was also like an STN reunion which was freaky haha. I like how Public Safety was there to ensure there was no alcohol and nearly everyone there had sports bottles (see previous blog) or juice bottles in hand.  It was just great to be there with my closest freinds singing away to PMB at an outdoor night show.  It sounded great and the atmosphere was wonderful.  I don't know if my friends enjoyed me serenading them though.  ;-) Having PMB play in Newark in one of my last weekends here was a good sendoff.   Off to Logan House!  Karen, Melissa, Aurora and I trke up 95 to LH to see LDE play next.  In the 15 minute carride we decorates Karen's car with pornographic images and Aurora and I had a conversation with each other while both on Phil's voicemail.  We go in and and a good time was had by all :-)  They played a good set of mostly all originals so yay.  Michelle and Jason and Tim made it down so it was great hanging out with them as well.  And LDE Jenn was there so we made her dance with us :-)  But all in all a great night at the LH once again.  And damn those boys.  I swear every time I see them I end up not feeling so well............. I love LH's backstage, its more like the balcony.  At least no one fell down the stairs this time.  I met Phil's family and think I confused them all.  Stole Phil's visor and someones sunglasses.  Ended up with black stuff all over me.  Gave Phil back his hat, but came home with another hat somehow.  A huge conversation was had about the 9:30 club.....see now there is a debate on who didn't talk to who at the 9:30 club gig they did a ways back.  Dammit for being 5 against 2.    Damn time for work, I will finish this blog when I get back FROM PETE YORN TONIGHT!!
     
    
</post>
<date>09,May,2003</date>
<post>

     
      Well, I don't even know where to begin. Last night was a great night.   I can't even begin to write right now on how much PMB has been a part of my life the past few years.  If you know me, then you would know, but if you don't then you will read about that all later.  But yes, PMB played an outside show in Newark last night.  Lauren and her boyfriend came down for the show and Karen, Melissa, and I ran into everyone there.  It was just a good time.  It was also like an STN reunion which was freaky haha. I like how Public Safety was there to ensure there was no alcohol and nearly everyone there had sports bottles (see previous blog) or juice bottles in hand.  It was just great to be there with my closest freinds singing away to PMB at an outdoor night show.  It sounded great and the atmosphere was wonderful.  I don't know if my friends enjoyed me serenading them though.  ;-) Having PMB play in Newark in one of my last weekends here was a good sendoff.   Off to Logan House!  Karen, Melissa, Aurora and I trke up 95 to LH to see LDE play next.  In the 15 minute carride we decorates Karen's car with pornographic images and Aurora and I had a conversation with each other while both on Phil's voicemail.  We go in and and a good time was had by all :-)  They played a good set of mostly all originals so yay.  Michelle and Jason and Tim made it down so it was great hanging out with them as well.  And LDE Jenn was there so we made her dance with us :-)  But all in all a great night at the LH once again.  And damn those boys.  I swear every time I see them I end up not feeling so well............. I love LH's backstage, its more like the balcony.  At least no one fell down the stairs this time.  I met Phil's family and think I confused them all.  Stole Phil's visor and someones sunglasses.  Ended up with black stuff all over me.  Gave Phil back his hat, but came home with another hat somehow.  A huge conversation was had about the 9:30 club.....see now there is a debate on who didn't talk to who at the 9:30 club gig they did a ways back.  Dammit for being 5 against 2.    Damn time for work, I will finish this blog when I get back FROM PETE YORN TONIGHT!!
     
    
</post>
<date>09,May,2003</date>
<post>

     
      I have decided to begin a new topic on this online journal...."Lessons I Have Learned Today" I will begin this thread with today's story and follow that up with a story from yesterday that I apparently did NOT learn my lesson and repeated again today....  Story from today: To avoid a mess in the kitchen, do not mix soda and alcohol in a water bottle then put your finger over the spout and proceed to roll the bottle to mix the two ingredients.  Because when you remove your finger from the spout, it will be like volcano eruption.  Tonight is yet another Logan House night if you have not guessed already.  And there are two reasons for drinking prior to going.  One, thats a few less drinks to actually purchase, therefore saving money.  And two, by pre-gaming, you do not lose valuable gaming time at the venue.  So yes, that is why I was mixing soda and alcohol in my Nike water bottle and thought it would be a good idea to roll it.  Not a good idea.  Story from yesterday that was repeated today:  When you pour pasta from a bag into a pot on the stove, do not spill any noodles on the red hot burner.  They will catch on fire.  Yesterday I dropped a noodle on the burner and did not know it until the smoke detector went off and I found a little flame coming from the noodle on the burner.   Now today, I made pasta again, and again, I spilled a noddle onto the burner.  the smoke detector did not go off, but again, there was flammage in the kitchen.  So yes, do not spill noodles on the burner.  You will cause a fire. 
     
    
</post>
<date>08,May,2003</date>
<post>

     
      I think Mr. Fish has a fungus.  Mr. Fish has a white spot on his back and is swimming a bit off kilter.  He has also been chilling in the plant.  Usually he doesn't chill in the plant, he prefers the back corner, but no, he was all up in the plant's business today.  This is my interpretation of Mr. Fish:  })</post></Blog>