<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>30,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       NEWater   Ok, that's just gross.   Another potentially gross thought:   What if atype of body fluid found in the pool is excreted by guys only?? (a la the movie 'y tu mama tambien'??) now that's NEWater with added nutrients in it.  Ever thought why the pool juice tastes salty? You can thank those who decided to blow their noses or clear their throats when they're swimming. 
      
</post>
<date>29,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       General Knowledge Update   Know your phobias Part one:  Lachanophobia - fear of vegetables Ephibiphobia - fear of teenagers Aulophobia - fear of flutes  Disclaimer: Simply put to swamp your already loaded brain with yet more useless information 
      
</post>
<date>29,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      Woo Hoo...and the weekend has just did its infamous disappearing act once more.... Here's my thought for the day (came up with it awhile ago..) Went for the Splash fest mass swim just now...whilst swimming, incidentally ingested a couple of gulps of pool juice...and this thought crosses my mind: Man, I'm like swimming in NEWater!!!! (get it? The pee and all other human excretions and body fluids coupled with good ol' tap water)  Yech.
      
</post>
<date>29,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       Quote for the week   Something to lift your spirits when you're down. [this is not the quote]  Now this is the quote:  "If you're going to do something tonight that you'll be be sorry for tomorrow morning, sleep late."   Henry Youngman 
      
</post>
<date>26,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       More Useless Information   Something new i learnt on fri. How to make soda lime or lime soda... (does it actually matter??)  Recipe: A  LOT  of soda.  A  BIT  of lime concentrate.  You wouldn't want to try soda lime that was 1/4 lime concentrate and 3/4 soda. 
      
</post>
<date>26,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       Clarification regarding the 'annoying neighbor' saga   With reference to the previous news about the attendant wanting to open the door with the master key, well, that information was inaccurate. It seems that Mdm Wong, after knocking repeatedly, wanted to unlock the door but found the door to be already unlocked. [gasp!] However, since she couldn't go in by herself (may be due to regulations  privacy), she asked this writer's roommate to be the witness. However, when she came back to the door, she found the door to be locked, which was impossible unless someone was already in the room but refused to open the door.  Seems that BU was dumber than it was thought originally.   Updates: As of last night, Mr BU and his Ms are still living together in the room. One wonders how long before they'll get into another mess again.....
      
</post>
<date>25,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       something on a similar note....   was walking ard halfnaked in my shorts at PGP (not black undies, besides, my fav color is blue)... to the toilet to bathe.... when this gal suddenly appeared from the pantry (which is located beside the toilet for some obscure architectural reason which evades my common knowledge of hygiene)... wld have walked rite into her if not for my superhuman reflexes n dextirity (who noes if dat was the true purpose of her diabolical plan??)  both of us got a fright when we saw each other (for different reasons i shld guess... me, for seeing a gal appearing from behind a wall in a place where only guys ar allowed... her, for seeing erm... well, i wldnt noe wat features gals notice abt halfnaked guys 1st)  anyway, after recovering from our respecive initial shocks, both of us juz side-stepped each other n went abt our own business... me to shower... her, to ambush another unsuspecting male??  on hindsight, im beginning to tink dat i may have been on the losing end of this encounter, considering dat the gal isnt dat chio.... not dat im cute myself, but hey, i was the victim caught in a state of undress here!  wunder wat wld happen if i went lurking ard the female levels n bumped into one in her underwear?  hmm......
      
</post>
<date>24,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      And there you have it,  JUSTICE IS SERVED!!!  No more BUs for you, but i sure face pastel colored ones here....  
      
</post>
<date>24,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       COMMENTARY   This writer would like to add that she's VERY Glad that BU was caught. She's sick and tired of having to look at BU (the item, and not the man) hanging on the hook in her bathroom.  Future improvements to be expected: 1) No BU in sight 2) No pubic hair lying all over the floor 3) Possibly a new neighbor(?) [one can only hope..]  This writer woud like to say that her dislike for BU and Co stems not from intolerance of neighbors, but from the general inconsiderate behaviour that she has had to put up with ever since the start of the school year. She has no complaints about neighbors who let their respective boyfriends co-habitate as long as they do not infringe on anyone's privacy ie no walking in the bathroom with just underwear, thus, making both himself and the neigbor uncomfortable. Actually, the writer's dislike is not so much for BU but for his Ms, due to incidents (mentioned in previous postings) that occurred. 
      
</post>
<date>24,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       BLACK UNDIES CAUGHT   Latest development in the 'annoying neighbor' saga.......  Today, hall officers caught Mr Black Undies, henceforth to be called BU, in the room without the presence of his female counterpart. The incident occurred at approximately 9.45am when hall attendant, let's call her Mdm Wong, came round to hand hostel forms to hostelites. She was persistently pounding on abovementioned neighbor's door but still no reply. After handing the forms to this writer and her roommate, she asked said writer's roommate to witness that she was going to open the door using the master key, but however, found the door to be latched from the inside. This meant that someone was inside! After not being able to deny his existence (cos BU was too dumb to hide in the bathroom and let Mdm Wong come in), he opened it and she handed in the form. After complaining a little to this writer's roommate (about a guy being in the room, not allowed, blah blah blah), she promptly went to the hall office to let the officer know about it.   [here comes the fun part]  Hall officer, A, knocked on the door and gave BU a good, and well-deserved lecture about how guys aren't allowed in female hostel room. (This writer couldnt' get the full conversation cos if she were to stand at the door, that would be too blatant. So the best she could do was to eavesdrop from the vicinity of her own room) Officer A wanted letters to be written by both Mr and Ms BU, who wasn't in the room at the time. Also mentioned that complaints have been made about the room regarding illegal squatters, MALE illegal squatters, that is. (This writer assumes it might have been the roommate who moved who lodged the complaint, cos it couldn't have been the writer herself.) Lecturing continued for about 15-20 mins, which is heck of a long time, cos BU was trying to explain himself. Officer A was joined by Officer B soon after. (The writer knows this cos she couldn't resist taking a peek. This was done tastefully by throwing out the garbage) The entire lecture was in essence about illegal squatters, letters that need to be written, threats of barring Ms BU from staying in halls, and the absurdity of the situation cos BU said that Ms BU gave him the key before she went to class and that he had never stayed there before. Luckily, Hall officers A  B had enough brains to know that the story was a load of Bull.   to be continued.... 
      
</post>
<date>24,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       Hall Life Part (aww heck, who's counting?)   Let me add on to what Es written on hall life.   1) You get guys who rollerblade down the corridor and play hockey at the same time at 1 am in the friggin morning! 2) Girls who love to get chased and tickled down the corridor shrieking as they run at 1 am in the friggin morning!   BLACK UNDIES ALERT  Spotted: A pair of black undies.  Gender: Unknown Place: In Moondancer's bathroom (yet again) Propose to burn it....  [evil laughter]
      
</post>
<date>23,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       MUNDANE INFO #101   Just realised something as I was chatting with Mr Lester Bangs on icq. I'm the only non-scholar on my own website!!! hahaha..   Fluke: MOE Teaching Scholar Lester: NUS Undergrad Scholar Es Ch: PSC Scholar  Hey, at least there's some form of standard here on the site. 
      
</post>
<date>23,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       Today' s General Knowledge Program, proudly brought to you by the b***h of rant: Do You Know this???   Topic of interest: Ear hair and Nose hair (since we remain on the topic of head hair and pubic hair, we shall continue... haha)  Well, how does it arise for old men - the ah peks with the wobbly walking canes? Basically, it's a manifestation of the law of conservation of hair. When males were young, the manly fluid filled their whole being, but as they got older a lot of it boiled off. By now it doesn't even reach the bottom of the old brainpan. The sad result is that hair grows in their nose and ears rather than on top of their head. The plus side is that they can now watch Pocahontas with the grandkids without thinking, "Whoa, nice rack."  Some findings: ( Excessive hair is called hypertrichosis. ( Even less is known about hairy noses than hairy ears. ( The tragus is the pointy projection on the front side of your ear opening. Interestingly, tragus can also mean any of the hairs growing at the entrance to the ear. So I guess what most old men get is a bad case of tragus on the tragus. (i.e, hair growing on front of ear) (I bet hair on the tragus is what's really important, since smart men have it too, like Einstein..geez, was he hairy or what? figure it, the amount on his head's a pretty good gauge.. (You can get hairy ears as a result of using minoxidil (some hair growth tonic) and, boy, does it look gross. DO NOT TRY UNLESS YOU WANT HAIRY EARS, BUT HOWEVER, A HAIRY CHEST NOT UNLIKE DR. EVIL(yummy....) and AUSTIN POWERS IS VERY WELCOME~~~~ ( Some great mind is going to have to do a lot of this work over if we're going to come to any firm conclusions about ear and nose hair. ( But it's not going to be me.  This one's to make up for the weekend. Plus website of the week:  urlLink Mummies! 
      
</post>
<date>23,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       Today's General Knowledge Program, proudly brought to you by the b***h of rant: Do You Know this???   If dieting was anything on your minds....how many calories are there in the average male ejaculation?  Answer: Start by assuming that male ejaculate is roughly equivalent in nutritional composition to raw egg white (a safe assumption, and bloody well tastes the same, SO I"M TOLD!!!!  =0) Heh Heh Heh ). The normal size egg is about 35 cubic centimeters in volume and contains about 14 calories and 3 grams of protein. the normal size ejaculation is about 5 cubic centimeters, or one-seventh the volume of an egg white; figure it, therefore, to contain about one-seventh the nutrients--approximately 2 calories and .1 gram of protein. Of course, you'll have to adjust those figures if you're talking about Jumbo Size (eggs, that is)......  Ah, the thirst for knowledge--it knows no bounds......happy dieting, folks!
      
</post>
<date>23,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
        Hostel life as I see it: A Tale from One who Has stayed for 2 years and is Still living it out  1) greatest risk - pple with peculiar habits to the left, right, down (below) and with you...what peculiar habits, one might ask:  &gt; playing extremely loud ear-drum busting music, the kind that forces your poor already overworked heart to throb along with the beat until a heart attack is the next thing on your mind &gt; Watching football/soccer/ESPN in the middle of the f***ing night and shouting like jaybirds to every goal or goal-attempt &gt; Splashing people with water, smacking their groins into pillars, rubbing cake into facial crevices as a birthday tribute  2) Late nights - work begins at midnight. Sleeping at 2 am is a LUXURY. Being able to sleep in quiet and peace is an even rarer commodity.   3) Bugs, creepy-crawlies of varieties possibly not yet recorded in the Museum and Guiness Book of Insects and Insectoids: - worms with wings - bugs that are orange in color - bugs that look like bees and dragonflies at the same time - bugs that don;t fear humans; only the spray gun - bugs that don't die - bugs that keep returning  TO BE CONTINUED....
      
</post>
<date>23,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      And hee haw haw haw, the b***h of rant has arrived ..time to unleash some tattle-tales and opinions...heh heh heh heh heh But first, a website only for the appreciative WLIIA fans:  urlLink http://www.geocities.com/hoedownsite/downloads.html   
      
</post>
<date>23,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       I'm BAAACK   helooooooooooooooo.. i am back, after being MIA for the past week or so. And back by popular demand.....  [Loud voice]  HALL LIFE PART 5   Juicy news coming from Hall 1!   Toilet mate (heh, only in NTU do you get a term called "toilet mate") has moved out! Why? I dunno, but p'haps might be due to the presence of Mr Black Undies. She cleaned out her room last night... and now, Mr and Ms Black Undies have the room to themselves. Heard him in the morning (about 5am) when i woke up. Hahaha.. I think he was bathing or cleaning, I dunno and I frankly don't care. I was tempted to open the bathroom door and scare the shit out of him, but decided not to embarrass myself at the same time.   Toilet is free of hair (from all places) at the moment. ;p  Wildlife status so far: A wasp flew in on Monday morning. It landed on the light fixture and I hit it with a broom after which I couldn't find it anymore. So, I suspect that at this moment, there's a dead wasp somewhere in the room. It can't be alive cos I've not heard it buzzing around. Window is still free from nests of any kind. Thank god for that.   And that's it for HALL LIFE PART 5 [voice fades]
      
</post>
<date>23,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       Wildlife Part 2   lets hear more about mr black undies. makes good fodder for entertaining our otherwise mundane lives
      
</post>
<date>14,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       Queen of the Jungle   heheh... u cld probly film a whole series of wildlife documentaries n air them on national geographic, all from the comfort of ur hostel room.  Who said s'pore doesnt have a rich ecosystem??  Wats Chek Jawa compared to dancing-moon's room? i propose the Ministry of Environment shld preserve the room in its natural state for posterity.  Wld make refreshing debate in parliament abt setting up a new nature reserve, instead of quibbling over price hikes... which occurs regardless of the debates anyway.
      
</post>
<date>13,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       Hall Life part 4   Icky stuff that can occur when staying in an NTU hall.  Firstly, you have horrid neighbors.  Secondly, you have animals that make a home on ur window sill. Yup.. my life isn't going very well nowadays. Just found a huge (well, to me it is) wasp nest on my window. So nicely tucked away, hidden from sight that i wouldn't have noticed it if i didn't happen to look up at my window on my way out. So, decided to spray the insects living in the nest before i knocked down the structure. Now, my corridor smells of insecticide. And guess who helped me clean my mess up? Surprise, surprise, it's my toilet neighbor's boyfriend. Yup, it's mr black undies. Nice enough to offer his help cos he was taking a cigarette break. So back to the insects, I've got remnants of the mud walls on my window pane. WIll have to remove it when i'm more awake. Totally gross. 
      
</post>
<date>13,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       UGH UGH UGH   I'm too pissed to check my bloody grammer.. so don't mind the weird sounding phrases. not thinking straight. 
      
</post>
<date>11,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       NEIGHBORS!   ugh.. neighbors can be such pleasant ppl if u get the right ones... it's really unfortunate if you are stuck with neighbors whom u share a bathroom with. i hate my neighbors.. i really do. i washed the toilets today at 12.30am!! yup, that's right, in the middle of the friggin' night. why, u might ask.. well, it's because, some lame-brained neighbor was either eating in the loo or squashed a bug which attracted a whole generation of red ants to gather round the poor creature or morsel of food. And guess what? They had no sense, ABSOLUTELY no sense to clean the mess up. Not only that, the whole bathroom is littered with hair. Hair from up there, hair from down there... All over the friggin place. They use the shower area and wash their hair. But they don't remove the hair that gathers round the drain and they let it gather, gather and gather some more. Maybe hoping to start a hair exhibition or something. They aren't like Rumplestiltskin who can turn straw to gold. That's head hair, pls don't get me started on pubic hair. Gosh.. how can pubic hair be found near the sink and not in the toilet bowl is beyond my comprehension. What do they do? Scratch themselves silly in the bathroom??? The floor is littered with pubic hair man.. Obviously not as much as head hair, but it's enough to spot when u're standing and not even scrutinising the damn floor. They use up all your toilet roll. I actually have to hide my stash of loo roll cos they use up 1 roll for every 2 days, unless it's their roll that they are using, then it'd wld last longer.. Bunch of freeloaders.. Is it just a typical singaporean thing? Must i stick posters on the wall to remind users to keep the toilet clean? It's supposed to be second nature. Be considerate. Keep the bathroom clean, cos there ain't no maid to do the cleaning everyday. We are in Uni for goodness sake. Where have all the manners gone? All those courtesy campaigns have not done any good at all. UGH. 
      
</post>
<date>11,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       Book Review   hahaa... yucks.... no more gross discussions pls... okok... book review time.... dats IF u ppl have anytime for books other than those u muz mug for exams...  u guys heard of Leon Uris? well, the gd news is hes dead, so its actually possible to catch up n  finish reading all his werks in a limited period of time... not like crichton n sheldon or some other crappy author who writes a new bk every 2 yrs. so, wat does Uris write? basically all his bks ar novels based upon actual historical settings... from the irish struggle of independence... to the ill-fated battle of Gallipoli... n the holocaust.  a gd bk to start wif wld be Redemption (abt irish migrants in New Zealand n the IRA), but neva ever start wif Ruins of God (or isit God of Ruins) cos dats really the last bk he wrote b4 he dieded n it aint as gd as the rest. other werks include Exodus abt the jewish plight in the middle east from 1890s all the way to 1970s... The Haj (on the same topic but from the arab pt of view)... Trinity (if i remember correctly, a sequel to Redemption)... Mila 18 (abt jews surviving the holocaust in a polish ghetto)... QBVII (the most provocative of his bks in my opinion, abt whether the perpetrators of the holocaust were forced into the act of exterminating jews by circumstances).... hmm... dats abt all his bks i remember reading i guess... not often u learn abt history n geopolitics while enjoying a novel ya noe...  happy reading dancing-moon n jester!  =)
      
</post>
<date>10,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       Two cents worth (or any amount you wanna pay for wat i'm saying now)   Brilliant discussion we're having now.... Just gonna nitpick on a coupla stuff.  1) What has tears overflowing from ur eyes got to do with mucus? I thought mucus was the icky green stuff (the color of TJC uniform) tt flows frm the nose (or dose, if u have a cold)? Well, if you're like me, the stupid stuff is just stuck somewhere in the deep recesses of my nose.   2) btw, fluke, it's   LESTER   and not JESTER.   3) Dust, dust!     Clean the house, i must!     OOh, brad pitt, how i lust!     Know wat i need? a bigger bust!  A short poem abt dust, and watever word that rhymes with it. :) I'm the next yeats...  
      
</post>
<date>10,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       The good thing abt sweat n mucus... =/   Perspiration, otherwise known as sweat, is one of many mechanism utilised by the body in the process of homeostasis... ie maintenance of a constant internal bodily environment. wat does sweat do? to keep body temp constant. y we need a constant body temp? cos enzymes function optimally at a temp of 37 C. y do we need enzymes? cos we... oops... out of pt... anyway... sweat when evaporating from the skin removes latent heat from the surface of the body, dats y dogs pant so much... saliva evaporating from the tongue removes latent heat from their bodies which cant sweat.. which explains y dogs have such long tongues, erm, dats if u believe me ;) no sweat means ur body gets hot... which means all ur enzymes cld be destroyed... which means u start frothing at the mouth, aphyxiate n ur muscles go into spasms... then u die after ALOT of pain... hmm... or did i mix it up wif how u die after eating potassium cyanide?  so wat does mucus do?? dat depends on where the mucus is coming from... the mucus lining ur trachea n bronchus or the tears overflowing from ur eyes into the tear ducts.  in my not so professional opinion, based upon a negligible amt of experience in the medical community, i wld say dat jester or watever he calls him/herself actually suffers from the latter. so y does ur eyes keep producing so damn much water they cld eventually be a new source of water for singapore?? cos its trying to unclog the drainage system of ur eyes n nose n get rid of watever irritant has entered ur breathing apparatus... probly an allergic reaction to pollen n/or dust... which leads us to the next question... Wat Good does Dust do???
      
</post>
<date>09,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       URGGGH RUNNY DOSE   haha and here's a bad way to start your holidays: a runny dose too! runny doses spoilt everything: first days at school, first days of vacation, first days at work.. what the heck first days of everything. everything that happens in your body has a purpose you say? runny doses don't quite do anything for anybody... in fact, mucus comes close to being the most useless bodily discharge i can think of (with the exception of puke). Come to think of it, getting anything out of your body should be a pleasant experience. crapping provides instant relief, sweating cools you down (apparently, but someone tell me how that works), but yet again i find no joy in blowing my dose. It has to be the most joyless purging process of the body (with the exception of puke again). Its likely that this is how our bodies invent mechanisms to counter these joyless purging processes. Sniffing gives you the instant high and tissue-less response to nose blowing. Choking stops you from talking with your mouth full. See everything has a purpose to add joy (ok so choking isnt that pleasant) to the mundane routines we subject ourselves to (of course, choking on your own puke doesn't count. you're hopeless if that happens to you on a regular basis). Well, guess that leaves us to crapping as the best option for letting anything out of our bodies. have fun people.
      
</post>
<date>06,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
        New Kid on the Block    yesyes... u got a new resident evil on the block... me!! n im worse than dat dancing moon or watever she calls herself, cos im one of those losers wif too much time to spare... which explains y im typing this rite now. i'll try not to make things up n post them... erm, tho i dun promise anything... u guys juz decide for urselves whether wat i say is true ornot lah... supposed to be intelligent,cynical, discerning, creative individuals... u'll noe it when i start saying i look like tom cruise n stuff yeah? till i get bored again.....
      
</post>
<date>06,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       Cinderella Dreams   A good production by Mime Unlimited. A story of the ever-popular Cinderella but with a twist. A good way to spend your sat esp if you have 16 bucks to spare. Watch it at night and have your own cinderella dream afterwards, along the Riverfront. Ahh.. L'amour. 
      
</post>
<date>06,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       Monday Blues   What's a bad way to start the new school week? Having a test and falling sick at the same time. Bleah... Head feels like it's the size of a huge watermelon (or any other big fruit) and nose seems to have a life of its own; it can't stop dripping. 
      
</post>
<date>06,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       A not so random musing   Horrid, distasteful and utterly gross. These words aren't enough to describe a certain club at Clarke Quay. What do you get when you put black music, lots of booze and a bunch of ' mats ' in one room? You get a place called LOX, where ass-rubbing is  the   move of the night. LOX is the place to go only if you are stone drunk, almost comatose or if you harbour a secret desire to be a pole-dancer. The dance floor was so hot, you would be exchanging body fluids with other equally sweaty people in no time at all. With strangers constantly dancing against one another, it was nearly impossible to avoid brushing against them.  All you pole-dancer wannabes, pay attention! LOX is a place for you to try out your moves. Shake that body and show them boobs.Rub your groin with a fellow dancer, be it male or female and don't forget the occasional stolen and not-so-chaste kisses as well. Throw your hands up in the air when asked to by the dj (who's da man of da night) and scream 'hey.. ho..' as often as you can.  Thirsty? Well, that $12 coupon can get you housepours. For teetotallers, I regret to inform you that your coupon only entitles you to a glass of coke. No OJ, and you can forget about asking for a Shirley Temple. This further emphasise the fact that in order to enjoy the music, one must be incredibly drunk first.  [shudder] Oh man... Gimme retro gimme bengs. I'd rather dance to synchronised steps than have to face such music again. If anyone is thinking of asking me to go LOX again, I'm gonna ask you to kiss my ass, honey. 
      
</post>
<date>05,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       Mundane Info #2   Aching feet should trod to  urlLink Daniel's Blog Spot  for comfort
      
</post>
<date>05,September,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       Mundane Info #1   Dancing too long at night will make your feet ache
      
</post>
<date>30,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
         I agree with Heffa's assessment of Ms I-Need-A-New-Image Aguilera. Just to gross everyone out, check out her pic. I couldn't find one from her video, but will post it as soon as i find one.. 
      
</post>
<date>29,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
         Font Colors To answer lester's really old question, here's a rough explanation of the hexadecimal color system, as far as I understand it. There are 6 digits in the code; 2 digits each for red, blue, and green color values. So the numbers basically define how much red, blue and green goes into the color mix. It's like in primary school where you take paint and mix different base colors to get new colors. So, your next question is, where do the letters come in, right? well, digits only go up to 9, so the letters represent values greater than 9 (like 10). Yeah. And as for the question of why can't you just type in the color name, well, guess what, you can. Have a look at  urlLink this page  to see what color names you can use.  And today's font color is: red. The moralizer appears... Now, about the things that Nephthys reviewed... no personal criticisms or condemnations are intended at all, but still, at the risk of being labled a prudish, self-righteous judge with outdated values, I shall proceed to state my personal opinion on such matters.   Firstly, I hate The Bachelor. Who would have believed that some of the women are Harvard grads and doctors and lawyers? They're just a bunch of desperadoes making fools out of themselves on TV. Furthermore, how can you possibly attempt to find a husband by going on a reality TV program? Are they serious about marrying this guy at all? Are they even considering what needs to go into a successful and stable marriage? Do they really think that the bachelor is a man of good character, considering that he's mass-dating a bunch of desperadoes and telling them sweet lies so that he can have fun with as many of them as possible? Did it ever cross these women's minds that this guy must have a substantial ego with a voracious appetite?  Secondly, Christina's new video is not hot, it's just gross. Yes, announce to the world that you're even sluttier than Britney. Have you noticed that the recent music videos involve a lot of references to mass sex orgies? In the past, we used to think that Madonna was being risqué. Now, risqué is cliché. What is the world coming to? Who wants to raise children in such a deteriorating environment?  Thirdly, no, I haven't seen SATC, but I outright reject the idea that lust outside of a stable relationship is fun and acceptable, and also that having multiple sex partners over time is good. In fact, it is very bad. If you believe in the spiritual dimension of things, every time you have sex with someone, you make a "soul tie" with them. It becomes a spiritually binding relationship. That's why you're only supposed to have sex with your spouse, because you are creating a permanently binding relationship with them. So what happens if you have multiple "soul ties" with many partners? It prevents you from developing lasting and stable relationships with anyone in the future! Of course, it's possible that accidents happen, and dead "soul ties" must be renounced to free yourself from them. But in any case, liberal, multiple-partner sex is not good for your soul, your heart or your mental health.  In conclusion, the world is in a bad, bad state. Time to get serious about where we're all going in life and what values we're gonna cling to.  
      
</post>
<date>28,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
           Reviews     The Bachelor   Although I admit to being a fan of reality tv, (ok, only survivor and TAR), the bachelor is the pits. The setting, 25 women vying for 1 man (TB: the Bachelor). TB is "charming, sweet, tall, handsome" yadda yadda yadda, as quoted by one of the women there. This show is even shallower than Temptation Island. Only Americans would think of producing and participating in such a show. *shudder*   Dirty - New Single by Christina Aguilera   Ok, you gotta admit, that girl has got talent. Not just to sing, but with her new single, she has shown that she is one raunchy miss. 'Dirty' is as dirty as you think it is (pardon the pun) and christina makes no apologies for it. Her video is even hotter than britney's "slave" with a skirt so short that you can see her red undies everytime she thrusts her hips towards the camera.    Sex and The City    Thanks to the creators of a lovely program called kazaa, we in singapore can now watch "Sex and the City (SATC)"! This show is refreshing and doesn't overload viewers with moral behavior, especially with regards to sex. Women have 'fuck buddies' and monogamy may be over-rated. Why look for love when lust is so much more fun?  [writer's aside: i'm not advocating such behavior, just looking from the perspective of the characters in the show]   Right, more reviews when there's actually something to review about. Till then...  
      
</post>
<date>23,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
         Amidst the Stress......    Amidst the stress comes more stress... well actually that isn't quite right, but i didn't know what else to say. how many of you here feel indifferent to exams? none? everyone? someone? after 2 years of it, i'm frankly quite sick of exams. the stress gets progressively lesser each year, but that isn't due to me being VERY prepared for it. NO. Actually, the stress doesn't get lesser, it just doesn't develop to a full-blown panic attack anymore.. doesn't rear it's ugly head.... doesn't manifests itself into something tangible like errr.. chewed nails. (no, i don't have that problem) (ok ok... i'll stop with the analogy)  1 paper down, 3 more to go. and what am i doing now? writing about things that have got nothing to do with Strategic Management.   preparing for exams is like running the 2.4 or any marathon. the journey sucks... some of us want to be first, or top 10% or top 15%. some of us want to remain in the middle.. while others had such a horrid journey that they want to just finish the damn thing, regardless of position and timing. the exam result slip is akin to the certificate that one receives for the napfa - gold, silver, bronze. and just like the certificate, it is worth shit when one leaves the institution. 10 years down the road, is anyone going to ask you, "so, how did you do for your napfa when you were in school?" no. i don't think anyone is going to ask that. similarly, no one is going to ask you, "so, how did you do for your first semester exams?"  despite knowing this, does it make the preparation any less important? no, it doesn't. we will still be doing this at the end of each semester, just like we would run our marathon, no matter how much we hate it.   and this, ladies and gentlemen, is the manifestation of my exam stress... 
      
</post>
<date>23,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
        HOW DOES THIS FONT COLOUR WORK ANYWAY   hey does every combination of letters and numbers give you a colour? we should be allowed to use english instead. makes so much more sense. like very black, unpopular pink, violent green, pukish yellow, or darker shade of grey than my pet elephant's bum. thats how i'd transpose them at least, but 3 giga cheers for heffalump! i can never play those tabs but great job anyway (did i mention i can't read those tabs either)! 
      
</post>
<date>22,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
        Whose Line Is It Anyway   Whose Line is coming! We should all go for it! Price: Not given as yet Location :   urlLink Bar None  . Date: 11 - 14 Nov (I think)  Those who are interested, aside frm Es and I, do lemme know.. Maybe we cld all go together or smth huh? Altho i think you NUS ppl have exams! [muahaha]   Guitar players   And Heffa, honey, i don't think anyone here is a guitar player. :) Unless u count my knowledge of playing "Greensleeves"    Annoying Song #1  Ok those of you who want to torture urselves for no apparent reason. Listen to Las Ketchup, "The Ketchup Song". That will surely drive you up the wall. 
      
</post>
<date>22,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
         Today's font color: 00CCFF (ain't it pretty?) Actually, the whole world is going down the drain... just read the newspapers... I try not to read them too often, actually.. too depressing.  On a happier note... Whose Line is gonna be in Singapore??? when??? I wanna go see!!!!!  And, if any of you are guitar players, I am pleased to announce that the On-Line Guitar Archive (OLGA) has accepted my latest tab for posting on the net... check out my transcription of Santana's "Game of Love", featuring Michelle Branch,  urlLink here . No, I can't transcribe Santana's guitar licks yet. Will work on it after exams. But at least I got the chords down... I also have a fantastic, totally accurate, full transcription of Michelle Branch's "All You Wanted"... unfortunately, someone beat me to submitting a transcription to OLGA, so they didn't accept mine... but if anyone is interested, let me know and I can email it to ya :)
      
</post>
<date>22,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      hi..man..haven't been online here for a long time....know jack about coloring my posts anyway. And basically, i don;t care...gotta be fair to the color-blind. Anyway, as moondancer knows..WHOSE LINE IS COMING TO SINGAPORE!!! 3 MEGA MEGA CHeers for that..thanks to the punchline comedy club we are gonna get to see the original UK cast of whose line!! yes..we have steve frost and tony slattery!! *drool drool... =0)  Been so caught up with the Washington DC sniper thing. Bloody guy's lost it. Shooting kids for kicks. If i were in the FBI now, i';ll know where to start looking..man..i've so many leads to start from..argh.   PE paper's just a day away..and i'm not done... 
      
</post>
<date>22,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
        Pink is my new obsession    I'm not gonna chnage the color, so too bad for u fluke.  but i do agree on the font type.. just hang on lah.. will change when i feel like it.     I HATE STUDYING. I HATE MUGGING.   
      
</post>
<date>19,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
        pink is my favourite crayon   think pink's fine... but haettenschweiler looks quite crammed up. quite a stuck up kinda font- bossy but no guts. ahaha we could just keep going on... you decide:)
      
</post>
<date>19,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      erm... im not trying to be picky or too fussy... errr... but muz it be in pink?? =/
      
</post>
<date>19,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
            IS THIS BETTER?      Changed the headline color and type. it's now supposed to be "haettenschweiler".  HAPPY STUDYING...    
      
</post>
<date>19,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      the heading on my screen looks like the words from a 1st generation MS-DOS v3.0 font magnified 10 times, complete wif jagged edges in other words... it totally sux man.... not to mention its in a yucky-yellow too
      
</post>
<date>18,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
         Rights my ass.... :) i like the green (default) font color that i allocated for ppl who dunno how to change the colors of their font.  Regarding the main heading, ie, "TALES OF THE MUNDANE" sign, what type of font do you see? I used "courier", and i wanted to use a fancy font that i downloaded, but i reailsed that only my computer wld reflect the new font, but for those of you with no fancy schmancy font types d/loaded, u won't be able to see the font, and thus wld only show times new roman, or some other boring font like that.  OOh ooh, i don't quite like a dancing skeletons either, but i was in a hurry to choose a gif. will change when i've got time to browse thru all those gif websites.    
      
</post>
<date>18,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       Aye Aye La Capitaine!   ooh... i like the maroon backgrd or watever color its called (guys ar only sensitive to the 7 colors of the rainbow n blind to all other shades)..... erm... i mean, my rights to monochrome fonts have been violated!! i demand to see justice n equality! n errr... nice dancing gay skeletons too... wif the pink top hats, so i assume they ar gay... no decent heterosexual skeleton wld ever be seen wif pink hats  the main heading for the site looks kinda eeky tho...
      
</post>
<date>17,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
             CHECK THIS OUT     ok ok.. comments ppl. what do u think of the page so far? see this is what i do when i'm taking a break. bleah.. hahaah.    
      
</post>
<date>17,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
        AYE!   guess im too late to say anything, but its definitely an aye! anyway.. keep it changing. 
      
</post>
<date>16,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
         The  COOL  new look...  Today's font color: CCAA99 Ah, now that's what I call a nice revamp. :) Give it up for Nephthys! *woo-hoo*  Check out this pretty desktop pic I downloaded to make my pretty Mac even prettier :)     Ok, exam fever is ON... let the mugging begin....  
      
</post>
<date>16,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
            UPGRADING   THis site is going to be upgraded. hah.. due to heffalump's comment abt changing the template. so if u happen to view the site when the color is like TOTALLY off and weird, just ignore it. it's probably just me, experimenting with the colors.   ciao  oh.. and  HAPPY STUDYING!     
      
</post>
<date>16,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      NEPHTHYS here: had to make changes to heffa's color as it clashed with the backgrd. may revert to original color if i change backgrd again.    Today's font color: 225522 Ah, I guess guys would never complain about seeing a gal in her underwear.. girls just have higher standards.. we complain when the guy in black underwear looks like crap and is already attached... am I right ladies?  Anyway, on a separate note, I propose trying out a new template/layout for the site. All who agree say "aye"... 
      
</post>
<date>15,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      hahaa... wld we ever complain if it was the guy's dorm n there was a Miss BU?? wld probly be fantasizing abt how to get her into ur room rather than ur neighbour's room... *already rubbing hands wif glee*  n yess... *in martin luther king mode* i see i stand alone in my support for the monochrome font... alas, i shall remain standing underterred n unperturbed... my resolve noes no bounds... no matter if i shld fall one day, n there would be none to take my place.... i have fought the gd fight n my perseverance shall resound in the chambers of justice... so loud shall it resonate dat it will last thruout history.... *in george bush jr mode* n hopefully outlast ur darn colored fonts n pics!
      
</post>
<date>14,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      i shall also have a font color thingie so there'd be more colors for us to avoid in the future.    oohh... PS2 eh? 500 bucks? is it that expensive?   haha.. i think So Close would have been better to watch than Transporter cos   1) there's 3 babes instead of just 1 2) there's 3 babes instead of just 1 3) there's 3 babes instead of just 1  ok.. i really can't think of any more good points.   ooh.. i lodged a complain against my stupid next door neighbors yesterday.. [evil laughter] hope they take action this time round. 
      
</post>
<date>14,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
        Hypothesis: Any "blockbuster" with Shu Qi in it will be a waste of money...  Today's font color: 996699 Why did you even  consider  watching that film? Did I tell you about the hilarious meaningless strip-fest that "So Close" was? I already wasted my money on that one, and hey, it may have been more worthwhile cos they stuck to Chinese for the most part, and there were three babes with plenty of flesh flashed, so there's  no way  I'm gonna console  anyone  by watching another dumb film. Too bad, lester ;-P  No Madame Clairvoyante, I'm not getting a drum set. I am attempting to buy a PS2. Mini-TV not included. 
      
</post>
<date>13,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       Black suit's back     No, this isn't the next instalment of MIB. Spotted: Mr BU Venue: In my bathroom Time: 6 am!!!  sigh... seems that they never learn. I was abt to go to the loo when the door to my neighbor's room and i caught a glimpse of Mr BU in his     BLACK UNDERWEAR  .  He saw me, panicked abit, and hurriedly closed his door.   I'm gonna lodge a complain. This has got to stop. Right here. Right Now.    
      
</post>
<date>13,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
         oh man lester my friend, u watched  ANOTHER  bad movie again?! why oh why did  you do that? i think you might be one of those ppl who love watching bad movies. hahaah.... and my dear heffalump... i know i'm smart. i'm madame la clairvoyant remember? *grins* so what you planning to get? a drum set so u two can jam together?? now that'd be great... and if u do get him a drum set, leave it at ur house so i can play around with it when i visit! harhar....i'll see ya week for dinner right? wld prefer fri u know.. do let our dear bv know abt it... heck, i think i'll just msg him lah...     testing colors  
      
</post>
<date>11,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       why everybody should watch transporter   oh another list you might say? don't shrug this off just yet. here's why you ALL should go watch the transporter:  1. to amuse yourself with shu qi's nonsensical english 2. to amaze yourself that the producers actually released the film with shu qi's nonsensical english 3. to watch all your dreams fulfilled in one movie (eg find shu qi in your car boot, tie a rope round shu qi's neck while she goes off to pee, scold shu qi for ruining your quiet morning, steal your enemy's car cos he blew yours up... awww you watch the rest) 4. to watch bruce lee's nemesis act as shu qi's father. 5. cos i wasted my $8 and i want you to waste yours too.
      
</post>
<date>11,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
         Give the gal a prize! All hail the ever-intelligent Nephthys! Yes, you are spot-on correct! I would give you a cash prize for your reward if I wasn't desperate for the money myself.. haha.  Right. Btw, if the font color looks horrendous, then it's because I'm just randomly making up a hex code for the color. Like the headline color for my last post was totally.. disgusting... what color is that, puce? ugh. Anyway, just for the heck of it, from now on I shall post the actual hex code of the color I'm using so you can use it too, if you like. We shall call this.. erm... "Font color of the day". How's that? hahaha....  And today's font color is... CC6699. yaay. ok. before I go let's post a comic to lighten up everyone's day.. (and please, please, don't sue me for posting the comic... I read the site copyright notice.. it didn't say anything about linking... so... )     Want to read more comics like this? Visit  urlLink The Norm . 
      
</post>
<date>10,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      errr... or at least they were gargantuan 5 mins ago... im serious!! u shld have seen them!! y doesnt anyone believe me??! go ask the dancing alligator!
      
</post>
<date>09,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      wah lau eh.... totally incredible.... fan-@#$%ing-tastic....... do u believe this??!....... oh my GOD..... for Pete's sake.... by Jupiter!....... *gasp*..... wah piang!!......  i've run out of expletives to describe the blinding gargantuan fonts
      
</post>
<date>09,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       hehe... am i correct if i were to say that the 500 bucks is for a certain someone's 21st birthday present? 4mths... that wld be in february next year? how to save money: 1) don't go out 2) keep a diary of expenses 3) have a weekly budget 4) put ur money in the bank the moment u receive it and go out w/o ur atm card 5) keep a certain amt of money in ur wallet and make sure u don't withdraw anymore money  
      
</post>
<date>09,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
         Oh crap the stupid Blogger!   Bloody thing timed me out again, just as I had finished typing and coding a long post... well, too bad for the rest of the world who wanted to see my  original  post, cos now that it's been erased, it's  never coming back....  *buahahahaha* right like anyone really cares, yah I know...  Ok, now I'm looking for tips on how to prevent oneself from spending so much money so that one can save a heck of a lot of money within 4 months.. $500, to be exact.  And for what purpose, pray tell?  yes, that's the burning question isn't it... right... ok I think I've exposed enough ego tonight already...  We now return to our regularly scheduled programming....   
      
</post>
<date>09,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       Back at Last....   Hey, it's good to be back after a few days. (feels longer than that actually)  Happenings in my life:  1) Aunt (dad's elder sis) died of a heart attack on mon nite, and that's the reason i've not been in hall for the past 2 days.   2) exams are coming and i'm not friggin prepared for it  3) getting fat  4) getting fatter  5) getting a lot fatter   seems that i'll have a new game to get addicted to just before exams... how nice. i thank you, lester old buddy old pal. *grins*
      
</post>
<date>09,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       GAME OF THE WEEK    urlLink     hide the stash before mom and dad come in. just how good are you (and your mouse pointing dexterity)?
      
</post>
<date>09,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       Proud Supporter of the Monochrome Font n the Pic-less Backgrd   The absurdity of my life reached new heights yesterday while i was waiting for my fren at orchard mrt...... in the space of 5 mins, as i was standing beside a pillar, reading my copy of the newpaper, n waiting for my fren to turn up...   1st, an italian woman (who cld be french or spanish or from any western european country for dat matter) approached me to ask for directions to citibank... well, i'd have thanked my lucky stars if she looked anything like virginie leydoyen or  erm... dunno any spanish or italian actress (wld probly have accompanied her to the bank)... she was juz middle-aged wif a 8 yr old daughter in hand... the nice guy dat i am simply told her how to go to citibank...  2 mins after dat.... a chinawoman asked me how to go to wisma... after telling her dat wisma is juz 10m away from where we were standing, i promptly searched myself for any sign dat i looked like a street directory... but to no avail.....  1 min after  dat... some arabic looking man then asked me how to use his singletrip fare card dat he juz bot in the station.... i muz have almost burst out laughing then, n made him tink dat im laughing at his stupidity (but of cos, i was laughing at myself).... anyway, it confirmed my suspicions dat i din look like a street directory, but a multi-purpose handbk for tourists...
      
</post>
<date>09,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      well, hey..it's nice to return... what's with the pictures and all? Looks good, though....  Spent a humiliating night..won't elaborate as yet..still licking my wounds and smacking my head with my hands for a stupidity for which i can only attribute to the disease 'temporal insanity'... Ah crap..and oh, by the way, people..kazaa works in ntu now!!! and it rocks!!!!   
      
</post>
<date>07,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
         hun, i don't think anyone here is a mac user. and i've lost my archive page, so if any of u know how to get it back, pls lemme know or tweak this bloody thing. btw, all of u are administrators.. (i'm such a nice person) and i hope no one gonna sue us... oh well, we'll just have to minimise the usage of pics. it slows down the page anyways.. 
      
</post>
<date>06,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
        oh, I didn't publish right away cos I had to edit the post a few times before it looked right, and like I said, stupid blogger had some screw ups and refused to let me post... it's ok :) anyway I thot maybe the "administrators" had a sched to publish or something? I'm a newbie, remember?   *grins*  btw, I hope no-one's gonna sue us for illegal weblinking with the pics....   now what I REALLY wanted to ask was.. does anyone here use a Mac (besides me)? 
      
</post>
<date>06,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
        awww... is fluke jealous? it's really easy to learn how to add stuff and colors to ur posts, all u have to do is read the "help" page and learn more abt HTML stuff! i'm currently at my friend's house, waiting for the bloody meeting to start but it ain't happening anytime soon as no one else is here!  ooh.. and l found out what does N.B stands for : nota bene (means note well) 
      
</post>
<date>05,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      ok... fine... leave me out of the fun... dun teach me how to change color n add pics... dun teach dun teach lor... *goes sulk in a corner*
      
</post>
<date>05,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
        Hey Check IT Out!!!     I managed to get the pic and the colored fonts!! hehe.. of cos i'm actually supposed to be doing my tax summary now and i have an 8 am meeting on a SUnday morning tomorrow... (or shld i say later today..) 
      
</post>
<date>05,October,2002</date>
<post>
</post>
<date>05,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      hey... tot u arent supposed to be able to upload pics?? n how can u change the color of ur text??! no fair!!! btw, i took the liberty to publish blue pig's post.... which was juz posted but not published on the page... was it meant to be liddat? yikes... sorie if im juz being a busybody =p
      
</post>
<date>04,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
        bloody  blogger keeps hanging when I post!!! Finally managed to post the pic.. stupid blogger site keeps rejecting my posts.. they've got a stupid coding problem....  *grrrrr...*  am very annoyed cos I've just wasted a lot of time trying to post when I should really be finishing up my essay.. drat drat drat... 
      
</post>
<date>03,October,2002</date>
<post>
</post>
<date>03,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
        tales of the  heffalump  and the  blue pig ...    drat.. tried to post a pic just now but I got VB runtime error (???) maybe I timed out... grrr.... I shall tweak the color instead.. anyway I watched some of season 1 of TAR and it was    LOUSY   . Anyway, whatever turns you on babe :)  You know what that color really sux :(
      
</post>
<date>03,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       nepthys is egyptian!! how many times muz i tell u??!   =p  Nepthys, or Nebet-Hus, is the daughter of Nut the sky goddess n Geb the earth god, is the Sister of Isis and Osiris, the Wife of Set, the desert God of storms, chaos, night, and wild nature, and with Set or Osiris, she is the Mother of Anpu, or Anubis, the funeral Priest who wears the mask of a Jackal, and whose name means "opener".  Her headdress is a cubic throne topped with a bread basket (*shrugs* im not kidding!).   She is the deity of the Harvest and Agriculture and the Moon. Like Isis, she is sometimes shown as a Falcon, and thus she probably became the Greek Goddess Hera (u noe... hercules' step-mum who keeps trying to kill hercules... knew abt her from watching the tv series). She is also probably related to the female deity Habonde or Abundance, the Bona Dea of the Witches (im sure my sec sch chinese teacher is one of them)  as if all this werent confusing enuf... she was Sets sister and wife, but was truly in love with Osiris, and she was able to trick him into conceiving a child with her, and this was accomplished by taking the form of his true wife, and their sister, Isis... eeks... INCEST!!! no wunder the son Anubis looks so ugly...  ok, so shes the wife of seth.. slept wif osiris... n also married zeus to become hera... woah... kindof a busy goddess huh?  anyway... dun u find the not-so-amazing race this season filled wif guys having broken-wrists?? really felt like breaking the neck of the son in the father-son team... n the twins ar only good at looking good... cos apparently they left their brains in their bags, which they left in the taxi, which they left... how brainless can u get??!  the 2 lawyers-cum-bitches look gd tho... esp eve.. heheh ;)
      
</post>
<date>03,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      well, since nephthys is my icq nickname, i'm assuming they would know who i am. FYI, nephthys is a greek (i think) goddess.   ahh heffalump.. piglet.. ok.. i geddit now. what i want to know is WHY?   hey.. TAR isn't that much of a bitch fest mainly cos it focuses more on intra grp dynamics ie between the partners.. ohhh. unless, you've been watching season 2. now that was a bitch fest. i think it's probably cos the participants were "media whores" (to quote some guy) so they acted for the benefit of the camera.  oh and lester, pretty cool pic u posted. How did u do it?? gotta learn, so that we can spice up this site of ours.. :)
      
</post>
<date>03,October,2002</date>
<post>
</post>
<date>03,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      huh? and people would recognize you more as nephthys? (what IS that anyway?) and heffalump is not me asking do u want a lump.. duh... heffalump is an elaphant-like creature that Piglet was afraid of, but he dug a big hole and caught one (if I remember that story correctly).. geddit rite.. cochon bleu/piglet/heffalump...(ok you have to know french to understand what cochon bleu is) "I am a seething mass of contradictions" to quote CK in his contradiction ad... heheh... oh dear. this bolg is bad for my sanity and my reputation.  And just for the record, I think TAR is just another bitch-fest. I guess that's why reality shows are appealing rite... *grins*
      
</post>
<date>02,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       The Amazing Race   Ok.. ok.. i'm a sucker for reality tv shows; survivor, temptation island (just love to watch how absurd the show is), and my ultimate favorite, The Amazing Race (TAR). TAR 3 made its debut on channel 5 this afternoon, 12 couples competing for a cool million. Did i forget to mention that it's a race around the world for 30 days?   Without getting into the nitty gritty bits of the show (i doubt you wld want me to summarise the whole ep, and i sure as hell wouldn't want to write it all down), TAR 3 is going to be interesting to watch for the next 12 weeks... uh-oh, i can forsee spending my thursday nights at the tv lounge trying to study and watch at the same. the nice uncle who cleans my blk told me that i shouldn't do my work and watch tv at the same time, at least that was what i assumed he was telling me, cos he was speaking in chinese...   For those who wld like to know more abt TAR   urlLink Official website   urlLink The amazing race links 
      
</post>
<date>02,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       Change of Nickname   Ok.. i've decided to change my nick as ppl kept telling me that they don't know which one is me... and has rejected my invites cos of it. so, nephthys is ME. i am NEPHTHYS. we are one and the same... so don't go tellin me that u deleted my invite cos u don't know who i am.  oh, and i'd like to welcome our latest member.. cochon bleu aka heffalump. [no, i don't want a lump] 
      
</post>
<date>02,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      Hi. I'm new here and I don't know what's going on, but Azri says to come, so I come... and I am welcomed by... a discussion on human excrement??? eww. I shall change the subject: who here is stressed out by projects and exams? raise ur hands! *waves and jumps about wildly* hehe no wonder this blog is called tales of the mundane.. ok I'm not creating a very good first impression here am I? 
      
</post>
<date>01,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      arggggh not that movie again! can just picture the blob splooshing into the water in typical john-woo slow-mo fashion. not a pleasant sight. still can't picture it? watch the  urlLink movie . 
      
</post>
<date>01,October,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      errr...... no comments on the Newater bit... =/
      
</post>
<date>24,November,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       Harry Potter - Goblet of Fire   As mentioned by Selin, yes goblet of fire (GOF) is alot more exciting than the first 3 instalments of Harry Potter. After reading it close to 3 times, I can't wait for the fifth one to be released! 
      
</post>
<date>18,November,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       i feel so useless   the angel has sprouted wings n flown away again.... the chicken has flown its coop... the caterpillar has morphed into a butterfly n taken to the air... im beginning to doubt if it was right for the wright bros to invent the plane... juz like how i doubted whether my life wld have been easier had newton not been hit by an apple... now all i can do is write letters, n wait 2 mnths till she comes back....... bleahhh....
      
</post>
<date>16,November,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      the 4th book (Goblet of Fire) is even more exciting!! there's always a twist in  the ending which is so unexpected... i get so hooked to the book tt i dun want to put it down till I've finished it :P waiting for the 5th book to come out man...........
      
</post>
<date>16,November,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
          REVIEWS    Harry Potter (Parts 1,2  3)  In the space of 2 weeks, I've read the first three instalments of Harry Potter, by J.K. Rowling. Well, not 2 weeks, more like 2 days over 2 weeks. (geddit?) Although not as thrilling as Lord of the Rings, it is fun to read. The plot gets more interesting in each book. Harry and friends are a curious lot, always seeking adventures and sneaking off into the night. The protagonists face new villains in each new instalment, although all the villains have a connection with  he-who-shall-not-be-named . Thankfully, Rowling does not try to sugar-coat the plot and villains and the story does get darker and more sinister as one progresses. Readers, along with Harry himself, will discover more about his past and will be drawn into Harry's life and ride along with him and his friends in each adventure that they embark on.   With specific reference to the second book, mainly because the movie is out.. I dislike Gilderoy Lockhart. He is such a  git!     the Book Vs the Movie  This is purely based on the first one, cos i've not watched the second one yet. While Chris Columbus does try to stick to the original story, like all movies that are adapted from books, certain scenes, dialogues have to be cut in the movie to fit the time frame and to make it watchable. In a certain sense, watching the movie before reading the book is good because one can have an idea of how Harry, Ron and Hermione actually looks like. I daresay, Daniel Radcliffe, Rupert Grint and Emma Watson fit their characters to a T. However, Harry Potter has more spunk in the book, I feel, than portrayed on the silverscreen. Hermione, on the hand, is perrrfect. And so is Hagrid. Well, once I catch the second movie, I'll be sure to write my two-cents worth.   Trivia: Hermione is pronounced as Her-my-own-nee
      
</post>
<date>13,November,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       About Bloody Time!!   Yeh should 'ave laid down yer cards a long time ago, boy. Time's a-tickin'. If yeh don't do nothin' about it, Taiwan gal may find herrsef a nice, jolly Taiwan Boy and where wld that leave yeh? Pinin' away 'ere and botherin' me abt it, that's what yeh wld do. So, yeh just 'afta brace yerself and go fer it. No point muckin' abt now. Be sure ta lemme know what 'appens, aye?  
      
</post>
<date>13,November,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       Taiwan gal is back!! n going off again!   y not? y arent u gonna watch the show? HUH??! its gd! go WATCH it!!!  hmm... ok... maybe not juz a fren lah... maybe a "special" fren... its a long story n rather complicated to relate... heheh... shes going back again on mon anyway... dun wanna bore u guys wif my misadventures in luv  =/ n i am going on all out attack aredi! no more goalkeeper left in goal... going for broke... all or nothing... showhand... do or die... erm... yah, i tink u get it
      
</post>
<date>13,November,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
        DoubleVisionnoisiVelbuoD   Never watched that show, don't think I'll ever will. My ex-roommate did watch it tho and she said that the ending is open-ended.. up to one's own intepretation.   On another note... OOOOOHH.. Friend is back from Taiwan eh? Still only a FRIEND? You're slow, fluke. Better get cracking, ol buddy, ol pal.   [grins]
      
</post>
<date>13,November,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       can someone watch Double vision n tell me wat really happened in the end?   heyhey... i noe my exams havent ended... but i've got a 6 day break b/w my 2nd last paper n the last wan.... n erm... a fren from taiwan came back erm... soooo one thing led to another lah... (gd thing abt blogs is they let us tok to no one n yet lets us assuage our own guilt)  anyway... Double Vision is a weird movie... ala x-files... wif an intriguing plot... weird characters... n even weirder ending.... acting is excellent, cinematography is superb wif art direction by tim yip, the same guy who werked in Crouching Tiger Hidden Dragon (or so my fren who came back from taiwan told me).... its not really a scary movie... tho there ar some gross scenes of amputation, gory images of rotting wounds n stuff... my fren screamed a bit in those scenes, n shes one of the braver gals i've met... sooo... watch if u dare gals! (or guys for the matter, juz to be politically correct)... david morse has been nominated for best-supporting actor, tony leung for best actor n chen kuo-fu for best director in the golden horse awards... so it tells u wat a gd production the film is... movies i watch n recommend ar always gd, n its not juz becos of who i watched it wif!  =p
      
</post>
<date>13,November,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       Wat price the look of youth??   i watched Red Dragon abt 2 wks ago.... really great movie if u ar into those detective/suspense/thrillers type of stories... besides.. wif anthony hopkins, edward norton n a naked ralph fiennes (yes, totally, stark, wholly, like a baby naked)... Red Dragon is simply irresistible whether u ar a fan of excellent acting, frontal nudity, psychopaths or cannibalism... shant say anything abt the plot, lest i spoil ur fun  oh yes, n how cld i neglect to mention dat i was checked for my ic watching this nc-16 movie 2 days b4 my 21st bday? who needs botox??
      
</post>
<date>10,November,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
         WHOSE LINE IS IT ANYWAY    This stand-up comedy show made its way to our Singapore shores on Monday and I must say, they are even funnier on stage then the are on TV. Scenes improvised by the quintet included a Bolivian expert giving a speech about funerals and llama-herding, a three-headed Captain talking about how horses can play cricket and a bizarre fairytale about Alice in Wonderland and the Whisk. Some games played are similar to the ones on TV, like scenes from a hat (or in this case, scenes from a bucket). Scenes ranged from 'three blind mice trying to mate' to 'four girls in the bathroom' to 'my mother, the green serpent'.  Trying to recall each specific scene/act is almost impossible, and frankly, I can't be bothered to try. They certainly had the audience rolling around laughing with their antics and especially when they bungle up. Their jokes seldom degenerated to toilet humour  a la  Boom Boom Room, but there was a penis puppet show and a lot of one liners like "shave my ass and call it a football", "shave my pubes and call it.. (i can't remember what)". Needless to say, it was worth every cent. Those who missed it can catch reruns of the Brit version at midnight on Wednesday on Central. 
      
</post>
<date>10,November,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      BLEAAAH!!!  hmph... the heading speaks for itself too...
      
</post>
<date>08,November,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
         NO MORE EXAMS!!!!!!!!!!!!!    Woohoo.... the heading speaks for itself. I don't have to say anything more.  
      
</post>
<date>08,November,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
        HANGING ON THE TWIRLING LINES THAT MAKE THE BEEFY PARABOLA OF NONEXISTENT PUNCTUATION       ah so everyones back what in the world has gotten into heffalump just what did the lowly pc have that the mac couldnt offer haha something here to flush all your worries away and in the meantime keep the faith and stick to your guns  what explodes like a fractal pops like a light bulb looks really awful at four in the morning moves with a dead stare coil's round yer ankles fangs long as neckties an' strikes without warning  lincoln's eyes a cruel black dragon lurks jonathan donahue
      
</post>
<date>07,November,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       Take this u egyptophile!   okok! sheesh... this egyptian dancing queen nags more than my mum.... well... juz in case u ppl ever feel an irrepressible urge to recite shakespeare in cameroon pidgin english...   Foh di foh dis graun oh foh no bi sehf -- dat na di ting wei i di bring plenti hambag .  for the rest of us boorish fools unaquainted wif the intricacies n beauty of african creoles:  To be or not to be -- that is the question .  *shrugs* i dunno y its so long lah.... n im not making it up either, in case u were suspecting.... =p btw, i've neva ever read a shakespearean play in my life... n im proud of dat fact too... heehee
      
</post>
<date>07,November,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
          I hate PCs! Since nephthys is complaining so much about not having any other voices on this site recently, I shall inject some democracy into it. haha. First of all that was a very sad attempt at Shakespeare. *bleah* I know I'm the only one who cares, being a lit student, but oh well. Erm, secondly... yeah, I hate PCs. I'm now borrowing Nephthys' one and it SUCKS. ahhh... I have nothing else to say. Death to the exams!!  
      
</post>
<date>06,November,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       Where have all the bloggers gone?   The blog site has been quiet these past 2 weeks, with the exception of this writer, herself. Is she the only lifeless one out here? Or are the other bloggers too busy mugging to write some stuff down?"   Oh blogger, blogger, where art thou? Hath thou forsaken mine site?    Well, write soon dang it..  Tís lonely being the only one blabbering away ALL the time. 
      
</post>
<date>06,November,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
         REVIEWS     Who Wants To Be A Princess   Not me!! Esp if i have to parade around and answer questions like "where's the most provocative place you've been intimate in?" This 1 1/2 hour show is almost like "The Bachelor" only shorter (thank goodness for that). It's a beauty parade (aren't they all??) but the winner doesn't get to wear a crown, she gets to date one that does. (If i were a prince, i wouldn't want to get a date through some stupid show like this, and i sure wouldn't want to date an American.) I bet all the prince wants is one good _ _ _ _ (fill in the blanks yourself).  And all those women! What can i say about them? Cheap-o, and lame-o. That's what. Of course, i can call them other vile names... but, i'm trying to be nice and give them the benefit of the doubt. *snort*  like real  I think American women (dunno abt European women) are so into the romantic, fantasy date. They want a fairytale life and are willing to subject themselves to such 'humiliation" in order to achieve that dream. "Ooh, he's so charming. He's the kind of guy i've dreamt abt since i was a little girl!" They want to be romanced, courted and charmed... Any guy can fulfill that role and in return, i'm pretty sure they are willing to do just abt anything for him afterwards. (With all the wine that's been poured down their throats, i don't think they'll be capable of thinking straight)   
      
</post>
<date>06,November,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       Useless News   Alright, this is for all those who love reading recaps of shows on the net.  urlLink Television without Pity  is a  GREAT  site to go to. The writers are humorous and give very witty recaps of all (ok, almost all) shows shown on tv.   As of today, I have 1 more paper left! WOOHOO!!! Hurrah for me.   
      
</post>
<date>03,November,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
         MORE REVIEWS     Temptation Island 2 (TI2)   Was up last night watching TI2, not by choice but simply cos the tv was turned on as i was reading my notes. Ok, this latest installment is  WORST  than the first season (which i watched cos it was soooo hilarious to see couples behaving like that. sometimes bad tv shows are fun to watch, mainly cos u can make fun of those in it). TI2.. what can i say abt it, while maintaining a neutral position at the same time? Frankly speaking, nothing. This show is  PATHETIC!!!! . The phrase 'cheap sluts' is an understatement, a euphemism, for the women in the show.. and don't get me started on the men... And these women are professionals.. teachers, event planners... Teachers(!) and they're the ones that are educating the young in America.  One scenario that really pissed me off: Couple guy (CG) liked single girl ,A, (SGA). SGA said they 'clicked', personalities matched.. yadda yadda.. anyway, CG and SGA went to CG's room to, ya know, mess around.. (another euphemism). ok whatever. the next day, all couple guys and their respective girlfriends are supposed to choose one Single girl or Single guy to go on a date with. so, all single girls/guys are dancing on this bridge thing, and each Couple guy/girl are supposed to dance up to the girl/guy they want. Back to CG... when it was his turn, he didn't dance with SGA, whom he slept with the night before, but instead chose  ANOTHER  single gal. [muahaha] so, SGA is like soooo sad, cries.. yadda yadda. Had a talk with CG and said something to the effect of "i'm not some girl u can screw. i thought we had something going on... " whatever...  CHEAP SLUT!!!! that's what i felt like saying... *sigh*   
      
</post>
<date>01,November,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
         My favorite comic (yes, one of the many places i go to when i'm surfing the net) FYI, it's found on Life! section as well.  [hint: i would like to have the comic calendar for christmas if anyone is paying attention. or the book, or the soft toy, but that's doubtful] 
      
</post>
<date>01,November,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       You Know You Need A Life When.............   1)   you start looking forward to watching next week's reality tv show after the current week's episode has just been aired 2)   you surf the net fanatically for links relating to the tv show on your study breaks and then proceed to complain that there are too few articles available 3)   you would consider joining the fantasy version of the tv show if only it wasn't so troublesome to sign up 4)   you end up voting for the most fave and least fave contestants online 5)   you realise that you don't talk to anyone (either online or offline) during the day unless you're studying with them 6)   you forget what day and date it is, and only live according to when the next exam is 7)   you download tons of old movies from kazaa to watch on your break 8)   you don't turn off your computer cos it's the only companion you have 9)   you end up surfing the net for useless reading material  10)_you end up typing this list....  [gee.. what a sad life... fret not, one more week left!] 
      
</post>
<date>01,November,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
      ugh.... i havent dropped in for 1 wk, n the 1st thing i see when load the pg is this freaky photo??! whos in charge ard here anyway?? oops... *whispers* its the dancing queen.... heheh... i mean, great job queenie! nothing like a gross controversial pic to shock the system n push our viewer ratings sky high! =)  hmm... i havent been watching tv much lately too... so cant really add to those, erm... insightful comments abt the detriments of modern television programmes.... *shrugs* sooo... wat else cld i be busy wif? considering i dun go sch dat often (in fact, no more sch till 7th jan 2003 for me)... havent been studying for exams either.... hmm.... its certainly a mystery....
      
</post>
<date>31,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      It is officially the Eve of Chinese New Year!!!  A big, hearty "HAPPY CHINESE NEW YEAR" to all of you!!! As you pig out during this holiday, think of me, and bring back some goodies ie lots of pineapple tarts, love letters and that pound peanut round thingies (no, they aren't peanut cookies, but round peanuty things, aw heck.. just gimme all)!! I may be baking cookies (just for the hell of it) and if you're nice to me, I'd give some to you...  So Gong Xi Fa Cai to one and all.
      
</post>
<date>30,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      In anticipation of V-day, I'll share poems once every few days, or whenever I find a nice one to share.. V-day is over-rated, but I like the poems, so there. Got a problem with it? Tough.    May I Feel Said He      may i feel said he    (i'll squeal said she    just once said he)    it's fun said she        (may i touch said he    how much said she    a lot said he)    why not said she        (let's go said he    not too far said she    what's too far said he    where you are said she)        may i stay said he    (which way said she    like this said he    if you kiss said she        may i move said he    is it love said she)    if you're willing said he    (but you're killing said she        but it's life said he    but your wife said she    now said he)    ow said she        (tiptop said he    don't stop said she    oh no said he)    go slow said she        (cccome?said he    ummm said she)    you're divine!said he    (you are Mine said she)  By: E.E Cummings 
      
</post>
<date>30,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Fight Club   Ever noticed how couples fight in public? I've been a witness to about 3 such spats and I must say they have been quite amusing. You have:  a)  Guy who points finger and shouts at girl . This made the poor girl cry. It was sad, cos the fight occurred at the bus interchange so everyone who walked by could see them arguing. He was a young punk, well, actually, so was she. I didn't know what they were fighting abt cos i can't speak Chinese.  b)  Guy who argues with girl in a bar.  This one took place at Next Page. I couldn't hear what they were saying cos it was too loud. The amusing part was that a group of Caucasians got involved as well, cos, they, being like their governments, like to butt into other people's problems. Soon, one big, hunky ang moh kinda threw the small Asian to the outer part of Next Page and someone called the bouncers. The girlfriend was screaming, "don't hurt him! don't hurt him." But they were apparently attacked by a sudden desire to be chilvarous. It was amusing.  c)  Girl sulks at guy cos guy pissed her off.  This one occurred last night on a bus from Orchard. She was so irritated by him. And he persisted in talking to her which pissed her off even more. She banged her bag against the front seat a couple of times and pulled such a long face that i think must have reached the floor at some point in time. And the most irritating thing was that, he was still talking to her! Doesn't he get it? Your girl's pissed with you, leave her alone. And he had his arm around her waist (doesn't it make his arm numb or smthg??) and she was trying to shove it away but he wouldn't budge. Geez... Even I felt irritated by him! 
      
</post>
<date>29,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        Of hand holding and all that jazz   Congratulations on the CD!! I've heard its good actually. :)   As for the holding hands issue, I think its ridiculous (ok, downright stupid) to assume that you're in an exclusive relationship because you've held hands, even if two platonic friends have no reason to hold hands (which I think they do, whatever happened to the days when we were little and you could hold hands with anyone and skip around the playground and run around and stuff?). Sometimes you just wanna hold your friends hand (boy or girl) and just... walk!   Anyway, back to the issue at hand, the problem here is, the lack of communication. If they had talked about it, and figured out what different gestures mean to both of them, this wouldn't be as much of an issue. Talk people! Talk and listen! And talk about things worth talking about. Most of the chatter that fills our lives is so... innane and inconsequential (did I even spell that right? Having issues with my brain right now, its saying go to sleep goddamit) that I sometimes wonder why we even bother talking, then I realise... its probably because no one is really listening... oh well... 
      
</post>
<date>29,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      I'm in a melancholic mood right now and so, this is for all of you...    BUT YOU DIDN'T    Remember the time you lent me your car and I dented it? I thought you'd kill me..... But you didn't.  Remember the time I forgot to tell you the dance was  formal, and you came in jeans? I thought you'd hate me...... But you didn't.  Remember the times I'd flirt with other boys just to make you jealous, and you were? I thought you'd drop me.... But you didn't.  There were plenty of things you did to put up with me, to keep me happy, to love me, and there were so many things I wanted to tell you when you returned from Vietnam......  But you didn't.   Merril Glass  
      
</post>
<date>28,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       My First Ever CD Review   I finally bought my first ever CD in more than 2 years. Yes yes, all this while I've been living off napster, audiogalaxy and recently, kazaa. [Stop frowning, you anti-piracy freak, you]   The CD I bought is called "  Lady Sings The Blues  ". It is a compilation of jazz songs all sung by women from legends such as Ella Fitzgerald and Billie Holiday to a newbie, Norah Jones. This 2 CD compilation is a steal at just $17.00 ( I think). There's something mersmerising about women jazz singers. I think it's their smoky voice, the slow beat and the fact that so much atmostphere can be packed into a 3 min song. Everytime I listen to the songs, I feel as though I'm in some swanky New York bar in the 1930s, wearing a red dress and holding a martini in my hand.   Anytime you find yourself drowning in the events of the day, play this CD and your mood will lighten considerably. And for a brief moment, life is good. 
      
</post>
<date>28,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Holding hands n skipping stones... Hugs n kisses....   hmm... holding hands? errr... depends on how n in wat context i guess... y wld 2 platonic frens wanna hold hands for anyway? i definitely dun wanna hold hands wif my guy pals n be mistaken for a gay... i mean, if its during some silly ice-breaker game for orientation camp or wat, then ok lah... but y wld i wanna hold my female fren's hand unless i was assuming a more intimate r/s wif her? i dunno abt gals, but dats how straight, normal guys like me think.  as for hugs.... the only time i wld ever hug anybody is   1. when the team scores a goal n we all hug each other in mutual camaraderie as team mates (or however u spell dat french-anglicised word) (gender neutral action)  2. when the team scores a goal n we all hug each other in mutual cameradeire as supporters of the same team (gender-neutral action)  3. when the female fren is in need of comfort n i offer the proverbial sholder to cry on (only applicable to gals, wld be seen as gay if done to guys, gender-specific action)  4. when an event occurs akin to the team scoring a goal n we all hug each other in mutual camaererdire in celebratory mood (gender-neutral action)  kisses shld be the same as hugs i suppose... tho i doubt many singaporeans kiss each other for fun (even on the cheek) given the conservative nature of public scrutiny (ala dancing queen's powers of observation on the mrt) =p wld be screwed if my mum saw me pecking a gal on the cheek n then doubly screwed when she knows its not even my gf im kissing...  ok... hope dat clears up the typical alpha male's side of the argument...
      
</post>
<date>27,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Events   If anyone's keeping scores, count me in for "shall we dance (fa la la la)" and the play...... But be forewarned: I have 2 left feet.
      
</post>
<date>27,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        Events    After my earlier diatribe about relationships and going steady, I'll shall move on to a more pleasant topic. A couple of  urlLink Romancing Singapore  activities caught my eye. This month long campaign is aimed at "Romancing Singapore" (duh).  1)  urlLink  Shall We Dance - A Bridge Version    Date: 7 Feb Venue: Read Bridge at Clarke Quay Time: 8pm til 2 am Cost: FREE! This should be a fun event. Dancing in the night with instructors to guide the participants. You can come with your gal pals, boy toys, boyfriends, lovers, ex-es, lesbian/gay lovers and even drinking buddies and dance the night away. Best thing is that this event is Free! So come on down and enjoy yourself. A side note: I'm thinking of going for it, so for those who are interested, hee, well, we could make an outing out of it.   2)  urlLink  Love Lane   Date: 7 Feb Venue: Open field beside Jurong East MRT Time: Not given Cost: Free! This sounded interesting. I think it's like a carnival set in the 60s. It's good for those who stay in the west are too lazy to get their butts down to Orchard on a Friday night.   3)  urlLink  Confessions of Three Unmarried Women   Date: 13 - 16 Feb Venue: Victoria Theatre Time: 8pm Cost: $21, $26, $31, $36, $41 Ooh! A play! As mentioned in the tagline, it's a play for singles and doubles. It is directed by Selena Tan (Under One Roof), and stars Amy Cheng (First Touch), Debra Teng (lady from Modern Jazz for Beginners), Suzan Karim, Melissa Wong and Loh Loke Pin.  A side note: I'll also be going for this one as soon as I can enthusiastic friends to go with me. Will give a review of it. 
      
</post>
<date>27,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Hall Updates   Guess who I spotted a few nights ago lurking around my hall? Ms Black Undies and the malignant growth by her side. Yes apparently she is now staying at the other end of my block after vacating the room next to mine during the holidays. Sheesh.. 
      
</post>
<date>27,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Much Ado About Relationships   An article in the Straits Times appeared a few days ago about the nature of relationships and how it has changed. The writer said that in the past, holding hands constituted as "going steady" and that nowadays, some people do not subscribe to that ideology anymore. A couple can spend the night together, see each other every single minute of the day and yet still consider themselves to be "just friends".   That article reminded me of a boo-boo I made with my friend (let's call her Jane) last year. A certain someone was pursuing her - calling her, visiting her etc. One day, she told me that they held hands and asked me what it meant. In all honesty, I don't see how holding hands can be considered going steady. So I told her that he liked her enough to hold hands but they were still just friends. Apparently, I was wrong. He did consider that as "going steady" and his friend was totally surprised as to how I came to my conclusion and conveniently called it "weird".  But seriously. How can holding hands equate to "let's be together?" How much should one or can one read into the act of hand holding? This goes with hugs and even kisses (french kissing or sucking face doesn't count). I'm no expert on this topic, having had only one relationship in my life, but I'm puzzled as to how people define the boundary between being "just friends" and "going steady".   Can just platonic friends hold hands? Similarly, can people like each other and yet not go steady? That's something to think about.... 
      
</post>
<date>27,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
         Cravings, Fetishes and Fantasies     As I walked around Jurong Point, something beautiful gleamed from afar like a jewel in the sun. It was perfect; the shiny black box and the pictures on its cover. Ahhhhhhhhhhh... it was the PC-game of Lord of the Rings. The words "PC-Game" on its front filled me with extreme joy. I no longer have to save money to get myself a PS2 (that's Playstation 2, for the uninitiated) in order to play the PS version of LOTR. I've been  craving   for that baby ever since I tried out the PS version at a Sony roadshow. Fantastic graphics as well as characters, and it's the type of RPG (role-playing game) that I really love. Move over, Diablo. Aside from LOTR, I saw 5 boxes of  The Sims  - Expansion pack, Living large, et al. OOoooh.. I tried hard not to water at the sight of those shiny boxes. How can a person fall in love twice in a day? I know where my next allowance is going to go to now. *grins*    Fetishes  aren't my cup of tea. It would certainly be interesting to read about a fetish for kinky underwear. But I'm not that perversed. :) If I could pick any fetish to have, I would want to have a fetish for shoes. That is one fetish I wouldnt' mind cultivating. After watching one too many seasons of Sex and the City (SATC), I've come to love those Manolo Blahniks that cost about $400 a pair. The way it fits into one's foot, the design, the color, those little straps and those high, high, heels.... Oh-so-sexy and oh-so-expensive....  Everybody has some kind of  fantasy . I'm willing to bet good money on that fact. Perversed, extreme, bizarre, or simply idealistic, fantasies are exciting to have. My fantasies are sedate, unlike what many of you may think.. haha.. As much as I've said otherwise, I do not wish to  be a pole dancer!! But I do fantasize of performing in public. And who knows? I may just do it... Performance is by invitation only though... hahaha... 
      
</post>
<date>27,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       I Lost My Muse   My muse ran away when the electricity tripped in my hall last night. It's coming back to me now, though. So get ready for the next post. 
      
</post>
<date>27,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Clarifications   I was a virgin clubber then!! :) And hey, for those who want to have a good time clubbing, you can come to me. No sex, no smooching, no groping.. But other than that, I'm game for anything. Oh wait, I'm not into  menage a trois  or any other kinky stuff you people can think of.   I'm not a big fan of mambo nights either, but it is EXTREMELY fun to diss everyone that does that schronized dance routine shit. Am I being mean for doing that? Hell yeah. But it's effing fun. Mambo people (what the heck do you call them anyway? Mambers? hahah) can form the 5th major race in Singapore.   And the one-liners that guys use on girls are hilarious!! I mean H.I.L.A.R.I.O.U.S. "err, you dance very well. What's your name?" or "You look like my friend" or "Is that guy your boyfriend?" Sigh.. A word of advice, guys. Please don't use such lame lines on us.   [As I'm writing this, Lady Marmalade is playing in the background.]
      
</post>
<date>26,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Clubbing Insights   I'm not a regular clubber: In fact, i've only stepped into the what-i-can-only-call-a-music-underground filled with loud-mouthed, half-high-and-crazed teenagers 4 times. My club-de-virgining experience was Mambo night at Zouk to celebrate the A-level results. Despite donning my most gung-ho, most randy outfit i could put together, I looked about as sexy as the old auntie hanging outside the loos eying each entrant with a watchful eye to see if they flush. So, anyway, upon queuing up to enter (despite valiant attempts to strike it with the 2 yokozuna-lookalike bouncers at the door, and paying an EXTRAORDINARY exorbitant $22 buckeroos to place my feet onto the black carpet) and entering, i came to the self-reckoning conclusion that i;ve missed my teenagedomhood. Man, the music was LOUD (at least several gazillion decibals, sooner or later you can have your pwn private band banging away between your head and eardrums), the crowd was raunchy was hell-of-a young. They had da moves and da grooves...shmuck, and i was the only 'kid' there downing my 2 free drinks with sparkling ribena. Geez. But i sure don;t envy the poor babes who spent half their day plucking their brows, shaving their legs, making up their faces, only to be thrown up all over by some enthusiatic underaged drunk who probably tried to say hello but his gut contents came out and introduced itself instead.  In my second experience, I was a little smarter --- &gt; i hid near the curtains and did my stuff: observing the crowd. I gather those punks must be regulars: For one thing..they knew not only the moves to EVERY song, but they even knew what song was going to come up next!!!! DUH HUH! ?????? All over the place ??????  My 3rd and 4th time were conciliatory accepted invites to NTU bashes. The first in year one..with dancing queen, my gal pal, and my ex-roomate. These gals were clubbers, even then: I was still the kid from the block. Anyway, hell, we dragged our butts to the platform and shook it for all it was worth. Hiak! Talk about making things happen...  My last time was another bash at Orange, where I, upon 21 years, first stepped into the famed MS. It sucked. My company was great. But the music sucked. I left, swearing no more would i cram myself into another club: My old faithful Sony hi-fi awaits my return and usage faithfully...
      
</post>
<date>26,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       The Latest Craze in Japan   From a japanese magazine comes the latest trend in Japanese fashion: Skirts with transparent behinds!!!   Whoa....just what do the guys make out of that..visible undies, thongs, g-strings, the i-don;t-wear-underwear regulars....
      
</post>
<date>26,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      heh heh heh..  i get the feeling that some (not all, i emphasize) seem to want the WHOLE world (or at least the whole MRT carriage) to know that they are an item. Even if they're not sitting, they're leaning against each other, cuddling, nibbling at ears, neck, any facial area.. pressing up to each other as if that bloody carriage were empty and there were not a million pairs of eyes boring holes right into their heads: OMIGOSH! What a show: Bang, bite me. What are they trying to say? "Ooh, look at me, Ay gott a boyyy-friendd/girrrllfriend...----&gt;&gt;ENVY ME????" Geez...get a life, and some ectasy while you're at it.  
      
</post>
<date>26,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Clubbing   This is a topic close to my heart. I love clubbing and I wish I'm in a smoky club dancing to trashy music rather than being in the computer lab doing my Audit tutorial. I love the pulsating music, the bright lights and even the crowd. Yes, the crowd makes or breaks a club. The crowd defines how popular a club is. In Singapore, there are many clubs that cater to all sorts of music. You want R/Hip Hop? Well, hop (pardon the pun) on down to Lox and you can grind the night away. Fancy some Retro shite? Then Zouk's Mambo night is just the thing for you. Trashy top 40 hits? One need not look beyond Next Page to get one's fill of trashy music and trashy people.   For some people, clubbing is a way to meet new "friends" or more realistically, ONS (one-night-stands). For others, the experience of clubbing is incomplete without a jug of beer, long island tea or anything that strikes their fancy. As for me, I club for the sole purpose of dancing. I'm not interested in the drinks, I'm not interested in the people, just get me a dance floor, good music and I'll be happy.   Unfortunately, I don't think that it is possible to club just for the sake of dancing. Many a time, I've encountered over-enthusiastic males trying to get fresh on the dance floor. I doubt it's cos I'm oh-so-hot (I know I am, but that's a different matter. *grin*). More often then not, these males just approach or grab any females that go by until they get one that responds. And, rest assured, they will find one.   
      
</post>
<date>26,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        Belated Announcements    To all Harry Potter fans!  The fifth edition of this famous series would be out on sale on the 21st of June at 7am (Singapore time). This is to coincide with the London sale which starts at midnight. This latest edition called Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix is one highly anticpated book, especially after the two successful movie adaptations.   50,000 copies are going to be shipped in, and I'll bet that the book will be out of stock by the end of June. Bookings for the book can be made up to one week in advance, although I've got no specific details about it.   So hoorah for us fans! All I can say to Rowlings is,  "IT'S ABOUT BLOODY TIME!" 
      
</post>
<date>26,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Random Musings   As I made my way back to school on the ever-so-reliable MRT, I was sitting strategically between two couples, both different and yet so alike in behavior. Are couples, by nature, exhibitionists? Guy will flick girl's hair, girl will place hand nicely at guy's crotch. I was ready to keel over by the time we reached Kallang. Thank goodness couple #1 alighted at that station. Couple #2 was less annoying. But guy loved to put his hands on girl's thigh and she was wearing such a short skirt! She, on the other hand, had her hand oh-so-close to his groin.   I'm not against couples or relationships per se, but man... Get a room!
      
</post>
<date>25,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       THIS IS TERRIBLE!!!!!!   The world is no longer a safe place....  Check this Link Out: Your passprt information revealed!  urlLink Click Here  -----Original Message----- From: Arshad Kashif, Muhammad  Subject: FW: important      Dear Friends, &gt;&gt; &gt;&gt;From the following mentioned site, the person can see his (her)  National Passport's details. It's very serious. How can they place very  confidential information on the net. I dont think that they have any right  to publish your confidential information on the net, globally. Please  check this out, and let's discuss signing a petition.  &gt;&gt; &gt;&gt;   urlLink Click Here   
      
</post>
<date>25,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Latest Alien Breakthrough!!!   XTRA, XTRA! ----&gt;&gt;&gt; A Mouse Was Found on Mars!!!  Check this authentic picture...      
      
</post>
<date>25,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
         Reviews     Modern Dance for Beginners      Do not let the title fool you. This is a play and has got nothing to do with dance. This is a play about love and sex, starring Mark Waite (the prat from Moulmein High) and Debra Teng (from I-don't know-where). This play is actually a series of scenes depicting many people. The two central characters are: Owen and Frances, played by Waite and Teng.   Commendable performances by Waite and Teng. Aside from Owen and Frances, they also play a host of other characters as well. Waite is a natural and his dialogue is sharper and wittier than Teng's. He moves in between scenes and characters effortlessly and the audience is able to see the change from one character to another. Teng, on the other hand, is slightly more awkward. Maintaining a Brit accent proved too be a slight problem for her, thus making her sound Singaporean at times. Mind you, this play is supposedly set in Britain. Her acting was a little wooden at times but on the whole, she could carry off her many roles as well.   This play goes to show that class/appearance plays no role in love and sex. The upper-class miss is one raunchy kitten who just wants to be taken by the handyman. The wimpy office colleague goes around hard most of the time. The promiscuous girl just wants to be loved. These issues are dealt with in the play but without any moral high-handedness.    
      
</post>
<date>25,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Attention!  This site can now be found on GOOGLE!  In conjunction with my plans for world domination, I've added this site to Google's database. Try doing a search on "tales of the Mundane" and it'll be listed on the 2nd page.   
      
</post>
<date>25,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Love the updated site! :) Two thumbs up, and toes if i can manage!   Had a similar experience with a beetle. But the one that flew into my balcony was HUGE and BLACK. And I was cheering it on because it was trying to fly out, but the windows weren't opened wide enough. The darn thing couldn't figure it out. But then again, beetles aren't very smart...   Oh well... 
      
</post>
<date>25,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Like the Updated Site?   Post your comments.
      
</post>
<date>23,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       MAKE LOVE NOT WAR       lets not fight it never works out and we will never win
      
</post>
<date>21,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      The beetle was a scarab beetle, i think. Gross looking thing
      
</post>
<date>19,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        Hall Life: The Final Chapter   It was foolish of me to think that i can have a bug-free life during my last semester in hall. Just 15 mins ago, a HUGE, and i mean HUGE beetle flew into my room and landed itself at the hinge of the door. Needless to say, my roommie and i screamed in the hope that we wld scare that mutant away. But, we weren't so lucky. Mutant beetle refused to budge and closing the door was risky as it cld either be squashed to death, which was fine by me, or it wld fly into our room and we would be in deep shit. So, me, being my brilliant self, thought that i cld push it out of the room using my broom. Hah! Problems soon arose. Firstly, I cldn't even get the beetle to move. It wasn't afraid of the broom. Secondly, it kept making this peculiar noise. It sounded as though it was sneezing. But I think it's just some defense mechanism where it sprays its enemy, hence the sneezing noise. Finally, it latched itself onto my broom, but now, I had a new problem. It was stuck on my broom. After a heart-stopping moment where we thought the beetle moved away frm the broom, we screamed, I pushed the broom out of the door and closed it shut.  Now, I refuse to be held hostage by a mere beetle! No doubt, one helluva beetle, but still, it's a darn BEETLE. I used my roomie's plastic cup. I trapped that bloody thing, put it inside a plastic bag, and promptly threw the whole thing into the dustbin.  Is that Brilliant? or is that Brilliant?   
      
</post>
<date>19,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      cant agree more with lester.. when i look at a person's feet the first thing that i look at are the toenails... for guys dirty toenails or clean, well trimmed toenails, for girls the colour of the nail polish suggest something abt the person.  
      
</post>
<date>19,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       If Clothes Maketh The Man, How do Shoes Fit in?   This is the following part to the section on feet.   No one lives in a Cinderella-world where shoes magically fit ones feet. Notice how she has such tiny feet, whereas her stepsisters and stepmother have ugly, bunion-filled ones. Nowadays, no one gives a hoot about feet shape particularly when it comes to buying shoes. While my earlier post about long skinnies wearing stilletoes and broad stumpies confined to low-heeled shoes, in reality, this situation does not exist.   It seems that shoes maketh the person. Court shoes to go with that black suit for that formal, executive look. Boots to go with that mini skirt for that cowboy chic wear. Chunky platform shoes with the weird dress for that Jap anime look. And of course, slinky shoes to go with that gorgeous cocktail dress. The combination can go on. Whether one's feet can actually fit into those shoes comfortably, nobody knows. The point is, the shoes complete one's outfit and in that sense, completes one's identity.   Notice how I rarely touch on the subject of men's shoes. To a certain extent, a man is not defined by his shoe. Well, not as much as a woman, at least.    
      
</post>
<date>19,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       everybody looks at feet       im facinated with feet i know that doesnt account for everybody but too bad if you really dont think so write your own article in fact i love toenails they tell you everything about the person chipped toenails reflect nonchalence overly trimmed toenails portray paranoia and the list goes on my own toenails are just plain awful which means im just plain awful  oh and back to feet theyre all fine to me fat or skinny its the toenails that count baby
      
</post>
<date>19,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        Who Looks at Feet?   I've got ugly feet. I must admit that, although I like to think of them as a "dancer's feet". That's a euphemism to say that my feet look deformed. But what exactly is the perfect feet? Long and skinny? Frankly, I get turned off by long, skinny feet. To me, they look weird, like a skeleton's feet. No doubt, just like  body size, long and skinny feet can suit all types of shoes. What about broad feet with stumpy toes?   Would people with long skinny feet look down upon those with broad stumpy ones? Does the type of feet affect one's entire being? Long skinny wears stilettoes, hence leads a fancy life where stilletoes are the norm. Broad stumpy, on the other hand, wears low-heeled sedate shoes since she can't fit into stilletoes. THe life she leads would be just like her shoes - sedate.   Guys have no such problem. Lanky or stumpy, shoes are made with a one shape fits all mentality. Any guy can fit into a pair of Kenneth Coles as easily as he can fit into cheapo Bata sandals. Would his life be affected by his shoes? I doubt so.   But who looks at feet?     
      
</post>
<date>19,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        Dancing Queen is the Ultimate WHOSER here!!  Brilliant post using movie themes there.. =0)
      
</post>
<date>18,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
         WELCOME TO SEMESTER 2 WEEK THREE.....NoOoOoOoOoOoOoOo....   Boy, oh boy..hitting the count of week 3 this sunday night.....  HooRAY to the Golden Globe Awards tomorroWW!!! GO Lord of the rings!! WOO HOOO!.. *sigh 
      
</post>
<date>18,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      That's moi! :) *curtsies, waves and flying kisses*  For those of you who were out today and donated generously to the people rattling tins for RDA (Riding for the Disabled Association of Singapore), give yourselves a pat on the back. Those who didn't, smack yourselves on the head!   Would like to mention that probably the BEST way to get through a crowd of people in say, orchard road, is to HOLD A DONATION TIN. Generally more preferable to going out stinking of fish (rotten, fresh et. al.). 
      
</post>
<date>17,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       New!   In my excitement to write about my life... I have forgotten to say that there is a new member on this site!  A big welcome to  FORAMINIFERA  aka  Spaceman Spiff ! 
      
</post>
<date>16,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      "I LOVE rock and roll!"   Sorry, Britney made me say that. She's quite insistent that way...   Anyway, a big HELLO to everyone. Its rather late now, so I'll post something more intelligent *cough* and thought provoking *cough cough* when... I... uhmm... sometime in the near future (Hey, some of us live in hope!). Rest assured, it will not have anything to do with Britney... but then again, it just might... ;)   Goodnight! 
      
</post>
<date>14,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Contest   What do the words in Italics in the previous post have in common?  No prizes for guessing though. 
      
</post>
<date>14,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
         I'm in LOOOOOOOOOOOOOVE      
      
</post>
<date>11,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Reviews: The Ring   I've not watched good scary movies in a long time. Asian movies don't count cos I think Chinese/Jap horror movies are much better than English ones. This adaptation of the Japanese movie "Ringu" does not deviate much from its original form. There are new bits in the English one that wasn't on the Jap one. For example,  the son of the reporter plays a larger role in this movie and he can communicate with Samara/Sadako. While the Jap version was a masterpiece of mood and atmosphere, this Hollywood adaptation is less subtle. Hollywood is Hollywood where being loud and obvious sells (probably because Americans are just dumb and can't appreciate the finer points of being subtle). But there is a sense of anticpation when watching as audiences are drawn into the story. Watching the Jap one does kill the joy in watching this version somewhat but it's similar to reading a book and then watching the movie-version of it.   However, as mentioned, the adaptation is fair. I wasn't disappointed when I watched it. On the whole, I would pay at most $7.50 for it. It was fun getting scared and screaming along with tons of other screamy girls in the theatre!
      
</post>
<date>10,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Important Message   ok guys.... im not gonna tok abt movies... but its something dat concerns us as students... not sure if this site is visited by many ppl... but still... its a free form of advertisement!  pls visit  http://www.PetitionOnline.com/NUS/petition.html   its titled Why the NUS Student is Angry...  n im hoping dat u ppl out there may support wat me n my fren ar trying to do... basically get our opinions heard, cos im quite sure we wun be able to change anything much... STforum has juz replied dat they arent gonna publish the letter, so we ar planning to refine it abit, then send it again together wif those signatures n the petition website... oh, n we ar also gonna send the letter to the relevant authorities at nus, like OSA n the deans or something... its aredi been sent to impotent nussu....  i started this thing since wed (8 jan) afternoon, n up till this moment have garnered ard 150+ signatures minus those fake ones... im hoping for more... so plees support! too bad if u ar in NTU tho, cos only lucky ppl stuck in the stoopid nus system can sign up =p
      
</post>
<date>09,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        Now it's my turn to write about the best/worst films of 2002    The honor of being the worst film in 2002 goes to " Slap Her, She's French! ".   Aargh! This movie is BAD. BAD. BAD. Teen flick gone wrong, and that's saying alot since almost all teen flicks are never right. But this is wrong. It's so wrong that it shouldn't have been shown in the cinema and gone straight to a video release, not even a VCD or DVD release. A VIDEO release. I'm not gonna bother writing about the plot. It stars whats-her-face, the girl who acted as Piper?Phoebe? in Coyote Ugly with a BAD french accent, that even I can do it better.    The second worst movie : "Star Wars - Attack of the Clones"   I can't remember the last movie I watched that made me cringe cos of its really, and I mean,  really  corny lines. Even Hayden whats-his-name wasn't cute enough to make me like the show. But Natalie Portman is a  HOTTIE .    The third worst movie : "Queen of the Damned"   The queen had a screen time of only about 30 minutes in the entire show! There is no plot and Lestat the vampire, played by Stuart Townsend, who was the original Aragorn but he was fired i think, thank god, was just sucky. A good waste of $6.50. Even the gory bits weren't gory. Aaliyah, who played the queen, had a funny accent which was supposed to be Egyptian but sounded abit Hispanic.    Best Film since Memento - Insomnia   This movie stars Robin Williams (in a non-comedic role!) and Al Pacino. A fantastic movie directed by the same guy who did Memento, Christopher Nolan. This movie is dark and very drawn out. The viewer is made to feel like Al's character who is having insomnia. The nights are long and unbearable and the viewer is treated with a visual of how Al's insomnia is affecting him physically; the tired, blood-shot eyes. Robin Williams is surprisingly good as the bad man. Very low key acting, very un-robin williams. One of the best shows I've watched without being a big budget Hollywood blockbuster. We can expect great movies from Mr Nolan. 
      
</post>
<date>09,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        my first movie of 2003   ah so 9 days into the new year and ive watched my first movie the wedding banquet doesnt count this is the first one in a real cinema and its  the experiment  rather disturbing show about a prison experiment gone wrong an explicit insight into how man abuses authority given to him and the unthinkable consequences of that freedom however the music choices of the show are questionable and so are certain character and plot involvements but on the whole a poignant and shocking take on man taking things into his own hands watch it one of these days cos theres probably nothing much else worth watching
      
</post>
<date>08,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        Best Films of 2002!!   (according to my worthless opinion)  alrite alrite... since i've nothing better to do... no thanx to nus screwing up my module selection (i was the only person i noe among all my frens to have been allocated only 1 mod after balloting, i muz be a damn lucky guy)   Best Comedy of 2002   *drumrolls* the award goes to  About A Boy   !!! a comedy wif touching undercurrents of single-parenthood n interpersonal relationships... witty n dry brit humour performed by hugh grant (who else?? john cleese is too old n mr brosnan has associative personality disorder as mr bond)   Best Horror of 2002   hmm... this is tough.... cos there werent really many horror movies this yr... but  Dark Water  has to get it. From the director of The Ring, this jap film portrays many of the scary elements so essential to the jap horror genre these days... u dun actually see the ghost.. the anticipation n dread of seeing 1 simply drives u nuts... also wif an underlying plot of a mother's luv for her daughter, to the delight of parents who enjoy watching scary movies??   Best Suspense/Thriller of 2002   well... well... is there any compeition??  Red Dragon  is it!! anthony hopkins... edward norton... wif a riveting performance thrown in by ralph fiennes... wat more do u need to win this category???   Best Drama of 2002   yesyes... all jude law fans... its ur day!  Road to Perdition  gets this even tho jude law appeared in only 3 scenes in the movie?? Tom hanks plays a father to a son... Paul Newman plays a father to Tom Hanks n another son... makes the father-son r/s kindof surreal n poetic, but realistic nonetheless....   Best Action/Adventure of 2002   wah lau...  Lord of the Rings: The Two Towers  lah!! how many times muz i say!?
      
</post>
<date>07,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       PICTURES!            Go  urlLink here  to see more pictures of friends and family. (my friends but not my family)
      
</post>
<date>07,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
         More Reviews     Gangs of New York   A compelling movie spanning almost 3 hours. Tells the tale of rival gangs in 19th century New York City. The opening sequence shows 2 rival gangs, "The Dead Rabbits" and "The Natives" getting ready to fight. This fight scene is disturbing and awfully bloody. Even this writer herself couldn't help cringing while watching the show and she loves blood and gore.   The political situation in the US, (the civil war occurred then and Lincoln was recruiting soldiers to fight) was juxtaposed against the political situation in New York, where everybody owes and everybody pays. Irish immigrants were despised by the Natives (men who were born and bred on US soil) and officials are corrupt.    Being the great reviewer that I am, I shan't write a whole long passage about it. Go watch. Cameron Diaz is surprisingly not annoying, and neither was Leonardo. If you aspect me to gush over them, forget it.        
      
</post>
<date>07,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        the return of punctuationless man   aha so the one who refuses to put an end to any sentence is back well i watched the wedding banquet today in school during soci lecture today and it was a pretty good show not a bad start to the year eh aha now everybodys talking about school and im talking about silly old films sorta lagging i suppose but who gives a rotten donut about that anyway well back to the show was a nice take on a chinese living america who lives in with his gay partner but stages a mock wedding to please his visiting parents but things get out of control thought it was done pretty well so i guess thats a good sign for better movies to come this year my favourite movie of last year was one hour photo starring robin williams as the harmless looking intrusive man who works at a photo developing shop rather disturbing but shot in a very clinical and engaging way so what were your fave movies of last year 
      
</post>
<date>03,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
         Back to school....    Well, well, well, whaddaya know? After 2 mths, we are back to a daily dose of lessons, tutorials and tons of readings. For some, it's still the first year, while for others, it is the FINAL semester! And for others still, it's still neither here nor there.   The first day of school brought surprises for me. I have new neighbors and a new roommate. All first years!! Aargh. Apparently Ms BLack Undies moved out and in place, I've got 2 girls from Comm Studies. First years! Need I say that again? My roommate is a very decent Malay girl, also first year, studying Engineering. Decent meaning that she's totally unlike me, but she doesn't wear the tudung. What do I do with first years?? AArgh. Thankfully, my roommate isn't the gushing, yabbering type cos frankly, I so don't have the energy to start chit chatting and having pow wow sessions with her. I miss my old roommate and now I understand why my second year roommate hardly spoke a word to me. I think by the time I reached my 3rd year, everyone below 20 just seems young, too young. All first years are very excitable esp when living away from home for the first time. But seems that my roommie and I have reached a nice state of silence. Heh. But she loves to keep the door closed and I'm feeling a tad claustrophobic in the room right now.   
      
</post>
<date>03,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        Rina the teenage scoring sensation    well... well... if it isnt rina, the player-manager back after a long spell of suspension n injury... marking her return to the side wif an excellent brace n sending the supporters wild in the stands...   Lord of the Rings - The Two Towers   the list of superlatives juz goes on n on doesnt it? breath-taking shots of backdrops in kiwiland... combined wif out-of-this-world, computer-generated, mind-boggling, adrenaline-pumping (how many more hyphenated adjectives can i find?) cinematography... lets juz say dat the visual effects ar something dat i've neva ever experienced in my life b4 as a movie-goer for 20 yrs... certainly beats Star Wars hands down... u cld imagine y Saruman's evil sidekick (forgot the guy's name, im not a mad fan) teared upon setting eyes on the uruki army... cos mine were on the verge of spilling too during  many scenes.. not cos i was touched emotionally, but simply moved by the utterly amazing scenes b4 my eyes... simply put, its a visual spectacle enuf to set ur heart on an emotional roller-coaster ride   The 2nd vs the 1st   hmm... i gotta disagree wif the gaffer... i find the 2nd was better in terms of storyline n pace... contrary to her view, i found bits dat were draggy in the 1st movie dat were absent in the 2nd =p besides, the battle scene towards the end in the 1st movie was, i felt (even then) kindof lame, cos it seemed dat it was juz ppl in costumes fighting wif nothing impressive... also, as the boss pted out, the amt of humour in the 2nd is much more than dat found in the 1st, so dat its become much more enjoyable on a diff scale... besides... Andy Serkis' voice impression of Smeagol as a schizophrenic "precioussss" fanatic certainly warrants an award of some sort... for other reasons, pls refer to the previous paragraph n aforementioned "visual spectacle"   The movie vs the book   okok... i gotta admit dat i neva even contemplated reading tolkien's books... 1. cos i was neva a big fan of fantasy... 2. cos i din wanna read the bk n get disappointed in the movies dat i was gonna pay at least 6.50 for... anyway, i did actually pay 6.50 for Twin Towers, erm... oops, i mean Two Towers (where did dat slip come from??)... so it werks out to abt 2 bucks per hr of swash-buckling entertainment... much more economic than any bk i'll ever read  ;)
      
</post>
<date>03,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Reviews   Lord of the Rings - The Two Towers   This movie is grandiose. By itself, ie, without taking into consideration that it is a sequel to The Fellowship of the Rings, it is a fantastic show. With beautiful scenery and beautiful people (well, except for Eomer and his funny moustache). The battlescene was MAGNIFICENT. I totally loved it! (For a more pro review, i'm sure you can find other sources to read. :) I'm just gonna gush.)   The Second Vs the First  However, I find that the first movie was better in terms of story line and pace. There were bits that were draggy in the second movie that was absent in the first one. The treebeard scene, for example, was slow. I'm sure that was the effect that Peter Jackson was going for, as Ents are unhasty creatures, but still...    The movie Vs the book  Frankly, I preferrred the book. The book was much darker and conveyed the seriousness of the entire quest. Although the movie was dark, it had funny moments which lightened the mood. I enjoyed the funny scenes, Gimli and his 'toss me over, cos i can't jump that far", Gimli again with "what's going out there?" and Legolas saying "do you want me to describe it to you or do you want me to hand you a box?" had me in stitches. Both scenes were not in the book (thank goodness) but it worked well in the show.  All in all, it was a fair adaptation of Tolkein's book. In a way, it was better that Peter Jackson didn't keep so closely to the book, unlike Harry Potter Chamber of Secrets, because trying to follow very closely to the original material would disappoint alot of fans cos there's no way one can follow everything to a T.  That's just my $0.02 worth. Any comments feel free to let it all out. 
      
</post>
<date>03,January,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       WELCOME BACK!!!!   Seems that I'm not the only one who did a disappearing act over the past 2 months. This site is now a ghost site! Well, I'm hoping that there may still be those who want to post stuff here so as to keep it going. :)   It's 2003 people! New resolutions should have been made and steps taken towards achieving whatever you resolved to do. For me, I resolve to...  1) Weigh less (as always) 2) Still remain single (as opposed to those who want to find their special someones this year) 3) Read every single book by Tolkien (haha i think that would take me a couple of years) 4) Travel!!!!! 5) Learn the salsa 6) Learn to speak spanish  Heh.. I guess that pretty much sums up my new year's resolutions.   A new year, a new beginning.. Sounds cliched, I know. :p
      
</post>
<date>28,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        can you tell your arse from your elbow?    urlLink take the test!   i barely passed
      
</post>
<date>26,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       MORE DYSFUNCTIONAL TESTS!!    What's Your Stripper Name?   Victoria Nun-- cause you favorite saying is you ain't gettin nun     urlLink  What's your stripper name? (female)     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      Which Personality Disorder Do You Have?     histrionic    urlLink   Which Personality Disorder Do You Have?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    Screw you, I'm Brilliant. 
      
</post>
<date>19,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Dysfunctional Test     Raver   hahah.. I'm Raver Bear. I guess if there was a Cabaret Bear, I'd be one too.. :)  I do hate ring pops tho.. But bright shiny things?? Most definitely. I'm into all those bling blings... Just bought shoes that are shiny. Now, all i need is a diamond on each ear, on my neck, around my wrist and on my fingers, and i'll be a happy bear. 
      
</post>
<date>19,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       The Term Break   This is just a euphemism for "there ain't no school, but u still have a shit-load of work to do". Midweek and work is still piling on me. I'm now drowning in my own work. If it was backlog that I have to clear, it wouldn't be so bad, cos it's my own fault that i've got backlog to clear in the first place. But nooooo... projects and more projects have to be done and handed in within the next 2 weeks.   I'll be a hunchback soon, carrying the weight of my work on my shoulders. A pack mule would be useful now. :)
      
</post>
<date>19,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       More Reviews    Chicago      I love musicals. Moulin Rouge, Phantom of the Opera and Les Miz. I've watched them all, with the exception of Cats and Chicago. I can't compare the movie versus the original musical cos i didn't watch the musical but I really loved the movie.   Plot-wise it's no Memento. Basically, it revolves around the life of Roxie Hart (Renee Zelwegger) and her trial. A short recap. Roxie murdered her lover as he lied to her (don't all men??). He had promised her that he would introduce her to club managers so that she would be able to be a star. She tried to get her husband to take the blame for it but he found out and therefore landed her in jail. Her lawyer is the very slick Billy Flynn (Richard Gere) who has never lost a trial, and with the princely sum of $5,000 he would be able to defend you and get you out of jail. There is also rivalry between Roxie and Velma Kelly (Catherine Zeta-Jones) who's in jail for a double homicide. She murdered her sister and her husband cos they were doing "the spread eagle" heh. Velma is the "star" in jail, but Roxie, being a media-whore wants the limelight as well.  The main draw of this movie is the SOUNDTRACK. I absolutely loved the soundtrack and the performances that I wanted to clap in the theatre. Unlike Moulin Rouge where the soundtrack is a rehash of old hits, Chicago's soundtrack is ORIGINAL. Check out the "Cell Block Tango" where 6 ladies tells us why the men they killed deserved to die. I loved another number which showed Mama Morton performing a very Mamasan-like number. Queen Latifah adds some groove and pizazz to the number. The lyrics are hilarious!!!  There are also a number of surprise stars. Lucy Liu, Mya and Christine Baranski (Cybill) make acting appearances in the movie.   Ratings: I would pay $8.50 to watch it. I'd pay it TWICE. :)
      
</post>
<date>19,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Reviews    Catch Me If You Can      This movie is actually worth watching. :) Tom Hanks as always was a delight to see and Leonardo wasn't annoying! Yay for us, non-Leo fans. I think he has redeemed himself with his 2 recent movies (Gangs of NY and Catch Me) and we can now forget that he ever acted in the Titanic.   Catch Me is a very light-hearted show, without any heavy drama a la Spielberg's last film, A.I. This mood is seen in the costumes, very pink-hued and the soundtrack as well. I need not describe the plot, as it has been described to death in all the reviews found in the papers.   In terms of acting, I think Spielberg did a good job in casting these 2 stars, as well as Christopher Walken as Frank Sr. The chemistry between the two main leads is obvious, which makes them more enjoyable to watch. If one wants to probe into the relationship dynamics of the show, then, Tom Hanks' character is the father figure that Frank Jr so desperately needs in his life. His own father, Frank Sr, hardly gives the boy the discipline that he craves. "Tell me to stop," cries Frank Jr. "I can't," says Frank Sr. While the movie glosses over the exact reason why Frank goes on his conning spree, one can assume it is due to the breakup of his family and his desire to "get everything back" so that his family would be together again. This is unfortunately very idealistic and in the end, things of course, don't turn out as planned.   A tidbit: The real Frank Abagnale made a cameo appearance as one of the French policemen.   Rating: I'd pay $7.00 to watch it. 
      
</post>
<date>19,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        more personality tests     Aryan Bear    urlLink   Which Dysfunctional Care Bear Are You?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla    there you go..no more braggin abt how cool your renton or sick boy character is and how well that fits your cool character. take the real test: which lousy care bear are you?
      
</post>
<date>19,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       And so the story goes.... di da di...   I'm baaaaack! I've not been updating this site for about a week now. Sheesh... it seems so long ago. I feel so tired and am doubting whether I made the right choice by being in this course. Sigh.... It's no secret that I hate accountancy, and all things to do with this course. Would things be better if I did something that I enjoyed? On hindsight, I would rather have done something I really enjoyed than to do something which would make my parents happy. Choices.. Choices.. Choices.... There's no right or wrong... Just bad choices or good ones.  Waaaaaaaaaaaaah.. But i'm so unhappy....... :(    [yeah yeah... allow me to indulge in a moment of self-pity]
      
</post>
<date>17,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        Leaving the Motherland   Argh! One day to go before I bid farewell to family, friends and glorious food, all for the sake of SCHOOL!! Damn NUS for not offering the course I want. *sob* No more roti prata, char kway teow, chicken rice and fried fish soup! Goodbye garlic naan, sushi, nasi briyani, mee goreng and fried wanton... Hello hall food... *gag* I'm gonna go eat my fill now, if anyone needs me, I'll be in the kitchen! 
      
</post>
<date>12,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Karaoke rawks my sawks... :)  
      
</post>
<date>12,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       KARAOKE PICTURES   Sick or not, I still had time to party.. :) such a hedonist.     Such emotion. Such passion!    Girls just wanna have fun!    Group shot  For more pics (risque as well as chaste ones) click  urlLink here 
      
</post>
<date>12,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Gah.. I'm sick and this is how I feel right now   
      
</post>
<date>11,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Are we all like Marquis De Sade?    For those who actually know who he is, then YAY good for you! If you are, then this is the  urlLink website  for you!! Don't let it's pink facade fool you. Watch the eps and tell me what you think.   
      
</post>
<date>10,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       My favourite things   Do you have a favourite thing that would probably make someone puke/feel disgusted/think it's simply ghastly? It could be a smelly pillow, a penchant for the macabre, or simply something grosteque? Well, i do.  My favourite bug; the small brown beetle. In fact, one particular member of this from the family Chrysomelid[ae] is calling up my chest towards my neck (again). These bugs come and 'bug' me quite often....hey, where did it go????? Uh oh..
      
</post>
<date>10,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Sex and the City    Mundane Sex Shop Directory   Now, you don;t have to be in the infamous desker road, red light glaring geylang alleys, or sleazy nightclubs doubled as brothels to get your little naughty toys! What am I saying? Simply, our prudish, stick-up-in-the-butt country does boast some naughty naughty shops of our own. And no, I'm not referring to the House of Condoms or Condomania that we thought (or at least I did) was the closest thing to sex humor we can get. Those 2 shops are at PSLE level. These shops deserve honours. Things sold at these shops leave little to the imagination. Dildos, sex games, lingerie that don;t cover what they ought to, that reliable sizzling pair of handcuffs, blow-up dolls.... The question is not that these shops exist, but rather, would you dare step in! Alone, or with friends? Would you relive your childishness all over again by blushing uncontrollably at the lewd products or appearing shocked at the variety? What would you do if you bumped into an aquaintance/friend/ and worse, relative? Dare you make a purchase by walking as nonchalantly as one who has been caught with a hand in the cookie jar and doesn't give a damn about who but the cookie? Dare you look in the eye(s) of the cashier, or your fellow shop-mates?  Get your kicks at: 1) Adult World: Far East Plaza #05-03 2) Black Pie: Bugis Village #01-03 3) Crazy Condoms: Orchard Towers #01-14 4) Aphrodisiac: Chinatown Point #02-12 5) U4Ria: MIdpoint Orchard #02-11A, Peninsula Plaza #04-54  The challenge to drop by one or all of these shops and getting myself something is seeding.... 
      
</post>
<date>10,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Kara-You-Oke, Kara-Me-Oke   I experienced my first karaoke session on sat. hee.. and i must say i enjoyed myself immensely. I'm a natural star! We sang english songs, mucked through a chinese one and attempted latino songs as well!! 3 hours wasn't enough to satisfy the desire to perform. We sang, we danced, it was like performing in our very own version of "Fame - The Musical".   Can't sing? No one cares!! Just turn on the "AD" and the fake singer will cover ur sad attempts to hold a note. Haha... It was a blast. 
      
</post>
<date>08,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Mundane Info  Ok. One thing to note, just cos a guy stands at the bar counter doesn't mean that he's the bartender. Made a slight boo-boo at China Black on Sat. Was at the bar counter waiting to be served, drink coupons in my hand. The guy next to me was getting glasses with ice and pouring whisky/brandy (cldn't tell which is which) from the huge bottle at the counter into those glasses. He then turned to me and asked what drink I wanted. Innocently, I gave him my coupons and said i wanted a glass of O.J (for me) and a beer (for my friend). He gave them to the bar guy on the other side of the counter and asked if I wanted to have a glass of that whisky/brandy. At this point, I was still clueless. I was wondering why in the world the bartender wld offer me a drink, if i'm supopsed to pay for it. When I declined, he told me his name was Eric and that he WASN'T a bartender. I promptly took my drinks and left. haha.. what a dumbass. But hey, in my defense, it was dark and smoky. I cldn't see a thing. And secondly, if a guy who stood at the counter asked what drink i wanted, of cos i assumed he worked there!! 
      
</post>
<date>08,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Minutes of Fame   Just something to say: the salsa is HOT! Whoo hoo! My dad and I were caught on the camera, taken pictures off, and interviewed by some reporter for some magazine..how bloody cool is that??!!  A site to visit:   urlLink    The official WHOSE LINE IS IT ANYWAY site = with clips, full episodes and news! YES YES YES!
      
</post>
<date>08,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       n in response to the Queen of Dance's posting on her views abt Native Speaker n Linguistic Ownership... here ar some excerpts from my postings in my sch forum...   The idea that language belongs to everybody and nobody at the same time, is, i believe, a desirable attitude which all language users should cultivate.    It may be true that language does serve as a marker of cultural and/or national identity, but such cultural markers are mere artificial social labels which proliferate ethnocentrism and chauvinism, and can do no good for a world striving for mutual understanding and peace.  Language as cultural/identity marker also does not validate a claim that the language hence belongs to the individual (who is a member of the particular sociocultural group), which immediately implies exclusive ownership, such that peoples outside of the sociocultural group cannot claim the language to be his/her own native tongue.  The reasons for this are simple.  1. with English as an example, the culmination of present-day English is a result of a large amount of words being "borrowed" from other languages, such that the number of loan-words is significantly more than words originating from Old English.  So does English really "belong" to the French or Greeks or Romans?  2.  There exists no natural state of law which decides who owns what language.  Is the language "owned" by the 1st sociocultural group that develops the language and uses it as a distinctive marker of identity?  If so, then the Americans cant own English as well. Who decides who owns what? You, me or tony blair?  Anyway, the process of language developing into a marker of identity is a long and protracted affair, rather than one with overnight clarity, so how do we determine which group developed it 1st?  If linguistoc ownership is not determined on a "1st come 1st served" basis, then any group which uses it as a marker of identity may stake equal claim "owning" the language rite?  My view is that language cannot be "owned" exclusively by any group or individual (since there exists no natural law that determines "ownership", so that any self-proclaimed "ownership" must be an artificial social construct n hence can be disputed by other societies not subscribing to such a construct).   While if one states that one can truly claim to "own" a language it wld almost immediately imply a certain trivialisation n marginalisation of users who do not "own" the language.  Hence, more importantly, the arguments about the ambiguity of "native speaker" isnt just a debate about terminology per se, but involves far more insiduous cultural underpinnings regarding social, racial and linguistic discriminations.  Much like the fight for equal rights and opportunities for all, it is a social debate we cannot afford to lose.
      
</post>
<date>07,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Music Review.....   yesyes... even i, the crude tone-deaf troll, listens to music.... i dunno if u guys ar into the local music scene... but if theres a reason for u to do dat now, it wld be Concave Scream...... juz d/led a few songs by the band after my fren told me abt it, n i was impressed enuf to d/l more on my own... Driven... Caged... Fade ar the few songs u can find on kazaa quite easily... but i tink Shattered is the best... full of originality n a gd lead singer voice... i neva tot s'poreans cld be capable of making such gd music.... n im glad i've been proven wrong =)
      
</post>
<date>07,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Dancing in the Moonlight   It's sad that Singaporeans aren't very romantic. Tonight's event would have been a good time for couples to learn how to dance together. But hey, it was still good fun. Us gals cldn't be bothered that we had no dates and no love interest, we just wanted to have a good time. And a good time it was! I have never missed latin dance so much! It was fun learning how to salsa and cha cha, taught by the same instructor that i used to be under!! Shawn and Gladys studio organised the event and the dances were taught by Shawn. Met up with dance friends who were there and it felt like old times.   Latin dance is by far the best dance to learn, in my humble opinion. Look at the moves... Even the music is great as well.. We went back sweaty and tired, temporarily forgetting our achy calves. :) Looking for the next opportunity to salsa the night away.... 
      
</post>
<date>07,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Celebrity Sightings   And so I was at the Romancing Singapore event with Selin and Cale. We went ga-ga over Pierre Png, who really looks much better in real life. Andrea is very thin and very fair. There was also a Channel 8 couple, dunno hwo to spell their names tho. Cherry Chocolate Candy also performed. The girls are very thin and one of them is especially pretty.. :) But Pierre blew us away. haha..   The next part of the night will be written in another post. 
      
</post>
<date>07,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       More Mundane Info   Dancing too much will make your calves ache. I've been walking around the past two days with achy calves. Actually, it's not walking.. I've been  hobbling  around school with achy calves. To make things worst, I'll be going for a dance thing later. What a masochist. No, no, I'm not clubbing later.. It's a salsa thing at Clarke Quay.
      
</post>
<date>06,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Hall Life Part V - How Lazy Can One Become?    My laziness knows no bounds. I've resorted to making my friend throw stuff across from her blk to mine cos i'm usually too lazy to go over to her place to get it. I wonder why we didn't think of it in the first year. What we do is, we usually go to the ends of our respective blks and just throw stuff over. Just a precaution, when throwing things over, it's usually beneficial to have a  GOOD  aim and not throw it off the balcony.   THis method saves alot of time and energy. Well, it only saves time and energy if the person throwing does it correctly. If not, one has to go all the way down to retrieve the items. Small things like boxes, tubes are good to throw, but a plastic bag of clothes is not advisable unless one has an arm like Hercules.   
      
</post>
<date>06,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Intellectual Debate     Native Speaker of English   By the term, I would assume that a native speaker of English is someone who speaks English as a First Language. I guess from this definition, one can say that the Brits are native speakers of English. One would want to say that Americans would fill this description, but Americans are made up of many cultures, it's a melting pot, and it isn't homogeneous, like the English (ok, you have to ignore the effects of migration and British-Asians, or British-Africans).     Ownership   This brings us to the question of ownership. I don't think a particular race/breed can claim to "own" a language. I dont' even think language is something one can own. Languages are specific to the different areas of the world, again ignoring globalization, and effects of migration. So you have French, spoken in France and other French colonies, English spoken by the Brits, Malay spoken by those from the Malay Archipelago, Chinese in China, Punjabi spoken by the Punjabs and so on and so forth. But to assume that these people own the language is not accurate, I suppose. They are probably the pioneer speakers of the language, hence the use of the term "mother tongue" and "native speaker" but they don't "own" it per se. 
      
</post>
<date>06,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Intellectual Debate!!   juz to get ur brain thinking abt stuff dat has absolutely nothing to do wif ur schwerk.... u can tink abt my schwerk! juz 2 simple questions u can post ur views on...  1. Wat do u understand by the term "Native Speaker of English"?  Who would u regard as such a "native speaker"?  2. Can anyone claim to own any particular language? (eg, can the brits claim to own english?)  its not some essay question im supposed to write on... actually, i dun mind if the essay is as easy as this..... =/ oops... juz realised its actually 3 questions... heheh...
      
</post>
<date>05,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Hall Life   It's funny how people can get all apologetic and polite when they see you doing something that they shld have taken the initiative to do in the first place. I'm talking about washing the toilets. It happened to me last semester as well. I was washing the common bathroom when my neighbor popped in and promptly offered to help. I declined her offer (cos I was finishing) but told her that she could do it the next time. She agreed, but of course, she didn't do it at all.   This time round, new neighbors, but the same reaction. The toilet was getting grimy, although considerably less hairy than last semester's. Decided it was time to give it a wash. The last time the bathroom was cleaned was before school started. Neighbor came in, saw me washing and also offered to help. I declined. NOt only was I abt to finish, but the bathroom is too small for 2 ppl to do it. I told her next time, which she agreed to.   I find it funny how no one can notice how dirty a toilet is until they see someone else washing it. Then the thought "oh, i shld help" will pop in and they will offer their help. Maybe deep down they wish that their offer wldn't be accepted and they only offered for politeness sake. Whatever the motive, frankly my dear, I don't give a damn. All I'm asking is for them to do their part as considerate neighbors and do the washing the next time.   Perhaps she will actually do as she agreed. Only time will tell....   
      
</post>
<date>05,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Movie Review - Shanghai Knights   Aargh. This is my 3rd attempt to write the review. The blog screwed up on me twice! So, i'm not going to bother writing a whole chunk of stuff.  Fann Wong - NOt bad Jackie Chan - so so Owen Wilson - ANNOYING! Plot - very thin, convoluted about English royal who steals imperial seal in china to give to bastard bro of Chinese emperor who wants it cos he wants to rule china. Bastard bro will then help English royal to kill royal family so that he also can become king. (i scratch your back, you scratch mine.. and together we can rule the world! muahahaha) Ending: bad guys die, sidekick (Owen) gets the girl (Fann) and hero (Jackie) lives to see another day.  Nitpicks Soundtrack - Awful! Didn't go with the time period of the show. Owen - ANNOYING! waste of screen time and space Fann - English was abit grating. Sweetie, it's "FA-THER" not "FAR-DER"  Ratings - Will only watch it if you paid me to. 
      
</post>
<date>05,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Movie Ratings   RIght, before I get on with my review proper, I'm going to standardize the movie ratings, so that those who want to do a review can/may follow the ratings that have been set.  From lowest to highest:  I'm not even going to watch it even if you paid me too  - oh puhleeze... go straight to a video release!!   I will only watch it if you paid me to  - the movie sucked!   I'm willing to pay $6.50  - hmm.. that wasn't too bad   I'm willing to pay $7.00  - I think I may like this movie   I'm willing to pay $7.50  - That was actually quite good!   I'm willing to pay $8.00  - oh boy oh boy, I loved it!   I'm willing to pay $8.50  - [trumpets blaring] We have a winner, you guys!!!
      
</post>
<date>05,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      erm... im a ricky martin, chandler n a bernese mountain dog.... O_o
      
</post>
<date>05,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Collin Powell's Iraq report    Argh..DAMN iraq... go read the report at CNN, BBC...whatever!   *Keep your peace and your sanities
      
</post>
<date>05,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      Ok I know this is kinda slow and totally not current, but I love emode! :)   Just to share:  I'm a bit of a Phoebe I'm a golden retriever and my inner rock star is Bjork 
      
</post>
<date>04,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       lame game time   we've had lame quizes.. now its time for lame games:)    urlLink match my socks! 
      
</post>
<date>04,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Mundane Coincidence   Hey whaddaya know?! I did a review abt movies with the word "mile" in it.. :)
      
</post>
<date>04,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       More Reviews - The Green Mile   While everyone was out playing mahjong and having their reunion dinner, I was home watching "The Green Mile" on Channel i. I never did watch the show at the cinema cos I thought it was going to be too sappy. 3 hours long. Now, that's a good way to waste time (and at no cost, whatsoever!). I liked the show primarily cos of Tom Hanks. (sigh) I think most of you would have watched the show, so I shan't bother giving a review abt the plot.  I liked the show. Have I said that already?  I guess I've been a fan of such prison movies, the other favorite being "The Shawshank Redemption". So anyway, the show does plod on a little, especialy the whole sequence about the mouse running across the floor. The ending bit was sad.. Yes, heartless ol me felt sad seeing what-his-face being executed. Err.. John Coffer, or smthg like that.   To sum it up. It was good. I wished I had watched it at the cinema. However, I'd only pay 6.50 for it. :)
      
</post>
<date>04,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
      You wanted Reviews? Well you got em.    Movie - 8 Mile   I didn't waste money to watch this. I did what any self-respecting cheapskate wld do; I downloaded it off kazaa. The plot has been tried and tested in various forms. Poor talented boy makes it big while trying to get out of the 'hood. I can't think of any movies off hand right now, perhaps, "finding forrester" or even "save the last dance" echoes certain aspects of the plot. So anyway, the main guy here is Eminem aka Jimmy "Rabbit" Smith. Yeah, no doubt abt it, this  dog  is good. He can rap and he can certainly talk like a GENUINE black. I actually like the theme song "Lose Yourself" and have tried unsuccessfully to follow the rap. (haha...)  Ok, back to the movie.. Need i say more abt the plot? Throw in a love interest, a few good friends, and you've got yourself a movie that's about 2 hrs long. Of cos, don't forget the white trash momma, cos hey, without her, you can't blame anyone else for the shitty life that you lead right? But you see, the protagonist can't be seen as a callous SOB who beats up his momma (no he doesn't do that, it's just an expression), so what you have to do is throw in a sister, who looks up to her older bro. And there you go, that's 8 mile for you.  Eminem is a surprisingly understated actor. You'd expect him to go around cussin' his head off, but he doesn't. He's pretty restraint, and that kinda brings out the vulnerability of his character. His character also likes to walk around dressed like Kenny from southpark. Yeah, the hooded parka thing. Apparently it's in. The dialogue is pretty hard to decipher. Firstly cos the quality of the download sucked and secondly, I don't do black speak.   Well, all in all, I'm glad i caught the show. i wld pay $6.80 to $7.00 for it. :) (i guess that cld be my rating system. 6.50 to 8.50)
      
</post>
<date>04,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
        theres hope yet for the french   he loves me he loves me not just caught the show a few hours ago and i must say twas a pretty unusual and quirky story audrey tantou just fits into the eccentric pychotic character perfectly say what happened to all the film reviews here must have disappeared under all the mundane tests haha
      
</post>
<date>04,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Events!!   1.  urlLink Stella Artois® Screen Starlight Cinema Classics  Date: 13 - 15 Feb 2003 Time: 2000 - 2200hrs Venue: Fort Canning Green Cost: $11 Yeah yeah, I know it's romancing singapore week/month/whatever. But I've always liked watching movies in the open (much like the movies in the park organized by Class 95). So this is an event for all movie/picnic lovers... They're showing sappy classics this feb, but i read somewhere that this is going to be a year long affair, so don't like sap? wait for the action flicks to come...      2.  urlLink Ballet Under the Stars!  Date: 21 - 23 and 28 - 30 Mar 2003 Time: 7.30pm Venue: Fort Canning Green Cost: $15 Woohoo! More dance events... Never been to this yet, so will make a point to catch at least 1 performance. 
      
</post>
<date>04,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Pissed off with School??   You've come to the right place.... Do lots of mundane tests that wld determine which "Friend" are you, what's your personal anthem and what breed of dog you are!! Click  urlLink here  for more tests...   It seems that:   1) I've got a little bit of Rachel going on..   2) My personal song is "I Will Survive"  3) And I'm a chi hua hua
      
</post>
<date>03,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
       Help   I'm in school mode now; SOMEONE OUT THERE PLEASE RESCUE ME FROM INSANITY!!! I've just came out of the most unproductive, most full-of-crap, most useless audit tutorial that there's not a scrap of information enough to wipe the sh** off a cockroach's a**. ARRGGGHHH!!! The freakin' test is barely a fortnight away, and my internal ACL guru has gone stoned on pineapple tarts and pis(s)tachio nuts.
      
</post>
<date>03,February,2003</date>
<post>

    
       
           urlLink Which Trainspotting Character Are You?     </post></Blog>