<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       Testando isso aqui 
    
    
</post>
<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      A fic da vez é Noite de Vento. É um conto com aproximadamente 20 páginas, narrado na primeira pessoa por Shane Filan (Westlife). Fala sobre o amor e seus mistérios. Foi escrita quando eu ouvia a música Strong Wind do Air Supply, mas eu não a considero uma song fic.  Basta clicar na capa da fic para ler sua versão em .html.   urlLink    
      
</post>
<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      My arms were opened And you didn’t hold me My mouth was wet And you didn’t kiss me My eyes were shinning And you didn’t look at me I was there, And you didn’t see me I was smiling While everybody was crying While everybody was pissed I was laughing And you didn’t laugh with me My heart was beating hard And you never heard it I was singing the most romantic songs And you never listened me I was screaming for the whole world Desperate words Love words And it didn’t matter to you I wrote the best poems And you didn’t read them I said your name a million times I confound the people with you And you didn’t understand me I cried a thousand rivers And you didn’t comfort me I was waiting for you And you didn’t arrive I was giving my whole life to you And you didn’t accept I put my heart in your hands And you let it fall I made everything for you And you no even knew who I was So, can you please explain Why the hell I love you?
      
</post>
<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      The day arrived dark And I didn’t see the sun I didn’t see the clouds And there were no birds flying in the horizon That was the worst morning I called you and you were not there You were not by my side I felt it was still night When I realise you’d not back When I realise you never was here When I realise it was totally fake And I could not change I could not change the world I could not change the things happening Even when they made me cry I awaked sad The shadows complimented me And the ghosts from the dark side of the life Were waiting me for the meal I had no company but you And you were not here To share the pain with me To share the joy with me You were not there… I thought I had a wonderful life after But everything I wanted was you  To see you once To stay with you once To kiss you, just once…  My dreams I would never make true My wishes I would never wish again My faith I would never believe  I was so lost I was so…without you And you were the only thing I asked To see the morning coming… 
      
</post>
<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Pois é, pessoal... finalmente o written dreams saiu da geladeira. Engraçado falar isso porque faz tempo que possuo um blog chamdo Post-it na geladeira... :)   De qualquer forma, vou começar a postar aqui fan fictions de minha autoria, e aguardo fanfics de visitantes também. Quem quiser postar aqui, é só  urlLink me mandar um e-mail . 
      
</post>
<date>27,July,2004</date>
<post>

    
       
      Antes que as luzes se apaguem, Ouça minhas palavras de amor... Elas podem sumir com o vento, Podem ser esquecidas com o tempo, Então ouça minhas palavras de amor... Antes do sol se pôr, Sinta meus beijos de amor... Cada toque, cada suspiro, Sei que tudo isso pode ser apagado da memória Então sinta meus beijos de amor... Antes do findar da noite fria, Diga que me ama pra sempre... Faça–me enlouquecer com meus delírios, Deixe–me enganar, Mostre–me o caminho para uma saída Pode ser que nada disso seja verdade. Que suas palavras um dia não mais sejam para mim, Então diga agora que me ama para sempre... Antes que as luzes se apaguem,  Quero você para mim... Porque um dia pode ser que não seja mais meu, Pode ser que me esqueça, Mas, se agora me ama, Antes que eu perca os sentidos de tanto pensar em você, Antes que eu me esvaia em devaneios, Antes que eu não possa mais dizer nada, Ouça minhas palavras de amor...  15/06/99   
      
</post>
</Blog>