<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>21,March,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hi! This is my new blog... I decided to move my blog here after I realized that I wouldn't be able to have any archives whatsoever with Geocities. So I'm making my Geocities site my personal site and this my blog!
    
</post>
<date>29,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Oh yea, I'll be thinking of some names too! n_n IMO the transfer student's name sounds better as Ashley. n_n But that's just my opinion.
    
</post>
<date>27,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       To Speedo-kun:  Yup! n_n Tell me the addies to those yaoi doujinshi sometime, alright? :)  urlLink Here  is a page with some scanlations of Yami no Matsuei. n_n It only goes up to volume three tho. But it's still worth checking out.    Well! I've changed my layout once again... I really like this one. n_n I think I'll stick with this for a while. It's even my fav. color! And I don't care if it's a dead color mom! &gt;    Anyway, nothing much has happened lately. Jeth's now trying out his new disposable contacts. n_n;; And I quote:  My eyes!!!!  Haha, it's funny. n_n;;    Ergh, I'm a bit braindead at the moment.. I've been doing a lot since this morning. &gt; 
    
</post>
<date>27,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I've read the first three volumes of Yami no Matsuei, and I'm hooked! n_n I like Hijiri for some reason. Oh yeah, I remember getting him on a quiz. Tsuzuki and Hisoka are priceless! And Muraki... Muraki interests me. n_n Seriously!     To Speedo-kun:  I think you should get a Yahoo Messenger. That way, if we're both online, we can chat! n_n You don't need a yahoo e-mail adress to sign or anything either! n_n   
    
</post>
<date>24,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Argh... My mom, dad and brother are going to Virginia,  and are leaving me behind!  Argh. It's so shitty! Really! &gt;P They're just going to leave me with my aunt. It's so mean!    I accidentaly cut my finger with a razor blade early this morning. It's pretty ironic, because my dad had just told me to be careful, then I cut myself. n_n;; I didn't tell him I cut myself though; he would probably freak out and suffer a panic attack. XD Anyway, it was sorta weird because it just surprised me. It didn't hurt much, but there was a lot of blood! &gt;    We went to Glorietta to watch Johnny English, but ended up just walking around. My mom bought me boots! n_n I also bought some books. I saw this one book;  A Guide to Tolkien . I wanted to get it, but I decided against it. I need to save like everyone else! &gt;  
    
</post>
<date>23,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I watched Animal Planet this morning, and the show was about animal fathers. Gosh! I was amazed at how quickly I realized that some males really suck. Can you believe that male seals actually  rape  female seals just for the sex?! Sheesh! It made me scream out one of my new mottos:     I wish men were more like sea horses!     Funny, but true. n_n 
    
</post>
<date>21,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Ahhh... I like my Winamp 3 Player... n_n I just got a Nataku [X] skin.X3
    
</post>
<date>21,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I have been flooded with surveys!! X_X I could only answer one, and I had to delete the others... I wasn't recieving any other mail! n_n
    
</post>
<date>21,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       New World  by  Round Table  has found a place in my head. It's a cute song! n_n    I've watched the first two episodes of Wolf's Rain. I loved it! The ending song,  Gravity  sung by  Maaya Sakamoto , is beautiful. I'm completely in love with the song. 
    
</post>
<date>14,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      By the way, the underwear that Duo has on his head in the pic is Heero's. n_n;;
    
</post>
<date>12,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I think I'm neither seme nor uke. n_n;; The thought just popped into my mind.
    
</post>
<date>12,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hay... it's 2:00 a.m... I have to stay up untill we leave for Iriga so I can sleep on the way there.n_n;;    I've really gotten into yaoi lately... n_n;; But I have no idea what 1x2 and all that other stuff means. XD And I had no idea that Jakult was actually... that. Yech. XP Maybe I still have some innocence in me. Nah. Anyway... I found some Gundam Wing doushinshi [?] you can see a pic  urlLink here . I found it quite funny. n_n Yeah, I've also gotten into that as well, and... well.. some  other  things. n_n    Speedo-kun, I wouldn't kill you either. n_n;;   
    
</post>
<date>12,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Oh. Here's the Address.     urlLink Which Yaoi Pairing are YOU?    
    
</post>
<date>11,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Nope. No luck. I just hope Speedo-kun doesn't kill me. n_n; I got HeeroxDuo. *sigh* can you believe it? Have the world hates me!! XP But I won't let one quiz spoil my day! Right? I should've gotten YukitoxTouya.... n_n;;    Men! What can you expect. *shrugs*   
    
</post>
<date>11,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Wahhhh... I just took this Yaoi Pairing quiz, and, well... n_n;;; I've already taken it twice! And it's still the same. Hmmmm.. Let's see if I get lucky this time! n_n
    
</post>
<date>11,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      It's amazing what people would say over a song. I download lot's of files using WinMX, a file sharing program like Kazaa. I was downloading anime episodes, so I kept the computer on all through the night. I was only able to get back to the computer at about 3:00 p.m today, and it turns out this guy was messaging me throughout the whole night. Apparently he wanted to download one of the songs on the computer, but kept on getting disconnected. n_n;; Poor guy. He wanted the song so badly he messaged me about 15 times. But then again, he got pissed off with me [duh! How the heck am I supposed to reply?] and told me that he had already downloaded the song off of someone else, saying that I was an 'ignorant bastard', and that I should go do a bear. n_n;;; MEN!    I'm currently looking up the anime,  Wolf's Rain.  I've been hearing that it's really good, so I've decided to look it up myself. From what I've read and found, I've been convinced to actually start downloading it on WinMX. n_n;; With that, I just have to say that I love  Google.  I usually find everything there. n_n What?? You thought I was going to say someone's name?? Heh! You wish! XD   
    
</post>
<date>11,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Well, lot's more happened than my previous post, so I'll post it. I'll try not to transmit gloomy vibes through your screens. n_n    I've been trying to write  something ,  anything  for quite a while now. Nothing's some out. n_n ARGH! I wonder if I'll ever get my character's past right. n_n; I wonder if I'll  ever  get anything right. n_n;;;     ''A little biRdy in the sKy  DroPped A poOpOO in mY eyE.  I didNt Laugh,  I diDnt cry.  I jusT tHanKEd God...      COWS DONT FLY''     I got this off of AC. I found it funny. n_n Here's another one.     "Duct tape is like the force, it has a dark side, it has a light side, and it holds the Universe together."  --Carl Zwanig     I got this off of a blog that's no longer updated. Too bad.    Oh yeah. I bought this manga... Shadow of the Dark River. This is the same manga that made Enid go on a kissing craze... n_n But this is the second volume, so it's got things other that FKs. Hehe. n_n;; I've shown it Gela already, and I think I've gotten her hooked. She wants me to look for the third volume. n_n *shrugs* What can I say?    Oh yeah, I've red streaks in my hair... my mom let me! n_n    
    
</post>
<date>07,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Ok. It hasn't sunken in yet, so I'll take this opportunity to post it now before I become increasingly depressed.    My aunt died early this morning... cancer. Tristan and Pocholo's mom. I'm scared to go to Iriga now... I dunno. Maybe I'm in denial or something.. Even my father pointed out that in a span of roughly four years, we've lost many of those close to us. Chiara, Eddie boy, Cheif, Indy, Uncle Sonny, Lolo Ernie, Lolo Judge and now Auntie Jing-jing. It's like some sick coincidence. Even freakier, at around 11:30 last night, something  'flashed'  in my eyes. I was freaked out to find out she died early this morning...    I'm not sure what I'm going to do when I het to Iriga. I'm probably going to become moral support.. I hope I can handle it this time.   
    
</post>
<date>07,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hehe. I haven't updated my blog lately, now have I. Nope!  My cousin from Austria was staying in the study room, so basically I was cut off from the internet for three days.  Oh well. Lalala... I'm quite bored. Let's just try to remember what I was feeling for the past three or so days.    Let's see... April 4!       April 4, 2003     My brother graduated high schoool today. I'm reluctant to say it, but I guess I'm a bit jealous of him. Most of the time I'm used to getting all the attention in the house, now everyone's concentrating on Jeth. Recognition Day, Graduation Day, Graduation Prom... I dunno. I'm just not used to it. I guess I'm pretty selfish huh? Weird to think. Goody-two-shoes me is not so angelic. But then again, who said I was angelic in the first place? n_n;;       April 5, 2003     Stephan is here. He's my cousin from my dad's side. He's from Austria, and can speak fluent German. Crystal and I had fun having him translate some phrases for us [Mostly Crystal; she was in a questionable state], like 'Fuck the truth', 'You suck!' and 'Shit!'. I still remember some of them. Haha. I wonder if I'll  actually  end up using them.    Crystal [my 17 year old aunt] and I were lying down on my top bunk doing nothing. We were talking about how we really didn't have anything to do, but the topic just led us to that; doing nothing. So we just stayed there, staring at the ceiling. Then Crystal asked me, "Ria, what's the meaning of our lives??" in a very subtle manner. I replied, "Gosh Crystal, are we really  that  bored?"    But that just brings me to why I don't like having nothing to do. It's not that I dislike not having anything to do because I don't have anything to do, but it makes me think of things I don't want to think about because there really is nothing else to do. [I hope you got that. n_n;;]    For some reason, I don't feel as if Jeth has already graduated. It's like I've always had to be the big sister to him, and he's off to college!    Gosh, the house will be so empty once he leaves.       April 7, 2003     I can't really remember anything that happened yesterday, so I'll just post about today. Stephan has gone back to Uncle Teddy's place, where he first started. Crystal is leaving tomorrow, so basically I'll be pretty alone in this house since Jeth locks himself up in his room all day long. Really, I don't want to be alone. It's makes me think too much. I remember this time during sophomore year, I was supposed to organize my group in cooking as the next day we would be cooking/baking something. [I forget.] I was sitting on the couch upstairs SMSing everyone, then I had to wait for their replies. I started to think too much during my wait, and I had to leave the organizing up to Mikara.    Hmmmmmmmmmmm. Here I go again. I'm starting to think too much. I don't want to be alone. Jeth is leaving, Crystal is leaving... I mean, even if Jeth holes himself up in his room, I still know he's  there . But in June, he'll be gone...      Schaisse!     I'm thinking too much again.    P.S--&gt; I did end up using the German words Stephan taught me. 
    
</post>
<date>01,April,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I just watched Forest Gump and Cast Away, both with Tom Hanks as the lead role. I dunno, both movies hit me in a way. It should have hit me a long time ago, since I've already seen them before. Forest Gump... it made me feel like I'm wasting my time. My mom told me that there is no such thing as a limited person. And I quote, 'Stupid is as stupid does.' Well, something like that. On the other hand, Cast Away made me feel like I was an island in the middle of the sea. I may have everything, but I'm surrounded by merely water.
    
</post>
<date>31,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hehe. Sorry for not updating lately. I've been overrun by my male cousins, and if they're not playing the PS downstairs, they're playing the computer. n_n;; I get cut off from using the internet. :P But I'm back! Back for now. :)    I took a quiz.        What Is Your X Japan Ballad?      *sigh* Love, it's so... thing! XP Ergh. Nevermind. n_n; 
    
</post>
<date>26,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      It's raining. Still raining. It's been raining for roughly three days. And I love it. n_n    I'm just waiting for school to jump me. In roughly one month, it'll be school again, and I'm waiting for my brain to comprehend it. Hehe, then I'll be panic stricken, running about the house screaming "OMG school starts tomorrow!". But I'll get to see everyone! :D Then I'll be all happy-dappy screaming "OMG school starts tomorrow!". That would tick my parents off either way because of my noise pollution. Hehe. Beh! :D    
    
</post>
<date>24,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
       *announcement*     Mikara would like to say that she is not dead. She can't blog because her keyboard is broken and their internet bill is too high. Poor Gretchie. n_n;;
    
</post>
<date>23,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Poo. I've been feeling weird lately.    After reading my past entries, I've realized that I'm no good at keeping one thought. n_n; I guess that's bad... but I guess I don't care much.    I bought a book of Hamlet. I couldn't find an english version of Noli, so I decided to buy it instead. I remember someone telling me that we might take it up in third year, so I decided to look it up. [Hoshi, was that you?]  I haven't read past the first scene... n_n; The way Shakespeare wrote is quite confusing. He has no sense of sentence construction! &gt;    Not much happened today... So I'll be signing off early. Sweet dreams. That's what we all need.
    
</post>
<date>18,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Yey! I'm back from Iriga! n_n I ate tons of Indian Mangos and did nothing but swim, play the PS and take up piano. Not to mention bum around the house, wake up late and... some other stuff. n_n;;    Sometimes I get the feeling that... I'm disconnected. Disconnected... from something. I'm not really sure. Then I snap back, just like that. It's weird when things suddenly pop into your mind without warning. That's one reason why I hate my imagination.    Speedo-kun! I saw you go online in YM! But it was only for a second or so... n_n; BTW, my Yahoo ID is  the_blacksolstice . Also, your archives don't work... n_n;;   Mikara:  Are you still looking for PS game suggestions? n_n Also, what genre are you into?    I watched  Matrix: Reloaded ! It was so cool! :D
    
</post>
<date>08,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I feel like hugging a tree. I feel like saving the ocean. I feel like lying down in front of a tractor on it's way to demolish the rain forest. No wonder... I got Earth on that angels quiz.
    
</post>
<date>03,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Hiya! I'm back from my mini vacation. n_n I went to Cauayan, Isabela for three days. I got to see Callao caves and the Rice Terraces. It was fun. Well worth the three days. :)     You are a Day Dreamer..   Daydreamers tend to be away from the normal, and have a deeper aspect when looking at things. Most of the time, thier outcasts of the social society, but don't worry. It just means your so deep it scares thier simple little brains.    urlLink   What kind of Dreamer are you?     brought to you by  urlLink Quizilla      There's a lot on my mind again.. It's a weird feeling when you have so much to think about, that you can't even think straight. It's like... you don't know where to start;  how  to start.    I think I'll go to bed. It's been a long day. 
    
</post>
<date>03,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I've just logged onto  urlLink Fanfiction.net . I remember just a few years ago, the first website I'd go to was FF.net to check for new stories and reviews. But now I only go there once in a while... Hm. Hey! Someone flamed me! &gt;    
    
</post>
<date>03,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I took the Belief-O-Matic test on  urlLink Belief Net , and here are my results:    1.  Orthodox Quaker (100%)  2.  Sikhism (84%)  3.  Orthodox Judaism (81%)  4.  Seventh Day Adventist (78%)  5.  Mainline to Liberal Christian Protestants (77%)  6.  Mainline to Conservative Christian/Protestant (76%)  7.  Jehovah's Witness (75%)  8.  Bahá'í Faith (74%)  9.  Eastern Orthodox (74%)  10.  Roman Catholic (74%)  11.  Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-Day Saints (Mormons) (73%)  12.  Hinduism (71%)  13.  Liberal Quakers (70%)  14.  Islam (68%)  15.  Jainism (67%)  16.  Reform Judaism (65%)  17.  Unitarian Universalism (58%)  18.  Mahayana Buddhism (54%)  19.  Theravada Buddhism (54%)  20.  New Age (51%)  21.  Neo-Pagan (49%)  22.  Taoism (37%)  23.  Christian Science (Church of Christ, Scientist) (36%)  24.  Scientology (31%)  25.  Secular Humanism (30%)  26.  New Thought (29%)  27.  Nontheist (17%)    I'm not all too sure about this though... I have my own questions about the infinite.   
    
</post>
<date>28,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I need to get a new layout for my blog. This one seems too cluttered now.
    
</post>
<date>15,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Woah, Blogger looks so... different. Sorta confusing. Anyway, I'm glad I'm finally online!! Yeah!    Ergh, my face hurts... I had a tooth extracted today. [Actually, I'd say my dentist yanked it out of my mouth... *rubs cheek*] I'm going to get braces pretty soon. &gt;    Tired........ I feel tired. And hungry. I haven't eaten lunch yet, and it's... 6:20 p.m?! &gt;    Gundam W will be showing on Cartoon Network after Tuesday! Digimon Tamers ended yesterday [I think] and I have only seen 2 episodes of Invader Zim. The one where he makes this one kid his 'best friend', the one where they had to sell chocolate bars to make money... and when Zim invaded Dib's body. Wait, that's three episodes. It doesn't matter anyhoo, I never catch it anyway. 
    
</post>
<date>15,June,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      I'm back again! *sigh* All this traveling is going to take it's toll on me one of these days. n_n;; Blogger doesn't like me right now. It won't load properly. I'm having doubts on whether this entry will even show up or not. &gt;</post></Blog>