<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>05,November,2002</date>
<post>

    
       
       Pondering the Mountaintop   Hello everybody!  I was talking to my mom one morning, and she was telling me about this cool thing she read in her devo book, and I thought I'd post it.  She was saying how in the Old Testament, when Moses went up to Mount Sinai and was talking to God, he asked God to show him His face.  Then God said He couldn't, cuz His full presence would kill Moses, but He showed Moses part of His presence.  When Moses came down from the mtn., he was covered in the glory of God and just glowing.  All the people in the village thingy, or whatever they lived in, asked if they could get that too, so Moses led a bunch of them to the top of the mtn.  At the top, God was showing Himself in a huge thrundercloud with lightning and thunder and stuff.  Moses told the people to walk inside of the cloud, cuz that's where they would find God, but they were afraid, and wouldn't do it.  So he went inside the cloud and was calling them from inside, telling them that they should just take the step from the edge into the cloud.  But they were too afraid, and therefore, missed out completely from seeing a beautiful experience with God.  A lot of times, we do that in worship, prayer, faith, or whatever God wants us to do, for that matter.  We get the the edge of the cloud and just get too freaked out to just take that one step into His glory.  And we miss out.  So I was thinking about that, and thought about how those people must've felt when the came down from the mountaintop.  Probably the way we do when we come back from Spring Fling, a prayer retreat, etc.  Charged up, but still thinking, in the backs of their minds, 'I didn't do enough.  I should've taken the step into God.'  Of course, most of us never talk about it, and we just brush that feeling away.  But it's true.  I mean, to be honest, there are so many times that I know God's leading me somewhere, but I get too scared to completely let go of it, and just ask if maybe He could hold off for another day.  And I miss my chance.  So I think that this is something everyone can relate to, and can use to really find out what's truly keeping them from God's presence.  Pride, selfishness, fear, inhibitions?  We all have things that keep us from going 100% for God 100% of the time, and I think that if all of us in Fusion, and especially on the worship team, let go to God, maybe we'd be in a different place.  Not that where we are is bad or anything, but I know sometimes it's really hard to get into worship onstage.  I dunno, maybe I'm alone here, but I thought I'd post this, becuz I can't help but wonder what if.    ~Erika </post></Blog>