<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Blog>
<date>16,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Well today was such a change in life.... I had a fabulous day. I turned in my term paper, no more worry about that and I finished my study questions... that was school, nothing special. .................. ..................... After school I got together with my chums: Erin, Andrew, Nathan and Tally, we all took the el bus-o to Andrew's where he gave me a cookie and got some money and we headed to 15th to buy CD's. I bought a Death Cab For Cutie compact disc and it was cheap, which made me happy. Then we walked over to Broadway and walked around going to different stores and eating shakes and cheeseburgers. Tally and I then took a walk to look at some of the great sites of Seattle, after making our rounds we went back to the village of value and met up with the rest of the gang and I bought a little T-shirt that makes me have a uni-boob, it was a laugh and a pour &gt;the rain made me laugh while Nathan, Erin and I ran to the bus stop to wait for the numero 7 ::we stopped underneath a bridge and watched the rain come down and it was so peaceful::  how is my brain? Not so large and full of sickness and full of glowingness *wink* what am I jamming to? °IT'S TRICKY!!!!° RRRUN RUUUN RUNNN DMC i should be...? working out and sleeping at the same time (hopefully sometime that will happen, i should try that 48 hour hollywood diet &gt;"WORKS WHILE YOU SLEEP!!!"   
     

    
</post>
<date>15,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      How many times do I have to say To get away, get gone Flip your shit past another lasses Humble dwelling You got your game, made your shot And you got away With a lot, but I'm not turned-on So put away that meat you're selling 'Cause I do know what's good for me And I've done what I could for you But you're not benefiting, and yet I'm sitting Singing again, sing, sing again How can I deal with this, if he won't get with this Am I gonna heal from this, he won't admit to it Nothing to figure out, I got to get him out It's time the truth was out that he don't give a shit about me 'Cause I do know what's good for me And I've done what I could for you But you're not benefiting, and yet I'm sitting Singing again, sing, sing again How can I deal with this, if he won't get with this Am I gonna heal from this, he won't admit to it Nothing to figure out, I got to get him out It's time the truth was out that he don't give a shit about me How many times can it escalate 'Till it elevates to a place I can't breathe? And I must decide, if you must deride That I'm much obliged to up and go I'll idealize, then realize That it's no sacrifice, because the price is paid And there's nothing left to grieve Fuckin go 'Cause I've done what I could for you And I do know what's good for me And I'm not benefiting Instead I'm sitting singing again, singing again Singing again, sing, sing, sing again How can I deal with this, if he won't get with this Am I gonna heal from this, he won't admit to it Nothing to figure out, I got to get him out It's time the truth was out that he don't give a shit about me How can I deal with this, if he won't get with this Am I gonna heal from this, he won't admit to it Nothing to figure out, I got to get him out It's time the truth was out that he don't give a shit about me  present state of my brain? large and full of sickness present music of my brain? one good spliff present thing my brain should be doing? writing a term paper
     

    
</post>
<date>21,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      you think you're denying me of something well, I've got plenty you're the one who's missing out but you won't notice 'til after five years if you'll live that long you'll wake up *all loveless*
     

    
</post>
<date>19,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Tuesday was a hoot and holler just ask emmy, WOO. ........... emmy and i came home and chilled with some of our homies and yeah had a good time with that and i dare not say more.... except, it was happy and so uncomfortable it was comfortable.  &gt;today I watched little girls and made $40 doing so... NICE.  ... tomorrow i am going off by myself to downtown to pick up a few things that i want, a couple of compact discs and i am terribly excited  nothing exciting happened today and it made me sad because usually comething exciting happens. *ah yes, i got to beat up Hoseph, that made my day*  i missed tally while he was gone, because he is nice and yeah, i am glad he is back  Andrew is leaving, i will miss my math buddy, he will be back though, good.  i am listening to my brothers gangster rap and it is pretty... sigh.  someone told me i was a bitch today ** to you** fuck you, maybe i am a bitch or maybe you are too sensative, or maybe it is a little of both, plus, i need to be a bitch, i don't know why, but i need a little bitchiness at all times. **someone told me i was a push over today, i don't get it, i am a bitchy push over??? oh snap.  ~i miss you, the way you made me laugh when nothing was funny, the way you laughed at yourself, the way you were happy, how slow you ate, i could tell you everything, how you got me, how you didn't care what i said and just took me for who i was, being attached at the hip, being so close, crazy lake swims, races that have nothing to do with cars, flying down the stairs in sleeping bags, cleaning out my sick bug cage, being mullet twins, mud wrestling, bollos de mantequilla, joselu.... i am happy you are coming back~  question frequently in my head: what if your life is someone elses dream and you are nothing but a dream? and are you a good dream or a bad dream?  secret of the day: i like bacon
     

    
</post>
<date>19,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      Monday Bonday, surprisingly pleasent. ...................bitter sweet symphony..........................  school was okay, lunch was better, i took Hoseph's shoes and he let me wear them like clown shoes and it made me feel all special and stuff, man i love Hoseph and he sure is a fox *wink* Next was school some more and that was that... yeah. After school I took the bus to Meals' house and he just had to work out, but it was okay because he made me laugh with his funny faces and I made him laugh with my lack of balance. I can bench 50 lbs once... BOO YA.  Let's see, then we went and had protein shakes, actually Meals had one and he made me try it, lets just say it wasn't the best shake i have ever had. &gt;Then we chilled and chilled some more and I got to see his hair AND i did a pull up, i think that deserves another BOO YA My mom picked me up and we went out for burgers and now i am here listening to my piano music and leaving soon to pick up emmy. :::::::::::::GOODNIGHT SEATTLE!!!::::::::::::::: "you fall into the trap till it tears you apart" she said "my trap is my escape" she replied "it is your escape until to fall into to it the last time and you find you can't get out" she said "i don't want to get out, i want to be stay there forever" she replied "someday it will be closed and you will lose everything" she said "i know, that is why i die inside everytime i escape, it closes a little every time." she replied "I love you" she said "you love me" she replied  
     

    
</post>
<date>18,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      "walk far from me" said the girl with the galaxy eyes "don't think you know me"  a·shamed adj.    1. Feeling shame or guilt: Are you ashamed for having lied?    2. Feeling inferior, inadequate, or embarrassed: ashamed of my torn coat.    3. Reluctant through fear of humiliation or shame: ashamed to ask for help.  fool·ish     1. Lacking or exhibiting a lack of good sense or judgment; silly: foolish remarks.    2. Resulting from stupidity or misinformation; unwise: a foolish decision.    3. Arousing laughter; absurd or ridiculous: a foolish grin.    4. Immoderate or stubborn; unreasonable: foolish pride; foolish love.    5. Embarrassed; abashed: I feel foolish telling you this.    6. Insignificant; trivial: spent all their money on foolish little knickknacks.  free   adj. fre·er, fre·est    1. Not imprisoned or enslaved; being at liberty.    2. Not controlled by obligation or the will of another: felt free to go.   
     

    
</post>
<date>18,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      ahhhhh Saturday was pure bliss... i am here to bore you, viva la mullet.  Took the bus was late and lost ben kell and nathan Met up at dicks with emmy and ate a deluxe dick Walked back to the ave and had a heart to heart, thank you em. Met up with the boys... erin showed up after seeing matrix reloaded, she said it was weird. Went back to my house with emmy and erin The boys showed up Went to madison park. Ate and drank goodness. Climbed the lifeguard tower and chilled at the beach chasing geese and watching otters. Bought instant pudding. Went home with Emmy and Nathan. Ate the pudding and listened to records. Watched The Breakfast Club. Watched The Brave Little Toaster. Watched The Rescuers Down Under. Lounged and had a peck of a time. Fell into deep slumber. Awoke to cell phone ringing ... "hello?" "hey, it's ross, i can't kick it today" "alright bye" "get some sleep"  -turns out he ditched us for Dani, woop woop-  Went downtown and to the gap. Bought matching thongs with Emmy and they are pink with polka dots and green coolness. We are dorks indeed, but at least we have cool underwear. Put on new under-roos in westlake bathroom. Went to see holes. Many cute boys in that movie. Took bus back to my house and are presently thinking, pondering and ringing.  present feeling?   ::::::::::::::::&gt;snazzified 
     

    
</post>
<date>30,May,2003</date>
<post>

	 
      what a day it has been indeed. good? bad? meh? it was good  i would say. it began with school, poopy school, but i got out at 10. then i went home ate took the bus to the zoo met up with rosso and we went on a speed viewing of the zoo that boy is crazy, i love him, he and i saw bats, hippos, and giraffes oh my. after ross sped off, emmy and i met up and went to see a movie not just any movie but finding nemo it was FABULOUS i laughed so hard and i can now speak whale BOO YA then we came home and ate and talked to miles and he was all beat up i laughed at him, it was funny yet sad *karma sucks ass doesn't it?* natalie had a fiasco emmy had to tend to it she left i am alone i am sad i am listening to sad music ----i hate having lows---- the two worst feelings? loneliness and envy sadly i am always envious and constantly lonely, but that is okay </post></Blog>